<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<tlk language="0">
  <string id="88799">It seems I need your wind map to travel north.</string>
  <string id="88802">Do you have any idea where I could find a flyer?</string>
  <string id="88805">What are you proposing in return for the wind map?</string>
  <string id="88806">What if I just killed you and took your wind map?</string>
  <string id="88807">What if I make you tell me where it is?</string>
  <string id="88809">What do you propose?</string>
  <string id="88811">You have a deal. I&apos;ll find out what&apos;s wrong with your land.</string>
  <string id="88812">What if I say no?</string>
  <string id="88815">Why do you think the ghosts are related to this spirit?</string>
  <string id="88817">What do you mean by &quot;a fox?&quot;</string>
  <string id="88820">Who is the Forest Shadow?</string>
  <string id="88822">I&apos;ve heard enough about this fox spirit. What do I need to do?</string>
  <string id="88825">I will do what I can to save her.</string>
  <string id="88827">She could be behind this. I&apos;ll just eliminate her.</string>
  <string id="88831" soundid="136073">If there are still people there, then whoever took the crystal might be there, as well. But... just be careful.</string>
  <string id="88833" soundid="189615"></string>
  <string id="88834" soundid="136076">I don&apos;t think so. He&apos;d have to be quite strong to pull the crystal loose. It doesn&apos;t make any sense to me, but then, what in this place does?</string>
  <string id="88836">Exit to Outer Courtyard</string>
  <string id="88838">What else is along this path?</string>
  <string id="88841">How will I recognize the temple?</string>
  <string id="88842">Might I find any help at the inn?</string>
  <string id="88844">That&apos;s all I need to know about the path specifically.</string>
  <string id="88845">Tell me more about Spear Catches Leaf.</string>
  <string id="88850">How will you know I&apos;ve succeeded?</string>
  <string id="88852">What happens if I can&apos;t reach this fox spirit?</string>
  <string id="88853">How can I be sure I can trust your end of the bargain?</string>
  <string id="88856">The more I know, the better chance I have of succeeding.</string>
  <string id="88857">I need that wind map, so I have work to do.</string>
  <string id="88858">Disturbance</string>
  <string id="88864">The Broken Wheel</string>
  <string id="88865">Would a child be able to pry the crystal from the pedestal?</string>
  <string id="88866">The Turning Wheel</string>
  <string id="88867">I should go to the inn and find out what I can.</string>
  <string id="88868" soundid="137845">Mmm. Can you smell that? Civilized tea and buns. It has been a long time since I have enjoyed such simple pleasures.</string>
  <string id="88870" soundid="137847">This is quite a remarkable market for such a small village. Perhaps my wife would like to retire here. With me, of course. Never a thought otherwise.</string>
  <string id="88872" soundid="137849">Step lightly around these fireworks, or whatever they are. After years of married bliss, I am uncomfortable around anything with a short fuse.</string>
  <string id="88876" soundid="137853">Flooded once more. Out of sight, out of mind I suppose.</string>
  <string id="88895" soundid="137872">*This* is the Ministry hostel? Where do they spend all the silver they demand of the Empire, then?</string>
  <string id="88897" soundid="137874">From what I know of them, the guild doesn&apos;t usually conduct business this openly, or in such elegance.</string>
  <string id="88900" soundid="137877">We need to get out of here! We&apos;ll be crushed!</string>
  <string id="88901" soundid="137878">That machine is massive. Who knew the assassins were constructing it in my father&apos;s tomb?</string>
  <string id="88902" soundid="137879">We have to find Jia and kill her before she brings Death&apos;s Hand!</string>
  <string id="88903" soundid="137880">This is an ancient repository of knowledge. It contains records of the Empire.</string>
  <string id="88905" soundid="137882">This site was to be my father&apos;s tomb. I doubt he knows what use Death&apos;s Hand has put it to.</string>
  <string id="88906" soundid="137883">The palace is ancient. Some say it was a celestial gift. It shouldn&apos;t be misused.</string>
  <string id="88907" soundid="137884">Try not to damage anything. The Empire has seen enough disgrace.</string>
  <string id="88908" soundid="137885">What is this horror? I pray my eyes deceive me.</string>
  <string id="88909" soundid="137886">Be careful. He still has great power to draw upon.</string>
  <string id="88919" soundid="137896">Filth, poverty, and crime: The docks in every city throughout the Empire are the same.</string>
  <string id="88920" soundid="137897">I&apos;m surprised this town has such a large market square. It&apos;s a wonder so many merchants can make a living.</string>
  <string id="88942" soundid="137919">There are so many people here! The sound of their voices inside can be almost... overwhelming.</string>
  <string id="88943" soundid="137920">I didn&apos;t think so many people could be in a place all at once. And all of them keeping so much inside....</string>
  <string id="88948" soundid="137925">Wow! This place is so pretty... and peaceful! But... the Guardian says appearances are deceiving.</string>
  <string id="88957" soundid="137934">This is the palace? Why have they let it fall apart? Isn&apos;t it supposed to be beautiful?</string>
  <string id="88958" soundid="137935">Chai Ka: My Lady....</string>
  <string id="88959" soundid="137936">Chai Ka: He is strong. Bloated with his stolen power. He is far from finished.</string>
  <string id="88969">Blacksmith Shop</string>
  <string id="88970" soundid="137947">There are so many people here! Such a big town! But... they all seem unhappy for some reason.</string>
  <string id="88974">To Black Leopard School</string>
  <string id="88975">To the Imperial Arena</string>
  <string id="88976" soundid="137953">The water covering everyone. Those poor children... I hate the water. It&apos;s too... familiar.</string>
  <string id="88978" soundid="137955">There was a lot of pain here. The Guardian says he can feel it soaked into the walls. I don&apos;t like it here.</string>
  <string id="88980" soundid="137957">The Guardian doesn&apos;t like what&apos;s happened. They&apos;ve brought others from Outside and made them fight.</string>
  <string id="88982">City Gate</string>
  <string id="88983" soundid="137960">The Guardian says that this is the home of a powerful spirit. He can&apos;t tell if we&apos;re welcome or not....</string>
  <string id="88986" soundid="137963">They&apos;re watching you closely, gauging your abilities. Be on your guard.</string>
  <string id="88988" soundid="137965">From their numbers, I&apos;d say we&apos;re getting closer to the Mother.</string>
  <string id="88989">Boathouse Key</string>
  <string id="88990" soundid="137967">Stories don&apos;t speak of foxes being this pretentious.</string>
  <string id="88991">From the markings on the head of the key, it looks like it would unlock the gate leading to the upper office in the Tien&apos;s Landing boathouse.</string>
  <string id="88992" soundid="137969">The Golden Way is the pride of the city, as any of its residents will gladly tell you.</string>
  <string id="88993" soundid="137970">I am not comfortable here. So many people without a clue of the danger that may be coming.</string>
  <string id="88996">Switch Upgrade</string>
  <string id="88997" soundid="137974">The Lotus Assassins know all about the Guild and places like this. They choose to do nothing because organized crime polices itself.</string>
  <string id="88998">Primary</string>
  <string id="88999" soundid="137976">This floating statue is perfect for the Scholars&apos; Garden. Their heads are always in the clouds.</string>
  <string id="89000">Ground</string>
  <string id="89001">Upgrade</string>
  <string id="89002">Mini-game Controller Setup</string>
  <string id="89003">Toggle game/mini-game</string>
  <string id="89005">I can&apos;t hurt you?!</string>
  <string id="89006">Don&apos;t underestimate me!</string>
  <string id="89007">We fight!</string>
  <string id="89008">My skills are tested!</string>
  <string id="89009">You won&apos;t defeat me!</string>
  <string id="89010">I will prove myself!</string>
  <string id="89011" soundid="137988">The destruction is what I expected. Clearly no one was meant to survive.</string>
  <string id="89012" soundid="137989">A very focused attack. Was this place a threat because of who the teacher was, what he might have been taught, or who he taught it to?</string>
  <string id="89013" soundid="137990">Your quarry has based himself in the north. There are paths right and left, but I doubt one is any safer than the other.</string>
  <string id="89014" soundid="137991">It looks like the soldiers have taken control from the bandits who normally rule here. I&apos;m not sure it&apos;s an improvement.</string>
  <string id="89015" soundid="137992">I never had cause to enter these caves. Gao will have to pay for this inconvenience.</string>
  <string id="89016" soundid="137993">The teahouse is the heart of a community, and the first place where sickness shows. Be wary.</string>
  <string id="89017" soundid="137994">Be careful. Trust no one in this place. We are a long way from your idyllic little village.</string>
  <string id="89018">Show me your true skills!</string>
  <string id="89019" soundid="137996">Even a village as small as this has a place to hide its undesirables.</string>
  <string id="89020" soundid="137997">Life seems normal enough here. You could almost ignore all that has happened.</string>
  <string id="89022" soundid="137999">The Assassins have adopted many new tools since I was in the ranks, but their methods have changed little.</string>
  <string id="89023" soundid="138000">This whole place is a giant watery grave. The past cannot be changed. It should have stayed buried.</string>
  <string id="89025" soundid="138002">The Lotus Assassins have spread their influence even here. It is a credit to Sun Li that you remained undiscovered as long as you did.</string>
  <string id="89026" soundid="138003">Water covers all, just as the people of Tien&apos;s Landing cover their memory of what happened here.</string>
  <string id="89028" soundid="138005">Forced labor is sometimes necessary when difficult work must be done. Perhaps not in this case, but sometimes.</string>
  <string id="89030" soundid="138007">They control demons, too? They have amassed a great deal of power.</string>
  <string id="89031">I am healed.</string>
  <string id="89032" soundid="138009">These rushing waters can&apos;t do anything to cleanse this forest.</string>
  <string id="89033">I have been... poisoned.</string>
  <string id="89034" soundid="138011">So much has happened. Please, when the others have left, we should have a moment together.</string>
  <string id="89035" soundid="138012"></string>
  <string id="89036" soundid="138013">You must be exhausted after what you&apos;ve been through, but... I need to speak with you when the others are gone. I&apos;ll come find you.</string>
  <string id="89037" soundid="138014"></string>
  <string id="89038" soundid="138015">We should all get some rest. We may as well be awake for what is to come.</string>
  <string id="89039" soundid="138016">That is... that is all we can do to save ourselves today, but... there was more that you learned in the spirit realm, wasn&apos;t there? I can tell. </string>
  <string id="89040" soundid="138017">I... saw hope in my vision that led us to you, but there was also something I didn&apos;t want to believe. I didn&apos;t tell the others. Can it be true?</string>
  <string id="89041" soundid="138018">Am I really Master Li&apos;s daughter?</string>
  <string id="89042" soundid="138019">What! Laughable! I see why you didn&apos;t tell us. That is ridiculous!</string>
  <string id="89043" soundid="138020">It&apos;s no more outlandish than half the things I have seen in your company. She is of the right age.</string>
  <string id="89044" soundid="138021">Lots of children are born every day. I was born at that time. If you don&apos;t count this latest rebirth, so was our friend here.</string>
  <string id="89045" soundid="138022">But I was named for the fires of Dirge. Hui said as much, and it seems obvious now. The red glow opposite the morning sun was the temple burning.</string>
  <string id="89046" soundid="138023">So what if it was? It could have been visible across the Empire.</string>
  <string id="89047" soundid="138024">But that&apos;s not... that would make her....</string>
  <string id="89048" soundid="138025">A cousin? A princess? A rival?</string>
  <string id="89049" soundid="138026">You be quiet. This is not amusing.</string>
  <string id="89050" soundid="138027">You still seek to redeem your master, even after what he did to you? Clearly you are beyond reason. Fine, believe what you wish.</string>
  <string id="89051" soundid="138028">Does anyone care how I feel about this?</string>
  <string id="89052" soundid="138029">I... I am unsure what this really means, but we must tell Master Li and try to appeal to his sense of decency. This could lift so much pain from his heart.</string>
  <string id="89053" soundid="138030">You are both crazy. I&apos;ll go along with it if it helps us in the end, but I&apos;ll need more proof to believe it, and I expect Sun Li will, too.</string>
  <string id="89054" soundid="138031">We have to survive the coming attack before anyone is told anything. We&apos;ve done all we can for now. Tomorrow will decide our fates.</string>
  <string id="89055" soundid="138032">We must use it to unsettle him. That will make it easier to defeat him. He used all of us... we can&apos;t let this opportunity go.</string>
  <string id="89056" soundid="138033">I don&apos;t want to be used like this. Did you enjoy being Master Li&apos;s tool? He should be told, but try to see this as a way to get through to him.</string>
  <string id="89057" soundid="138034">A ploy with potential, but you might as well make up anything. This is hard to swallow.</string>
  <string id="89058" soundid="138035">Fortifications... hmmm... perhaps I will remove some of the ordnance from the Marvelous Dragonfly. Properly applied, it may prove useful tomorrow.</string>
  <string id="89059" soundid="138036">Come Whirlwind! I need your muscle!</string>
  <string id="89060" soundid="138037">That&apos;s the *Black* Whirlwind, and as long as it makes the coming fight more interesting, I&apos;ll lift whatever you want.</string>
  <string id="89061" soundid="138038">That is all we can do for now. Tomorrow will decide our fates.</string>
  <string id="89062" soundid="138039">We should all get some rest. But... if I could have a word with you when the others have gone... I need to speak with you.</string>
  <string id="89063" soundid="138040"></string>
  <string id="89066">There was something. It was about you and Master Li.</string>
  <string id="89073">The burning temple was only visible from the palace.</string>
  <string id="89076">Perhaps this will restore Master Li&apos;s good side.</string>
  <string id="89078">Of course, Dawn Star. What should we do about this?</string>
  <string id="89083">Not especially. We will use it to my benefit, regardless.</string>
  <string id="89088">No, it is a very useful tool. Master Li will be weakened when I tell him.</string>
  <string id="89090">No. The Water Dragon says otherwise. Only from the palace.</string>
  <string id="89091">Yes, a bit of information about you that is sure to rattle Master Li.</string>
  <string id="89099">I can&apos;t hurt you?!</string>
  <string id="89100">For the Emperor!</string>
  <string id="89101">Down, peasant!</string>
  <string id="89102">Do not resist me!</string>
  <string id="89103">Guards! To me!</string>
  <string id="89104">You can&apos;t escape!</string>
  <string id="89105">This is your end!</string>
  <string id="89107">Tomb Rubble</string>
  <string id="89108" soundid="162513">From what I have seen, he is stronger than that. If he is damaged by the blast, good, but you are the one meant to fight the power behind him.</string>
  <string id="89112">Why didn&apos;t you tell me before? I could have prepared!</string>
  <string id="89114">I am glad you trust me, but they still plan to launch a sneak attack?</string>
  <string id="89116" soundid="138173">Well, that&apos;s convenient for my nerves.</string>
  <string id="89117" soundid="138174">My wounds will make me a burden if I stay at your side. I will keep guard over the temple itself. Groups landing there should be small enough for me to handle.</string>
  <string id="89118" soundid="138175">I&apos;ll signal with the temple bell if it&apos;s too much for me to handle. I&apos;m sure we will be ready for whatever comes.</string>
  <string id="89119">Collapsed Tunnel</string>
  <string id="89123">Then I personally defeat Death&apos;s Hand, and the army will fall. I like it.</string>
  <string id="89124">Why not just blow them all up? Death&apos;s Hand included?</string>
  <string id="89126">If you turned them down, why are they still going ahead with this plan?</string>
  <string id="89140" soundid="138242">[The sphere grows dim.]</string>
  <string id="89141" soundid="138243">[The sphere grows dim.]</string>
  <string id="89142" soundid="138244">[Nothing happens.]</string>
  <string id="89143" soundid="138245">[Nothing happens.]</string>
  <string id="89144" soundid="138246">[Nothing happens.]</string>
  <string id="89145" soundid="138247">[The sphere grows dim.]</string>
  <string id="89146" soundid="138248">[The symbol of the Old Master is still in the lion&apos;s mouth. Something activates as you approach. The sphere begins to glow.]</string>
  <string id="89147" soundid="138249">[You leave the statue and altar as they are.]</string>
  <string id="89148" soundid="138250">[You collect the figurines and step away.]</string>
  <string id="89149" soundid="138251">[You recover the figurine and step away.]</string>
  <string id="89150" soundid="138252">[The statue does not acknowledge your presence. It has given out whatever reward it was intended to give.]</string>
  <string id="89151" soundid="138253">[The sphere grows dim.]</string>
  <string id="89152" soundid="138254">[Nothing happens.]</string>
  <string id="89153" soundid="138255">[Nothing happens.]</string>
  <string id="89154" soundid="138256">[Nothing happens.]</string>
  <string id="89155" soundid="138257">[Nothing happens.]</string>
  <string id="89156" soundid="138258">[The sphere begins to glow again.]</string>
  <string id="89157" soundid="138259">[The sphere changes color to glow red.]</string>
  <string id="89158" soundid="138260">[The sphere changes color again, glowing with a yellow light.]</string>
  <string id="89159" soundid="138261">[The statue dispenses a silver coin. An unfamiliar voice begins to emanate from the lion.]</string>
  <string id="89160" soundid="138262">The obvious path is humble, safe, but pays the wage of a cook, not a champion.</string>
  <string id="89161" soundid="138263">[The sphere grows dim.]</string>
  <string id="89162" soundid="138264">[Nothing happens.]</string>
  <string id="89163" soundid="138265">[The sphere grows dim.]</string>
  <string id="89164" soundid="138266">[Nothing happens.]</string>
  <string id="89165" soundid="138267">[Nothing happens.]</string>
  <string id="89166" soundid="138268">[Nothing happens.]</string>
  <string id="89167" soundid="138269">[Nothing happens.]</string>
  <string id="89169" soundid="138271">[There is a small bag of coins in the rubble. An unfamiliar voice begins to emanate from the lion.]</string>
  <string id="89170" soundid="138272">Rash action will reveal much about the task and the man. Reward may be immediate, but there is no going back.</string>
  <string id="89171" soundid="138273">[Something activates as you approach. The sphere in the lion&apos;s paw begins to glow.]</string>
  <string id="89172" soundid="138274">[There is an indentation in the statue&apos;s mouth, reminding you of another shape you saw recently.]</string>
  <string id="89173" soundid="138275">[Something changes inside the statue. The sphere glows green.]</string>
  <string id="89174" soundid="138276">[Nothing happens.]</string>
  <string id="89175">[Approach the altar.]</string>
  <string id="89176">[Place the red figurine on the altar.]</string>
  <string id="89177">[Place the red figurine on the altar.]</string>
  <string id="89178">[Place the yellow figurine on the altar.]</string>
  <string id="89179">[Place the red figurine on the altar.]</string>
  <string id="89180">[Remove the blue figurine from the altar.]</string>
  <string id="89181">[Place the red figurine on the altar.]</string>
  <string id="89182">[Place the blue figurine on the altar.]</string>
  <string id="89183">[Remove the red figurine from the altar.]</string>
  <string id="89184">[Place the red figurine on the altar.]</string>
  <string id="89185">[Place the blue figurine on the altar.]</string>
  <string id="89186">[Remove the yellow figurine from the altar.]</string>
  <string id="89187">[Place the blue figurine on the altar.]</string>
  <string id="89189">[Place the yellow figurine on the altar.]</string>
  <string id="89190">[Place the blue figurine on the altar.]</string>
  <string id="89191">[Remove the yellow figurine from the altar.]</string>
  <string id="89192">[Place the red figurine on the altar.]</string>
  <string id="89193">[Place the yellow figurine on the altar.]</string>
  <string id="89194">[Place the yellow figurine on the altar.]</string>
  <string id="89195">[Place the red figurine on the altar.]</string>
  <string id="89196">[Leave.]</string>
  <string id="89197">[Place the blue figurine on the altar.]</string>
  <string id="89198">[Place the yellow figurine on the altar.]</string>
  <string id="89199">[Remove the figurines.]</string>
  <string id="89200">[Place the yellow figurine on the altar.]</string>
  <string id="89201">[Place the blue figurine on the altar.]</string>
  <string id="89202">[Remove the figurine.]</string>
  <string id="89203">[Place the blue figurine on the altar.]</string>
  <string id="89204">[Place the red figurine on the altar.]</string>
  <string id="89205">[Place the yellow figurine on the altar.]</string>
  <string id="89207">[Place the yellow figurine on the altar.]</string>
  <string id="89208">[Place the red figurine on the altar.]</string>
  <string id="89209">[Place the yellow figurine on the altar.]</string>
  <string id="89210">[Place the red figurine on the altar.]</string>
  <string id="89211">[Place the blue figurine on the altar.]</string>
  <string id="89212">[Place the blue figurine on the altar.]</string>
  <string id="89213">[Place the red figurine on the altar.]</string>
  <string id="89214">[Destroy the altar.]</string>
  <string id="89215" soundid="158322">Chai Ka: The Other, Ya Zhen, has been held back for now. He will no longer bother the girl. How long it will hold, I cannot tell, but I will keep him away as long as I can.</string>
  <string id="89218">[Place the token from the Old Master&apos;s grave in the lion&apos;s mouth.]</string>
  <string id="89219">[Place the red figurine on the altar.]</string>
  <string id="89220">[Place the blue figurine on the altar.]</string>
  <string id="89222">Some Assassins must have got past us somehow. I will go look.</string>
  <string id="89224">You just keep the Lotus Assassins busy here. I will go to the temple.</string>
  <string id="89256" soundid="138412">I am sorry. Some hope was better than none. Your world is as dark as theirs.</string>
  <string id="89257" soundid="138413">I had to take a chance. You... you aren&apos;t even mortal like the rest of us anymore. I *know* what they are capable of, but you....</string>
  <string id="89258" soundid="138414">I had to... there was no promise that you would be better. It was for my daughter... I&apos;m sorry.</string>
  <string id="89259" soundid="138415">And you are becoming them! You aren&apos;t even mortal like the rest of us anymore. I *know* what they are capable of, but you....</string>
  <string id="89260" soundid="138416">Use my daughter against me, will he? Make him hurt.</string>
  <string id="89261" soundid="138417">I&apos;m sorry.</string>
  <string id="89262">The Landing Site</string>
  <string id="89263">Town Square</string>
  <string id="89265">What have you done, Sky?</string>
  <string id="89268">You made a deal with the enemy? Traitor!</string>
  <string id="89271">Dawn Star&apos;s Garden</string>
  <string id="89272">Sparring Ring</string>
  <string id="89273">To Forest</string>
  <string id="89274">Forest Shadow&apos;s Temple</string>
  <string id="89276" soundid="138436">I will return you to the earth. I am the will of the Emperor. I am Death&apos;s Hand. Sun Li commands that you die. I must obey.</string>
  <string id="89277" soundid="138437">Rrrgh! You have a better grip on your fellows than my master thought. The plight of a dead child is difficult motivation to resist.</string>
  <string id="89278" soundid="138438">Fear is all that is needed for the masses. That is why I exist. I am the will of the Emperor. I am Death&apos;s Hand. Sun Li commands that you die. I must obey.</string>
  <string id="89279" soundid="138439">He would kill you for your slander, but he will not have to. I am Death&apos;s Hand. Sun Li commands that you die. I must obey.</string>
  <string id="89282">It is no &quot;grip.&quot; You rule through fear, I inspire loyalty.</string>
  <string id="89284">Li knows much about perverting such motivation. His child is his excuse.</string>
  <string id="89286">I will surprise you in many ways, Prince Kin.</string>
  <string id="89287">Master Radiant&apos;s Chambers</string>
  <string id="89288">Master Smiling Hawk&apos;s Chambers</string>
  <string id="89289">Dining Hall</string>
  <string id="89290">Garden</string>
  <string id="89291">To City Core</string>
  <string id="89292">Can I ask you some questions?</string>
  <string id="89315" soundid="158323">Chai Ka: Wild Flower is safe from him for now.</string>
  <string id="89316">The small seal is made of ancient stone and carved with intricate designs. Though it appears lifeless, you can sense a powerful energy contained within.</string>
  <string id="89317">Lion&apos;s Head Token</string>
  <string id="89318">Palace Gate</string>
  <string id="89319">Palace Gate</string>
  <string id="89327">Water Dragon Spirit</string>
  <string id="89350" soundid="166040">We thought you&apos;d asked for her to join you, Judge! Good thing we followed her!</string>
  <string id="89351" soundid="166041">We thought you *wanted* him to come down here, Judge! Good thing we followed to make sure!</string>
  <string id="89365" soundid="138609">What is the old saying? Honor among thieves?</string>
  <string id="89367" soundid="138611">Layers upon layers. As if this wasn&apos;t complicated enough.</string>
  <string id="89368" soundid="138612">Now you are really stepping beyond the realm of reason. Why would Zu know this?</string>
  <string id="89369" soundid="138613">Only partially, it would seem, or they would both be alive.</string>
  <string id="89370" soundid="138614">Does this change anything? We can tell Master Li and give him hope, but we must rescue him first.</string>
  <string id="89371" soundid="138615">Then let&apos;s quit talking and go to the palace! I will lead the way.</string>
  <string id="89372" soundid="138616">Well, I certainly see why he would keep that a secret.</string>
  <string id="89373" soundid="138617">He must have felt very guilty about it. Perhaps that is why he shadowed us for so long. Even in the swamps he must have wanted to make amends.</string>
  <string id="89374" soundid="138618">That&apos;s all very sad, but it changes nothing. Our immediate concern is my father. I will guide you to the palace.</string>
  <string id="89375" soundid="138619">Then you can brief us on the way. I am eager to end this as well.</string>
  <string id="89377">He was part of the group sent to kill them. He had a change of heart.</string>
  <string id="89381">It doesn&apos;t matter. We have to accept that it is possible.</string>
  <string id="89382">There is more. Zu said he was with the group that killed Master Li&apos;s family.</string>
  <string id="89386">There is more to discuss, but I want to get moving.</string>
  <string id="89389">ITEM_PLOT_J04_FANG_POISON</string>
  <string id="89390">ITEM_PLOT_J04_FANG_POISON Description</string>
  <string id="89391">ITEM_PLOT_J04_LOTUS_JIADOOR_KEY</string>
  <string id="89392">ITEM_PLOT_J04_LOTUS_JIADOOR_KEY Desc</string>
  <string id="89393">Thief Liver</string>
  <string id="89394">ITEM_PLOT_J04_NEC_THIEFLIVER Desc</string>
  <string id="89395">Preserved Liver</string>
  <string id="89396">This liver has been preserved by special medical and arcane means. It&apos;s so well preserved that it almost looks alive.</string>
  <string id="89397">Dragon Powder</string>
  <string id="89398">A small canister of the volatile black substance called dragon powder. The Lotus Assassins were clearly using this substance to excavate in the lower ruins of Tien&apos;s landing, but this charge doesn&apos;t look sufficient for blasting anything. It might be useful as a primer for a larger explosive.</string>
  <string id="89401">Patron</string>
  <string id="89404">Patron</string>
  <string id="89407">Outlaw</string>
  <string id="89410">ITEM_SPIRIT_JADEWAR</string>
  <string id="89411">ITEM_SPIRIT_ELEPHANT</string>
  <string id="89412">ITEM_SPIRIT_BULL</string>
  <string id="89413" soundid="144745">Are you all right? You fell over after the fight. There was something here, but I couldn&apos;t see it clearly.</string>
  <string id="89425">A vision. The same creature I saw in the spirit cave in the school.</string>
  <string id="89427">Never mind. Let&apos;s just get moving.</string>
  <string id="89499" soundid="168499">The ingredients are very rare and it costs me quite a bit to procure them, especially while I&apos;m stuck in this... quaint village. I&apos;ll need another 300 silver from you.</string>
  <string id="89500" soundid="189514"></string>
  <string id="89533">Commoner</string>
  <string id="89535">Commoner</string>
  <string id="89538">Commoner</string>
  <string id="89544">Commoner</string>
  <string id="89547">Commoner</string>
  <string id="89550">Commoner</string>
  <string id="89553">Commoner</string>
  <string id="89577" soundid="144837">Those pillars don&apos;t look stable!</string>
  <string id="89578" soundid="144838">She&apos;s too strong to defeat without using your head!</string>
  <string id="89579" soundid="144839">That ceiling can&apos;t be stable with that hole in it!</string>
  <string id="89580" soundid="144840">That thing&apos;s hide is too tough to cut!</string>
  <string id="89581" soundid="144841">She&apos;s just trying to wear you down! You can&apos;t beat her with just your fists!</string>
  <string id="89582" soundid="144842">Quit wasting time! You&apos;ve got to drop the ceiling on her!</string>
  <string id="89586" soundid="144843">If you knock those pillars down this place will collapse like a bad cake!</string>
  <string id="89587" soundid="144844">Isn&apos;t this why you practice breaking all those bricks? Hit the pillars!</string>
  <string id="89588" soundid="144845">That&apos;s it! You could feel the earth move when that pillar fell!</string>
  <string id="89589" soundid="144846">Keep doing that! She&apos;ll be in for a surprise!</string>
  <string id="89590" soundid="144847"></string>
  <string id="89591" soundid="144848">You know what I like about this place? Absolutely nothing. Let&apos;s get what we need and get to the Imperial City.</string>
  <string id="89592" soundid="144849">Wang said something about a screwable power horse. You should get that, then maybe we can get going.</string>
  <string id="89593" soundid="144850">Kang! It&apos;s *Kang,* not Wang! And it&apos;s an inscrutable power source, you dumb ox.</string>
  <string id="89594" soundid="144851">Whatever. Just get that thing he said.</string>
  <string id="89595" soundid="144852">What do you want from me? I&apos;m here to kill things. You want answers, ask someone else.</string>
  <string id="89597">Sign</string>
  <string id="89606">Boy</string>
  <string id="89609">Girl</string>
  <string id="89612" soundid="145157">I know this one by reputation, and that&apos;s enough. I trust you&apos;ll consider this discussion private and potentially very beneficial.</string>
  <string id="89613" soundid="145158">Your introductions are unnecessary, Cho. I know this one personally. I trust you&apos;ll consider this discussion private and potentially very beneficial.</string>
  <string id="89614" soundid="145159">When Cho approached me regarding this matter, I felt that it might be in the best interests of the greater Guild if I were involved.</string>
  <string id="89616">Disturbance</string>
  <string id="89617">Statue of Mah Tsung</string>
  <string id="89618" soundid="145250">Here, I salvaged this gem out of some sort of power source. I imagine you will have some use for it.</string>
  <string id="89619" soundid="145251">Now that we&apos;re here, we should see if anyone knows anything about flyers. Maybe whoever is in charge of the town can help us get underway again.</string>
  <string id="89620" soundid="145252">There you are! I&apos;m... I&apos;m sorry, I didn&apos;t want to wait back there any longer. I don&apos;t think anything will hurt the flyer. It is plenty hurt already.</string>
  <string id="89621" soundid="145253">I found this gem in the wreckage. I&apos;m not sure what it was attached to, but I&apos;m sure you can use it for something.</string>
  <string id="89622" soundid="145254">I won&apos;t discuss that. Perhaps I will say more when I know *your* motives better, but for now, my past is my own.</string>
  <string id="89623" soundid="145255">I wouldn&apos;t have much respect for you if you did, but it is all that I am going to offer right now.</string>
  <string id="89624" soundid="145256">I am not concealing anything that will harm you or your cause. You and Dawn Star have my full support, but my past is my own affair.</string>
  <string id="89625" soundid="145257">You can&apos;t, but if the Lotus Assassins wanted to get a spy close to you, they would not use one who bears their stained hands as openly as I.</string>
  <string id="89626" soundid="145258">I also doubt he would announce his former status. And if he did, he would probably appease you with something more detailed than, &quot;I don&apos;t want to talk about it.&quot;</string>
  <string id="89627" soundid="145259">And I have declined to answer those questions. My past is my own business. If that changes, I will let you know.</string>
  <string id="89628" soundid="145260">Nothing to concern yourself over. Very old business. I traveled this way when I was fleeing the Lotus Assassins.</string>
  <string id="89629" soundid="145261">It was nothing. Some vagrant waif I passed off after making sure its belly was full. A far less surprising turn than what Hui said about your Master Li.</string>
  <string id="89630" soundid="145262">I know Hui to be a truthful and honorable person. Much more so than I consider myself to be. I do not question her belief, but belief alone is not enough.</string>
  <string id="89631" soundid="145263">What if it *is* true? Much will have to change to accommodate this &quot;truth.&quot; It means the Emperor lied about Li&apos;s death, and he may have assaulted the heavens.</string>
  <string id="89632" soundid="145264">The *Emperor* subject to the common vice of deception? Unthinkable.</string>
  <string id="89633" soundid="145265">Perhaps, but that, too, implies a weakness that the Emperor cannot have.</string>
  <string id="89634" soundid="145266">I warn you, this will lead in a dangerous direction for you and Dawn Star. I cannot condone it... but I have agreed to help, and I will.</string>
  <string id="89635" soundid="145267">Just don&apos;t blame me when the whole world is against you.</string>
  <string id="89636" soundid="145268">You and your companions have shown me a path I previously thought closed. Give me no more thought than that. Now, is there anything else?</string>
  <string id="89637" soundid="145269">No, he is not. He is Emperor Sun Hai. He is as close to the heavens as a mortal can be.</string>
  <string id="89638" soundid="145270">Perhaps my path has joined the low road once or twice, but you don&apos;t have to be an earnest schoolboy to know that anarchy is madness. The order of things is important.</string>
  <string id="89639" soundid="145271">Oh, choosing to leave is easy enough. Surviving the choice is not. Is that a surprise, given their nature? Hui&apos;s comments about Master Li are more outlandish.</string>
  <string id="89640" soundid="145272">I won&apos;t get in your way if you don&apos;t get in mine. I have nothing more to say about where we are.</string>
  <string id="89641">Your connection to your guardian demon severed, your soul is lost for all eternity.</string>
  <string id="89643" soundid="145275">Our enemy? The sure sign of an effective fighter is that he has many enemies. Which are you most curious about?</string>
  <string id="89644" soundid="145276">A small man. He bears a grudge against the world because his wealth cannot buy him the status he wants. At least, that is my estimation of him.</string>
  <string id="89645" soundid="145277">If we encounter him in his holdings near Tien&apos;s Landing, I doubt he will be very welcoming. Not after he learns the fate of his son.</string>
  <string id="89646">I have questions about you and the Lotus Assassins.</string>
  <string id="89647">Why did you leave them?</string>
  <string id="89648">I want to talk about you.</string>
  <string id="89649">What do you think about our current situation?</string>
  <string id="89650">I have questions about our enemy.</string>
  <string id="89651">Tell me about Gao the Greater.</string>
  <string id="89653">I want to go back to my other questions.</string>
  <string id="89654">I want to know about the Emperor.</string>
  <string id="89656">It seems to me that either he approves or he has lost power.</string>
  <string id="89658">Why not?</string>
  <string id="89659">Tell me about Death&apos;s Hand and the Lotus Assassins.</string>
  <string id="89662">Goodbye for now.</string>
  <string id="89668">I am supposed to accept that answer?</string>
  <string id="89670">Very well, but I will be watching you.</string>
  <string id="89671">Then I will not press the matter. For now.</string>
  <string id="89672">How can I be certain of that?</string>
  <string id="89674">I want to know what you and Hui were talking about.</string>
  <string id="89675">I want to know more about this &quot;child&quot; she mentioned.</string>
  <string id="89676">She confirmed that he is the Emperor&apos;s brother.</string>
  <string id="89677">Are you dismissing what she said?</string>
  <string id="89679">Cannibal</string>
  <string id="89682">Cannibal</string>
  <string id="89686">Then Death&apos;s Hand has far more influence than he should.</string>
  <string id="89689">I appreciate your help, even if you give it reluctantly.</string>
  <string id="89690">Why stay if you are so reluctant?</string>
  <string id="89691">Why is it unthinkable? He is a man, like any other.</string>
  <string id="89693">You don&apos;t seem the type to hold such allegiance to the Empire.</string>
  <string id="89695">You were fleeing? So leaving the Lotus Assassins was not a choice?</string>
  <string id="89696">I want to talk about you some more. You seem agitated.</string>
  <string id="89697">I want to talk about what Inquisitor Lim said about you.</string>
  <string id="89706" soundid="139127">Look, we have fresh blood. Another soul for the forge, or a new pet for the masters? We don&apos;t need more competition for attention.</string>
  <string id="89707" soundid="139128">With the rise of the golems, we acolytes have fewer opportunities to serve. You are unwelcome.</string>
  <string id="89708" soundid="139129">We all serve, but those who serve are not all equal. </string>
  <string id="89709" soundid="139130">You spout big words, but you are in no position to back them up.</string>
  <string id="89710" soundid="139131">We are losing status to the golem army and you want to take more attention away from us? I think you need to prove your worth.</string>
  <string id="89711" soundid="139132">Should he prove his worth? No, he can defend it, or die.</string>
  <string id="89712" soundid="139133">Accepted, yes, but not tested. If you die here, clearly you are not capable of joining us. We have no need of acolytes that cannot even reach their master.</string>
  <string id="89713" soundid="139134">You, kill this fool.</string>
  <string id="89714" soundid="139135">More blood to stain my hands. A badge of honor.</string>
  <string id="89715" soundid="139136">Ah, you realize the inevitability of this challenge. Good, that will make it easier to justify.</string>
  <string id="89716" soundid="139137">Bah! You are skilled, but Assassins are not just quick steps and cuts. We will see if you are strong enough. This isn&apos;t over.</string>
  <string id="89717">Your end is near!</string>
  <string id="89720">I only seek to serve the Lotus Assassins. Let me pass.</string>
  <string id="89722">Out of my way, or you&apos;ll be dead when I&apos;m running the place.</string>
  <string id="89725">Your masters will not like this. I am an accepted recruit.</string>
  <string id="89728">If any of you think you can beat me, step up now, or stand aside.</string>
  <string id="89730">My style is flawless!</string>
  <string id="89732">I will sacrifice what I can for her life.</string>
  <string id="89739">I have done all I can.</string>
  <string id="89745">You ask too much of me.</string>
  <string id="89751">If I help you, you&apos;ll only tell the others what I&apos;ve done. I have to let you go.</string>
  <string id="89752">For that price, I&apos;m your man. Stand down, Aishi!</string>
  <string id="89754">For that price, I&apos;m your woman, Captain Sen. Stand down, Aishi!</string>
  <string id="89760">Help him, Doctor An.</string>
  <string id="89912">Will she be all right?</string>
  <string id="89918">I will take my reward from his possessions.</string>
  <string id="89920">He&apos;ll make it worth your while.</string>
  <string id="89922">You can&apos;t make her help you.</string>
  <string id="89927">My investigation made it clear that he had already slipped away.</string>
  <string id="89930">What could he possibly offer me? He&apos;s gone and there&apos;s no point catching him.</string>
  <string id="89937" soundid="145551">They tried to take from me, and they died. I feasted on their souls. Such is the evil I was in life, and am again in death! The underworld has no place for me! Ji Xin lives!</string>
  <string id="89938" soundid="145552">It doesn&apos;t? But I *want* it to! Blood. Horror. Pain. Despair. The sounds of flesh ripping. This is the music I dream of in my cursed undeath.</string>
  <string id="89939" soundid="145553">I am evil incarnate. A man so vicious and vile that the spirits deemed me unfit to pass into death and cursed me into this wretched form. Ji Xin lives, indeed....</string>
  <string id="89940" soundid="145554">Now, I feed on the flesh and souls of the living in payment for my vanity. My perfect body is a testament to my crimes. My very touch spreads my corruption.</string>
  <string id="89941" soundid="145555">[Success] A chance... to repent. Can it be that after all this time, after years of living death, I am given this one chance to make something right?</string>
  <string id="89942" soundid="145556">What is this &quot;chance&quot; you speak of, mortal? What is this false hope you dangle before me?</string>
  <string id="89943" soundid="145557">Ah, you are a scholar as well. If one believes in one&apos;s own damnation, then that one is truly damned. But then, at least, they will never be proven wrong. The vanity of intellect.</string>
  <string id="89944" soundid="145558">Hah... haha... Hahaha! So true! So true, mortal. For me, there is no hope. For me, there is nothing! And so, for you too, there will be nothing.</string>
  <string id="89945" soundid="145559">[Failure] Never! My sins can never be redeemed! This is my fate! The curse of years weighs down on my soul, and I can never rise from it!</string>
  <string id="89946" soundid="145560">It is, and will forever be. Now you, too, will share in this cursed fate!</string>
  <string id="89947" soundid="145561">Something of mine? You think I&apos;ll part so willingly with something, even if it is just a piece of my own corrupt body?</string>
  <string id="89948" soundid="145562">A girl... after so long, a girl. Hah! But I&apos;m a vile and corrupt being, forever damned by the life I led. Set here in this wretched form to walk forever.</string>
  <string id="89949" soundid="145563">Redemption... for one such as me? I think not. My life was spent in greed and vanity and corruption. Even in death I sought to preserve my perfect form.</string>
  <string id="89950" soundid="145564">For one whose madness and evil progress even into death? No, there is no hope for me. None at all. And you stand here, mocking me for it.</string>
  <string id="89951" soundid="145565">Ah, the temptation! Yes... so much logic... so much philosophy, but who knows what the heavens will truly decide in the end?</string>
  <string id="89952" soundid="145566">But... for the chance... And it is a girl... so young... I can taste her pain and suffering lingering about you. So like my own.</string>
  <string id="89956" soundid="145567">The blood is thick in my veins. A solid mass where fluid used to flow. Now dried and brittle. But the heart still stirs, and it can be moved, though tears no longer flow.</string>
  <string id="89957" soundid="145568">My life has been wasted on my own sins... and in death I have nothing except them. This young thing... this girl... she still deserves life.</string>
  <string id="89958" soundid="145569">If my end means this girl lives, then may the heavens look kindly upon me, even though I know they won&apos;t. If damnation is my fate, then let it be worth something in the end.</string>
  <string id="89959" soundid="145570">Take what you need, mortal.</string>
  <string id="89960">There&apos;s nothing I could tell you, regardless of your offer.</string>
  <string id="89961" soundid="145572">Haha, you have a wit, mortal. I think I&apos;ll enjoy cutting it from your soul, piece by piece.</string>
  <string id="89966" soundid="160019">There&apos;s got to be no better feeling than joining the legends of the Empire itself. Except maybe a good bowl of wine.</string>
  <string id="89973" soundid="154629">[By removing the Jade Heart, you have permanently destroyed the dam&apos;s control mechanism.]</string>
  <string id="89974" soundid="139469">When they asked me to work for the school exclusively, I accepted. I&apos;d rather have a steady life, making weapons by the bunch, than doing special orders all the time.</string>
  <string id="89975" soundid="139470">And every once in a while, I get to make something unique. The masters have some amazing scrolls describing weapons I never even knew existed. </string>
  <string id="89976" soundid="139471">Hmm. Well, it&apos;s the best of its kind in all the Empire, or at least that&apos;s what I&apos;m told. &apos;Course, it&apos;s seen better days.</string>
  <string id="89977" soundid="139472">But, now that you&apos;ve dealt with Smiling Hawk, maybe they can get back to way they once were. I&apos;m sure Kai will make an excellent master.</string>
  <string id="89978" soundid="139473">Having two masters has really hurt the school, if you ask me. Seems the students spend more time bickering than fighting. But what do I know?</string>
  <string id="89979" soundid="139474">If it was me, I&apos;d just kick one of the masters out on his ear. I&apos;d like to tell you which one, too, but I&apos;d better not. Best not to get involved.</string>
  <string id="89980" soundid="139475">Suit yourself. I have a lot of work to do. Good day.</string>
  <string id="89981">The will of the heavens was fulfilled. The heart of the Water Dragon was restored, and her soul, reborn. Balance returned to the heavens, and the Jade Empire endured. His duty discharged, Chai Ka the Heavenly Gate Guardian returned to his heaven once more. 

In honor of her service to the heavens, the girl, Wild Flower, whom Chai Ka had raised to serve as his anchor, was granted the most precious gift of all: Life. She was given a chance to live a new life according to her own whim.</string>
  <string id="89982">In the shattered mind of Wild Flower dwelled the demon Ya Zhen. The power of the one who freed him grew, giving the demon endless possibilities. For a time, he lived by the pledge he made, serving a power greater than himself, but mortals remain mortal, and in time, they die. And when his pledge no longer binds him... then the demon&apos;s time will come again.</string>
  <string id="89984">Yes I would.</string>
  <string id="89985">Cannibal</string>
  <string id="89986">Show me your weapons again.</string>
  <string id="89987">Tell me about yourself.</string>
  <string id="89990">Could I see what you have for sale?</string>
  <string id="89991">Tell me about the Black Leopard School.</string>
  <string id="89994">I should be going.</string>
  <string id="89995" soundid="139555">Master Radiant does not want to waste his time on someone who is unprepared. If you can defeat each of us, then you are ready to learn from a master.</string>
  <string id="89996" soundid="139556">An impressive feat, but it was only one fight. As skilled as you are, you must understand that a great fighter must be consistent to remain great.</string>
  <string id="89997" soundid="139557">You have proven you can defeat our novices. Now you must prove yourself against the brothers. The brothers have trained long and are second only in skill to the masters.</string>
  <string id="89998" soundid="139558">Sixth brother is the least skilled, so you will start with him. Work your way to Third Brother. If you succeed against him, you will then challenge me.</string>
  <string id="89999" soundid="139559">You&apos;ll find plenty of challenges here, I assure you.</string>
  <string id="90000" soundid="139560">Second Brother is... not here. For now, you must face only Third Brother and myself... after you&apos;ve defeated the other brothers.</string>
  <string id="90001" soundid="139561">Our students are the best in the Empire. They just might surprise you.</string>
  <string id="90002" soundid="139562">I must be honest with you... I believe Master Radiant has a plan in allowing you to join us. As you may have heard, there are two masters at this school.</string>
  <string id="90003" soundid="139563">Master Radiant and I have tried for some time to temper Master Smiling Hawk&apos;s... ways. He is cunning and ruthless and has little regard for students.</string>
  <string id="90008">I&apos;ll be careful.</string>
  <string id="90010">Why does Master Radiant tolerate him?</string>
  <string id="90012">We&apos;re all fighters. We are all dangerous.</string>
  <string id="90015">No thanks. I have better things to do.</string>
  <string id="90016">Yes. I would like to join the school after all.</string>
  <string id="90017">Remind me why I would want to join.</string>
  <string id="90018">No. I&apos;m still not interested in joining.</string>
  <string id="90019">Yes, I wanted to ask you about the school.</string>
  <string id="90020">What can you tell me about Third Brother?</string>
  <string id="90023">Why are there two masters at the school?</string>
  <string id="90026">Which master do you follow?</string>
  <string id="90029">Where is Second Brother?</string>
  <string id="90032">Why is it called the Black Leopard School?</string>
  <string id="90035">What can you tell me about events outside of the school?</string>
  <string id="90037">I should get back to fighting.</string>
  <string id="90038">How do I set up a fight with the brothers?</string>
  <string id="90039">No. I should get back to fighting.</string>
  <string id="90042" soundid="154946">Bai the Outcrier can direct you if needed. He stands over by where the flyers dock.</string>
  <string id="90043">I&apos;d like to practice some more.</string>
  <string id="90046">Thanks, it was a difficult fight.</string>
  <string id="90047">Third Brother was easy to defeat.</string>
  <string id="90049">I think he had help from Smiling Hawk.</string>
  <string id="90053">I&apos;m glad I could help. Is there anything more I can do?</string>
  <string id="90054">I just hope your master made the right choice in leaving the school to you.</string>
  <string id="90055">Leaping Tiger Style</string>
  <string id="90056" soundid="160759">As you wish. Once you&apos;ve defeated Fifth Brother, come and see me for a match.</string>
  <string id="90057">I want a practice fight.</string>
  <string id="90059">Storm Dragon Style</string>
  <string id="90060">I&apos;d like to see those items again.</string>
  <string id="90061">No thanks.</string>
  <string id="90062">White Demon Style</string>
  <string id="90066">Greetings. I apologize if I&apos;ve caused any problems.</string>
  <string id="90067">Your students could use a bit of restraint.</string>
  <string id="90068">Your novices are fortunate you came when you did!</string>
  <string id="90070">Yes. I would like that.</string>
  <string id="90071">Why would I want to join your school?</string>
  <string id="90074">Yes. I think I&apos;d like to join the school.</string>
  <string id="90077">That sounds reasonable.</string>
  <string id="90078">Why do I have to prove myself?</string>
  <string id="90080">But I just defeated four of your students... at once!</string>
  <string id="90083">Good. I like a challenge.</string>
  <string id="90084">What about Second Brother?</string>
  <string id="90086">I look forward to defeating all of you!</string>
  <string id="90087" soundid="139647">So you&apos;ve defeated Fourth Brother Yu... finally. You&apos;ll get your chance to see what a real fighter can do soon enough!</string>
  <string id="90088" soundid="139648">Don&apos;t patronize me. I&apos;m not falling for your false flattery.</string>
  <string id="90089" soundid="139649">I would like that, more than you can guess. But I have other orders.</string>
  <string id="90090" soundid="139650">You came to this school. That&apos;s enough.</string>
  <string id="90091" soundid="139651">Master Smiling Hawk wants to see you. He sent me to escort you. Follow me.</string>
  <string id="90092" soundid="139652">Then you are a fool. But I suppose I already knew that. </string>
  <string id="90093" soundid="139653">You are a student, and I am Third Brother. You will do as I say.</string>
  <string id="90094" soundid="139654">Master Smiling Hawk has even less patience than I do. Let&apos;s go!</string>
  <string id="90095" soundid="139655">What do you want? I&apos;ve told First Brother that I withdraw, now go and challenge him.</string>
  <string id="90096" soundid="139656">You are a fool to choose Radiant over the Smiling Hawk. Are you also fool enough to challenge me to a fight?</string>
  <string id="90097">I&apos;m sure you are very skilled, Third Brother.</string>
  <string id="90098">How about right now!</string>
  <string id="90099">What&apos;s the matter? Did I do something to you?</string>
  <string id="90101">I&apos;m not interested in meeting with him.</string>
  <string id="90103">What if I don&apos;t want to meet him?</string>
  <string id="90105">Good. I&apos;ve been looking forward to meeting him.</string>
  <string id="90106" soundid="139666">It was foolish of us to challenge you earlier. I apologize for my impudence.</string>
  <string id="90107" soundid="139667">I can see why the masters chose you to join the school. Even Fourth Brother cannot withstand your skills.</string>
  <string id="90108" soundid="139668">It is a shame that blood was shed, but the school is better off without Smiling Hawk.</string>
  <string id="90109" soundid="139669">I apologize, but I cannot talk right now. I must prepare for a sparring match with Brother Shangjin.</string>
  <string id="90110" soundid="139670">Well, I can&apos;t say I like you anymore now, but I&apos;m grateful that you rid us of that senile old man, Radiant.</string>
  <string id="90111" soundid="139671">We may be novices, but we&apos;re still skilled. You&apos;re lucky Third Brother stopped that fight when he did.</string>
  <string id="90112" soundid="139672">I can&apos;t believe Third Brother lost to *you*. I hope Master Smiling Hawk teaches you a lesson or two.</string>
  <string id="90113" soundid="139673">I don&apos;t really feel like talking right now.</string>
  <string id="90114" soundid="139674">Sorry, I&apos;m new here. There&apos;s really nothing I can do to help you, I&apos;m afraid.</string>
  <string id="90115" soundid="139675">I&apos;m glad Master Smiling Hawk is gone, that man terrified me.</string>
  <string id="90116" soundid="139676">You certainly taught us a thing or two about fighting. I&apos;m just glad you didn&apos;t hurt us too badly.</string>
  <string id="90117" soundid="139677">I can&apos;t believe you defeated Fourth Brother. If I had known you were so skilled I would have never attacked you.</string>
  <string id="90118" soundid="139678">You may have defeated us, but Third Brother will teach you what real fighting is like.</string>
  <string id="90119" soundid="139679">I&apos;m impressed, Third Brother is a difficult opponent. I&apos;ve never seen anyone even come close to defeating him before.</string>
  <string id="90120" soundid="139680">I don&apos;t have time to talk right now.</string>
  <string id="90121" soundid="139681">With Radiant out of the way, Master Smiling Hawk can finally lead this school as it was meant to be led.</string>
  <string id="90122" soundid="139682">Come in, come in quickly, and shut that door behind you. It gets so cold and drafty in here, I can almost feel the wind blowing right through me.</string>
  <string id="90123" soundid="139683">Ha! That was a joke, my young student. You are free to laugh if you feel so inclined. [sigh] Everyone is so serious around here these days.</string>
  <string id="90124" soundid="139684">But Smiling Hawk failed to realize the true nature of his technique. It does not merely borrow your style and power; it takes your life.</string>
  <string id="90125" soundid="139685">And so, with one stealthy encounter, Smiling Hawk not only gained my fighting powers but also eliminated the one person who could challenge him.</string>
  <string id="90126" soundid="139686">There&apos;s nothing more humiliating for a master than waking up and realizing you&apos;ve been beaten by a bookworm... and in your own room, no less!</string>
  <string id="90127" soundid="139687">Yes, but deadly just the same. There is a fine line between ambition and greed, need and lust. Smiling Hawk crossed the line and hasn&apos;t looked back since.</string>
  <string id="90128" soundid="139688">Some might call it that, though I would not be one of them. Boldness is derived from courage, not fear. Smiling Hawk&apos;s lust for power drove him, not his courage.</string>
  <string id="90129" soundid="139689">No doubt you can. You are very astute for someone so young.</string>
  <string id="90130" soundid="139690">Smiling Hawk chose the easy route to power, but it has cost him. The power has changed him and corroded his spirit, but it also makes him very powerful.</string>
  <string id="90131" soundid="139691">First Brother and I have kept him in check, barely. But the balance slowly turns in his favor as he gains more and more power.</string>
  <string id="90132" soundid="139692">That is precisely why I brought you here. You alone have the skill and strength to defeat Smiling Hawk. There is something... different about you.</string>
  <string id="90133" soundid="139693">As a spirit, I can see your power... and its source. It is different for you than for anyone I have ever met.</string>
  <string id="90134" soundid="139694">I won&apos;t tell you that Smiling Hawk cannot harm you, but I&apos;m certain that he cannot steal your power. Not the way he stole mine, at any rate.</string>
  <string id="90135" soundid="139695">Ha! Humility is not one of your strengths. Fortunately, you will not need humility against the Smiling Hawk.</string>
  <string id="90136" soundid="139696">Good luck, young one. Be careful, but be courageous. I know you have what it takes to defeat Smiling Hawk.</string>
  <string id="90137">Just pretend that you told me nothing. I don&apos;t want to risk your son.</string>
  <string id="90139" soundid="139699">Well done. Well done, indeed. There&apos;s something about your fighting... I&apos;m not sure what it is exactly, but it is most unique. Whatever it is, it serves you well.</string>
  <string id="90140" soundid="139700">With Smiling Hawk gone, I can finally heed the call on my spirit. Much longer and I would have been torn from this place forcibly.</string>
  <string id="90141" soundid="139701">Master, why must you leave? I still have so much to learn from you, and we need a strong master to rebuild the school.</string>
  <string id="90142" soundid="139702">Brother Kai, there are some things you must learn for yourself. As long as I stay here, I am holding you back.</string>
  <string id="90143" soundid="139703">And besides... you are ready. You know enough. And what you do not know, you&apos;ll figure out. That is what it means to be a master.</string>
  <string id="90144" soundid="139704">Thank you, if it wasn&apos;t for you... well, this never would have happened. It seems to me that you&apos;re the one who should receive this honor.</string>
  <string id="90145" soundid="139705">Ha! Don&apos;t let Kai&apos;s compliments go to your head. You did us a great favor, and you&apos;re welcome here anytime, but you&apos;re no master.</string>
  <string id="90146" soundid="139706">Yes, that sums it up. You did us a great favor, and you&apos;re welcome here anytime. But you&apos;re no master.</string>
  <string id="90147" soundid="139707">You *are* very likely the most skilled fighter I&apos;ve ever known, but your path lies in a different direction... many directions, if I don&apos;t miss my guess.</string>
  <string id="90148" soundid="139708">This school needs stability, and right now, Kai offers that. One day, when your adventures are done, you&apos;ll make a great master. Until then....</string>
  <string id="90149" soundid="139709">Bah! Humility is overrated. I will offer something more than thanks. Before I leave, I&apos;ll teach you a style I learned in the spirit world.</string>
  <string id="90150" soundid="139710">Of course you don&apos;t. Ha! But I will offer something more than thanks. Before I leave, I&apos;ll teach you a style I learned in the spirit world.</string>
  <string id="90151" soundid="139711">Did I say that was it? You are so impatient! I have one more thing to offer you. Before I leave, I&apos;ll teach you a style I learned in the spirit world.</string>
  <string id="90152" soundid="139712">I was afraid to use it against Smiling Hawk. If he had stolen it from me, he would have been almost unstoppable.</string>
  <string id="90153" soundid="139713">Well? Are you interested in learning, or are you just going to stand there?</string>
  <string id="90154" soundid="139714">Watch and learn. If you are as good as you seem, I should only have to show you once.</string>
  <string id="90155" soundid="139715">The style you just learned is very rare. Its original master died centuries ago, but the spirits know it, and now you do as well.</string>
  <string id="90156" soundid="139716">I must be going. First Brother Kai will never truly be master until I am gone. The students must follow him, and him alone.</string>
  <string id="90157" soundid="139717">I would speak with you alone Master Radiant, before you go.</string>
  <string id="90158" soundid="139718">If you wait outside, I will join you in a minute. I have something I would like to offer you in thanks for your help.</string>
  <string id="90159" soundid="139719">Good luck to you, as well. You&apos;ll need it.</string>
  <string id="90160" soundid="139720">Goodbye, and good luck. You&apos;ll need it.</string>
  <string id="90161" soundid="139721">What has happened here?</string>
  <string id="90162">I won&apos;t let anything happen to your son.</string>
  <string id="90163" soundid="154918"></string>
  <string id="90164" soundid="154919"></string>
  <string id="90165" soundid="154920"></string>
  <string id="90167" soundid="139727">If there&apos;s one thing I&apos;ve learned since I died, it&apos;s not to take yourself too seriously. It can all end in an instant, and then it&apos;s too late to enjoy your life.</string>
  <string id="90168" soundid="139728">Dead and buried. Food for the worms, as they say. Now you&apos;ll be wondering why the school still follows a dead master, hmm?</string>
  <string id="90169" soundid="139729">Ha! I don&apos;t know about great, but yes, I am a ghost. Food for the worms, as they say. Now you&apos;ll be wondering why the school still follows a dead master, hmm?</string>
  <string id="90170" soundid="139730">I choose to remain in my room for reasons beyond my... appearance.</string>
  <string id="90171" soundid="139731">My spirit could not leave this place, due to the way I was killed. First Brother and I keep my death a secret, well he and Second Brother, until his recent demise.</string>
  <string id="90172" soundid="139732">The other students just think I&apos;m an irritable old curmudgeon who doesn&apos;t like to be disturbed... not too far from the truth. But no doubt you&apos;re wondering how I died.</string>
  <string id="90173" soundid="139733">Good. It&apos;s nice to have an eager listener, unlike some people who nod their head and pretend to listen. Wouldn&apos;t you say, First Brother?</string>
  <string id="90174" soundid="139734">Too bad. If you&apos;re not interested, just nod your head and pretend to listen, like First Brother does when I go on about the way things used to be.</string>
  <string id="90175">I&apos;m not going to be beaten!</string>
  <string id="90177" soundid="139737">Ha! I&apos;m the master of this school! When I speak, you certainly have nothing better to do than listen. At least First Brother will nod his head and *pretend* to listen.</string>
  <string id="90178" soundid="139738">Now, where was I? Oh yes, the story of my demise. Before Master Smiling Hawk was a master, he was Third Brother Liu.</string>
  <string id="90179" soundid="139739">He was a gifted student, although not a very good fighter. He preferred books and knowledge over combat... but his thirst for knowledge was unhealthy.</string>
  <string id="90180" soundid="139740">Smiling Hawk was never content with his place here. Eventually, he sought to move beyond his station and take what he had not yet earned.</string>
  <string id="90182" soundid="139742">Very dangerous, especially for anyone who got in his way. At any rate, Smiling Hawk turned his considerable intellect to advancing himself.</string>
  <string id="90183" soundid="139743">Ha! We all want more, otherwise we&apos;d never learn! But you miss the point... it&apos;s not the wanting, it&apos;s how you get what you want that matters.</string>
  <string id="90184" soundid="139744">Smiling Hawk was smart, but he wasn&apos;t wise. He discovered a technique that allowed him to harness another person&apos;s style and power.</string>
  <string id="90185" soundid="139745">This technique was unnatural. I reprimanded him and told him to stop dabbling with things that he could not control.</string>
  <string id="90186" soundid="139746">Of course, in my arrogance, I assumed he would obey my wise instructions. But Smiling Hawk had no intention of letting go of his newfound technique.</string>
  <string id="90187" soundid="139747">An excellent point, and one that very few people grasp. You may yet prove to be an excellent student.</string>
  <string id="90188" soundid="139748">If you don&apos;t know, then I doubt I can explain it to you. Some people possess power, while others are possessed by it. Smiling Hawk fell into the latter group.</string>
  <string id="90189" soundid="139749">Ha! You&apos;re picking up First Brother&apos;s bad habits.</string>
  <string id="90190" soundid="139750">At any rate, Smiling Hawk decided to try out his technique on me. With my power, he could become First Brother... and more.</string>
  <string id="90194">Power is hard to gain and even harder to let go.</string>
  <string id="90196">Of course not. Why would he?</string>
  <string id="90198">[Nod head and pretend to be listening.]</string>
  <string id="90203">What a shameless act of cowardice!</string>
  <string id="90205">It sounds like Smiling Hawk was very bold and daring.</string>
  <string id="90207">Well, I think I can see where this is going.</string>
  <string id="90210">So how can we stop him?</string>
  <string id="90211">I&apos;ll deal with Smiling Hawk.</string>
  <string id="90212">His power is nothing compared to mine!</string>
  <string id="90216">Crane</string>
  <string id="90217" soundid="164309">Well, good for you. Do you want to me to bake a special dessert in your honor!</string>
  <string id="90219">I want to know more details about this problem before I go.</string>
  <string id="90220" soundid="154926">That&apos;s one of them there.</string>
  <string id="90225">A wise choice. Kai will make an excellent master.</string>
  <string id="90226">Congratulations, First Brother. Or should I say, Master?</string>
  <string id="90229">So, *I* defeated Smiling Hawk and *he* gets to be master?</string>
  <string id="90232">Your thanks is enough.</string>
  <string id="90234">That&apos;s okay. I didn&apos;t really want to be a master.</string>
  <string id="90236">After all I&apos;ve done, that&apos;s it?</string>
  <string id="90239">Yes, I&apos;m very interested.</string>
  <string id="90240">Finally, something for all my work.</string>
  <string id="90245">Farewell and good luck, Master Radiant.</string>
  <string id="90246">Goodbye, then.</string>
  <string id="90248" soundid="156146">I don&apos;t think you should go in there. The Serpent is no good for anybody. I&apos;ll... be around if you need me.</string>
  <string id="90249" soundid="154928"></string>
  <string id="90250" soundid="154929">Damn it! Get him... and don&apos;t be gentle!</string>
  <string id="90251">I&apos;m afraid your men won&apos;t be joining you anytime soon.</string>
  <string id="90252" soundid="154931">What? So it&apos;s true. Master Radiant suspected as much. We must find a way to stop Smiling Hawk.</string>
  <string id="90253">So... you&apos;re dead?</string>
  <string id="90255">The great Master Radiant is a... ghost?</string>
  <string id="90257">I wondered why you never appeared outside your room.</string>
  <string id="90260">Yes, I would like to know.</string>
  <string id="90262">No, I&apos;m not really interested.</string>
  <string id="90264">Dong Ping needs to get Zhong the Ox Carrier to leave the Teahouse. He needs Zhong to help him with the manual chores on his farm. If Zhong is hurt or killed, Dong Ping will be ruined.</string>
  <string id="90265">Zhong the Ox Carrier</string>
  <string id="90266">I suppose. I&apos;ve got nothing better to do.</string>
  <string id="90270" soundid="154932">Go. Challenge Third Brother. I will speak with Master Radiant.</string>
  <string id="90271">That&apos;s a dangerous path to tread.</string>
  <string id="90273">What&apos;s wrong with wanting more?</string>
  <string id="90275">I see. Go on.</string>
  <string id="90277" soundid="139837">Do you really think we&apos;ll find Second Brother here in the city?</string>
  <string id="90278" soundid="139838">Why ask me? I don&apos;t even want to be here. Second Brother probably decided he didn&apos;t want to listen to Master Radiant anymore, and left to get some peace.</string>
  <string id="90279" soundid="139839">Never! Second Brother is devoted to Master Radiant. If anything, I suspect Master Smiling Hawk had something to do with his disappearance.</string>
  <string id="90280" soundid="139840">What? You dare accuse Master Smiling Hawk?</string>
  <string id="90281" soundid="139841">Quiet, you worms! You&apos;re here to look for Second Brother, not bicker like school children. Now get moving.</string>
  <string id="90286" soundid="139846">You&apos;re a fool if you believe what Master Smiling Hawk teaches. Brute force is not always the best way to win a battle.</string>
  <string id="90287" soundid="139847">Oh, and Master Radiant&apos;s ways are better? I don&apos;t think so. Brute force *is* the only way to get what you want, and I can prove it.</string>
  <string id="90288" soundid="139848">How?</string>
  <string id="90289" soundid="139849">I&apos;ll show you.</string>
  <string id="90290" soundid="151801">I expect there will already be enough chaos to go around without your... talents.</string>
  <string id="90295" soundid="139855">Y... you! You&apos;re back! Have you decided to help me? My daughter... she won&apos;t last long, I fear.</string>
  <string id="90296">I&apos;ll find a liver for you.</string>
  <string id="90302">You knew that ghost?</string>
  <string id="90306">It was a woman?</string>
  <string id="90307">You owe me for this.</string>
  <string id="90309" soundid="145573">Ahhh... then you shall learn the depths to which I have sunk!</string>
  <string id="90310">You&apos;re robbing her grave?</string>
  <string id="90312">You&apos;re *married*?</string>
  <string id="90315">What a nice home life you must have.</string>
  <string id="90320" soundid="146309">[Failure] Why? All he does is ask for money and try to line his own pockets with my hard work! I won&apos;t let him take this from me! I won&apos;t!</string>
  <string id="90322">I guess you&apos;re going to have to die, Elder Fong.</string>
  <string id="90323">I won&apos;t kill him. We&apos;re leaving. *Now*.</string>
  <string id="90324">Actually, I think I&apos;ll just kill you both.</string>
  <string id="90326" soundid="146321">That one didn&apos;t listen to me; I hope you have more sense.</string>
  <string id="90327" soundid="163963">No, I *was* weak, otherwise I would have ignored you by the river. I&apos;m going to pay for my crimes, but there&apos;s one thing I have to do first. I have to kill you.</string>
  <string id="90328">Do you deserve to be standing here any more than her, Captain?</string>
  <string id="90331" soundid="146326">If you came here because of the rich reward on my head, you may even know him. Captain Sen of the Imperial Army is my quarry. I must make him pay for that boy&apos;s life.</string>
  <string id="90332" soundid="146327">You know him, clearly.</string>
  <string id="90333" soundid="146328">Until now, I wasn&apos;t sure how I would approach him, but you may have provided the answer.</string>
  <string id="90334" soundid="146329">If you help me, I know how I can reach Sen. You need merely to escort me to his station by the gate.  A &quot;subdued&quot; prisoner could get close enough to deal with Sen.</string>
  <string id="90335" soundid="146330">Once I have dealt with him, you shall have your bounty. I couldn&apos;t let you be implicated in my final murder.</string>
  <string id="90336" soundid="146331">They do not call me the Mournful Blade because I enjoy what I do. Years of remembering the first time I &quot;let it go,&quot; have caused me to develop a conscience.</string>
  <string id="90337" soundid="146332">Why else ask this boon of you? One last chance to do something right, before one of the hunters finally catches me.</string>
  <string id="90338" soundid="146333">I have only one thing left to &quot;try.&quot;</string>
  <string id="90339" soundid="146334">Let&apos;s go write an ending to my tale.</string>
  <string id="90340" soundid="146335">I would do the same thing in your place. The prudent, efficient thing. Let us see who proves the stronger.</string>
  <string id="90341" soundid="146336">Sen is dead. Dead like that poor boy we let wash away. I should have made him suffer more.</string>
  <string id="90342" soundid="146337">Stranger, I cannot thank you enough. I have touched a thousand lives with my crimes, and yet now I feel some peace. It is time my story ended.</string>
  <string id="90343" soundid="146338">I have only one more favor to ask. Face me now and grant me an hon... no, there is no honor left for me. Just grant me an end.</string>
  <string id="90344" soundid="146339">You can&apos;t be the one to let Aishi the Mournful Blade walk free. That would cast undeserved suspicion upon you, and *that* crime I will not commit.</string>
  <string id="90345" soundid="146340">I have been waiting for this moment for years.</string>
  <string id="90346" soundid="146341">We are kindred spirits. Thank you.</string>
  <string id="90347" soundid="146342">Face me, and let this battle be glorious enough that the city will talk of it for generations!</string>
  <string id="90348" soundid="146343">I have a tale to finish. I see no need to tell it to anyone but myself.</string>
  <string id="90349" soundid="146344">There is a price on my head. It may be crusted with silver, but it will not be easily collected.</string>
  <string id="90350" soundid="146345">Likewise.</string>
  <string id="90351" soundid="146346">Stranger, if you continue to talk to me, I will stand up and face you. If that happens, our meeting will end with one of our deaths.</string>
  <string id="90352" soundid="146347">So be it.</string>
  <string id="90353" soundid="146348">This woman has looked death in the eye and refused to blink. She is... strong.</string>
  <string id="90354" soundid="146349">I&apos;ve heard of Aishi before. Whatever happens, tales of her have earned my respect.</string>
  <string id="90355" soundid="146350">I would play no games with this woman if I were you.</string>
  <string id="90356" soundid="146351">You are not what I expected. Harmony surrounds you and flows out into the world as you pass.</string>
  <string id="90357" soundid="146352">You are far from the worst I&apos;ve met, but you are not at peace with your world. </string>
  <string id="90358" soundid="146353">You are like me. We revel in chaos and discord. I, however, have made a decision that will restore my balance.</string>
  <string id="90359" soundid="146354">I have a story I would share willingly with you, if you would hear it.</string>
  <string id="90360" soundid="146355">That is fair. I would not dirty my ears listening to a murderer if I were you either. It was a fool&apos;s hope.</string>
  <string id="90361" soundid="146356">I have a story that must be told, but I do not think you are the one to hear it.</string>
  <string id="90362" soundid="146357">I am tempted to tell it to you, but I wish the right person to hear it.</string>
  <string id="90366">Ghost</string>
  <string id="90369" soundid="145575">You seek me? You seek one so evil that his very touch spreads the corruption his vanity has caused? My perfect body is a testament to my crimes.</string>
  <string id="90370" soundid="145576">To live and feed in death are all that are left to me.</string>
  <string id="90372">Who are you?</string>
  <string id="90373">That fumbling twit over there is your man. He&apos;s not worth covering for.</string>
  <string id="90374">You&apos;re nothing, and that is what I&apos;ll make you.</string>
  <string id="90375">You&apos;re most generous, Captain. That&apos;s your man right there.</string>
  <string id="90376">Now that you mention extra silver, that&apos;s Yukong right there.</string>
  <string id="90377">You&apos;re just what I was looking for.</string>
  <string id="90379">This really doesn&apos;t have to become a fight, you know.</string>
  <string id="90382">[Intuition] You have a chance to repent for your sins.</string>
  <string id="90384">I need your liver to save a young girl.</string>
  <string id="90385">All hope is false if you never allow it to be true.</string>
  <string id="90386">You declare it false before giving it a chance? Perhaps you are beyond redemption.</string>
  <string id="90388">Your curse will be your undoing, then. It is your fate.</string>
  <string id="90390">You have something I need, and I will take it from you.</string>
  <string id="90391">A girl is dying and needs a liver preserved like yours.</string>
  <string id="90392">If one is willing, there is always the chance for redemption.</string>
  <string id="90394">If you save her life, you may be redeemed.</string>
  <string id="90402">A sacrifice from you could change all that.</string>
  <string id="90403">I will put you to rest, then!</string>
  <string id="90404">I never said you&apos;ll part willingly. Just part.</string>
  <string id="90406" soundid="145696">He&apos;s buying your silence, which speaks of his guilt. Well done finding a way to profit from an old crime.</string>
  <string id="90407" soundid="145697">We eliminated a murderer, but his bribe tells me that we&apos;ve let another one go. I wish this could have ended another way.</string>
  <string id="90408" soundid="145698">I liked Aishi better than this coward. She spoke with steel, not silver.</string>
  <string id="90409" soundid="145699">I&apos;m afraid I currently have no room to negotiate. The Ministry of Harmony will be watching this silver.</string>
  <string id="90410" soundid="145700">You have a cold heart in that lovely body.</string>
  <string id="90411" soundid="145701">Your silver is richly deserved. Take it with the thanks of the entire Empire.</string>
  <string id="90413" soundid="145703">I&apos;m a strong candidate to look after the slaves for the Wall. It will be a delightful opportunity to &quot;test&quot; them.</string>
  <string id="90414" soundid="145704">Hello again, citizen. I&apos;m still looking for some competent help in tracking down a pair of criminals, if you&apos;re interested.</string>
  <string id="90416">Creative Yukong has left the city.</string>
  <string id="90418">I don&apos;t need your praise. I&apos;m just here for the silver.</string>
  <string id="90422">I&apos;m interested. Tell me what you need done.</string>
  <string id="90429">You&apos;ve got a deal.</string>
  <string id="90430">If you&apos;ll hold to your earlier offer of more generous rewards, I&apos;ll do it.</string>
  <string id="90431">I&apos;m too good for standard rates. Offer me something better.</string>
  <string id="90432">[Charm] Surely this money doesn&apos;t come out of your pocket. The Empire won&apos;t miss a few extra coins.</string>
  <string id="90434">[Intimidation] From the sounds of it, you bargain the army&apos;s money away pretty often. Who would I talk to about that?</string>
  <string id="90436">[Intuition] If everyone else bargains, you must have extra silver set aside for me, too.</string>
  <string id="90438">At that price, I&apos;m happy to help.</string>
  <string id="90440">Forget it. I&apos;ll do it for the normal fee.</string>
  <string id="90443">Let&apos;s not discuss the bounties quite yet.</string>
  <string id="90444">I&apos;m not interested right now.</string>
  <string id="90445">Just answer some questions for me.</string>
  <string id="90446">I have a bounty I wish to collect.</string>
  <string id="90448">The poor deserve your protection, too.</string>
  <string id="90450">Whatever, I&apos;m just here for the silver.</string>
  <string id="90451">There are more efficient ways of eliminating peasants.</string>
  <string id="90453">Communion of the Stream</string>
  <string id="90454" soundid="140025">I should have killed you sooner. You had such promise, but in the end you were just like Second Brother. Soon you will share his fate, as well.</string>
  <string id="90455" soundid="140026">Fortunately, I do not require you to be afraid in order to kill you. You can die in ignorance, like Master Radiant before you. But for what?</string>
  <string id="90456" soundid="140027">Goodbye.</string>
  <string id="90457" soundid="140028">Thank you, Third Brother. That is all.</string>
  <string id="90458" soundid="140029">You are dismissed!</string>
  <string id="90459" soundid="140030">Yes, Master Smiling Hawk.</string>
  <string id="90460" soundid="140031">So, you are the new student I have heard so much about. Rarely does someone so young display the ability that you have shown.</string>
  <string id="90461" soundid="140032">I noticed that you did not come from one of our usual schools. Do you mind if I ask you who your real master is?</string>
  <string id="90462" soundid="140033">I don&apos;t think I&apos;ve heard of him. Nevertheless, he obviously taught you well.</string>
  <string id="90463" soundid="140034">Ha! In fact, it is my business, but what of it? If I really wanted to know, I could find out easily enough. I did not mean to offend you by asking.</string>
  <string id="90464" soundid="140035">You have talent, and with Second Brother&apos;s death we have need of a new brother.</string>
  <string id="90465">Lucky Cho</string>
  <string id="90466" soundid="140037">I asked him to do something for me. He refused.</string>
  <string id="90467" soundid="140038">No? Then what interests you? Wealth, power... everyone has a price.</string>
  <string id="90468" soundid="140039">An interesting thought, though that wouldn&apos;t solve my problem. No, we already have two masters here, and that&apos;s one too many.</string>
  <string id="90469" soundid="140040">Let me be blunt. Master Radiant is holding this school back. He&apos;s holding *me* back. Radiant is weak. He follows the way of harmony; his methods are slow and pitiful.</string>
  <string id="90470" soundid="140041">This school belongs to me! I want Master Radiant removed, and you&apos;re the one to do it. You have certain abilities that will enable you to defeat my rival.</string>
  <string id="90471" soundid="140042">I would deal with it myself... if I could. However, Radiant is a unique problem... and you are the solution.</string>
  <string id="90472" soundid="140043">Master Radiant is... resistant to my style. But you... you are something different, I could sense it as soon as you arrived.</string>
  <string id="90473" soundid="140044">Ha! I cannot deal with Radiant... and Third Brother is no where near as powerful as I am. No... you have something that neither of us have... I can sense it.</string>
  <string id="90474" soundid="140045">You are the only one here capable of defeating Master Radiant. And rest assured, I will reward you extremely well for ridding me of him.</string>
  <string id="90475" soundid="140046">To begin with, you&apos;ll have to deal with First Brother Kai. Destroy him, and you&apos;ll be left only with Radiant, but together they would be too powerful.</string>
  <string id="90476" soundid="140047">So, First Brother is already winning you over I see. He is pathetic, and so is his precious master.</string>
  <string id="90477" soundid="140048">Do as I ask, and I will teach you things that no one else can. I also have a few rare items that should appeal to you.</string>
  <string id="90478" soundid="140049">Simply kill First Brother and Master Radiant. The task is straightforward.</string>
  <string id="90479" soundid="140050">You are a fool! You could have had everything. Instead, you will not survive your match with Third Brother. I will see to it. Now get out!</string>
  <string id="90480" soundid="140051">Do not return until First Brother and Master Radiant are dead.</string>
  <string id="90481" soundid="140052">With only you to stop me, I&apos;m afraid there will be no other choice.</string>
  <string id="90483" soundid="140054">I will give you one chance to change your mind. Now that you&apos;ve seen what Radiant truly is... help me remove him and I will reward you.</string>
  <string id="90484" soundid="140055">I liked you, and I had so hoped we could come to some sort of... agreement. But I suppose that just won&apos;t...</string>
  <string id="90485" soundid="140056">...work.</string>
  <string id="90486" soundid="140057">Now I will give you a demonstration of true skill.</string>
  <string id="90487" soundid="140058">Unfortunately, you won&apos;t be around long enough to learn from it.</string>
  <string id="90488">Understand the Way of the Closed Fist</string>
  <string id="90489" soundid="140060">He&apos;s attacking Master Smiling Hawk!</string>
  <string id="90490" soundid="140061">She&apos;s attacking Master Smiling Hawk!</string>
  <string id="90491">If you wish to aid Scholar Six Heavens, it seems you will have to prove yourself a follower of the Way of the Closed Fist and then talk to him again in Tien&apos;s Landing.</string>
  <string id="90492" soundid="154552"></string>
  <string id="90493" soundid="154561">I know your kind. Assassin!</string>
  <string id="90494" soundid="140065">Master Smiling Hawk... you killed him!</string>
  <string id="90495" soundid="140066">What? No! First Brother sent me to find you. He was worried Master Smiling Hawk&apos;s followers might overwhelm you. I can see that isn&apos;t the case.</string>
  <string id="90496" soundid="140067">Master Radiant and First Brother are waiting for you. I&apos;ll go tell them that you survived.</string>
  <string id="90497" soundid="140068">Very impressive. Your skills are powerful and... unique. I can&apos;t tell what it is exactly, but it certainly seems to serve you well. Come, we must speak privately.</string>
  <string id="90498" soundid="140069">At last, I can rule this school like it was meant to be ruled. No more of that interfering old man. I&apos;ve always preferred his room to mine as well. This will do nicely.</string>
  <string id="90499" soundid="140070">And you... you have certainly earned a share of the spoils. Take whatever you find in Master Radiant&apos;s room.</string>
  <string id="90500" soundid="140071">You have earned your reward, but I have some... terms. You must agree to remove yourself as a student of the Black Leopard School.</string>
  <string id="90501" soundid="140072">Do you really need to ask? I would be a fool to give you such power and then allow you to remain a student here. I just gained control, I will not give it up to you.</string>
  <string id="90502" soundid="140073">I didn&apos;t? It must have slipped my mind at the time. Nevertheless, these are the terms.</string>
  <string id="90503" soundid="162120">Good bye, and good fortune to you.</string>
  <string id="90504" soundid="140075">My debt is paid, and now you must go. Take what you can from Master Radiant&apos;s room on the way out. And remember, you are no longer a student here.</string>
  <string id="90505">I&apos;m not afraid of you, Smiling Hawk!</string>
  <string id="90507">You said you had some items of interest.</string>
  <string id="90508">I certainly hope you have something better to offer me!</string>
  <string id="90509">Why must I quit the school?</string>
  <string id="90510">You said nothing about terms!</string>
  <string id="90511">I&apos;ve no more interest in your school. Give me my reward.</string>
  <string id="90512" soundid="154718">Master Smiling Hawk&apos;s sole advantage is stealing others&apos; power, but he can&apos;t steal from me what he&apos;s already stolen, or so he believes.</string>
  <string id="90518">Master Li of Two Rivers.</string>
  <string id="90520">Why do you want to know?</string>
  <string id="90521">That&apos;s none of your business.</string>
  <string id="90523" soundid="154562">I&apos;ve heard a rumor that the man leading the bandits seemed to know Master Li, but I really couldn&apos;t say why.</string>
  <string id="90524">What happened to Second Brother?</string>
  <string id="90526">I&apos;m not interested in becoming Second Brother.</string>
  <string id="90528">Forget it! I want to be master!</string>
  <string id="90531">Deal with this yourself. I want no part of it.</string>
  <string id="90533">Why do you need me to help you?</string>
  <string id="90535">Why not get Third Brother to do it for you?</string>
  <string id="90538">I would never hurt First Brother Kai or Master Radiant.</string>
  <string id="90540">And what do I get in return for all of this?</string>
  <string id="90541">I&apos;m starting to like the sound of this.</string>
  <string id="90543">No. I would rather die than help you!</string>
  <string id="90544">I&apos;ll do it, but I expect to be paid well.</string>
  <string id="90545">I can&apos;t allow you to remain master of this school!</string>
  <string id="90547">Why do you hate Radiant so much?</string>
  <string id="90548" soundid="154563">It&apos;s scary to think they came here with a purpose, though. Why don&apos;t you ask Master Li?</string>
  <string id="90549">I&apos;d rather die!</string>
  <string id="90550">You are crazy if you think I&apos;d join you.</string>
  <string id="90551">All right. I&apos;ll help you, but I expect to be well paid.</string>
  <string id="90559">Do you have any idea why someone would be looking for Master Li?</string>
  <string id="90561" soundid="154566">Oh, I know. That rumor spread very quickly, though not many people want to talk about it. It&apos;s quite disturbing, so some people prefer to pretend they never heard it.</string>
  <string id="90562">My fear is strong!</string>
  <string id="90563">What about it? Do you wish to defend his honor?</string>
  <string id="90564">I could not let him ruin the school. Will you be joining him?</string>
  <string id="90565">He chose his fate. Attack me and your fate will be similar.</string>
  <string id="90569">Default Settings</string>
  <string id="90570">Yukong didn&apos;t seem like that bad a guy.</string>
  <string id="90571">Just pass some of the motivation my way and I&apos;ll be happy.</string>
  <string id="90572" soundid="140150">No. Losing an exceptionally talented servant like you is of no benefit to me, even if acolytes are expendable. They die often in the machinations between masters.</string>
  <string id="90573" soundid="140151">You are perceptive. It is a tricky matter and therefore a good test for an otherwise expendable acolyte. Your kind die often in the machinations between masters.</string>
  <string id="90574" soundid="140152">The politics of the Lotus Assassin order are complicated. It is all right if murder is *suspected*, so long as it appears deserved because of incompetence.</string>
  <string id="90575">Miss Chan Banished</string>
  <string id="90576" soundid="140154">That is your task to figure out, acolyte! This is a dangerous place. Find a way for him to have an accident that disgraces him. I, of course, must not be implicated.</string>
  <string id="90577" soundid="140155">I am your master here. Do this and you will be favored. This is a dangerous place, it should be simple for Shin to have an accident that does not implicate me.</string>
  <string id="90579" soundid="140157">Proceed, but do not waste my time.</string>
  <string id="90580" soundid="140158">I will hear you.</string>
  <string id="90581" soundid="140159">Shards infuse the golems with life. Souls are extracted from the vessel that holds them, whether a corpse or slave, and sealed within a crystal shard.</string>
  <string id="90582" soundid="140160">The more recent and brutal the death, the more effective the golem. Our soul extraction process is deliberately painful.</string>
  <string id="90583" soundid="140161">Essence gems are trinkets that can focus minimal amounts of chi. There are very few people who can make use of them effectively.</string>
  <string id="90584" soundid="140162">Golems are utterly obedient, but that does not mean they are always easy to control. In great numbers there can be... discord.</string>
  <string id="90585" soundid="140163">Jade Golems are infused with spirit shards made of multiple souls. They are highly ordered servants, and they serve as pacifiers for other golems.</string>
  <string id="90586" soundid="140164">One or two golems can be controlled by will alone, but an army requires these jade intermediaries to maintain order. Such numbers are dangerous without a lieutenant.</string>
  <string id="90587" soundid="140165">I do not know. Hundreds? More? Many are here, waiting for a Jade Golem to command them. In the end, we will replace the weaklings of the Imperial Army entirely.</string>
  <string id="90588" soundid="140166">Imagine it, acolyte. An army of loyal, nearly indestructible golems, dedicated to enforcing the will of the Emperor under Death&apos;s Hand. A beautiful sight.</string>
  <string id="90589" soundid="140167">You already know enough about him. He is insufferable, concerned only about his own advancement. He sabotages my efforts at every turn.</string>
  <string id="90590" soundid="140168">When he is gone, I will ascend in rank, and I will reward acolytes that are loyal to me. Perhaps I will even introduce you to Grand Inquisitor Jia in the heart of the fortress.</string>
  <string id="90591" soundid="140169">He is no longer a concern, thanks to your efforts.</string>
  <string id="90592" soundid="140170">Remember your tasks, acolyte. Create a spirit shard in the extraction chamber for the Jade Golem, and find a creative way to kill and disgrace Master Shin.</string>
  <string id="90593" soundid="140171">Finish your task, acolyte. Oversee the creation of a spirit shard in the Soul Extraction chamber.</string>
  <string id="90594" soundid="140172">Finish the task I have given, acolyte. Find a creative way to disgrace and kill Master Shin.</string>
  <string id="90595" soundid="140173">Ah, that is true. I like that you do not suffer formality. I have struggled under the weight of the same thing from others, myself.</string>
  <string id="90597" soundid="140175">Well done, acolyte. I knew it was best to keep your mind intact. When you finish making the Jade Golem spirit shard, I will introduce you to Grand Inquisitor Jia.</string>
  <string id="90598" soundid="140176">The inner chambers are not usually accessible to acolytes, but you have proven a valuable ally. You will go far in the Lotus Assassins.</string>
  <string id="90599" soundid="140177">So, you are done with the extractor. That spirit shard will allow the Jade Golem to control a battalion of clay golems. Eliminate Shin, and I will present you to Jia.</string>
  <string id="90600" soundid="140178">Yes, acolyte? Why have you chosen to disturb me, instead of working on the tasks I have set before you?</string>
  <string id="90601" soundid="140179">Yes, I am aware. When you have finished your other task for me, I will let you present it in the inner sanctum of the fortress.</string>
  <string id="90602" soundid="140180">That will be a great honor for a Lotus Acolyte. You may even meet Grand Inquisitor Jia.</string>
  <string id="90603" soundid="140181">Hmm... an interesting idea. It has happened before, and the victim was certainly considered a fool for letting it occur, but it is impossible.</string>
  <string id="90604" soundid="140182">You may as well try and drop one of the golems on him. He would never be so distracted as to enter the press. We are Lotus *Assassins,* after all.</string>
  <string id="90605" soundid="140183">A possibility, but Shin does not leave the inner chambers often. Only to inspect the new slave shipments arriving in the Hall of Induction.</string>
  <string id="90606" soundid="140184">You would have to close a great many eyes to get away with an assassination in the hall and moving the body to the press, but it would certainly send a message.</string>
  <string id="90607" soundid="140185">The hall cleared of all witnesses, the press operator distracted, and the slave shipment stopped outside in the Necropolis before it arrives? A daunting list of tasks.</string>
  <string id="90609" soundid="143144">We have warriors across the Empire, and other Jade Golems that are not corrupted. You have diminished us, but it is not a mortal wound.</string>
  <string id="90610" soundid="140188">A terrible tragedy has reached my ears. Our respected Master Shin has met his end in a rather embarrassing fashion.</string>
  <string id="90611" soundid="140189">I came quickly after hearing of his stumble. Perhaps it was the cold of the sanctum that made him careless and dulled his senses.</string>
  <string id="90612" soundid="140190">Open the press.</string>
  <string id="90613" soundid="140191">How unfortunate. I will make certain he is dead, but not from too close. I don&apos;t want to share his tragically foolish fate.</string>
  <string id="90614" soundid="140192">Yes, quite dead. How unfortunate.</string>
  <string id="90615" soundid="140193">We should honor our fallen comrade, but I am distracted by thoughts of who will take his place. I think the choice is obvious.</string>
  <string id="90616" soundid="140194">Master Shin is coming to inspect the new slaves in the Hall of Induction. If you have a plan in place to entrap him, go there now!</string>
  <string id="90617" soundid="140195">Very good, acolyte, very good, indeed. You have secured a promising future for your master despite some minor disruptions.</string>
  <string id="90618" soundid="140196">I trust I have made myself clear?</string>
  <string id="90619" soundid="140197">Yes, Master Shin.</string>
  <string id="90620" soundid="140198">I thought so. Do not let anything delay you further. It would be a shame to once more remind Grand Inquisitor Jia how incompetent you are.</string>
  <string id="90621" soundid="140199">Yes, an absolute shame.</string>
  <string id="90622" soundid="140200">What do you want? So help me, if you are just some wandering slave, I&apos;ll have you butchered to color the clay golems.</string>
  <string id="90623" soundid="140201">Wait, no, you are the one I was told to expect. A new recruit. Hmph, as if I don&apos;t have enough trouble watching over the other fools in my care.</string>
  <string id="90624" soundid="140202">Your best is no longer the limit of what we expect, despite what you have achieved elsewhere. You will be reconstructed into the perfect obedient slave.</string>
  <string id="90625" soundid="140203">If you survive, then you will be an Assassin. For now, you are a Lotus Acolyte, and your life expectancy is not long.</string>
  <string id="90626" soundid="140204">Follow me down to the central chambers when you are ready to begin your indoctrination. Do *not* keep me waiting. A battalion of golems stand idle.</string>
  <string id="90627" soundid="140205">You are no Assassin yet, fool, despite what you may have achieved outside. Here we strip you down to nothing and rebuild you as we like.</string>
  <string id="90629" soundid="140207">Damn the heavens for the fools I lead! I am destined to suffer for their incompetence, and I have one man to blame for it! Shin!</string>
  <string id="90630" soundid="140208">The old scorpion had one of his followers shatter a spirit shard during training. There are ghosts everywhere! I&apos;ve lost eight slaves and three acolytes to them.</string>
  <string id="90631" soundid="140209">You, new-blood! Get over there and occupy those ghosts until I can get real Lotus Assassins to clean them up. Golem production cannot be delayed by this!</string>
  <string id="90632" soundid="140210">Go on, it&apos;s your first sacrifice for your new life. I&apos;m sure it will be glorious.</string>
  <string id="90633" soundid="140211">I gave you an order, acolyte! Go spill your new blood on those ghosts while I get some real Assassins in here!</string>
  <string id="90634" soundid="140212">You... you live. And the ghosts are gone? Well, I did not expect this. It would seem that I have a competent acolyte for once. Interesting.</string>
  <string id="90635" soundid="140213">Recruits are rarely of use before we strip them of their outside identities, but you beg a more... interesting application. Could you be the one I have waited for?</string>
  <string id="90636" soundid="140214">I need a favored protege, someone willing to risk everything in my service. I will preserve your intellect, allow your inventive mind to remain, in exchange for two tasks. </string>
  <string id="90637" soundid="140215">Your duties would normally include a period of deprivation in a cell until every hint of self and identity was stripped away. It is a draining, brutal awakening.</string>
  <string id="90638" soundid="140216">One is your duty anyway. The other is something to secure your future at the heart of the Assassins. Lotus Acolytes are utterly expendable. You deserve better.</string>
  <string id="90639" soundid="140217">You must operate the Soul Extractor, past the room where you fought the ghosts. In the coming weeks, you will help swell the ranks of the Empire&apos;s glorious golem army.</string>
  <string id="90640" soundid="140218">Golems are fueled by the souls of the dead. The recently dead, it turns out, make far more obedient and powerful golems. Especially if brutally killed.</string>
  <string id="90641" soundid="140219">We no longer mine the Necropolis for souls that linger near their resting place. We butcher slaves instead, and extract their souls into spirit shards.</string>
  <string id="90644">It cannot be as simple as that, or he would be dead now.</string>
  <string id="90646">Return to Shen and tell him Miss Chan has been banished.</string>
  <string id="90647">How do I go about doing that?</string>
  <string id="90648">I am not certain I want to do your dirty work.</string>
  <string id="90650">I have some questions, Master Gang.</string>
  <string id="90651">I want to ask about golems and shards.</string>
  <string id="90652">What are spirit shards? Are they similar to essence gems?</string>
  <string id="90655">What is so important about the Jade Golem?</string>
  <string id="90658">How many golems have been produced?</string>
  <string id="90660">Let&apos;s go back to my other questions.</string>
  <string id="90661">Tell me about Master Shin.</string>
  <string id="90663">Goodbye for now.</string>
  <string id="90664">A simple matter. What else?</string>
  <string id="90665">You speak as if I have a choice. You can order what you want.</string>
  <string id="90667">So, favored students are spared some pain? I agree.</string>
  <string id="90668">I am no mere student. I earned my place here.</string>
  <string id="90672">I have the spirit shard for the Jade Golem.</string>
  <string id="90674">Master Shin would be disgraced if killed by the golem press.</string>
  <string id="90676">Then I will kill him and put him in there.</string>
  <string id="90679">He could meet his end elsewhere. Something could be arranged.</string>
  <string id="90680" soundid="143145">Death&apos;s Hand will be here soon. You will be my gift to him, drawn as you were by your precious amulet. Live or die, the will of the Emperor be done!</string>
  <string id="90690">I will endeavor to serve as best I can.</string>
  <string id="90693">You will find me a competent Assassin, I assure you.</string>
  <string id="90700">I welcome the compliment. I hope I serve you well.</string>
  <string id="90703">I will serve as needed, Master Gang.</string>
  <string id="90707">And what is the second task, Master Gang?</string>
  <string id="90708">You wish me to take the blame for such an act?</string>
  <string id="90715" soundid="140299">When the Jade Golem is done, have a normal spirit shard made and replace this clay golem. The ranks must be full when the Jade Golem is activated.</string>
  <string id="90716" soundid="143109">Thank you.</string>
  <string id="90717">No, you are free.</string>
  <string id="90720" soundid="140306">I am the Watcher, and this is the fortress of the Lotus Assassins. It was built amid the graves of a thousand generations, the tomb of the Emperor at its core.</string>
  <string id="90721" soundid="140307">Come, I will show you to the Hall of Induction. If you have servants, they will be allowed to accompany you, but you are responsible for their actions.</string>
  <string id="90722" soundid="140308">Formed from the defunct Order of the Lotus, the Lotus Assassins are an extension of the Emperor, as dictated by Death&apos;s Hand and implemented by Grand Inquisitor Jia.</string>
  <string id="90723" soundid="140309">Thanks to her direction, we are becoming the face of power in the Empire. The Imperial Army will soon be stationed only at taverns and fish markets.</string>
  <string id="90724" soundid="140310">The great golem army constructed here will spread across the Empire. Our masters will be all-powerful. You will assist, if you survive. Weak recruits die quickly.</string>
  <string id="90725" soundid="140311">Master Gang is one of our trainers. He will be your master as you seek to become an Assassin. He is harsh, but his knowledge will be invaluable to you.</string>
  <string id="90726" soundid="140312">You will find him at the opposite end of the Hall of Induction, near the entrance to the central chambers. Do not keep him waiting.</string>
  <string id="90727" soundid="140313">What do you wish?</string>
  <string id="90728" soundid="140314">What would you like to know?</string>
  <string id="90729" soundid="140315">Death&apos;s Hand is the one who brings us the will of the Emperor, but Grand Inquisitor Jia rules in his absence.</string>
  <string id="90730" soundid="140316">Death&apos;s Hand rules us all. We obey him in all things, for he is the will of the Emperor. There is no more to tell. Our lives are his.</string>
  <string id="90731" soundid="140317">Grand Inquisitor Jia is the foremost acolyte of Death&apos;s Hand. She was one of the first converted from the old Order of the Lotus, and she is fearsome in her power.</string>
  <string id="90732" soundid="140318">You would be wise to never even give the *appearance* of challenging her. She takes offense easily, and even masters have been killed for displeasing her.</string>
  <string id="90733" soundid="140319">She is not *found* by just anyone. Excel in your tasks, and perhaps you will be blessed with her attention. Fail, and you will be cursed with it.</string>
  <string id="90734" soundid="140320">I will answer, but you should not delay your duties.</string>
  <string id="90735" soundid="140321">This was to be the tomb of the Emperor. It rests in the heart of the Necropolis, the accumulation of thousands of years of the Empire&apos;s dead.</string>
  <string id="90736" soundid="140322">It was the perfect place to begin constructing the utterly loyal golem forces the Emperor demanded through Death&apos;s Hand. We could harvest all the spirits we need.</string>
  <string id="90737" soundid="140323">They are the perfect soldiers: unrelenting, obedient, the ideal that all Lotus assassins aspire to achieve. Slaves that die to be golems are blessed.</string>
  <string id="90738" soundid="140324">No, you fool, we harvest *spirits.* Many linger where their body is interred, although the freshly dead produce a far more responsive golem.</string>
  <string id="90739" soundid="140325">I saw no one. Only the most skilled of our number can enter this place without my knowing. I am the Watcher.</string>
  <string id="90740" soundid="140326">May the will of Death&apos;s Hand and the Emperor guide you.</string>
  <string id="90741" soundid="140327">Go to your teacher, acolyte. Do not keep him waiting. The far end of the hall, at the entrance to the Central Chambers.</string>
  <string id="90748">I want to ask you some questions.</string>
  <string id="90749">Tell me about the leaders of the Lotus Assassins.</string>
  <string id="90750">Tell me about Death&apos;s Hand.</string>
  <string id="90751">Tell me about Grand Inquisitor Jia.</string>
  <string id="90753">Where can I find Grand Inquisitor Jia?</string>
  <string id="90754">I want to return to my questions.</string>
  <string id="90755">Tell me about this fortress and the golem army.</string>
  <string id="90757">Why are you constructing golems?</string>
  <string id="90758">Do you harvest bodies from the Necropolis?</string>
  <string id="90759">Did someone try to enter the fortress just before I did?</string>
  <string id="90760">I don&apos;t have any more questions for now.</string>
  <string id="90761">Farewell, Watcher.</string>
  <string id="90762" soundid="140348">You must be Master Gang&apos;s latest acolyte. I heard there might be a new recruit, but they typically aren&apos;t ready for service so quickly. Stripping a will can take time.</string>
  <string id="90763" soundid="140349">But, Master Gang is known for being generous to those who please him. You must be quite exceptional to be allowed into service so... directly.</string>
  <string id="90764" soundid="140350">Fight! It is our only chance!</string>
  <string id="90765" soundid="140351">Vermin! I&apos;ll kill you all!</string>
  <string id="90766">Jade Golem</string>
  <string id="90767" soundid="140484">My own demons distract me in this place, but I hold no love for your new master or the master above him. If you kill one, why not two?</string>
  <string id="90768" soundid="140354">This device is the Soul Extractor. It has a loftier name, but we are here to glorify Emperor Sun through Death&apos;s Hand, not pay tribute to some distant celestial lord.</string>
  <string id="90769" soundid="140355">It is mounted on an elevator that reaches deep into the Necropolis. Until recently we excavated bodies to extract spirits that lingered near their graves.</string>
  <string id="90770" soundid="140356">The results were... unpredictable. Now we use slaves. Freshly killed spirits make the best golems. The more painful the death, the better. The extractor is not gentle.</string>
  <string id="90771" soundid="140357">I am a Lotus Acolyte, like you. My name is unimportant. I have not yet earned the right to have a title. I must prove my worth through service here.</string>
  <string id="90772" soundid="140358">What do you want?</string>
  <string id="90773" soundid="140359">Then you should select a suitable victim for the procedure. I would recommend one of the slaves on the prison level.</string>
  <string id="90774" soundid="140360">Selecting from elsewhere could bring unfortunate results, and I would not wish to see you disgraced so early in your time with us.</string>
  <string id="90775" soundid="140361">Use the lever to select a floor, and this platform will move there. You are free to go where you wish, but I would avoid the lower mines. They are... restless.</string>
  <string id="90776" soundid="140362">What kind of questions?</string>
  <string id="90777" soundid="140363">If you must. It is a simple machine to operate. I&apos;m sure you will come to enjoy the subtle joys of it.</string>
  <string id="90778" soundid="140364">Spirits that die in trauma can linger near their mortal form. The Empire is soaked in blood; many restless dead haunt the Necropolis. But slaves produce a better result.</string>
  <string id="90779" soundid="140365">Only on the prison level. Many of the mines are impassable. The graves were never intended to be stable during excavation. Several have collapsed.</string>
</tlk>