<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<tlk language="0">
  <string id="90780" soundid="140366">Much of the surrounding ground is weak. We do not march too many golems at once. Even that might shake something loose.</string>
  <string id="90781" soundid="140367">Slaves are placed in the extractor, and the extraction fluid produces exquisite agony. Focused by this pain, the soul is forced to crystallize into a spirit shard.</string>
  <string id="90782" soundid="140368">That shard is implanted in a golem, infusing it with the energy of the deceased soul. Your task is the creation of a new shard for a Jade Golem. Do not delay.</string>
  <string id="90783" soundid="140369">Your place in the ranks of the Assassins is clear. What do you want to know?</string>
  <string id="90784" soundid="140370">Death&apos;s Hand owns my soul, as he does yours and everyone else who has given themselves to him. In obedience and submission, we find our purpose.</string>
  <string id="90785" soundid="140371">He is the living will of the Emperor. Through him, we are closer to the heart of the Empire.</string>
  <string id="90786" soundid="140372">Grand Inquisitor Jia is the embodiment of the will of Death&apos;s Hand, even as *he* is the will of the Emperor. She governs us all while he is elsewhere.</string>
  <string id="90787" soundid="140373">To defy her is to defy the Empire. Death is her first and last means of education on the matter.</string>
  <string id="90788" soundid="140374">It is our home, but not for much longer. With the golem forces of the Emperor almost complete, there is little to tie us here. When the army marches, so shall we.</string>
  <string id="90789" soundid="140375">I do not imagine we will leave much behind us. The ground here is weak. Such a movement of power will likely shake the walls to their foundation.</string>
  <string id="90790" soundid="140376">You should get on with your work. Grand Inquisitor Jia is growing impatient for the Jade Golem to be completed. Select a suitable victim, and create a spirit shard.</string>
  <string id="90791" soundid="140377">What is this? Who opened the slave cells?</string>
  <string id="90793">What is this place?</string>
  <string id="90796" soundid="140485">Distractions are the key to weakness in a target. If you look to the future, Master Gang will have his plans come crashing down on him.</string>
  <string id="90799">Who are you?</string>
  <string id="90801">What do you do here?</string>
  <string id="90802">I must make a spirit shard for the Jade Golem.</string>
  <string id="90805">I want to ask you some questions.</string>
  <string id="90806">I want to ask about the extractor and spirit shards.</string>
  <string id="90807">Do corpses still have souls to extract?</string>
  <string id="90808">You store slaves here?</string>
  <string id="90810">How does the extractor function?</string>
  <string id="90812">Let&apos;s return to my other questions.</string>
  <string id="90813">Tell me about the Lotus Assassins and our leaders. </string>
  <string id="90814">Tell me about Death&apos;s Hand.</string>
  <string id="90816">Tell me about Grand Inquisitor Jia.</string>
  <string id="90818">Tell me about the fortress.</string>
  <string id="90820">Goodbye.</string>
  <string id="90828" soundid="140414">A welcome exercise, actually. We can always get more slaves.</string>
  <string id="90829" soundid="140415">The slaves in the cells are all dead. You will have to wait for new ones to be brought in from the outlying areas.</string>
  <string id="90830" soundid="140416">What? Then I will deal with them! They will not have the honor of dying for the extractor!</string>
  <string id="90831">The slaves have freed themselves. They need to be killed.</string>
  <string id="90836">Why are you here, slave?</string>
  <string id="90839">How many slaves have passed through here?</string>
  <string id="90841">I may try to help you.</string>
  <string id="90843">Goodbye.</string>
  <string id="90846">Get there on your own. I&apos;ve done enough for you.</string>
  <string id="90847">Just one. If you can&apos;t handle him, you don&apos;t deserve freedom.</string>
  <string id="90849">If you don&apos;t hurry, there will be more. Go!</string>
  <string id="90850">I will remove the guard when I am done with the extractor.</string>
  <string id="90851">The guard is dead. Go now.</string>
  <string id="90852">You were strong enough, they weren&apos;t. Thank yourself.</string>
  <string id="90853">Go before I regret letting even you live!</string>
  <string id="90854" soundid="140477">I can&apos;t let this continue! This area is my responsibility! I don&apos;t care who you are!</string>
  <string id="90855" soundid="140478"></string>
  <string id="90864" soundid="140490">So, you are the new Lotus Acolyte under Master Gang. No one else has reason to be here. He was quick to favor you. New recruits are typically held in isolation.</string>
  <string id="90865" soundid="140491">The press is simple to use. Using this machine, we can create a legion of warrior golems in a day.</string>
  <string id="90866" soundid="140643">You there! Stand aside, or risk the ire of the Lotus Assassins.</string>
  <string id="90867" soundid="140493">Death&apos;s Hand is master of us all. It is by his whim that we live and die, for his is the will of the Emperor. Obey him, or fall before his might.</string>
  <string id="90868" soundid="140644">These prisoners must be delivered to the fortress to be inspected by Master Shin. I will not allow you to make me late.</string>
  <string id="90869" soundid="140495">I will return to my tasks.</string>
  <string id="90870" soundid="140645">A fine slaughter, even if there was no challenge. I will return to our agents in the city and demand fodder of better quality.</string>
  <string id="90871" soundid="140646">If they don&apos;t deliver, perhaps I will enlist their assistance more directly. You have inspired me, acolyte. You will make a fine Assassin.</string>
  <string id="90872" soundid="140647">And why is that? Keep your reason short, or you&apos;ll be dead before you&apos;re done.</string>
  <string id="90873" soundid="140648">You are mad to test an Assassin! I&apos;ll kill you where you stand!</string>
  <string id="90874" soundid="140649">A mere acolyte will steal my work to gain favor? What are you, one of Gang&apos;s little children? I serve Master Shin, and I do not take orders from acolytes!</string>
  <string id="90875" soundid="140650"></string>
  <string id="90876" soundid="140651">[Success] You make a good point, acolyte. I am not used to your kind being so persuasive. Perhaps you *will* be a force to contend with.</string>
  <string id="90877" soundid="140652">Very well, I will let you deliver these slaves. Be certain they arrive in good order! If I suffer any loss of standing, I swear you will answer for it!</string>
  <string id="90878" soundid="140653">You have my assistance, acolyte. Do not abuse it.</string>
  <string id="90879">Master Shin</string>
  <string id="90880" soundid="140506">She is merciless, violent, and sadistic. You would do well to emulate her.</string>
  <string id="90883" soundid="143117">Er, and my efforts to accelerate his training.</string>
  <string id="90884" soundid="140658"></string>
  <string id="90885" soundid="140659"></string>
  <string id="90886" soundid="140660">A mere acolyte questions the quality of my work? I am not laughing, child. Why should I allow this?</string>
  <string id="90887" soundid="140513">This is only one step. Here we create husks, devoid of energy. Each golem needs a spirit shard to move, and a Jade Golem must guide them all.</string>
  <string id="90888" soundid="140514">For each shard, a spirit must be reduced to its essence. For a time we used those that lingered near their graves, mining them as if they were silver. No longer.</string>
  <string id="90889" soundid="140515">The recently dead make a stronger, more obedient golem, if the death is painful. With a Jade Golem guiding them, legions act as one, utterly obedient.</string>
  <string id="90890" soundid="140516">The average citizen of the Empire is worthless. They are nothing more than cattle. In this, they can at least serve some useful purpose.</string>
  <string id="90891" soundid="140517">The press is simple to operate. You select the type of body at the first station. Once the material is poured, it is funneled to the press.</string>
  <string id="90892" soundid="140518">The press serves as a mold and a kiln. In short order it can be opened and the new body is ready to be moved. The crane controls are at the end of the ramp.</string>
  <string id="90893" soundid="140519">You can experiment with each station if you want, but you may as well reduce what you produce to rubble. There are no shards to power any more golems for now.</string>
  <string id="90894" soundid="140661"></string>
  <string id="90895" soundid="140662">[Success] Hrm... they are not the best I have encountered, and Master Shin did say he needed good quality slaves for a special project.</string>
  <string id="90896" soundid="140663">Bah, I can&apos;t take the risk of earning his displeasure. You are right to warn me, acolyte. Help me dispose of these worthless sacks.</string>
  <string id="90897" soundid="140664">Ready, you lot? The good acolyte says you are so worthless you should die! I say I agree! Defend yourselves so your deaths are at least entertaining!</string>
  <string id="90898" soundid="140665">Mwaaah! Heavens help us!</string>
  <string id="90899" soundid="140666">[Failure] You fail to convince me of anything except your impudence, acolyte! I will not accept this!</string>
  <string id="90900" soundid="140667">Defend yourself, fool. I will suffer this delay no longer!</string>
  <string id="90901" soundid="140668"></string>
  <string id="90902" soundid="140669"></string>
  <string id="90903" soundid="140670">I don&apos;t know your face. You don&apos;t even bear our markings. State your intent before I end this encounter... and your life.</string>
  <string id="90904" soundid="140530">What do you want?</string>
  <string id="90906">I cannot allow this delivery to take place.</string>
  <string id="90908">[Intimidation] You do not dare insult your masters with such poor wares!</string>
  <string id="90909" soundid="140535">Grand Inquisitor Jia directs us all in the absence of Death&apos;s Hand. She is one of the few that survived the transition of the Lotus Order into the Lotus Assassins.</string>
  <string id="90911">Don&apos;t you recognize one of your own? Stand down!</string>
  <string id="90913">They will not be delivered. Abandon them or fall, slave driver!</string>
  <string id="90914">[Lie] I am an acolyte. I will deliver the slaves to gain favor.</string>
  <string id="90915">Tell me about Inquisitor Jia.</string>
  <string id="90916">[Charm] Two allies of moderate influence are stronger than one alone.</string>
  <string id="90918">Tell me about Death&apos;s Hand.</string>
  <string id="90919">Has the Emperor ever visited this fortress?</string>
  <string id="90923">Goodbye for now.</string>
  <string id="90924" soundid="143118">Shut up, Gang. Your contribution has been noted.</string>
  <string id="90925" soundid="143119">Now, we must complete the ritual. A score of clay golems stand idle without a focus. This Jade Golem will awaken them all, direct them as one.</string>
  <string id="90926" soundid="143120">Insert the spirit shard. Let this legion of immortals give glory to our masters!</string>
  <string id="90927" soundid="143121">I command you all, be ready for the orders of Death&apos;s Hand. The will of the Emperor!</string>
  <string id="90928" soundid="143122">What? What is wrong? I command you! I demand that you obey!</string>
  <string id="90929">[Intuition] Your master has enemies. You need other allies.</string>
  <string id="90931">[Intimidation] Do not question me! You want me as an ally as I ascend!</string>
  <string id="90933">I am an acolyte. These slaves are substandard. Kill them, and get more.</string>
  <string id="90935">[Charm] Just a friendly gesture to save the order the loss of a fine agent.</string>
  <string id="90941">[Intuition] Your standing will be lessened if they are considered weak.</string>
  <string id="90942" soundid="140702">What is going on here? Where are my slaves? The golems require spirit shards!</string>
  <string id="90943">Our power must be growing at an incredible rate.</string>
  <string id="90946">You kill people to make shards for the golems?</string>
  <string id="90947" soundid="140703">Attendants, do you know anything about this? Blood will flow if the extractor is left idle because of this! Someone has disobeyed my orders!</string>
  <string id="90948" soundid="140704">You... you are Gang&apos;s new acolyte. I see what is happening here. You think to promote your master by threatening me. You are bold, but foolish.</string>
  <string id="90951" soundid="140705">Was this empty hall arranged to make me vulnerable? A miscalculation. I am one of Grand Inquisitor Jia&apos;s favored! I will not fall to the likes of you!</string>
  <string id="90953">I regret that there will be no slaves delivered today, Shin.</string>
  <string id="90955">Your orders are worthless. No one is here to receive them.</string>
  <string id="90957" soundid="140711">What is this? Another acolyte feeling their way around in the dark?</string>
  <string id="90958">Lotus Acolyte Du Gah</string>
  <string id="90961">Lotus Acolyte Jin Tao</string>
  <string id="90964">If we are able to create that many golems, why haven&apos;t we?</string>
  <string id="90966" soundid="140719">Sometimes I wonder if I am ready to train with others of such skill, even in the robes of a junior student. I feel a long way from my home in the Imperial City.</string>
  <string id="90967" soundid="140593">I will instruct you on the use of the golem press and crane. Forming the golems is an honored task that elevates us above slaves and mere servants.</string>
  <string id="90968" soundid="140594">One or two golems can be controlled by will alone, but larger numbers are unwieldy. They grow confused, their wills creeping back and bringing madness.</string>
  <string id="90969" soundid="140595">Jade Golems keep order. Command a Jade Golem and you command them all. The current legion has not yet been assigned a Jade Golem.</string>
  <string id="90970" soundid="140596">Master Gang will probably order you to help with that, if he has not done so already.</string>
  <string id="90971" soundid="140597">What do you wish to know, acolyte? There is much to learn if you want to ascend in the order.</string>
  <string id="90972" soundid="140598">Beyond the veil of death, if you impose your presence uninvited. Master Gang may present you if you please him, but even he has few opportunities to appeal to her.</string>
  <string id="90973" soundid="140599">No, and there is no reason for him to. I would throw myself in the press if even his robes were discolored by the dust of the machine.</string>
  <string id="90974" soundid="140600">I have no doubt that Grand Inquisitor Jia would... extend my demise if I did not.</string>
  <string id="90975" soundid="140601">You test my patience, acolyte.</string>
  <string id="90976" soundid="140602">The Extraction Chamber is a far more interesting place to work. The screams over there are music. Here, we have only the creaking of clay.</string>
  <string id="90977" soundid="140603">Is that so? Why should I step aside for a new-blood acolyte? I have my own position to think about, and I will not be so easily replaced.</string>
  <string id="90978" soundid="140604">If you bring an order from Master Gang, I will relent, as he is my master, too. Until then, I am not moving.</string>
  <string id="90979" soundid="140605">I see. The ways of the order are mysterious and brutal. If an... opening is created away from witnesses, all of us under him will benefit. I understand.</string>
  <string id="90980" soundid="140606">I will tend to the golems that are being readied for the Jade Golem&apos;s command. I do not think I will be able to return to this room today.</string>
  <string id="90981" soundid="140607">But... a thought occurs to me: If one opening raises us all, two openings will raise us further. If something were to befall the good master....</string>
  <string id="90982" soundid="140608">Just something you might want to ponder.</string>
  <string id="90983" soundid="140609">You nearly saw one as you entered, but they are rare. Falling victim to an obvious danger like a dropped golem--or worse, the press--would take a monumental fool.</string>
  <string id="90984" soundid="140610">The machines are loud, and you can see the operator from anywhere in the room. A past victim of the press suffered more damage after the incident than during it.</string>
  <string id="90985" soundid="140611">Reputations are very important in the Lotus Assassin order. Falling victim to the press would cause a loss in status almost fatal in and of itself.</string>
  <string id="90986" soundid="140612">You do not need to know much. We can make husks right now, but there will be no more spirit shards until the Jade Golem is completed.</string>
  <string id="90987" soundid="140613">Clay golems are weaker, but can be made swiftly. Bronze golems are stronger and heavier, but they take longer to construct.</string>
  <string id="90988" soundid="140614">Jade Golems are the strongest of that size, but they are a topic all their own.</string>
  <string id="90989" soundid="140615">Perhaps, but they are constructed elsewhere and are only deployed in siege situations. True monsters to behold.</string>
  <string id="90990" soundid="140616">Very few are made. They are expensive and difficult to construct, but they are also essential. A single Jade Golem can direct and pacify a legion of others.</string>
  <string id="90993">What do you mean by &quot;direct and pacify?&quot;</string>
  <string id="90996">Tell me about the Lotus Assassins.</string>
  <string id="90997">Where can I find her?</string>
  <string id="90999">Let&apos;s return to my other questions.</string>
  <string id="91001">I need to relieve you at this post. You must leave the room.</string>
  <string id="91003">Your position depends on Master Gang&apos;s. I can raise him *if* there are no prying eyes.</string>
  <string id="91007">Master Gang would rather not be associated with what I am planning.</string>
  <string id="91008">The machine looks dangerous. Have accidents claimed any lives?</string>
  <string id="91011">Tell me about the crane and press.</string>
  <string id="91012">Tell me about the different golems.</string>
  <string id="91013">What are the different kinds of golems?</string>
  <string id="91015">Of that size? Are there larger ones?</string>
  <string id="91016">Why is the Jade Golem special?</string>
  <string id="91017" soundid="140720">You&apos;re right. Master Li would not have accepted me if he did not see potential. He measures all people carefully.</string>
  <string id="91018" soundid="140721">I haven&apos;t yet settled in. My studies in the Imperial City were far inferior to the instruction you&apos;ve had.</string>
  <string id="91019" soundid="140722">You&apos;re right. Sometimes I just feel that I&apos;m so far behind you that I may never catch up.</string>
  <string id="91020" soundid="140723">What can I do to help you?</string>
  <string id="91021" soundid="140724">Is there something you need from me?</string>
  <string id="91022" soundid="140725">Everyone is talking about Gao the Lesser&apos;s expulsion, of course. I knew he wasn&apos;t... disciplined, but that was truly out of line. There&apos;s always you, of course.</string>
  <string id="91023" soundid="140726">I haven&apos;t been here long enough to hear anything but rumors. Everyone prefers not to think about that place. I certainly don&apos;t envy you for having to go down there.</string>
  <string id="91024">Communion of the Dragon</string>
  <string id="91025" soundid="140728">I&apos;m no map maker, but I know the basics of the way the Empire is laid out. What do you want to know?</string>
  <string id="91026">Chi +5

The Spirit Monks have long used the meditation wheels lining the entryway of Dirge&apos;s inner temple to aid their meditations. Only one of the wheels operated when you meditated before them, and you gained only a small benefit from your moment of reflection.</string>
  <string id="91027" soundid="140730">It was a beautiful place to grow up: the brightest minds, the most noble houses, all the greatest warriors gather there. It&apos;s truly the most vibrant place in the world.</string>
  <string id="91028" soundid="140731">I&apos;m glad to be here, don&apos;t get me wrong. Two Rivers, though, is very... peaceful. I&apos;m used to a more hectic pace, I think. It&apos;s taking me some time to adjust.</string>
  <string id="91029">Health +5
Chi +15

With five of the ancient meditation wheels of Dirge spinning as you meditated, you soon realized that, like the amulet, the wheels were merely a training tool. You feel closer to understanding the nature of the Water Dragon than before, and with that understanding comes power. How you choose to use it remains to be seen.</string>
  <string id="91030" soundid="140733">Two Rivers is quiet... subdued. This province has a lot of rich agricultural land. Actually, fields cover pretty much everything south of the Great Southern Forest. </string>
  <string id="91031">From the scattered pages you have recovered, this tome seems to outline some sort of ritual. While the ritual deals with curses of some sort, it&apos;s hard to make out exactly what effect it might have if performed.</string>
  <string id="91032">You seem to have roughly half of the missing sections from this ancient book. From what you can piece together, the Tome of Release details a ritual that can free spirits bound to a place by a curse or other magic. If what you read is correct, this ritual might be enough to disperse the ghosts of the last Imperial Army soldiers still trapped in Dirge. You&apos;d need to find additional sections of the tome to be sure, though.</string>
  <string id="91033" soundid="140736">They consider farmers uneducated rustics, though they&apos;d use less... polite terms. They&apos;d change their tune if they could see such a skilled tutor as Master Li out here.</string>
  <string id="91034">You almost have all of the missing sections of the Tome of Release, and except for a few key elements, you could almost perform the ritual outlined within. Doing so would clearly free the spirits of the last few Imperial Army soldiers who haunt Dirge.

This section of the Tome makes it clear that the ritual must be performed at the shrine dedicated to Mah Tsung the Water&apos;s Source, one of the first Spirit Monks. Elevated to the heavens for his tireless service to the Water Dragon, his influence is said to guide the invoked magic.</string>
  <string id="91035" soundid="140738">The Empire is divided into four massive provinces. This area, largely agricultural, is the Golden Delta. To the north lies the Seat of Heaven, which holds the Imperial City.</string>
  <string id="91037" soundid="140740">In the Prosperous East, you can find port cities like Phoenix Gate. To the west lie the Hills of the Six Holy Scrolls. I know little about those two provinces, though.</string>
  <string id="91040" soundid="140743">Don&apos;t let me distract you from the people singing your praises for defeating the bandits. I should get back to my studies so I can one day match your greatness.</string>
  <string id="91041" soundid="140744">I&apos;m sorry, senior student. I must attend to my studies so as not to waste anyone&apos;s time.</string>
  <string id="91042" soundid="140745">I&apos;ve heard that Dawn Star is missing!</string>
  <string id="91043" soundid="140746">Given the way you treat some of us, I&apos;d be almost surprised if you cared, but I&apos;m not going to hold a grudge if you need my help.</string>
  <string id="91044" soundid="140747">If anyone can find her, it&apos;s you.</string>
  <string id="91045" soundid="140748">Master Li once asked me not to use the style I learned in the Imperial City. It was a fair request, so I agreed. Gao should have known better than to use a forbidden style.</string>
  <string id="91046" soundid="140749">Those bandits learned a hard lesson! Master Li is not a man to stand by while the town is attacked. Same with you. When something has to be done, you do it.</string>
  <string id="91048" soundid="140751">What would bandits want with a sleepy town like Two Rivers? They&apos;re in for a surprise if they think the school won&apos;t leap to the town&apos;s defense.</string>
  <string id="91049" soundid="140752">It is an honor to be approached by the school&apos;s most senior student. My mother had high hopes for this school when she sent me here from the capital.</string>
  <string id="91050">Do you know anything about the cavern beneath the school?</string>
  <string id="91052">What can you tell me about places other than here?</string>
  <string id="91053">Tell me about the Imperial City.</string>
  <string id="91055">It sounds like you miss it.</string>
  <string id="91057">How do you like this area?</string>
  <string id="91060">What do people from the city tend to think of this area.</string>
  <string id="91062">Let&apos;s hear about the rest of the Empire.</string>
  <string id="91072">If you are here, you belong here.</string>
  <string id="91074">Why do you doubt yourself?</string>
  <string id="91076">If you believe that you are inferior, you make it true.</string>
  <string id="91077">Stay focused and you will succeed.</string>
  <string id="91078">Your whining does nothing but waste our master&apos;s time.</string>
  <string id="91079">If you are too weak to be at this school, leave before you waste our Master&apos;s time.</string>
  <string id="91175" soundid="140884">It takes some time for their eyes and skin to adjust. For the first few weeks, they are as easy to kill as newborn kittens.</string>
  <string id="91176" soundid="140885">If we must. What do you want?</string>
  <string id="91177" soundid="140886">Leave us, acolyte.</string>
  <string id="91178" soundid="140887">What do you want, acolyte? We&apos;ve done our work for the day and don&apos;t want to be disturbed. Unless the press is broken, leave us.</string>
  <string id="91179" soundid="140888">What do you want now, acolyte? Unless the press is damaged, you have no reason to speak with us.</string>
  <string id="91180" soundid="140889">What? Which one of you idiots threw off the mixture? Bah, it doesn&apos;t matter.</string>
  <string id="91181" soundid="140890">Three days calibrating it for perfect clay husks, and some new-blood fool ruins it in an instant.</string>
  <string id="91182" soundid="140891">The supports for the mold injectors will be charred. We&apos;ll have to find a smith to forge new ones. Ugh, what a mess.</string>
  <string id="91183" soundid="140892">I don&apos;t want any of you stunted acolytes touching them. In fact, I will request that only full-fledged assassins operate the machine from now on.</string>
  <string id="91184" soundid="140893">So much wasted work. If we don&apos;t get it fixed, Jia will have us slaughtered.</string>
  <string id="91185" soundid="140894">I know, I know. We need to go to the market district and find a smith. Come on. We&apos;re wasting time.</string>
  <string id="91186" soundid="140895">I don&apos;t need you to tell me that, acolyte. I swear, I&apos;m going to recommend that your kind never touch it again.</string>
  <string id="91187" soundid="140896">That is unfortunate, because the needs of an acolyte are of little concern.</string>
  <string id="91188" soundid="140897">Our tasks are done for the day, but Grand Inquisitor Jia could request us at any time. We must be ready to respond if the golem press malfunctions.</string>
  <string id="91189" soundid="140898">Nothing short of her order or an emergency repair will move us. Step away, acolyte. You are of no concern to us.</string>
  <string id="91190" soundid="140899">You are right to marvel at its stability. It is a machine in balance. Only errors of its operators have damaged it before.</string>
  <string id="91191" soundid="140900">Several foolish acolytes were killed for damaging it. It&apos;s not so hard to use properly. All you do is work the crane and occasionally add Phoenix Oil to the Material Selector.</string>
  <string id="91192" soundid="140901">The measure of oil has been wrong too often. Kia Jong gives it out too freely. I will see to it that your kind are only given pre-measured containers of it.</string>
  <string id="91193" soundid="140902">Gang needs to better train his acolytes. You were obviously rushed through the initiation process.</string>
  <string id="91194" soundid="140903">Phoenix Oil is a viscous liquid that burns at an incredible temperature. It heats the press to cure the golem husks.</string>
  <string id="91195" soundid="140904">If there is too much in the machine, it burns too hot. Too little, and the golems crumble. The merchant brings the oil from the craftsmen of the Golden Delta.</string>
  <string id="91196" soundid="140905">You would not understand the complex balance of gears and sorcery that makes it function. Even flyers are simpler creations.</string>
  <string id="91197" soundid="140906">By the will of the Emperor, Death&apos;s Hand had it created.</string>
  <string id="91198" soundid="140907">With parts stolen from some great celestial furnace.</string>
  <string id="91199" soundid="140908">That&apos;s nonsense. Not everything our craftsmen create is stolen or gifted from somewhere else. We have the capability on our own.</string>
  <string id="91200" soundid="140909">We keep the golem press functioning. Without us, the machines could not keep up the ambitious pace that Grand Inquisitor Jia has set.</string>
  <string id="91201" soundid="140910">It takes two minds, two pairs of hands to control the inner structures of the press. You fools just see the controls. Inside the machines, it is impossibly complex.</string>
  <string id="91204">Goodbye.</string>
  <string id="91205">The press malfunctioned. Someone used too much Phoenix Oil.</string>
  <string id="91208">Will you require assistance?</string>
  <string id="91211">You better get to it, then.</string>
  <string id="91213">I need everyone out of the hall. </string>
  <string id="91216">What could cause a machine as sophisticated as the press to break down?</string>
  <string id="91219">What is Phoenix Oil? Where does it come from?</string>
  <string id="91222">Tell me about the golem press.</string>
  <string id="91223">Who built the press?</string>
  <string id="91226">What is your purpose here?</string>
  <string id="91228">Let&apos;s go back to my other questions.</string>
  <string id="91233" soundid="140942">[These are the controls for selecting which type of golem is to be made. It is locked on &quot;Clay Golem.&quot;]</string>
  <string id="91234" soundid="140943">[There is an opening in the side that looks like it accepts clay containers of some kind. Other than that, it seems quite simple.]</string>
  <string id="91235" soundid="140944">[The Lotus Acolyte would see your sabotage. He should be convinced to leave, first.]</string>
  <string id="91236" soundid="140945">[It slides neatly into the machine. It does not take long for a malfunction to occur. The machine shuts down.]</string>
  <string id="91237" soundid="140946">[The press is blocked by an existing golem. A new one cannot be made until the previous one is moved with the crane.]</string>
  <string id="91238" soundid="140947"></string>
  <string id="91239" soundid="140948">[The controls for the mixer do not appear to be functioning. Too much Phoenix Oil was added.]</string>
  <string id="91241">[Insert Phoenix Oil container.]</string>
  <string id="91242">[Make a clay golem.]</string>
  <string id="91243">[Leave the machine.]</string>
  <string id="91244">Ghost</string>
  <string id="91247">Lotus Acolyte</string>
  <string id="91250">Lotus Acolyte</string>
  <string id="91253" soundid="140962">[These are the controls for using the crane to move golems from the press to the walkway. A golem must be in the press for the crane to activate.]</string>
  <string id="91254" soundid="140963">[The golem is easily lifted into the air.]</string>
  <string id="91255" soundid="140964">[The crane swings to the right.]</string>
  <string id="91257" soundid="140966">[The golem smashes to the ground.]</string>
  <string id="91258" soundid="140967"></string>
  <string id="91259" soundid="140968">[The crane swings to the right.]</string>
  <string id="91260" soundid="140969">[The crane swings to the left.]</string>
  <string id="91261" soundid="140970">[This function disabled for the safety of those on the main walkway. Golems can only be lowered onto the center walkway.]</string>
  <string id="91262">[Retrieve the golem from the press.]</string>
  <string id="91263">[Move crane right.]</string>
  <string id="91265">[Drop golem.]</string>
  <string id="91266">[Move crane right.]</string>
  <string id="91267">[Move crane left.]</string>
  <string id="91268">[Drop golem.]</string>
  <string id="91269">[Leave the machine.]</string>
  <string id="91607" soundid="151802">A pity that the rest of us don&apos;t have the luxury of cowardice.</string>
  <string id="91608" soundid="141334">Who? I don&apos;t know anybody by that name. And I don&apos;t know anything about slave traders.</string>
  <string id="91609" soundid="141335">Don&apos;t you have something else you should be doing? I certainly do.</string>
  <string id="91610" soundid="141336">I suppose you are looking for Dawn Star? I&apos;m sorry, but I haven&apos;t seen her.</string>
  <string id="91611" soundid="141337">I wonder if you would look for any of the rest of us with the same interest. Somehow I doubt it.</string>
  <string id="91612" soundid="141338">I&apos;m surprised you don&apos;t know where she is. I would have thought you, if anyone, would know.</string>
  <string id="91613" soundid="141339">Gao was a fool to cheat. Our teacher is a kind man, but he is not soft and doesn&apos;t tolerate that kind of thing.</string>
  <string id="91614" soundid="141340">You&apos;ll face worse things than Gao in the cavern if what I&apos;ve heard is right. I hope you&apos;re ready.</string>
  <string id="91615" soundid="141341">To hear Gao tell it, he singlehandedly beat back the bandits, but I know you did the lion&apos;s share. Too bad I was stuck up here minding the younger students.</string>
  <string id="91616" soundid="141342">It would have been great to see Master Li deal with that sorcerer. We so rarely see our Master&apos;s true abilities in action.</string>
  <string id="91617" soundid="141343">I may finally get a chance to see some combat if there are truly bandits coming!</string>
  <string id="91618" soundid="141344">I&apos;m sure Master Li will be able to save Kia Min even if she&apos;s wounded, but I wonder who will salve her pride? &quot;Walking along the shore,&quot; my foot.</string>
  <string id="91619" soundid="141345">Our most senior student has a spare moment to spend with me? An honor!</string>
  <string id="91620" soundid="141346">No, wait, I shouldn&apos;t be like that. Master Li always reminds me that jealousy is a low path, and not worthy of one of his students.</string>
  <string id="91621" soundid="141347">I understand your training is almost complete. I wonder who will replace you as our &quot;example?&quot;</string>
  <string id="91622" soundid="141348">It certainly won&apos;t be me. I can&apos;t even imagine Master Li saying, &quot;You must strive to be like Lin in all things,&quot; to the others. Just the opposite, more likely.</string>
  <string id="91623" soundid="141349">That makes sense. Is that how you live your life? If so, it certainly seems to be an effective philosophy.</string>
  <string id="91624" soundid="141350">You could just be pouring honey in my ears, but that&apos;s not half as fun as other places it could go.</string>
  <string id="91625" soundid="141351">Lin, you&apos;re incorrigible.</string>
  <string id="91626" soundid="141352">Oh my, you&apos;ve gone kind of red. I shouldn&apos;t tease you like that.</string>
  <string id="91627" soundid="141353">That&apos;s easy enough for you to say. You&apos;re already the best in the school. The rest of us just stare at your back.</string>
  <string id="91628" soundid="141354">Of course, there could be worse views.</string>
  <string id="91629" soundid="141355">This from Master Li&apos;s favorite. We can&apos;t all be blessed with such favor. Any of us could have been the best in the school if we had been Master Li&apos;s first student!</string>
  <string id="91630" soundid="141356">Maybe I should spend more time training and less time worrying about where I stand in the school.  How else will I be good enough to take you down one of these days?</string>
  <string id="91631" soundid="141357">Besides, there might be bigger things to worry about. I find myself intrigued by the ghost tales that everyone&apos;s mentioning.</string>
  <string id="91632" soundid="141358">I don&apos;t need to take this. Your impending graduation has clearly gone to your head, and if you ask me, it can&apos;t come soon enough.</string>
  <string id="91633" soundid="141359">What do you need from me?</string>
  <string id="91634" soundid="141360">Something on your mind?</string>
  <string id="91635" soundid="141361">Come to think of it, he was muttering threats under his breath. That&apos;s just Gao, so I didn&apos;t think anything of it.</string>
  <string id="91636" soundid="141362">No one really knows anything about that cavern, except that Master Li has strictly forbidden us to go in there.</string>
  <string id="91637" soundid="141363">He has always said that it is a place of final testing. I hear whispered rumors that there&apos;s something horrible down there.</string>
  <string id="91638" soundid="141364">I even asked around town and there&apos;s old, old stories of masters before ours sending students into that cavern, and the students never finding their way out.</string>
  <string id="91639" soundid="141365">I don&apos;t have a clue, but I don&apos;t envy you having to go down there. Then again, you are the strongest of us, as we&apos;re so often reminded, so you&apos;ll be fine.</string>
  <string id="91640" soundid="141366">This is all rumor, mostly gossip from the people in Two Rivers.</string>
  <string id="91641" soundid="141367">As I said, no one really knows what&apos;s down there. Well, no one but you, once you tell Master Li you&apos;re ready.</string>
  <string id="91642" soundid="141368">Tales of people being haunted by loved ones, and mad ghosts attacking people on the roads or even in their homes.</string>
  <string id="91643" soundid="141369">And Master Li accepts Dawn Star&apos;s ability to see and sense things others can&apos;t. If he believes her, then how could I believe otherwise?</string>
  <string id="91644" soundid="141370">They&apos;re exactly what you&apos;d expect: the souls of humans who&apos;ve died. According to all the legends, when you die your soul travels to the underworld.</string>
  <string id="91645" soundid="141371">Once there, your soul is judged and placed upon the wheel of life so that it can return to this world in a new life.</string>
  <string id="91646" soundid="141372">A soul that doesn&apos;t return to the wheel of life becomes a ghost.</string>
  <string id="91647" soundid="141373">According to the stories, ghosts are usually people whose souls are trapped in this world either by circumstance or because they won&apos;t let go of their old lives.</string>
  <string id="91648" soundid="141374">The thing is, those circumstances are very rare, and you never heard about ghosts ten years ago. Now everyone&apos;s talking about them.</string>
  <string id="91649" soundid="141375">It&apos;s like something has happened, and people aren&apos;t leaving this world like they should be. Either that, or it&apos;s mass hysteria, but I can&apos;t believe that explanation.</string>
  <string id="91650" soundid="141376">We can always discuss this privately if you&apos;re curious, but I&apos;m interested in Lin&apos;s impressions.</string>
  <string id="91651" soundid="141377">From what I understand, Dawn Star is very sensitive to magic and to the spirits we call ghosts. She sees things that others can&apos;t.</string>
  <string id="91652" soundid="141378">Sometimes she knows things that she shouldn&apos;t. I really can&apos;t say if it is intuition or something else.</string>
  <string id="91653" soundid="141379">That was my first question when I started hearing these rumors. Apparently they can look just like us, though possibly pale and faded.</string>
  <string id="91654" soundid="141380">Some ghosts have been around a long time, and apparently they begin to change. They grow distant from their bodies and become more monsters than people.</string>
  <string id="91655" soundid="141381">The scary thing is that a lot of the stories I&apos;ve been hearing are about these old ghosts, the ones that look like monsters. It just doesn&apos;t make sense.</string>
  <string id="91657" soundid="141383">I suppose we all owe you our thanks, just like always.</string>
  <string id="91658">If you want Master Li to say it, don&apos;t give him a choice. Be the best you can.</string>
  <string id="91663">Don&apos;t worry about following others. Walk your own path.</string>
  <string id="91666">You lack the skills and the discipline to be a leader.</string>
  <string id="91667">You&apos;re right. I shouldn&apos;t underestimate your skills.</string>
  <string id="91669">You flatter yourself. Time does not excuse your clumsy strikes. </string>
  <string id="91671">Do you know anything about the cavern beneath the school?</string>
  <string id="91674">Do you know what this horrible thing is supposed to be?</string>
  <string id="91675">Where did you learn about the cavern?</string>
  <string id="91679">What exactly are these ghosts?</string>
  <string id="91682">Where do these ghosts come from?</string>
  <string id="91685">Tell me more about Dawn Star&apos;s sensitivity.</string>
  <string id="91688">What do ghosts look like?</string>
  <string id="91705" soundid="141441">Dawn Star wanted to be here when you left the cavern, but she&apos;s gone. If you ask me, something&apos;s wrong.</string>
  <string id="91706" soundid="141442">I don&apos;t know where she could have gone, but Wen or Lin might have some idea. You could ask in town as well.</string>
  <string id="91707" soundid="141443">Gao was a fool for challenging you. He&apos;s good, but you&apos;ve always been stronger. He just wouldn&apos;t admit it to himself.</string>
  <string id="91708" soundid="141444">Thing is, your &quot;prize&quot; is going into the cavern beneath the school. To hear Lin tell it, that place is going to challenge even you.</string>
  <string id="91709" soundid="141445">Next to nothing. I know Master Li forbids us to go in there until our final test, but that&apos;s about the only fact I have.</string>
  <string id="91710" soundid="141446">I hate repeating stories that aren&apos;t my own. Lin has no such qualms, so go ask her about the cavern.</string>
  <string id="91711" soundid="141447">Glad to see you&apos;re still well. By most reports, you faced down many of those bandits yourself. Impressive, senior student.</string>
  <string id="91712" soundid="141448">Who else? Gao the Lesser won&apos;t let a chance to glorify himself slip away.</string>
  <string id="91713" soundid="141449">That&apos;s the difference a lifetime of practice will make. I&apos;m sure their survivors learned a lesson.</string>
  <string id="91714" soundid="141450">Now you&apos;re sounding ever so slightly like Gao.</string>
  <string id="91715" soundid="141451">To hear Gao&apos;s side, he pushed back the bandits, but I know you dealt with the greater share of them.</string>
  <string id="91716" soundid="141452">Of course, it was best that our Master was there to deal with that sorcerer. The stories about their confrontation spread quicker than a plains fire.</string>
  <string id="91717" soundid="141453">Bandits coming here? They must not know about the school, or at least about Master Li. He&apos;s not a man to stand idly by while people suffer.</string>
  <string id="91718" soundid="141454">If they hurt Kia Min badly, Master Li will be angry. I&apos;d hate to be the captain of that ship if Master Li is angry.</string>
  <string id="91719" soundid="141455">Always good to see you wandering the school. You are the best among us after all, so it makes everyone train a little harder when you&apos;re around.</string>
  <string id="91720" soundid="141456">The tricky part is making sure we&apos;re emulating you, not hoping to take you down a peg. You should think carefully before bruising the tender egos around here.</string>
  <string id="91721" soundid="141457">Oh, and I did tell you to see Master Li when you have a chance? I&apos;m not taking the blame if you forget.</string>
  <string id="91722" soundid="141458">It&apos;s always good to see you again, but I should keep practicing. </string>
  <string id="91723" soundid="141459">They&apos;d probably skin me alive if they heard me say this, but Wen and Lin look like they&apos;ve got a little more free time right now.</string>
  <string id="91724" soundid="141460">Go pester them so they don&apos;t pester me.</string>
  <string id="91725" soundid="164299">(Sobbing)</string>
  <string id="91726" soundid="141462">I shall leave you to it. Take care, my friend.</string>
  <string id="91729">What do you know about the cavern?</string>
  <string id="91731">What does she say about it?</string>
  <string id="91732">Most reports? Who disagreed?</string>
  <string id="91734">They were unskilled and easily beat.</string>
  <string id="91736">I just wish Master Li had let me face their leader.</string>
  <string id="91744">I don&apos;t wish to spar with you right now.</string>
  <string id="91745" soundid="164121">We can find peace for a time at least, maybe until the voice of the shepherd returns so that we can find peace forever.</string>
  <string id="91747" soundid="141483">It means, however, that I must accelerate your training. These invaders discovered us by accident, but as you likely suspect, they are related to your destiny.</string>
  <string id="91748" soundid="141484">You have trained hard and are ready. You will have a pivotal role in some great events, my student... after you return from the Spirit Cave.</string>
  <string id="91749" soundid="141485">I object!</string>
  <string id="91750" soundid="141486">Gao? What is the meaning of this intrusion?</string>
  <string id="91751" soundid="141487">Your pet student is not the only one who fought those outlaws. Perhaps I did not stand in their midst on the beach like a fool, but I did my part!</string>
  <string id="91752" soundid="141488">If you spent less time coddling him, you would have many promising students instead of one.</string>
  <string id="91753" soundid="141489">This is not a matter that can be decided by effort, Gao. There are things at play that you do not understand.</string>
  <string id="91754" soundid="141490">I understand that this student has received preferential treatment and I have suffered for it. Whatever is in this Spirit Cave, I am worthy of facing it too!</string>
  <string id="91755" soundid="141491">If he is truly better than me, let him prove it. I challenge him.</string>
  <string id="91756" soundid="141492">If she is truly better than me, let her prove it. I challenge her.</string>
  <string id="91757" soundid="141493">If you spent less time coddling her, you would have many promising students instead of one.</string>
  <string id="91759" soundid="141495">Sometimes all you learn in defeat, is that you have been defeated. This world is out of balance. Spirits grow restless, and you have a role to play that I have kept secret.</string>
  <string id="91760" soundid="141496">The people are scared... I do not have all the answers, but I know you will become very important to the fates of many. You will be called to face a great evil.</string>
  <string id="91761" soundid="141497">Master! Master Li!</string>
  <string id="91762" soundid="141498">What is this interruption? This had better be important... there is much to say.</string>
  <string id="91763" soundid="141499">Master! Ni Joh came to warn me! He saw a boat from the outlook past the fields! Strange outlaws. They fired... something at him, and Kia Min was injured!</string>
  <string id="91764" soundid="141500">Where is she now?</string>
  <string id="91765" soundid="141501">Still outside the village by the outlook. Ni Joh couldn&apos;t carry her. Please come, Master Li. The bandits are not at the village yet, but they could arrive at any time!</string>
  <string id="91766" soundid="141502">Hmm... we will have to continue our discussion later, my student. It appears we have more pressing matters.</string>
  <string id="91767" soundid="141503">The time for practice is over. Go to Gujin the weapon master and get a weapon. You may soon be called to use it.</string>
  <string id="91768" soundid="141504">You will have your chance to fight soon enough. Go to Gujin the weapon master; he has a weapon for you, and you will have need of it before long.</string>
  <string id="91769" soundid="141505">On your way, make certain Dawn Star is aware of the danger. Her skills have always complemented yours, so take her with you.</string>
  <string id="91771">Slave Driver Rong</string>
  <string id="91779">No one is denying your skill, Gao.</string>
  <string id="91782">Cry somewhere else. I am simply better than you.</string>
  <string id="91792">What would you have me do, Master?</string>
  <string id="91794">I will fight them! Let me come with you!</string>
  <string id="91860" soundid="141640">I will not have you brawling in the street. If this must happen, it will happen in the ring, as a proper test of your abilities.</string>
  <string id="91861" soundid="141641">Gao, you are restricted to styles that I have taught. I know the dark tutoring your father, Gao the Greater, has imparted, but I won&apos;t have any such sorcery here.</string>
  <string id="91862" soundid="141642">Hobbled before I begin. Of course, how else will your precious protg win?</string>
  <string id="91863" soundid="141643">My student, I do not trust Gao to fight honorably. Consider your attacks carefully. Prepare yourself and return when you are ready.</string>
  <string id="91864" soundid="141644">Remember the basics. They will serve you well.</string>
  <string id="91865" soundid="141645">Then let the fighters meet in the arena.</string>
  <string id="91866" soundid="141646">I will explain what I can after we have dealt with Gao&apos;s interruption. I don&apos;t want to confuse matters. Trust that I am right.</string>
  <string id="91867" soundid="141647">Return to me when you are ready to address this challenge by Gao.</string>
  <string id="91868" soundid="141648">Gao awaits your signal to start the challenge, my student. Tell me when you are ready and I will have the combat ring prepared.</string>
  <string id="91869" soundid="141649">Fighters, are you ready? This challenge will continue until one of you is incapacitated. This is not a practice bout... injury is a possibility.</string>
  <string id="91870" soundid="141650">A possibility? I think it is more than likely.</string>
  <string id="91871" soundid="155031">So simple, yes? Rat demon help you, now rat demon can go. Yes?</string>
  <string id="91876" soundid="141656">Master? Are you certain this is appropriate?</string>
  <string id="91877" soundid="141657">They have a dispute, and this is the only way to settle it with certainty. It will be an honorable contest. I have restricted Gao from using his father&apos;s sorcery.</string>
  <string id="91879" soundid="141659">I said you would regret getting in my way.</string>
  <string id="91880" soundid="141660">Fighters! Begin!</string>
  <string id="91882">If that is what you wish, I will accept.</string>
  <string id="91886">I will return when I am ready, Master.</string>
  <string id="91887">I am ready now. Let&apos;s begin.</string>
  <string id="91888">I want to ask about this cave and the bandit leader.</string>
  <string id="91889">[TUTORIAL: Remember advanced combat lessons]</string>
  <string id="91890">You can call it a challenge, but my victory will be easy.</string>
  <string id="91906" soundid="143820">I can&apos;t believe Gao would kill one of our own.</string>
  <string id="91908" soundid="142607"></string>
  <string id="91913" soundid="143821">This has been a terrible day.</string>
  <string id="91924">Golem</string>
  <string id="91927">Kia Min</string>
  <string id="91930" soundid="143847">I couldn&apos;t believe it! He killed him with a single blow, and laughed as this poor boy gasped his last!</string>
  <string id="91931" soundid="143848">You! Gao the Lesser did this! He was dragging some sort of sack and this boy challenged him.</string>
  <string id="91933" soundid="143849">This brave young man stopped Gao and demanded to know what he was carrying.</string>
  <string id="91935">Could I hear about the outstanding bounties again?</string>
  <string id="91937">Why did he kill student Si Pat?</string>
  <string id="91938">I want to hear more about Fading Moon.</string>
  <string id="91946" soundid="142615">Zeng Sai feels you... feels the pain again. So close. So close to perfect chaos, and you ended it all!</string>
  <string id="91947" soundid="142616">With Shin out of the way, I am free to present you and the Jade Golem spirit shard to my masters. I will be lauded, and you will share in my good fortune.</string>
  <string id="91950">What did you do then?</string>
  <string id="91951">That was a brave thing you did.</string>
  <string id="91952">I can&apos;t believe you killed your own father.</string>
  <string id="91954">It must have been very difficult.</string>
  <string id="91955">Your wits, huh?</string>
  <string id="91957">I&apos;ll bet you were a very dangerous child.</string>
  <string id="91959" soundid="166934">The water&apos;s back!</string>
  <string id="91960" soundid="166935">I heard Minister Sheng say he&apos;d hired a young warrior to take care of things.</string>
  <string id="91961" soundid="166936">That young man with the tattoos, right? It was a lucky star that guided him here.</string>
  <string id="91962">Are you referring to the incident that prompted your exit?</string>
  <string id="91963" soundid="166937">Must be that young man with the yellow sash! Thank heavens.</string>
  <string id="91964">Summoned Ghost</string>
  <string id="91980" soundid="142147"></string>
  <string id="91981" soundid="142148"></string>
  <string id="91982" soundid="142149"></string>
  <string id="91983" soundid="142150"></string>
  <string id="91992">[Intuition] Consider it an investment. The power structure here is about to... change.</string>
  <string id="91994">[Intimidation] You want to stay safe, don&apos;t you? I&apos;d hate to see you hurt in the coming storm.</string>
  <string id="91996">What if I compensated your effort with some silver?</string>
  <string id="91997">How about 1000 silver?</string>
  <string id="91998">200 silver should suffice.</string>
  <string id="91999">I could just kill you.</string>
  <string id="92001">What can you tell me about the Lotus Assassins?</string>
  <string id="92003">Goodbye for now.</string>
  <string id="92004">Is it wise to dismiss me? Tomorrow I could be important.</string>
  <string id="92006">If I ask to see your goods, show them. I won&apos;t ask twice.</string>
  <string id="92008">Your surname is &quot;Kia?&quot; I knew a Kia Min once.</string>
  <string id="92009">She is dead. She fell in an attack related to the Lotus Assassins.</string>
  <string id="92010">That&apos;s it? No righteous rage at the link to the Lotus Assassins?</string>
  <string id="92012">Let&apos;s get back to business.</string>
  <string id="92013">The last I saw of her, she was well.</string>
  <string id="92015">A fine girl. Long flowing hair.</string>
  <string id="92016">Quite short, if I recall.</string>
  <string id="92017">Her hair was tied in many small knots.</string>
  <string id="92019">She is... of a spectacular girth.</string>
  <string id="92020">I don&apos;t recall. It has been some time since I saw her.</string>
  <string id="92022">What do you have for sale?</string>
  <string id="92023">Do you have Phoenix Oil?</string>
  <string id="92025">I need this hall cleared. Move to another room.</string>
  <string id="92027">Perhaps I could persuade you to move.</string>
  <string id="92028">[Charm] It&apos;s just a friendly request from someone who wants you to stay safe.</string>
  <string id="92032">Lost Spirit</string>
  <string id="92033">One Chance</string>
  <string id="92034" soundid="142431">I&apos;m just glad you two got a chance to try those weapons out for real. Looks like they handled themselves well, just like you two.</string>
  <string id="92035" soundid="142432">Something else you need?</string>
  <string id="92036" soundid="142433">It&apos;s a sleepy little town usually, and bandit attacks are virtually unheard of. Who wants to rob farmers? Rice isn&apos;t worth enough to carry it away.</string>
  <string id="92037" soundid="142434">The best thing about this place is Master Li&apos;s leadership. It&apos;s like the man was born to it.</string>
  <string id="92038" soundid="142435">I used to be a guard in Broken Path, a little town in the western part of the Empire. It was a sleepy place like this, though the residents were miners, not farmers.</string>
  <string id="92039" soundid="142436">That whole province is called the Hills of the Six Holy Scrolls for a reason. It&apos;s rocky, as rich in minerals as it is in ancient temples.</string>
  <string id="92040" soundid="151803">He is worthless for what comes.</string>
  <string id="92041" soundid="142438">After the body takes enough of a beating, it just doesn&apos;t fight as well as it once did.</string>
  <string id="92042" soundid="142439">About ten years ago, something just...broke loose. Ghosts stormed out of the hills, dozens of &apos;em charging from the west.</string>
  <string id="92043" soundid="142440">We tried to fight them, and it worked to some degree, but these ghosts were howling mad. Some of them didn&apos;t even look human any more. Like monsters, they were.</string>
  <string id="92044" soundid="142441">They came from the hills in the west, but beyond that, no one knows. The scary part is that these days I hear more and more stories about ghosts haunting the roads.</string>
  <string id="92045" soundid="142442">I wonder if we in Broken Path saw the beginning of whatever is happening now. It&apos;s hard to say, but there are an awful lot of rumors about ghosts these days.</string>
  <string id="92046" soundid="142443">I haven&apos;t the whisper of a clue. They simply attacked, all transparent and screaming rage in those hollow voices of theirs.</string>
  <string id="92047" soundid="142444">Ghosts can&apos;t die, but they can be... dispersed is the best word. They come back after a while, though.</string>
  <string id="92048" soundid="142445">I guess there&apos;s no peace for the dead, except to go to the underworld like most everyone does when they die.</string>
  <string id="92049" soundid="142446">We won, but many people joined the ghosts&apos; ranks that day. People were spooked, claiming that the hills were haunted.</string>
  <string id="92050" soundid="142447">Soon enough, Broken Path became an empty path. It was deserted. Still sore from the fighting, I made my way south, to what I&apos;ve found to be more peaceful lands.</string>
  <string id="92051" soundid="142448">Suit yourself. It&apos;s an old saw anyway.</string>
  <string id="92052" soundid="142449">You&apos;re right. There&apos;s plenty to do.</string>
  <string id="92053" soundid="142450">Dawn Star, I watched you practice with that new blade yesterday, and I must say you take to it naturally. I want you to keep it and use it as your own.</string>
  <string id="92056">Fight For Your Freedom</string>
  <string id="92057">What are your thoughts on Two Rivers?</string>
  <string id="92059">How did you end up training at this school?</string>
  <string id="92061" soundid="151804">I doubt this visit will be any less violent than the last.</string>
  <string id="92062" soundid="143417"></string>
  <string id="92063">What made you take up training?</string>
  <string id="92066">Where did these ghosts come from?</string>
  <string id="92068">Why would they attack your town?</string>
  <string id="92069">How could you defeat ghosts?</string>
  <string id="92071">What happened in the end?</string>
  <string id="92073">I&apos;ll hear the rest of this tale later.</string>
  <string id="92074">I should let you get back to work.</string>
  <string id="92076">Guard</string>
  <string id="92077" soundid="142617">Come to me when you are ready for the ritual. I will be outside the door to the inner chambers, waiting for their acknowledgement that the Jade Golem is ready.</string>
  <string id="92078" soundid="142618">Are you ready to be presented to my masters and participate in the creation of the Jade Golem? It will be glorious.</string>
  <string id="92079" soundid="142619">Make certain you have finished all other business in the fortress. Lotus acolytes are rarely the same after meeting with Grand Inquisitor Jia.</string>
  <string id="92080" soundid="142620">Yes, now we shall reap the rewards we both deserve.</string>
  <string id="92081" soundid="142621">Hurry back. I do not want to keep them waiting after working so hard for their favor.</string>
  <string id="92085">I am ready.</string>
  <string id="92086">I will return shortly.</string>
  <string id="92087" soundid="142627">The ways of the masters are mysterious and secretive. It is best to not ask questions about events that promote your allies.</string>
  <string id="92088" soundid="142628">If Master Gang is promoted to Shin&apos;s position, I hope he does not forget the acolytes that served him.</string>
  <string id="92089" soundid="142629">The loss of Master Gang is very distressing. I might shed a tear, had he not beaten them out of me.</string>
  <string id="92090" soundid="142630">Gang and Shin can sort their differences in the underworld. At least we are no longer trapped in the middle.</string>
  <string id="92091" soundid="142631">Hey boys! Look who it is!</string>
  <string id="92092" soundid="142632">Is &apos;at the one Gao the Lesser&apos;s always goin&apos; on about?</string>
  <string id="92093" soundid="142633">I think so! I say we teach a li&apos;l lesson about stayin&apos; in your place when great men like Gao are around!</string>
  <string id="92094" soundid="142634">You&apos;re not goin&apos; anywhere! Gao&apos;ll give us fat silver bonuses if we teach you a lesson about respect.</string>
  <string id="92095" soundid="142635">We&apos;re twice the men you are, drunk or sober!</string>
  <string id="92096" soundid="142636">Uh, this isn&apos;t a man.</string>
  <string id="92097" soundid="142637">Shaddup!</string>
  <string id="92098" soundid="142638">Teach this whelp a lesson in manners!</string>
  <string id="92101">I&apos;m not looking for a fight. I&apos;ll just leave.</string>
  <string id="92102" soundid="156818">The earth, the heavens. The living, the dead. All will grovel before my master when he unleashes himself from Dirge.</string>
  <string id="92103">There&apos;s no honor in thrashing a bunch of drunks.</string>
  <string id="92107">There will certainly be a lesson learned here today. Let&apos;s begin.</string>
  <string id="92112" soundid="142654">Preparations are complete. The spirit shard is prepared, thanks to the skills of our newest Lotus Acolyte.</string>
  <string id="92113" soundid="143133">Zeng Sai knows you! Knows your meddling scent! Zeng Sai will destroy you! Destroy it all!</string>
  <string id="92114" soundid="142656">You there, you are Master Gang&apos;s new Lotus Acolyte, correct? Master Gang has kept Grand Inquisitor Jia waiting for too long. Where is he?</string>
  <string id="92115" soundid="142657">Fools! They had more important things to do than worry about their personal stations. *My* station is at risk if Jia does not get her Jade Golem!</string>
  <string id="92116" soundid="142658">You were Gang&apos;s acolyte. You deal with this and get me the spirit shard I require. Since your master is dead, you may present it in the ritual.</string>
  <string id="92117" soundid="142659">When you have the spirit shard, come to me at the door to the inner chambers. Finish whatever business you have, you will not have time once the ritual commences.</string>
  <string id="92118" soundid="142660">What? No doubt from some petty maneuvering gone wrong. I suppose Shin had something to do with it? Both of them be damned! Jia wants her Jade Golem!</string>
  <string id="92119" soundid="142661">There you are, acolyte. I have been waiting for you, as has everyone involved in this ritual. The Jade Golem must be completed tonight!</string>
  <string id="92120" soundid="142662">Return to me when you have the spirit shard. Only then will you have earned the right to present yourself to Grand Inquisitor Jia in the heart of our fortress.</string>
  <string id="92121" soundid="142663">You have the spirit shard? Very good, acolyte; you are on the verge of being welcomed into the heart of the fortress. Have you completed all other business?</string>
  <string id="92122" soundid="142664">Good. Grand Inquisitor Jia will be pleased, I am sure.</string>
  <string id="92123" soundid="142665">Do not test my patience, acolyte. I am not the fool Master Gang was.</string>
  <string id="92124">Master Gang and Master Shin have... resolved their differences poorly.</string>
  <string id="92126">I will bring it to you soon.</string>
  <string id="92127">I apologize on behalf of my Master. He is dead.</string>
  <string id="92130">Yes, proceed to the ritual.</string>
  <string id="92131">I will return shortly.</string>
  <string id="92161" soundid="142757">What? What do you want?</string>
  <string id="92162" soundid="142758">No, we&apos;ve got better things to do right now. Maybe I&apos;ll feel like talking after I&apos;ve bloodied up my axes a few more times.</string>
  <string id="92163" soundid="166938">Sheng finally did something right. It must be that young man in the robes who has been around.</string>
  <string id="92165" soundid="142761">Nuh.</string>
  <string id="92166">What did you do before you were with Lord Yun?</string>
  <string id="92167">What do you think about our current situation?</string>
  <string id="92168">Tell me something about your past.</string>
  <string id="92169" soundid="166939">I expect it was that large fellow with the shoulder pad. Thank heavens things are restored.</string>
  <string id="92170">That&apos;s all for now.</string>
  <string id="92175">Slave</string>
  <string id="92363">Be safe. Now go!</string>
  <string id="92364">You are nothing to me. Go.</string>
  <string id="92365">Run from here. Go.</string>
  <string id="92366" soundid="143123">Er, and my efforts to accelerate her training.</string>
  <string id="92367" soundid="143124">You are very fortunate to be welcomed so quickly into the heart of our order. Grand Inquisitor Jia will be pleased with you.</string>
  <string id="92378" soundid="143136"></string>
  <string id="92385" soundid="143146">What is the meaning of this! Who has corrupted this Jade Golem? It is linked to a legion of warriors that now run mad! The foundation will crumble!</string>
  <string id="92386" soundid="143147">Who are... you. Wait. I can... sense it on you. You are the one! You carry the other pieces of the amulet!</string>
  <string id="92387" soundid="143148">I... I&apos;m so sorry, Grand Inquisitor Jia. It is my new acolyte... there was some kind of mistake.</string>
  <string id="92388" soundid="143149">Fool! So blinded by petty schemes that you cannot see a threat in our midst! You are worthless!</string>
  <string id="92389" soundid="143150">And you... hidden in plain sight, like your master. You caught us unsuspecting, but not unprepared. Who are you, to think you could enter our lair so easily?</string>
  <string id="92390" soundid="143151">A simple student? I don&apos;t think so. An invader, conspirator, traitor. We survive by seeing the enemy in everyone.</string>
  <string id="92392" soundid="143153">Defeat us? No, we are well insulated against your kind. Whether an invader, a conspirator, a traitor, we survive by seeing the enemy in everyone.</string>
  <string id="92394" soundid="143155">My gravest apologies, Grand Inquisitor Jia. This new acolyte has corrupted the ritual.</string>
  <string id="92412">I am a simple student searching for his master.</string>
  <string id="92414">I am a simple student searching for her master.</string>
  <string id="92415">It doesn&apos;t matter what I am. I will defeat you.</string>
  <string id="92428" soundid="143189">There you are. Remember me? I &quot;welcomed&quot; you in the hall when you first arrived. Well, I said I wasn&apos;t through with you. I&apos;ve got numbers on my side, now.</string>
  <string id="92429" soundid="149476">Then leave me to deal with Gao and return when you are ready.</string>
  <string id="92498" soundid="143418">Everyone&apos;s heard about Gao the Lesser&apos;s little outburst. It figures he&apos;d try something like that when he was losing.</string>
  <string id="92501" soundid="143421">Unlike Gao, I want to learn my lessons properly. I would never disgrace myself the way he did.</string>
  <string id="92504" soundid="143424">Gao must have made his way through the gate. As I said, if he&apos;s headed for the swamp, he&apos;s a fool. There&apos;s nothing but bandits and beasts in that direction.</string>
  <string id="92508" soundid="143608">At my age, you don&apos;t dwell on dark subjects. There&apos;s not enough time to waste. Still....</string>
  <string id="92509" soundid="143609">For generations, masters have used that cave to test students. Not all of them possessed your master&apos;s wisdom, though, and some students were... lost.</string>
  <string id="92510" soundid="143610">Superstitious folk say that place is haunted, but I just think it&apos;s dangerous. I don&apos;t know the nature of that danger, so you be ready for anything.</string>
  <string id="92511">Tell me more about the cave under the school.</string>
  <string id="92514" soundid="143614">Master Li has asked that no students leave the school until the morning meditations are concluded.</string>
  <string id="92516" soundid="143617">No, of course not! It is just your way, and I would as soon ask you to change it as ask the leopard to shed its spots.</string>
  <string id="92653">Slaver Documents</string>
  <string id="92656" soundid="180317">I will show them the way, and they can join you. Not me, of course. I&apos;ll be there for you if you win, but I have to plan for any possible outcome.</string>
  <string id="92660" soundid="143872">Prosperous tidings. What can humble Hou do to assist you today?</string>
  <string id="92661" soundid="143873">Thank you again for rescuing me from those... things. I owe you my deepest gratitude. Is there some way I can be of assistance?</string>
  <string id="92665">Master Li</string>
  <string id="92668" soundid="143880">As you wish. I will be here waiting impatiently if you require anything.</string>
  <string id="92669" soundid="143881">As I mentioned, I am but a simple bun master, with a dear wife who has turned my life into a miserable cesspool devoid of humor and excitement. Bless her soul.</string>
  <string id="92670" soundid="143882">My wife ensures that I work very hard every day to become the best bun master in the Imperial City. Perhaps the best in all the Empire.</string>
  <string id="92671" soundid="143883">Though I was one of the most respected fighters in the Empire before I met my precious bride, she made sure that I became something more... or less.</string>
  <string id="92672" soundid="143884">As I mentioned before, my style requires that I drink. She detests drinking, though there are things she detests even more. Like talk of us... separating.</string>
  <string id="92673" soundid="143885">My loving wife would knead me into several small dumplings and boil me in hot oil if she suspected I was even speaking to you about leaving her.</string>
  <string id="92674" soundid="143886">Life is not all bad though. I may have lost all my dignity and self-respect, along with my ability to fight or even make a tight fist, but I am a bun master of some renown.</string>
  <string id="92675" soundid="143887">Oh yes. I&apos;m very proud of that. Indeed. Something very useful... buns that is. Everybody needs them. Oh yes, very proud.</string>
  <string id="92676" soundid="143888">I would sooner return to the cannibals and offer them what little flesh is left on my bones. Let&apos;s not discuss such things, if you don&apos;t mind.</string>
  <string id="92677" soundid="143889">I think we need to find that wind map and get out of here. Pardon my craven nature, but I&apos;m afraid it&apos;s all I have left after long years of... wedded bliss.</string>
  <string id="92678" soundid="143890">We have the wind map, so I think we should leave... immediately. I have many fine traits, but I&apos;m afraid my backbone has been crushed by years of... wedded bliss.</string>
  <string id="92681" soundid="143893">It would seem we have our work cut out for us. But as my darling wife likes to say, when things are tough... quit your whining and get to work.</string>
  <string id="92682" soundid="143894">I can almost hear her screaming at me now. If ever you find a cure for bad memories, please let me know.</string>
  <string id="92685" soundid="143897">I never realized that getting back to the Imperial City would be so... hazardous to my health. I was hoping the cannibals were the worst thing I would see.</string>
  <string id="92686" soundid="143898">I think we should keep moving. I have a bad feeling that if we stay in one place too long, we won&apos;t ever leave.</string>
  <string id="92687" soundid="143899">It would seem that we at last have the means necessary to get us back to the Imperial City, and for that I should be very glad.</string>
  <string id="92688" soundid="143900">However, I must now face the greatest trial of all; My sweet wife will no doubt be waiting for me. Soon my time with the cannibals with be nothing but a fond memory.</string>
  <string id="92690" soundid="143902">Perhaps in a little while. Memories of my wife are... difficult to bear. Especially when she is so very far away, and I may never see her again.</string>
  <string id="92691">Kill Zhong</string>
  <string id="92693">Tell me about your life before you were captured.</string>
  <string id="92696">You killed Zhong the Ox Carrier. Dong Ping will be ruined, but the ogre will no longer scare the patrons in the Teahouse.</string>
  <string id="92697" soundid="166591">The lessons you learn from me, or from any trainer for that matter, will stay with you, and help make you stronger, or better able to focus your mind or magic.</string>
  <string id="92698">That&apos;s all for now.</string>
  <string id="92700">That&apos;s too bad, Hou.</string>
  <string id="92701">Why doesn&apos;t she like you fighting?</string>
  <string id="92703">Just divorce her, and get it over with.</string>
  <string id="92705">Well, that&apos;s something to be proud of. I guess.</string>
  <string id="92706">When we get you home, I&apos;ll speak with your wife.</string>
  <string id="92707">I think it&apos;s time you told your wife what you think.</string>
  <string id="92708">What do you think about our current situation?</string>
  <string id="92714">Tell me more about yourself, Hou.</string>
  <string id="92715" soundid="166592">Let&apos;s see what you can learn.</string>
  <string id="92716" soundid="166593">Training has worth, and Master Li allows me to collect a small fee to reinforce this. Travel outside Two Rivers and you will find my prices are *quite* reasonable.</string>
  <string id="92717">A restless sleep before a battle has now become something worse. It seems that Master Li is manipulating your dreams, or that your dreams are manipulating you. Either way, the burning school you once called home is now the setting of a nightmarish battle.</string>
  <string id="92718" soundid="166595">No, I try to improve base abilities. But through the basics that Master Li has instilled, when you have the opportunity I&apos;m sure you will pick up new styles quickly.</string>
  <string id="92719">Spirit Font</string>
  <string id="92720" soundid="166597">Fair enough. I am patient as the rock facing the wind. What else was on your mind?</string>
  <string id="92722">Show me what you have.</string>
  <string id="92723" soundid="143935">I wish I&apos;d looked to see what he was dragging. He was heading toward the gate. The only place he could get to on foot is the swamp.</string>
  <string id="92725" soundid="143937">Of course not! I know there&apos;s more at stake! Someone will have to pay for the memorial, for flowers, and.... Er, yes, I see what you mean. Very sad.</string>
  <string id="92726" soundid="143938">Maybe you should ask Gujin. He always watches *me* like a hawk, why not others?</string>
  <string id="92727">Your only concern is that you&apos;ve lost a potential customer?</string>
  <string id="92730" soundid="143943">Your Master claims the throne and my power. He will rule as a god unless he is stopped.</string>
  <string id="92732" soundid="156390">And where are my Attendants? Delays and laziness will be repaid in blood! No one disobeys the orders of Shin!</string>
  <string id="92733">If he planned all of this, his lies have spanned years.</string>
  <string id="92809">Dawn Star&apos;s Garden</string>
  <string id="92810">Master Li&apos;s quarters</string>
  <string id="92811" soundid="144480"></string>
  <string id="92844" soundid="144058">Of course. I&apos;m sure you will find my company enjoyable.</string>
  <string id="92845" soundid="144059">A wise preference. No offense intended to your amusing companions.</string>
  <string id="92846" soundid="144060">Of course, I look forward to it.</string>
  <string id="92847">Travel with me now.</string>
  <string id="92848">Travel with me now. Dawn Star can go wait at the flyer.</string>
  <string id="92849">Travel with me now. Zu can go wait at the flyer.</string>
  <string id="92850">Travel with me now. Hou can go wait at the flyer.</string>
  <string id="92851">Travel with me now. The Black Whirlwind can go wait at the flyer.</string>
  <string id="92852">Travel with me now. Wild Flower can go wait at the flyer.</string>
  <string id="92853">Travel with me now. Sky can go wait at the flyer.</string>
  <string id="92854">Wait at the flyer. I will speak with you later.</string>
  <string id="92856" soundid="144070">I didn&apos;t think there would be so many! They&apos;re coming from the beach!</string>
  <string id="92857" soundid="144071">I know you&apos;ll stop them. You have to! They&apos;re coming from the beach!</string>
  <string id="92858" soundid="144072">The bandits are here! You have to stop them!</string>
  <string id="92859" soundid="144073">There are so many bandits all coming from the beach! I don&apos;t want to die!</string>
  <string id="92860">Ghost</string>
  <string id="92864">Lost Spirit</string>
  <string id="92868" soundid="144083">Where could he go, though? It must have been through town. There&apos;s nowhere to hide in the school.</string>
  <string id="92872" soundid="144089">There are more daunting problems to consider. For example, how will you sneak past Sheng&apos;s guards to make the switch?</string>
  <string id="92876" soundid="144096">The amulet, its pieces spread like petals to the wind. You have caught a few, but you are far from your peak, and not every golem was linked to this corrupted husk.</string>
  <string id="92877" soundid="144097">Goodbye, Spirit Monk. I will inform Death&apos;s Hand of your passing.</string>
  <string id="93101">There&apos;s no trade to be found in stability?</string>
  <string id="93103">Let&apos;s talk about what you can do for me.</string>
  <string id="93104">Gate</string>
  <string id="93105">Gate to the Golden Way</string>
  <string id="93106" soundid="156362">Is there something you need? If not, we should concentrate on getting the information I require from the Lotus Assassins.</string>
  <string id="93108">City Gate</string>
  <string id="93109" soundid="158475">Who&apos;s there? More of Gao&apos;s soldiers? I&apos;m through hiding. The marsh is outlaw territory!</string>
  <string id="93118" soundid="144376">It is not my job to rescue those who are not strong enough to protect themselves. That is an endless, foolish road.</string>
  <string id="93120" soundid="144389">Discomfort? If it was any smaller I&apos;d have to leave my axes behind. That, or start clearing some room. It can&apos;t need *all* of those shiny bits.</string>
  <string id="93121" soundid="144390">There&apos;s nothing mysterious about it. Our paths lead in the same direction. Anything else we discuss is between you and I. I&apos;ll thank you to keep it that way.</string>
  <string id="93122" soundid="144391">As you wish. I was merely curious. Just a little friendly talk between trusting friends. The group could use a little more of it.</string>
  <string id="93123" soundid="144392">I show interest in beautiful things. I meant no offense. I just want to learn more about my fellows.</string>
  <string id="93124" soundid="144393">I won&apos;t, but our cause will not wait for us. Thank you both for your concern.</string>
  <string id="93125" soundid="144394">Your resolve is absolute. I thought Dawn Star might be convinced to be more sensible.</string>
  <string id="93126" soundid="197676">I&apos;d go look for Dawn Star, but there might be ghosts out there.</string>
  <string id="93127" soundid="144396">Your station is already... low. Stepping down would serve no purpose, and I doubt you would find it easy to move up.</string>
  <string id="93128" soundid="144397">Oh, certainly. Those without titles regularly declare their unimportance.</string>
  <string id="93129" soundid="144398">I doubt the princess can. Those with titles tend to rely on them too much... and earn a few more along the way.</string>
  <string id="93130">This ends *NOW*!</string>
  <string id="93131">He&apos;s right, Dawn Star. Don&apos;t overdo it.</string>
  <string id="93132">That is true, Black Whirlwind.</string>
  <string id="93133">Why do you care about discomfort, Black Whirlwind? You&apos;re a warrior.</string>
  <string id="93134">Come now, Zu, why all the mystery?</string>
  <string id="93135">Let him be, Sky. We all have our secrets.</string>
  <string id="93136">You&apos;re showing a lot of interest in Dawn Star, Sky.</string>
  <string id="93137">We all need rest, but we can&apos;t stop now.</string>
  <string id="93139">Enough, Whirlwind. I apologize for his behavior, Princess.</string>
  <string id="93141">Not everyone places such value in titles, Princess. </string>
  <string id="93142">Arguing about roles is pointless. We need to move beyond this.</string>
  <string id="93186" soundid="144481"></string>
  <string id="93192">Let&apos;s hear the details surrounding Creative Yukong.</string>
  <string id="93197">Why is there a fee?</string>
  <string id="93198">I am a weapon of vengeance. I seek the head of Death&apos;s Hand!</string>
  <string id="93200">I am a Spirit Monk. I must stand against the Emperor!</string>
  <string id="93204">Save</string>
  <string id="93206">Gao&apos;s Mercenary in Spirit Cave</string>
  <string id="93211">You were challenged by a woman clad in black as you approached Tien&apos;s Landing. She apparently saw you leave Two Rivers, and assumed you were a minion of Death&apos;s Hand. You convinced her otherwise after surprising her with your martial skills.</string>
  <string id="93212" soundid="144517">I can&apos;t believe Two Rivers is gone. It was home... the people there were the only family I&apos;ve known. And now, they&apos;re all gone.</string>
  <string id="93213" soundid="144518">I understand, Dawn Star, but the path you are on may lead to even darker places. You must prepare yourself.</string>
  <string id="93214" soundid="144519">What do you want, Sky? You are watching me very closely, and not with the eyes of a friend.</string>
  <string id="93215" soundid="144520">Nothing, nothing. I just wanted to know what it felt like to work for Death&apos;s Hand. That&apos;s right, isn&apos;t it? You&apos;re one of them?</string>
  <string id="93216" soundid="144521">I was. Do you seek an apology for their actions, or am I just the latest target in your search for vengeance? I have to disappoint you. I will not accept either role.</string>
  <string id="93217" soundid="144522">I have not hidden that fact from you, or anyone else it was relevant to tell. Your true enemies will not reveal their nature to your face.</string>
  <string id="93218" soundid="144523">So you say, but he certainly wears the uniform.</string>
  <string id="93219" soundid="144524">Does any of this scare you, Wild Flower? You&apos;re so young, and our journey is... well, dangerous.</string>
  <string id="93220" soundid="144525">Why would I be scared? I have the Guardian to protect me. I&apos;m always safe with him, and he is always here.</string>
  <string id="93221" soundid="144526">I see. How exactly does he protect you? I use my blades and my wits to keep me safe. Are you sure this... Guardian can do the same for you?</string>
  <string id="93222" soundid="144527">Chai Ka: Very sure. Do you wish me to demonstrate?</string>
  <string id="93223" soundid="144528">No, no. That&apos;s quite all right. I... can see quite clearly how... you would be more than adequate protection. Nice demon.</string>
  <string id="93224" soundid="144529">Chai Ka: Rest assured, mortal, the girl is well protected against dangers without and within.</string>
  <string id="93225" soundid="144530">The equipment you carry with you, Kang... it seems quite expensive. Have a stash of silver somewhere, do you?</string>
  <string id="93226" soundid="144531">That&apos;s enough of that. I know a look of larceny when I see one. Besides, it will do you no good. With Gao gone I am... between benefactors.</string>
  <string id="93227">x</string>
  <string id="93228">x</string>
  <string id="93229">x</string>
  <string id="93230">x</string>
  <string id="93231">x</string>
  <string id="93232" soundid="144537">Hmm... the marks of the Lotus Assassins. You have covered some, Zu, but left others plain.</string>
  <string id="93233">x</string>
  <string id="93234">x</string>
  <string id="93237" soundid="144542">I don&apos;t want to think like that. We will set things right. We have to.</string>
  <string id="93238" soundid="144543">Returning your friends was never an option, but there are a great many more things that you can lose.</string>
  <string id="93239" soundid="144544">I... I know. I just wish there was a way to put things back the way they were.</string>
  <string id="93240" soundid="144545">In the past I have shared the company of others that... moved outside traditional paths, but this band of folks is by far the most... exotic.</string>
  <string id="93241" soundid="144546">You looked at me as you said that. What are you trying to say, Sky?</string>
  <string id="93242" soundid="144547">Actually, you took it the wrong way around. You seem a bit more conventional than, say, Wild Flower, or Zu.</string>
  <string id="93243" soundid="144548">The Guardian says that everyone hides a part of themselves, that they don&apos;t always look like what they really are.</string>
  <string id="93244" soundid="144549">I certainly hope that part&apos;s in there somewhere.</string>
  <string id="93245" soundid="144550">I can&apos;t help it.</string>
  <string id="93246" soundid="144551">Really, now?</string>
  <string id="93247" soundid="144552">Are we certain there is no room for us to stay in Tien&apos;s Landing? Do we really need to camp outside?</string>
  <string id="93248" soundid="144553">The ground is soft enough for a warrior. Walls just get in the way when the fighting starts. Besides, I&apos;ve yet to find a bed that fits me.</string>
  <string id="93249" soundid="144554">Not everyone has a hide as thick as yours.</string>
  <string id="93250">Sailor</string>
  <string id="93254" soundid="144559">That&apos;s good wine you&apos;ve got here, Hou! Not too sweet, not too sour... and it has a good kick to it.</string>
  <string id="93255" soundid="144560">I&apos;m pleased you like it, though I&apos;m afraid you like it a little bit too much. At this rate, we&apos;ll run out of wine before we get back to the Imperial City.</string>
  <string id="93256" soundid="144561">I hope you&apos;re joking, Hou! You don&apos;t want to see me when I&apos;m sober. You really don&apos;t.</string>
  <string id="93257" soundid="144562">I have an ointment you should try. Put it under your tongue, and it will stop your desire for alcohol. Well, more like &quot;replace.&quot;</string>
  <string id="93258" soundid="144563">More? Well, I suppose I hadn&apos;t thought about that. Let&apos;s see, distillation... crop variation... slide the three....</string>
  <string id="93259" soundid="144564">I don&apos;t usually offer a choice.</string>
  <string id="93260">On Agriculture</string>
  <string id="93266">That&apos;s a good idea, Chai Ka. Show him how you protect her.</string>
  <string id="93267">Enough, Chai Ka. Sky was just looking out for her.</string>
  <string id="93272">x</string>
  <string id="93273">x</string>
  <string id="93275">x</string>
  <string id="93278">She&apos;s right, Zu. More killing won&apos;t bring our friends back.</string>
  <string id="93279">I don&apos;t think we can. We may have to settle for vengeance.</string>
  <string id="93283">So we can assume Sky is hiding the part that doesn&apos;t ram its foot into its mouth?</string>
  <string id="93284">We all have hidden &quot;demons,&quot; but not literally. Your nature *is* odd.</string>
  <string id="93285">Yes, and Dawn Star does have strange abilities.</string>
  <string id="93288">The village is in rough shape. We must make do out here.</string>
  <string id="93291">Toughen up. If this is the worst we encounter, I&apos;ll be surprised.</string>
  <string id="93295">And how hard would it be to get more ointment to appease him?</string>
  <string id="93296">I like the Black Whirlwind as he is.</string>
  <string id="93297">
Food, and the shortage of it, has always been a primary concern within the Empire. With so many people crowded into cities, a lack of food in an urban area can result in deaths of thousands. While this is not itself a primary concern, the economic disruption and the outbreak of disease it usually causes are. Agriculture is, therefore, a critical industry of the Empire. Fertile areas can frequently have 2 or 3 crops a year, providing greatly for the cities. Due to the abject poverty in which these peasants live, they feel the need to grow as many crops as they can, as often as they can. This depletes the health of the soil, making future crops sickly and weak. I propose the institution of growing cycles, whereby a time is allowed for the land to renew itself. I have sent a copy of my proposal to the Imperial City, where I hope that it will gain the attention of the Minister of Agriculture.</string>
  <string id="93300">Can you blame him for his suspicion? You were one of them.</string>
  <string id="93301">You shouldn&apos;t have to. Zu is not an enemy, Sky.</string>
  <string id="93304">Enough about the bounties.</string>
  <string id="93305">I want to talk to you about a criminal named Aishi the Mournful Blade.</string>
  <string id="93307">What if I told you she is in the city?</string>
  <string id="93310">What crimes has she committed?</string>
  <string id="93312">If I brought you proof that she was dead, would I collect that bounty?</string>
  <string id="93314">All I want is to know about her.</string>
  <string id="93315">What can you tell me about the city?</string>
  <string id="93318">Could I ask you for more specifics about these areas?</string>
  <string id="93319">Do you have any information on that criminal hunted by the Assassins?</string>
  <string id="93321">It sounds to me as if the Assassins are worried.</string>
  <string id="93322">Sounds like you&apos;re angling for a quick promotion.</string>
  <string id="93323">Is there a bounty on this &quot;Scourge of the South?&quot;</string>
  <string id="93325">I wonder if we&apos;re being told the whole story. Could this criminal be justified in their actions?</string>
  <string id="93327">That&apos;s enough about the Scourge of the South.</string>
  <string id="93328">I should go.</string>
  <string id="93329">I certainly do. That&apos;s Yukong right over there.</string>
  <string id="93332">Why would you think that?</string>
  <string id="93334">I might be, for the right price.</string>
  <string id="93336">You assume I&apos;m a common mercenary?</string>
  <string id="93339">What criminals do you need help with?</string>
  <string id="93341">It sounds like these mercenaries have just forfeited their job to me.</string>
  <string id="93342">Sounds like you&apos;re out of luck. Goodbye.</string>
  <string id="93346">Before she died, she told me a most interesting story about you.</string>
  <string id="93352">For an opponent that dangerous, I expect a generous bounty.</string>
  <string id="93355" soundid="145807">I don&apos;t think we&apos;re alone. Something does not rest easy.</string>
  <string id="93358" soundid="145810">Do... do you feel that? Something is here. Something that hates the living!</string>
  <string id="93359">Jade Heart</string>
  <string id="93366">Why was nothing done to catch her earlier?</string>
  <string id="93368">Could I see the scene of the crime?</string>
  <string id="93370">What could she tell me?</string>
  <string id="93686" soundid="146236">The safe bet&apos;s on both of those being true. I don&apos;t think you&apos;ll have any trouble catching the attention of the Inquisitors.</string>
  <string id="93687" soundid="146237">It&apos;s clear that they don&apos;t know your real identity, and your skills are obvious</string>
  <string id="93688" soundid="146238">No... I&apos;m sure they have no idea of your real identity. I wouldn&apos;t worry about that.</string>
  <string id="93689" soundid="146239">I didn&apos;t mean to upset you. I was just making an observation. Let&apos;s go meet this Inquisitor.</string>
  <string id="93690" soundid="167914">We need to keep at our practices. Some of us don&apos;t believe in cheating during our matches; we want to win honestly.</string>
  <string id="93691" soundid="146241">Let&apos;s get back to the Dragonfly. If we hurry, we can have a couple drinks before this other guy shows up.</string>
  <string id="93692" soundid="146242">Well, we got what we wanted. I just hope you know what you&apos;re getting into. We should head back to the Dragonfly and let the others know what&apos;s happening.</string>
  <string id="93693" soundid="146243">You got the chance you wanted. No sense wasting it by showing up late. Let&apos;s head back to the Dragonfly.</string>
  <string id="93694" soundid="146244">We should get back to the Dragonfly. If we&apos;re late, the Inquisitor might get angry, and then he might not help us at all.</string>
  <string id="93695" soundid="146245">Well, you&apos;ve got what you wanted. I don&apos;t approve of this course, but if you want to deal with the Inquisitors you better not be late for this meeting. Let&apos;s go.</string>
  <string id="93697" soundid="146247">Nobody here suspects me to be anything but an overzealous scholar, and I&apos;d like to keep it that way. So, you want to know about the recruiter?</string>
  <string id="93698" soundid="146248">You have a flying machine, do you not? Yes, I know about that. Go back to the landing area and someone will meet you there.</string>
  <string id="93699" soundid="146249">The location is public, yet relatively private. Common folk are not welcome on the landing area, so there will be no crowds to hide spies... or an ambush.</string>
  <string id="93700" soundid="146250">If the Lotus Assassins wanted you dead, your life would be over before you even knew you were in danger. </string>
  <string id="93701" soundid="146251">I don&apos;t think so. I&apos;ve already told you what you need to know. I&apos;m not about to risk being discovered just to make you feel at ease.</string>
  <string id="93702" soundid="146252">He already knows, I&apos;m sure. Now go, I will not speak to you about this any further.</string>
  <string id="93703" soundid="146253">They already know about you. That means one of two things. Either the Princess is exceptionally good at spreading rumors, or they&apos;re desperate for new people.</string>
  <string id="93706">Why should we meet there?</string>
  <string id="93707">How do I know this isn&apos;t a trap?</string>
  <string id="93708">I want to ask you some questions.</string>
  <string id="93710">Tell the Inquisitor recruiter I&apos;ll be there.</string>
  <string id="93713">What makes you so sure?</string>
  <string id="93715">I just hope I don&apos;t draw too much attention.</string>
  <string id="93717">If I wanted your opinion about this out here in the open, I&apos;d have asked.</string>
  <string id="93719" soundid="167915">After hearing about the way you dealt with those bandits, we wanted to make sure we were ready if they ever came again.</string>
  <string id="93725">Captain Sen</string>
  <string id="93743">Bandit Camp</string>
  <string id="93750" soundid="152351">You&apos;re going to rescue Master Li. I know you&apos;ll find a way, but still....</string>
  <string id="93753" soundid="146358">[Success] True. You are more reasonable than I would have suspected from my first impression.</string>
  <string id="93754" soundid="146359">[Success] That I could tell instantly. You carry yourself with confidence born of skill. Perhaps a talk would be good before our confrontation.</string>
  <string id="93755" soundid="146360">[Success] Hmm. That it is, and who am I to be selective about who hears my tale?</string>
  <string id="93756" soundid="146361">Do you know anything of me? Anything of the terror that is Aishi the Mournful Blade?</string>
  <string id="93757" soundid="146362">[Failure] You are meant to face me, not to listen to me. Listening is not in your nature, and so I will not force my history on you.</string>
  <string id="93758" soundid="146363">Let us see who proves the stronger.</string>
  <string id="93759" soundid="146364">You should.</string>
  <string id="93760" soundid="146365">&quot;If we help him, he&apos;ll only tell the others what we&apos;ve done. We have to let him go.&quot; Simple words, but they still echo in my head, even now.</string>
  <string id="93761" soundid="146366">Nights are worse. I can&apos;t sleep for the screams of that boy as he washed away; I still hear them to this day.</string>
  <string id="93762">An old man told me you had a story to tell.</string>
  <string id="93764">I can&apos;t walk away from a potential bounty.</string>
  <string id="93766">You don&apos;t know what you&apos;re dealing with if you think you can threaten me.</string>
  <string id="93768">That&apos;s a risk I&apos;m willing to take.</string>
  <string id="93776">Let&apos;s hear this tale of yours.</string>
  <string id="93777">I&apos;m not here to talk to a murderer.</string>
  <string id="93779">I would like to hear your tale.</string>
  <string id="93780">[Charm] How many would have let you talk this long?</string>
  <string id="93782">[Intimidation] If you know me as well as you claim to, you know our fight will not be easy.</string>
  <string id="93784">[Intuition] I think this is a story you want to be heard.</string>
  <string id="93787">If you&apos;re done analyzing me, I have a bounty to collect.</string>
  <string id="93788">I should just leave you alone.</string>
  <string id="93790">I don&apos;t know if it was really your fault.</string>
  <string id="93795">Dock</string>
  <string id="93796">Ru&apos;s Barge</string>
  <string id="93797">Captain Sen was the young man you were in love with?</string>
  <string id="93799">He is a powerful man. How do you plan to attack him?</string>
  <string id="93802">Why do you care about this? Aren&apos;t you a heartless criminal?</string>
  <string id="93804">If what you say is true, Sen deserves what&apos;s coming to him.</string>
  <string id="93805">I&apos;m going to take you to Sen. We&apos;ll see how he reacts.</string>
  <string id="93807">Touching story. Really, it was. Sadly, it&apos;s also over. Time to die.</string>
  <string id="93810">Just walk away. You deserve your peace.</string>
  <string id="93812">I&apos;m ready when you are.</string>
  <string id="93814">I wasn&apos;t going to let you go without my bounty.</string>
  <string id="93816" soundid="146423">There is another in this city with a price on her head. A richer price than those two.</string>
  <string id="93817" soundid="146424">Her name is Aishi the Mournful Blade, and you can find her at the Black Leopard School.</string>
  <string id="93818" soundid="146425">I watched her walk into this city, and now I tell you. There&apos;s no mystery in this.</string>
  <string id="93819" soundid="146426">She is accused of most crimes, and several had to be invented to account for her actions. She is a terror upon the face of the Empire.</string>
  <string id="93820" soundid="146427">Murder, theft, and worse, yet never a smile or a hint of revelry in what she did. That is why she is known as Aishi the Mournful Blade.</string>
  <string id="93821" soundid="146428">It is across the river and at the far end of the Market District. A grassy path leads up, away from the noise of the city.</string>
  <string id="93822" soundid="146429">Atop the hill lies the Black Leopard School, and within, Aishi. She is waiting for someone to come find her, I think.</string>
  <string id="93823" soundid="146430">Because I want you to know. My role in this matter is of no concern to you. I am simply an old man who sees a chance for some good to come from bad.</string>
  <string id="93824" soundid="146431">I&apos;ve heard of this Aishi. She&apos;s reputed to be deadly and merciless, yet cloaked with deep sadness.</string>
  <string id="93825" soundid="146432">This Aishi sounds like my kind of woman!</string>
  <string id="93826" soundid="146433">We shouldn&apos;t let a criminal run free. Something tells me that there&apos;s more to this story than this man&apos;s telling us, though.</string>
  <string id="93827" soundid="146434">When you reach her, you should ask her for her story. She has a most interesting tale to share.</string>
  <string id="93828" soundid="146435">I hoped it would end this way. She may have found some peace.</string>
  <string id="93829" soundid="146436">Here, take this. It&apos;s something Aishi would have wanted you to have, I think. I hate for a good deed to go unrewarded.</string>
  <string id="93830" soundid="146437">Ha! There&apos;s little reward in a good deed, and just the opposite for those who walk the low path. I know that better than most.</string>
  <string id="93831" soundid="146438">Aishi the Mournful Blade was my daughter.</string>
  <string id="93832" soundid="146439">My daughter&apos;s life was nothing but pain. Her crimes were a way to forget, for a while.</string>
  <string id="93833" soundid="146440">Wait, he&apos;s... he&apos;s dead! He&apos;s a ghost, but his will is so strong I couldn&apos;t tell until just now!</string>
  <string id="93834" soundid="146441">I think she must have found some peace now, and I can finally rest. It has been too long since I turned away from the Water Dragon&apos;s embrace.</string>
  <string id="93835" soundid="146442">You couldn&apos;t tell? A Spirit Monk? Ahh, but you are not fully trained, and I have refused to let any part of myself slip away.</string>
  <string id="93836" soundid="146443">Some things are stronger than anger, Spirit Monk. Love is one of them.</string>
  <string id="93837" soundid="146444">I know that, Spirit Monk, but I am a patient man, and I refuse to let myself slip away.</string>
  <string id="93838" soundid="146445">I have some idea of what you face. Take my best wishes as you try to set things right.</string>
  <string id="93839" soundid="146446">I have waited more than two decades. I can wait a bit more, and now... now I have a reason to smile.</string>
  <string id="93843">How do you know where a criminal can be found?</string>
  <string id="93844">What is this Aishi accused of?</string>
  <string id="93846">Where is the Black Leopard School?</string>
  <string id="93848">Why are you telling me this?</string>
  <string id="93849">Thank you for the information. You can go.</string>
  <string id="93854">Good deeds are their own reward.</string>
  <string id="93856">Thank you, but why?</string>
  <string id="93857">Who are you?</string>
  <string id="93858">Why did you tell me she was in the Imperial City?</string>
  <string id="93859">You turned her in. Some father.</string>
  <string id="93862">Turned away... wait, you&apos;re dead?</string>
  <string id="93864">If you&apos;re a ghost, why haven&apos;t you gone mad?</string>
  <string id="93865">How do you know about my heritage?</string>
  <string id="93866">What will you do next?</string>
  <string id="93869" soundid="146476">Don&apos;t you just love the Imperial Arena? No other place like it in all of the Jade Empire.</string>
  <string id="93870" soundid="146477">Hold on, you&apos;re Raging Dragon, aren&apos;t you? I&apos;ve heard all about you. It&apos;s a pleasure. I&apos;m Lady Rento.</string>
  <string id="93871" soundid="146478">Wait a moment! You&apos;re Silver Phoenix! How very nice to meet you. I&apos;m Lady Rento.</string>
  <string id="93872" soundid="146479">If it isn&apos;t Tiger Lifts the Mountain. How exciting to meet you! I am Lady Rento.</string>
  <string id="93873" soundid="146480">Were you looking for me? I&apos;m Lady Rento, and I was expecting someone sent by Captain Sen.</string>
  <string id="93874" soundid="146481">Hello again. What can I do for you?</string>
  <string id="93875" soundid="146482">Oh, poor Yukong. Captain Sen&apos;s still willing to do my husband&apos;s bidding and hunt him down, is he?</string>
  <string id="93876" soundid="146483">I swear, my husband is insufferable. Yukong&apos;s a harmless aspiring actor who asked me if I would act as his patron.</string>
  <string id="93877" soundid="146484">Since my husband was away from the city... again... I accepted and gave Yukong a moderate stipend. I thought he was charming.</string>
  <string id="93878" soundid="146485">That was how my husband presented the situation to the authorities. He didn&apos;t want to face the &quot;shame&quot; of supporting a humble actor.</string>
  <string id="93879" soundid="146486">My husband&apos;s a fool, but when he lowers his head, all I can do is let him charge and hope he rams something solid enough to slow him.</string>
  <string id="93880" soundid="146487">Probably less than my husband is putting forth as a bounty for poor Yukong. That young man doesn&apos;t deserve this.</string>
  <string id="93881" soundid="146488">I would wager that you&apos;ll find him in the Scholars&apos; Garden. Yukong was going to try out for that new play.</string>
  <string id="93882" soundid="146489">I&apos;m sure you heard about it when it was performed in the Golden Way. Made quite the impression, I&apos;m told.</string>
  <string id="93883" soundid="146490">It&apos;s going to be put on soon in the Golden Way, I&apos;m told. Should be exciting to watch.</string>
  <string id="93884" soundid="146491">Yukong was going to try out for a role as a scholar, so he may be using his costume to hide in the garden. He&apos;s not much of a scholar, so you should be able to spot him.</string>
  <string id="93885" soundid="146492">Oh, normally I would be happy to chat, but now really isn&apos;t the time.</string>
  <string id="93886" soundid="146493">I&apos;ve had a trying day and I just want to relax in the Heart of the Empire for a few minutes before I rush home to attend the family accounts.</string>
  <string id="93887" soundid="146494">My husband claims he has no head for figures, though I suspect he just has no back for work.</string>
  <string id="93888" soundid="146495">If you happen to find Creative Yukong, do go easy on him, would you?</string>
  <string id="93889" soundid="146496">The poor boy did nothing wrong, and my husband is being unusually cruel to him.</string>
  <string id="93890" soundid="146497">Thank you. I have so little time to take in the ambiance of this place.</string>
  <string id="93892">I&apos;m here to talk to you about Creative Yukong.</string>
  <string id="93895">Why is Yukong wanted for confidence schemes?</string>
  <string id="93897">How much did you give this actor?</string>
  <string id="93898">Do you have any idea where I could find Creative Yukong?</string>
  <string id="93902">Would you mind if I asked you a few questions?</string>
  <string id="93905">I should let you get back to what you were doing.</string>
  <string id="93907" soundid="150714">Chai Ka: You have drawn some attention, but their description lacks accuracy. What they have will not reveal you.</string>
  <string id="93908">Too much a fool to accept your fate.</string>
  <string id="93913" soundid="146520">Dancing pretty lights. There&apos;s fire in the air and fire inside. They scream like music.</string>
  <string id="93914" soundid="146521">You&apos;ll scream like a demon when Fading Moon puts the light inside of you.</string>
  <string id="93915" soundid="146522">There&apos;s more than that on my head. There&apos;s a crown of flame that burns all the time, even when it gets tighter!</string>
  <string id="93916" soundid="146523">None of us are alive anymore, not until the lights dance with us!</string>
  <string id="93917" soundid="146524">You don&apos;t get to leave. We have to dance like the pretty lights.</string>
  <string id="93918" soundid="146525">You&apos;ll scream like those maggot people, leeching off the Empire until they burn!</string>
  <string id="93919" soundid="146526">Dancing lights.</string>
  <string id="93920" soundid="146527">Leaping flames inside us all. Purity.</string>
  <string id="93921" soundid="146528">Climbing higher &apos;til all fall down!</string>
  <string id="93922" soundid="146529">Red to black to gray.</string>
  <string id="93924">You&apos;re Fading Moon? There&apos;s a bounty on your head.</string>
  <string id="93926">It&apos;s always harder when they&apos;re insane, I&apos;ll wager.</string>
  <string id="93928">Maybe I&apos;ll leave you to your &quot;lights.&quot;</string>
  <string id="94226">I can&apos;t hurt you?</string>
  <string id="94263">You were ordered to kill innocents? Why even consider it?</string>
  <string id="94264" soundid="146886">I have my reasons. For now I&apos;ll tell you this... it&apos;s a part of my life I wish I could forget. But no matter how much I drink, it stays with me.</string>
  <string id="94267" soundid="146889">Just keep clear of this place... that&apos;s what I wanted to tell you. It&apos;s rotten to the core... or at the top... or maybe at the core of the top. You know what I mean.</string>
  <string id="94268" soundid="146890">You don&apos;t need anything else from this place, so just stop here. You don&apos;t want to go any further... let&apos;s just leave it at that.</string>
  <string id="94269" soundid="146891">What? What do you want?</string>
  <string id="94270" soundid="146892">Tried that once, it didn&apos;t work out. Prefect Mu Hong pledged his daughter Meishan to me, after I cleared his district of bandits. She wasn&apos;t ugly, so I agreed.</string>
  <string id="94271" soundid="146893">The night of the wedding feast, I got more than a little drunk, and in the morning I woke up in the prefect&apos;s bed, next to the prefect&apos;s wife.</string>
  <string id="94272" soundid="146894">I got up and went to my bride&apos;s room, and there was strange man in her bed. I killed the bastard and was about to kill her when Meishan came into the room yelling!</string>
  <string id="94273" soundid="146895">Apparently, I had just killed her sister&apos;s husband and was about to kill her sister. I tried to tell her it was an honest mistake, but she wouldn&apos;t hear it.</string>
  <string id="94274" soundid="146896">The brother-in-law&apos;s family was pissed, and so was the prefect when he found out about his wife. They tried to subdue me, so they could send me to prison.</string>
  <string id="94275" soundid="146897">I killed them all swiftly. None of them suffered. Still, Meishan wouldn&apos;t leave with me; she kept crying and complaining about her family. Family life just isn&apos;t for me.</string>
  <string id="94276" soundid="146898">Whatever.</string>
  <string id="94277">Lost Spirit</string>
  <string id="94278" soundid="146900">I&apos;m a fighter, not a damn history book! No more stories. You&apos;ve got my fists and my axes, that&apos;s enough. Let&apos;s find someone to kill!</string>
  <string id="94279" soundid="146901">Not now, I&apos;m done talking about myself. Let&apos;s go do something fun... like kill someone.</string>
  <string id="94280" soundid="146902">Too much talking and thinking can be dangerous. I should know. I remember one cold winter I took a job clearing rats from a local monastery.</string>
  <string id="94281" soundid="146903">I was supposed to make sure the pests stayed out of the sacred pools, but hunting rats one at a time is boring work. So I had an idea, a way to catch &apos;em all at once.</string>
  <string id="94282" soundid="146904">I convinced the monks to give me some of their sacred wine, and I filled the sacred pools. I figured if I could get the rats drunk they&apos;d be so much easier to catch.</string>
  <string id="94283" soundid="146905">Nothing happened at first, so I helped myself to the wine. I passed out before the rats came. In the middle of the night I was woken up by screaming monks and fiery explosions.</string>
  <string id="94284" soundid="146906">It was just the rats. The poor furry buggers were just trying to get warm near the monk&apos;s fires after their swim in the wine! Not a good combination!</string>
  <string id="94285" soundid="146907">The monks wanted me gone. I might have deserved the blame, but the abbot insisted it was a sign from the gods and closed the monastery. See what happens when you think too much?</string>
  <string id="94286">The strong must rule, but simple murder is a waste.</string>
  <string id="94287" soundid="166940">It must be that young woman in blue. I saw her and thought, &quot;If anyone can help us, it&apos;s her.&quot;</string>
  <string id="94288" soundid="166941">The young woman in red, right? We should thank the heavens she came to our town, then.</string>
  <string id="94289" soundid="166942">It must be that woman in plum I&apos;ve seen around town! Well, thank the Emperor she arrived!</string>
  <string id="94292" soundid="166945">They say the dam will never close.</string>
  <string id="94293" soundid="146915">I always figured if I saw the Emperor it would be for my own execution. &apos;Course, the day&apos;s still young.</string>
  <string id="94294" soundid="146916">I just hope I get to meet the man who taught you how to fight. I&apos;ve never seen someone so small fight so well. First, we have to free him.</string>
  <string id="94295" soundid="146917">Let&apos;s get to the palace and give the Emperor a taste of real power! We&apos;ll have your master free in no time.</string>
  <string id="94296" soundid="146918">Well, the city has everything you could ever want. Fighting, money, wine, and... hmm... there was something else that people like, but I can&apos;t quite remember what it is.</string>
  <string id="94297" soundid="146919">Oh well, I&apos;m sure it&apos;ll come to me once I&apos;ve had a few bowls of wine. Let&apos;s get something to wet our tongues!</string>
  <string id="94298" soundid="146920">This is going to be fun. Those Lotus Assassins won&apos;t know what hit &apos;em. This might just be the most exciting day of my life.</string>
  <string id="94299" soundid="146921">You know, battles like this don&apos;t come along every day. We could very well die in there, cut up into small pieces, trying to fight off hundreds of enemies.</string>
  <string id="94300" soundid="146922">I&apos;m getting goose bumps just thinking about it. C&apos;mon... let&apos;s go to the fortress and have some fun.</string>
  <string id="94301" soundid="146923">These Lotus Assassins really aren&apos;t all that tough; they&apos;re just trained well. I&apos;ve seen men a lot tougher than this run scared from a fight, but not these guys.</string>
  <string id="94302" soundid="146924">They&apos;re like well-trained dogs, and just as dangerous... though they smell slightly better, and I&apos;m willing to bet they wouldn&apos;t taste as good over a plate of rice. </string>
  <string id="94303" soundid="146925">Damn it, now I&apos;m getting hungry... and thirsty. Let&apos;s get this finished so I can get something to drink.</string>
  <string id="94304" soundid="146926">I can&apos;t believe Silk Fox is the princess! Who&apos;d have thought a spoiled little emperor&apos;s daughter could fight like that? Her dad certainly brought her up right.</string>
  <string id="94305" soundid="146927">That&apos;s one way to make sure your little angel doesn&apos;t get despoiled by anyone... teach her how to kick a man&apos;s ass into his throat!</string>
  <string id="94306" soundid="146928">Speaking of kicking, you&apos;d better keep going if you&apos;re ever going to pass as a Lotus Assassin.</string>
  <string id="94307" soundid="146929">Nothing&apos;s changed since the last time you asked me. Unless I passed out... did I pass out? No... how could I? I haven&apos;t been drinking!</string>
  <string id="94308" soundid="156043">Some things are best kept a secret, and I tried to warn you. This is the last time, I promise.</string>
  <string id="94309" soundid="156044">My brother became the arena champion... the Raging Ox. They said he retired, but he didn&apos;t retire... he was killed. I should know; I&apos;m the one who killed him.</string>
  <string id="94310" soundid="156045">I&apos;ve killed hundreds, thousands of men. Death has no hold over me... even my brother&apos;s death.</string>
  <string id="94311" soundid="156046">I wanted nothing from this place. He would have kept his title if it wasn&apos;t for Kai Lan.</string>
  <string id="94312" soundid="156047">Raging Ox was one of Kai Lan&apos;s men... well, he wasn&apos;t always. Kai Lan approached me first, and when I turned him down, he went to my brother instead.</string>
  <string id="94313" soundid="156048">I&apos;m sure you know all about that, what with the Khana thing and all. I knew what was happening as soon as I saw her sway, but that&apos;s another secret I&apos;m keeping.</string>
  <string id="94314" soundid="156049">When Ox joined up with Kai Lan, I stopped getting good matches. Ox was fighting his way to becoming champion, and doing a little work for the Guild on the side.</string>
  <string id="94315" soundid="156050">He was so cocksure and wouldn&apos;t listen to his older brother. Once he fell in with Kai Lan, he stopped talking to me.</string>
  <string id="94316" soundid="156051">Soon, Ox became Kai Lan&apos;s enforcer and carried out his bidding. He&apos;d skulk around in robes so no one would know the arena champion was a common thug.</string>
  <string id="94317" soundid="156052">One night, I followed Ox back to Kai Lan&apos;s. I was drunk, and I was mad. I just wanted to tell Ox how dangerous Kai Lan was... convince him to leave.</string>
  <string id="94318" soundid="156053">But Kai Lan was there, he tried to interfere. I attacked him, and Ox tried to stop me. When it was over... Ox was dead, and my axe was covered in his blood.</string>
  <string id="94319" soundid="156054">I didn&apos;t do it on purpose. It was stupid... but it was an accident.</string>
  <string id="94320" soundid="156055">Kai Lan just stood there, smiling. I would have killed him if I wasn&apos;t so stunned.</string>
  <string id="94321" soundid="156056">After that, I left. For the first time in my life, I ran. I ran, and then I drank myself into a stupor that lasted for half a year.</string>
  <string id="94322" soundid="156057">Sometimes these things have to come out, or they&apos;ll kill you. Still, don&apos;t try to give me a hug, or I&apos;ll lop your head off.</string>
  <string id="94323" soundid="156058">You do what you have to in the arena. Just don&apos;t fool yourself about working with the Serpent.</string>
  <string id="94324" soundid="156059">Good idea. We&apos;ll leave Kai Lan to explain how Cho&apos;s body ended up in his room.</string>
  <string id="94325" soundid="156060">Lucky Cho&apos;s death just put you on the Serpent&apos;s wanted list. I&apos;d really like to see Kai Lan&apos;s face if you become arena champion. &apos;Course, I&apos;d rather just kill him.</string>
  <string id="94326">Innocents die. That is what they do. So what?</string>
  <string id="94327" soundid="156061">C&apos;mon. Let&apos;s go.</string>
  <string id="94328">Are you all right?</string>
  <string id="94332">Again you tease with secrets. Out with it!</string>
  <string id="94333">You claim knowledge but share nothing. I have no further interest in you.</string>
  <string id="94335">Kai Lan truly is a serpent.</string>
  <string id="94337">Enlighten me.</string>
  <string id="94338" soundid="146960"></string>
  <string id="94339" soundid="146961">I thought there&apos;d be more half-dressed serving girls with bowls of wine and food. What kind of Emperor doesn&apos;t have serving girls?</string>
  <string id="94340" soundid="146962">Let&apos;s get going. Maybe he keeps the good stuff farther in.</string>
  <string id="94341" soundid="146963"></string>
  <string id="94342" soundid="146964">Now what is it?</string>
  <string id="94343" soundid="146965">I&apos;ve already told you all I can. Besides, this is the time for battle, not words!</string>
  <string id="94344" soundid="146966">What? This isn&apos;t the time for stories... it&apos;s time to fight. Let&apos;s sharpen our blades instead of our tongues!</string>
  <string id="94345" soundid="146967">I never thought I&apos;d see the day when somebody would actually defy a god... and live. You&apos;ve got some spirit... and soon you&apos;ll have her spirit, too.</string>
  <string id="94346" soundid="146968">C&apos;mon, there&apos;s nothing stopping us now. Let&apos;s find that old bastard Li and give him a taste of his own medicine!</string>
  <string id="94347" soundid="146969">I&apos;m not sure what happened back there with the dragon, but one thing&apos;s for sure... Li&apos;s in for the fight of his life!</string>
  <string id="94348" soundid="146970">Never thought we&apos;d be back here again, and still no serving girls! These Sun brothers are a strange lot. C&apos;mon, let&apos;s find this dragon and be done with it.</string>
</tlk>