<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<tlk language="0">
  <string id="100175">Who was this enemy?</string>
  <string id="100176">The Assassins need a historian? That cannot be your only duty.</string>
  <string id="100178">Goodbye.</string>
  <string id="100179" soundid="154081">Stop right there, acolyte. I am well aware of what that... that... Lotus Expositioner records. Rumors and lies routinely turned over to Grand Inquisitor Jia.</string>
  <string id="100180" soundid="154082">If you wish to remain more than a footnote in her pages you will not speak to me again about her. The old fool will see my potential, and you will help me.</string>
  <string id="100181">I spoke with the Keeper of the Archive about you.</string>
  <string id="100183" soundid="154085">Right now is an interesting time for an organization known as The Guild. I have no doubt that Qui has told you about us if you didn&apos;t already know.</string>
  <string id="100184" soundid="154086">Our organization is involved in many different activities, most of which operate below the view of the authorities of this great Empire.</string>
  <string id="100185" soundid="154087">Come now. We are above calling each other names, aren&apos;t we?</string>
  <string id="100186" soundid="154088">I am suggesting that we align our goals for a time. An arrangement that could benefit us both.</string>
  <string id="100187" soundid="154089">The Guild, you see, has recently developed a vacancy in its upper ecehelons. A man by the name of Gao the Greater has been killed and with his death a new leader must be chosen.</string>
  <string id="100188" soundid="154090">I intend to replace him in that role, and I need good people to back me.</string>
  <string id="100189" soundid="154091">Did you? An interesting claim, and one I&apos;m not sure I believe. You don&apos;t match the descriptions we have of the killer, but then the descriptions are fairly... tenuous.</string>
  <string id="100190" soundid="154092">You knew him? Yet you aren&apos;t associated with our organization. The logical conclusion is that you are his killer.</string>
  <string id="100191" soundid="154093">If you are the one who killed Gao, then I owe you a favor. Consider my reluctance to turn you in to the Lotus Assassins a repayment of that debt in full.</string>
  <string id="100193">You&apos;re a bunch of criminals.</string>
  <string id="100195">Are you suggesting that I join you?</string>
  <string id="100198">You realize that I&apos;m the one who eliminated Gao the Greater?</string>
  <string id="100200">You want to be a pirate backing, slave trader with an arrogant dog of a son?</string>
  <string id="100203" soundid="154105">You seem at peace with the world now. I suppose... what you&apos;ve been through could do that to a person.</string>
  <string id="100204" soundid="154106">You&apos;re right. We&apos;re going to deal with Master Li; let&apos;s make sure it&apos;s for the right reasons.</string>
  <string id="100205" soundid="154107">It seems hard to hang on to anger right now, but we must still deal with your former master. He must pay for what he has done.</string>
  <string id="100206" soundid="154108">I agree with you, though, let&apos;s deal with him for the right reasons.</string>
  <string id="100207" soundid="154109">[Success] I suppose I wasn&apos;t. Even in my darkest rage, I wouldn&apos;t have said that.</string>
  <string id="100208" soundid="154110">[Success] I suppose I wasn&apos;t. Even in my darkest rage, I wouldn&apos;t have said that.</string>
  <string id="100209" soundid="154111">[Success] You&apos;re right... about everything. Anger makes me no better than your Master.</string>
  <string id="100210" soundid="154112">[Success] You&apos;re right... about everything. Anger makes me no better than your Master.</string>
  <string id="100211" soundid="154113">[Success] Pinmei. Damn, you&apos;re right. I&apos;d grown accustomed to seeing the world as a struggle, but what you say makes perfect sense.</string>
  <string id="100212" soundid="154114">[Success] Pinmei. Damn, you&apos;re right. I&apos;d grown accustomed to seeing the world as a struggle, but what you say makes perfect sense.</string>
  <string id="100213" soundid="154115">[Failure] I&apos;m sorry, I just can&apos;t get past what your Master has done, what he tried to take from us.</string>
  <string id="100214" soundid="154116">Just remember, some of the others may not see your goals in the same light. Dawn Star leaps to the front of my mind, but the others, as well.</string>
  <string id="100215" soundid="154117">The only thing that really matters is that you made it back to me. I knew even death wouldn&apos;t stop you, my last Spirit Monk.</string>
  <string id="100216" soundid="154118">If you can tell me, I want to hear all about it... in a bit.</string>
  <string id="100217" soundid="154119">No, I made that mistake once. Never again.</string>
  <string id="100218" soundid="154120">I never did say what I wanted to before the palace, you know?</string>
  <string id="100219" soundid="154121">You had the courage to say what I wanted to, but I wasn&apos;t able to reply. Not properly.</string>
  <string id="100220" soundid="154122">Actually, you did know, and you told me so, which was kind.</string>
  <string id="100221" soundid="154123">Of course you did. You even gave me a second chance to spit it out.</string>
  <string id="100222" soundid="154124">When I heard you were.... I knew I&apos;d missed my chance to tell you I had fallen in love with you.</string>
  <string id="100223" soundid="154125">I would never have expected this, but you and I... we&apos;re more than companions. I didn&apos;t get a chance to tell you that....</string>
  <string id="100224" soundid="154126">That you were in my every thought. That whenever I could, I kept you in my sight just to know you were there. That you had become everything.</string>
  <string id="100225" soundid="154127">When you fell, it was like a part of me shattered. I thought that piece would be broken forever, but... we have another chance. I love you, and I never want to let you go.</string>
  <string id="100226" soundid="154128">That I&apos;m in love with you? Gladly, but there&apos;s something we should do first. Come here.</string>
  <string id="100227" soundid="154129">I was just getting to that part, but as my lady wishes....</string>
  <string id="100228" soundid="154130">Absolutely.</string>
  <string id="100229" soundid="154131">It&apos;s quiet tonight. It won&apos;t last. Your Master has already unleashed his hounds.</string>
  <string id="100230" soundid="154132">At least we got here first. I don&apos;t like to think of you walking out of that gate and into their arms.</string>
  <string id="100231" soundid="154133">I would need a dastardly clever plan to get you out of that.</string>
  <string id="100232" soundid="154134">The slaughter might have put Whirlwind to shame if I had to fight my way to you.</string>
  <string id="100233" soundid="154135">I thought about our discussion earlier. Remember, I was asking you about the future and what you wanted for yourself when all this was done?</string>
  <string id="100234" soundid="154136">You talked about starting a school and finding some peace there. It might seem strange, but I think you&apos;re the kind of person who would fight for that peace.</string>
  <string id="100235" soundid="154137">You wanted to learn more about your people, remember? That clicked when Dawn Star mentioned Dirge, and I knew you were fighting your way back.</string>
  <string id="100236" soundid="154138">You swore you wouldn&apos;t rest until you&apos;d destroyed those responsible for what had happened.</string>
  <string id="100237" soundid="154139">You were joking when you said you&apos;d try and settle down with some dashing rogue, but since then, you&apos;ve seemed more serious.</string>
  <string id="100238" soundid="154140">I remember you saying you wanted to rest after all this ended. Somehow, I suspected you wouldn&apos;t consider what happened the &quot;end.&quot;</string>
  <string id="100239" soundid="154141">When Dawn Star began having visions, I just knew that you were fighting your way back. What else could she be seeing?</string>
  <string id="100240" soundid="154142">So we followed, and here we are, with the new Emperor&apos;s army on the way. I don&apos;t know how we&apos;ll survive, but we&apos;ll find a way.</string>
  <string id="100241" soundid="154143">Since you&apos;ve... returned, you&apos;re stronger than you ever were before. There&apos;s no denying the truth of what you say.</string>
  <string id="100242" soundid="154144">You&apos;re so angry when you say that. There&apos;s no more hope for your Master in your eyes? I mean he must be stopped, but....</string>
  <string id="100243" soundid="154145">[Success] Then you shall have it. Sun Li will pay for trying to take you away from me.</string>
  <string id="100244" soundid="154146">[Success] You&apos;re right. If he would do that to his own student, then I can&apos;t imagine what he would do the Empire.</string>
  <string id="100245" soundid="154147">We will stop him, if it takes tearing his heart out.</string>
  <string id="100246" soundid="154148">[Success] You&apos;re right. He really was behind it all, wasn&apos;t he? Damn him. If only we&apos;d known. Oh well, this new Emperor will learn his lesson soon enough.</string>
  <string id="100247" soundid="154149">[Failure] I understand how you feel, but I won&apos;t give up hope for your Master just yet.</string>
  <string id="100248" soundid="154150">Whatever it takes. I&apos;ll be there with you until the end.</string>
  <string id="100249" soundid="154151">When we followed, I knew there was still a chance that you&apos;d come back for revenge.</string>
  <string id="100250" soundid="154152">When you&apos;re ready, I&apos;ll stand beside you. We will crush Emperor Li, and if you want his power, I will be there to help you take it.</string>
  <string id="100251" soundid="154153">I have noticed something different about you. No less skill or determination, but less of an edge.</string>
  <string id="100254">You seemed less surprised than the others when I stepped through.</string>
  <string id="100255">Why were you so sure I&apos;d be coming back?</string>
  <string id="100263">Forget survival. This is about making Sun Li pay for what he has done.</string>
  <string id="100265">[Charm] You and I have great things ahead of us, Sky, but I need your strength.</string>
  <string id="100267">[Intimidation] You don&apos;t care that he struck me down? I need your help to destroy him, Sky.</string>
  <string id="100270">[Intuition] He was behind everything, Sky. All the loss. I need you to harden your heart.</string>
  <string id="100273">There is a way, we just have to find it.</string>
  <string id="100274">No one else can stop Master Li, but I can&apos;t do it alone.</string>
  <string id="100277">Some things have changed. I&apos;m not that interested in power anymore.</string>
  <string id="100281">[Charm] You weren&apos;t like that when I met you, Sky.</string>
  <string id="100282">[Intimidation] I need you with me, Sky, not questioning me.</string>
  <string id="100283">[Intuition] Would your daughter want to hear you sounding like that? Let go of the anger.</string>
  <string id="100285">You&apos;re right, Sky. Neither of us can afford to forget what Sun Li has done.</string>
  <string id="100286">It&apos;s good to know I can trust you to help me, whatever happens.</string>
  <string id="100287">I&apos;m not sure how, but I&apos;ll find a way to tear my Master&apos;s heart from his chest.</string>
  <string id="100289">I did. It wasn&apos;t easy.</string>
  <string id="100291">That&apos;s all you have to say?</string>
  <string id="100300">I liked that. Say that again.</string>
  <string id="100301">You leave me no choice, Sky. I&apos;m going to have to kiss you now.</string>
  <string id="100302">Let&apos;s make sure we don&apos;t waste that chance.</string>
  <string id="100303">For tonight, let&apos;s forget about the army. We have some... catching up to do.</string>
  <string id="100304">We each have our path, Zu. I will listen when you are ready.</string>
  <string id="100305">There will be no one else able to assist. I am destined for this.</string>
  <string id="100306">Bah! You fear him, but I have skill you do not. I don&apos;t need to know anything else.</string>
  <string id="100307" soundid="154304">We will not allow you keep these people!</string>
  <string id="100308" soundid="154305">You can&apos;t be serious?</string>
  <string id="100309" soundid="154306">These people have done nothing!</string>
  <string id="100310" soundid="154307">You seriously contemplate this?</string>
  <string id="100317">The man leading the bandits seemed to know Master Li.</string>
  <string id="100320" soundid="154572">Lotus Assassins? It makes no sense. Why would they be here? It must have just been a bandit. You should really ask Master Li, though. Such things aren&apos;t mine to discuss.</string>
  <string id="100321" soundid="154318">You look to be worth about a silver and a half. What do we need to prove to you?</string>
  <string id="100323" soundid="154320">Do you think yourself worthy of making such a demand? What proof are you worthy of?</string>
  <string id="100324" soundid="154321">A foolish, foolish mistake. You have no idea.</string>
  <string id="100326" soundid="154488">He doesn&apos;t come close to Master Li&apos;s skill, but Smiling Mountain is good for the younger students. He pairs novices and more advanced students so we can learn.</string>
  <string id="100329" soundid="154326">You will not keep them this way!</string>
  <string id="100330" soundid="154327">These people are not cattle for you!</string>
  <string id="100331" soundid="154328">They are not animals for you to imprison!</string>
  <string id="100335" soundid="154332">He thinks it&apos;s too tough, but impossible odds make the best fights.</string>
  <string id="100337" soundid="154334">We won&apos;t allow you to use them this way!</string>
  <string id="100338" soundid="154335">It is not your place to decide for these people.</string>
  <string id="100339" soundid="154336">They will be free of your cages.</string>
  <string id="100340" soundid="154337">Yes, what do you have to say to that? You want to fight, right?</string>
  <string id="100341" soundid="154338">You&apos;d betray them this way?</string>
  <string id="100342" soundid="154339">Even fighting for themselves, at least they have a chance.</string>
  <string id="100351" soundid="154348">It would be no less than you deserve.</string>
  <string id="100352" soundid="154349">It is justice... of a sort.</string>
  <string id="100353" soundid="154350">I think they might even enjoy it.</string>
  <string id="100354" soundid="154351">A truly practical approach that most people I&apos;m sure find lacking.</string>
  <string id="100359" soundid="154356">If a man can&apos;t earn his own freedom, he does not deserve it.</string>
  <string id="100360" soundid="154357">Never doubt when someone gives their word.</string>
  <string id="100361" soundid="154358">The Lotus Assassins are not the only authority in the Empire.</string>
  <string id="100362" soundid="154359">We&apos;ll see what we can do.</string>
  <string id="100363" soundid="154360">Freedom cannot be given, it must be earned.</string>
  <string id="100364" soundid="154361">At least you&apos;ve managed to survive! There&apos;s always something to be thankful for!</string>
  <string id="100365" soundid="154362">This is heartless. Were you always like this and I didn&apos;t see it?</string>
  <string id="100366" soundid="154363">Giving them some chance is better than none... and our own mission needs attending to.</string>
  <string id="100367" soundid="154364">A man can ask no more than for the chance to fight for his own life.</string>
  <string id="100378">Keeper of the Archive</string>
  <string id="100381">For years you have been enslaved to the power of the Water Dragon, but now a flicker of hope exists to break free of enslavement as Death&apos;s Hand. You may be the youngest brother, but you were always a match for your siblings in battle.</string>
  <string id="100382" soundid="154379">I&apos;ll stop the little guys! The big one&apos;s yours!</string>
  <string id="100383" soundid="154380">Down!</string>
  <string id="100384" soundid="154381">There&apos;s no end to them! Just like my wife&apos;s cousins!</string>
  <string id="100385" soundid="154382">Keep your head down, bun man, I&apos;m killing things here!</string>
  <string id="100386" soundid="154383">You&apos;ll kill us if we don&apos;t get out of here soon!</string>
  <string id="100387" soundid="154384">Look! There! That&apos;s our only chance!</string>
  <string id="100388" soundid="154385">[Panting.]</string>
  <string id="100389" soundid="154386">[Panting.]</string>
  <string id="100397">Time to switch tactics.</string>
  <string id="100398">You haven&apos;t got what it takes!</string>
  <string id="100399">You&apos;re dealing with a veteran!</string>
  <string id="100400">I&apos;ve seen it all.</string>
  <string id="100401">This is my battlefield!</string>
  <string id="100402">Time for a lesson in warfare!</string>
  <string id="100403">This will hurt you more than me!</string>
  <string id="100408">Old dogs die hard!</string>
  <string id="100409">Damn, that stings!</string>
  <string id="100410">That&apos;s experience, kid!</string>
  <string id="100411">What? That blow did nothing?</string>
  <string id="100412">This arena is mine!</string>
  <string id="100413">Nothing can save you!</string>
  <string id="100414">I am the true champion!</string>
  <string id="100415">You will die screaming!</string>
  <string id="100422">You can&apos;t stop me.</string>
  <string id="100423">Poisoned? Me?</string>
  <string id="100424">[Evil laughter]</string>
  <string id="100425" soundid="154425">This will be a great tragedy!</string>
  <string id="100426" soundid="154426">The humanity of it all.</string>
  <string id="100427" soundid="154427">If only I could find a way to put things right!</string>
  <string id="100428" soundid="154428">I&apos;m ruined. I know I&apos;m ruined.</string>
  <string id="100429" soundid="154429">This will, er, go over very badly.</string>
  <string id="100438" soundid="154449">Oh, be fair. I may be the weapon master around here, but it&apos;s Master Li who really does the training. I help out, but he&apos;s the real reason you two are so good.</string>
  <string id="100442">Chapter 1</string>
  <string id="100449">I... I cannot face this!</string>
  <string id="100463" soundid="154476">If only I had had the time to study his techniques for a few years before you faced Crimson Khana!</string>
  <string id="100464" soundid="154477">The others might overlook what you have done or believe that Khana died of natural causes, but I will not!</string>
  <string id="100465" soundid="154478">I can&apos;t honestly say. Your meridians are pulsing with power, but there&apos;s something strange about your strength.</string>
  <string id="100466" soundid="154479">I don&apos;t know what it is about you, exactly, but I would say you have been trained like no other warrior in this place.</string>
  <string id="100469">What are you babbling about?</string>
  <string id="100472" soundid="154486">Should she prove her worth? No, she can defend it, or die.</string>
  <string id="100477">How has Smiling Mountain helped you train?</string>
  <string id="100480" soundid="154496">Wait, I know this.... Yes! It&apos;s Weapon, Martial, Support, Transformation and Magic.</string>
  <string id="100481" soundid="154497">Weapon and Martial styles are pretty self explanatory. Support styles allow you to paralyze, slow or otherwise hamper your foes.</string>
  <string id="100482" soundid="154498">Chi is our internal magical energy. Is that it? Yes, and we can use our Chi to hasten the healing process of superficial wounds.</string>
  <string id="100483" soundid="154499">Additionally, chi can be used to strengthen our blows making the most of each strike.</string>
  <string id="100484" soundid="154500">I&apos;m sure that&apos;s right. I can&apos;t channel my chi like you and Dawn Star yet, but one day!</string>
  <string id="100485" soundid="154501">Of his history? Nothing. He is supposed to be a great master, but I just arrived, so I know very little about him.</string>
  <string id="100486" soundid="154502">I wish I knew more, senior student, but that is all I can answer about our Master.</string>
  <string id="100487" soundid="154503">Oh good. I mean... yes, thank you, senior student, for the chance to answer your questions.</string>
  <string id="100488" soundid="154504">I&apos;m barely worthy, senior student. You&apos;ve shown me that already.</string>
  <string id="100489" soundid="154505">No! It&apos;s just that I feel that this is something to keep me occupied.</string>
  <string id="100490" soundid="154506">It is an honor to guard this gate, even if I worry that I might not be able to do more than cower behind it in times of trouble.</string>
  <string id="100491" soundid="154507">I... maybe I am. I can&apos;t seem to say anything right. I&apos;m sorry, senior student. I&apos;m clearly a failure.</string>
  <string id="100492" soundid="154508">No... that&apos;s... I simply meant that I was a burden to him. It seems all I can do is offend you, and you are considered the best here.</string>
  <string id="100493" soundid="154509">How quickly I fail when I&apos;ve barely begun. I&apos;m sorry, senior student.</string>
  <string id="100494">What are the main classifications of styles, student?</string>
  <string id="100496">How does your chi affect combat?</string>
  <string id="100499">What do you know of Master Li?</string>
  <string id="100501">That will be all, Student Si Pat.</string>
  <string id="100503">You consider this task a waste of time, do you?</string>
  <string id="100505">You will do fine, I&apos;m sure.</string>
  <string id="100506">Then you are too weak to be in this school?</string>
  <string id="100507">A worm like you dares to question Master Li&apos;s decisions?</string>
  <string id="100509" soundid="154526">At least we&apos;re hearing about bandits and not ghosts right now. Those ghost stories scare me.</string>
  <string id="100510" soundid="154527">If those bandits think we students won&apos;t protect the town, they&apos;re fools.</string>
  <string id="100511" soundid="154528">I hope Kia Min isn&apos;t too badly hurt. She&apos;s very nice.</string>
  <string id="100513">Master Li called the man on the beach an &quot;assassin.&quot; That mean anything to you?</string>
  <string id="100514">Acquire Your Weapon</string>
  <string id="100515">Gujin, the weapon master for your school, has a workshop in Two Rivers. Make your way out of the school via the gate and head for town.</string>
  <string id="100518" soundid="154535">It&apos;s a good thing we have Master Li here.</string>
  <string id="100519" soundid="166262">Oh, you... you are a friend of Dawn Star, right? I am looking for her.</string>
  <string id="100522" soundid="166263"></string>
  <string id="100524" soundid="154541">Radiant is dead... his time has passed. Now is the time for the living! Help me destroy him and I will make this school more powerful than ever before!</string>
  <string id="100525" soundid="154542">I&apos;m going to finish you off this time!</string>
  <string id="100526" soundid="154543">No, Third Brother. I have a much better use for you.</string>
  <string id="100527" soundid="154544">Master... no!</string>
  <string id="100528" soundid="154545">Now we will finish this!</string>
  <string id="100534" soundid="160772">Of course. I&apos;ll be glad to spar with you once you&apos;ve defeated Sixth Brother.</string>
  <string id="100535" soundid="162058">[The altar and statue serve to show students a real example of lessons otherwise presented abstractly in class. It has not seen use in some time.]</string>
  <string id="100536">I&apos;d like to spar with you now.</string>
  <string id="100537">You&apos;re nothing!</string>
  <string id="100538" soundid="154588">As you wish. Follow me.</string>
  <string id="100539">I&apos;d like to fight with you for now.</string>
  <string id="100543" soundid="154596">Zhong won&apos;t listen to me. If I can&apos;t get him home, I&apos;ll be ruined.</string>
  <string id="100544" soundid="154602">I... would not normally ask, but would you be interested in joining our school? It would be an honor to have someone of your skill.</string>
  <string id="100551" soundid="154609">You haven&apos;t accomplished nearly enough to warrant my attention. Maybe you&apos;ll be good enough... one day.</string>
  <string id="100552" soundid="154610">Ha! Master Smiling Hawk has given me new training. I&apos;ll enjoy watching you suffer!</string>
  <string id="100553" soundid="154611">You... you cheated. You can&apos;t beat me... I&apos;m... better than you!</string>
  <string id="100554" soundid="154612">Do not disgrace yourself further, Third Brother. Accept your defeat and learn from it.</string>
  <string id="100555" soundid="154613">This isn&apos;t over! You&apos;ll both pay for this!</string>
  <string id="100556">Your talk is cheap, Third Brother. Let&apos;s fight!</string>
  <string id="100557">We will see who the fool is soon enough.</string>
  <string id="100558">I will destroy you, Third Brother!</string>
  <string id="100564">You were desperate enough to ask me to find you a man. Tian&apos;s a man; what&apos;s the problem?</string>
  <string id="100565" soundid="197971"></string>
  <string id="100566" soundid="154624">Not yet, but word has it they&apos;re coming by river, so this might be where they land.</string>
  <string id="100567" soundid="154625">They&apos;re fools to land in the sight of the Emperor&apos;s statue. His glory will inspire us to fight back. Of course, in a pinch we could always drop him on a few of them.</string>
  <string id="100568">Any other sign of bandits down here?</string>
  <string id="100570" soundid="154630">[Closing the dam exhausted the power of the Jade Heart, disabling the enchantment that once controlled the mechanism.]</string>
  <string id="100571" soundid="154631">[The mechanism to open and close the dam is controlled by a powerful enchantment focused on the Jade Heart at its center.]</string>
  <string id="100572" soundid="154632">[You close the dam, unleashing a blast of magical energy from the Jade Heart.]</string>
  <string id="100573" soundid="154633"></string>
  <string id="100574" soundid="154634">[Removing the Jade Heart will break the enchantment controlling the dam, locking it in the open position. Once damaged, the controls will be beyond all repair.]</string>
  <string id="100575" soundid="154635">[You seize the Jade Heart, unleashing a blast of magical energy that destroys the controls beyond all hope of repair.]</string>
  <string id="100576" soundid="154636"></string>
  <string id="100577" soundid="154637">[You leave the controls alone.]</string>
  <string id="100578">[Close the dam.]</string>
  <string id="100580">[Remove the Jade Heart and disable the dam so it can never close.]</string>
  <string id="100581">[Remove the Jade Heart.]</string>
  <string id="100583">[Close the dam instead.]</string>
  <string id="100584">[Do nothing.]</string>
  <string id="100587" soundid="154662">The dam is downriver from this pathetic little town. When it is closed, the river flows more slowly. The water backs up and the level rises.</string>
  <string id="100588" soundid="154663">But since it was opened by--well, Sheng can&apos;t say, but you know who--the water has drained away, leaving the river nothing but a small trickle.</string>
  <string id="100589" soundid="154664">Closing the dam will slow the river once more, causing the water level to rise as the water backs up, saving the town and Minister Sheng&apos;s glorious career!</string>
  <string id="100590" soundid="154665">So now Minister Sheng must explain the laws of physics and nature to you? I am reduced to the role of simple tutor, but as I need your assisstance I shall answer your questions.</string>
  <string id="100591" soundid="154666">The dam is down river from this pustule of a town. When it was closed, it caused the flow of the river to slow. The water backed up and the level of the river rose.</string>
  <string id="100592" soundid="154667">Now, however, the dam is open and the water drains away, leaving the river nothing but a trickle in a bed of muck. This town is doomed... along with my political aspirations!</string>
  <string id="100593">How will closing the dam raise the river level?</string>
  <string id="100596">If the dam is open, why is the river so low?</string>
  <string id="100599">Enter Portal</string>
  <string id="100600">They shouldn&apos;t have to put up with that.</string>
  <string id="100601" soundid="154693">Another tradition I&apos;d rather see abolished.</string>
  <string id="100602" soundid="154694">You aren&apos;t honestly considering this, are you?</string>
  <string id="100603" soundid="154695">That&apos;s a generous offer. Lead roles pay fairly well.</string>
  <string id="100604" soundid="154696">I think you should do it. You&apos;d make a wonderful Lady Fourteen Flowers.</string>
  <string id="100609" soundid="154701">I shouldn&apos;t have enjoyed that as much as I did. Intellectual plays bore me to tears, but that was brilliant.</string>
  <string id="100610" soundid="154702">I&apos;ll admit, that was truly memorable.</string>
  <string id="100611" soundid="154703">At least we know you&apos;ll have something to fall back on if our other endeavors fail.</string>
  <string id="100612" soundid="154704">You continue to surprise me. I wouldn&apos;t have thought you the aspiring actor.</string>
  <string id="100617" soundid="154709">As promised, I will teach you a new style. Watch closely.</string>
  <string id="100619">I want to fight with you.</string>
  <string id="100620">Fine. Just give me my reward.</string>
  <string id="100622">Good bye.</string>
  <string id="100625">Look For Gems in the Quarry</string>
  <string id="100626" soundid="154719">He took my power, and Second Brother&apos;s too, he is at least my equal now, if not more. If First Brother tries to aid me, Smiling Hawk would steal his power too.</string>
  <string id="100627" soundid="154720">How would he explain it? How would he know I was dead, unless, of course, he had something do with it? To prove my death, he&apos;d have to implicate himself.</string>
  <string id="100628" soundid="154721">You see! This is the man you&apos;ve been following! He&apos;s only a ghost... he&apos;s not even alive anymore.</string>
  <string id="100629" soundid="154722">I think they can see that for themselves, Third Brother.</string>
  <string id="100630" soundid="154723">Have you decided to confess to my murder, Smiling Hawk, or are you just here to preside over another senseless death?</string>
  <string id="100631" soundid="154724">How dare you speak to Master Smiling Hawk that way! You will pay!</string>
  <string id="100632" soundid="154725">He was always too impetuous. No matter... I have a new assistant now. One I think you will find to be a much more difficult opponent.</string>
  <string id="100633" soundid="154726">You? You did this to First Brother? I never should have invited you here!</string>
  <string id="100634" soundid="154727">No! We won&apos;t let you harm Master Radiant!</string>
  <string id="100635" soundid="154728">I see I will have to deal with you myself. So be it.</string>
  <string id="100636">Why doesn&apos;t he just... finish you off?</string>
  <string id="100637">Why don&apos;t you kill him yourself?</string>
  <string id="100638">Why didn&apos;t Smiling Hawk just tell everyone you were dead?</string>
  <string id="100639">I will destroy the Smiling Hawk!</string>
  <string id="100640">Actually, I am a student.</string>
  <string id="100646">It&apos;s too late now, Radiant.</string>
  <string id="100647">Now you will pay for your mistake!</string>
  <string id="100648">You&apos;re right... you shouldn&apos;t have!</string>
  <string id="100649">Belly of Iron</string>
  <string id="100650">I decided to help Smiling Hawk instead.</string>
  <string id="100651">Smiling Hawk is right. You and Radiant are weak!</string>
  <string id="100652" soundid="154960">She came in, asked to meditate, and then killed the first person who came near her. She&apos;s either crazy or just very angry.</string>
  <string id="100653">What can you tell me about the woman near the shrine?</string>
  <string id="100654">I want to challenge you to a fight.</string>
  <string id="100655" soundid="154963">Very mysterious, and very deadly. She came in a while ago asking to use the shrine. Shortly after that, a man followed her... and died quickly by her sword.</string>
  <string id="100656">Tell me about the woman near the shrine.</string>
  <string id="100657">I&apos;d like challenge you to a fight.</string>
  <string id="100658" soundid="154966">I honestly don&apos;t know. She came here a short while ago seeking refuge. She wanted to use our shrine and to be left alone. I saw no harm in it, so I agreed.</string>
  <string id="100659" soundid="154967">The man lying there followed her in. When he went over to her she cut him down and then went back to her mediation.</string>
  <string id="100660" soundid="154968">The masters are content to let her be... for now. That&apos;s about all I can tell you. Is there anything else?</string>
  <string id="100661">Who is that woman over by the shrine?</string>
  <string id="100664">You matched my stance.</string>
  <string id="100665">Accept your retribution.</string>
  <string id="100666">You&apos;ll regret this day!</string>
  <string id="100667">Down you go!</string>
  <string id="100668">For honor&apos;s sake!</string>
  <string id="100669">How dare you?!</string>
  <string id="100670">I shall school you!</string>
  <string id="100675">I recover.</string>
  <string id="100676">My blood is impure.</string>
  <string id="100677">You were foolish to challenge me.</string>
  <string id="100684">That feels better.</string>
  <string id="100685">I feel sick.</string>
  <string id="100686">That&apos;ll show &apos;em!</string>
  <string id="100695">Mugger</string>
  <string id="100698">Mugger</string>
  <string id="100704" soundid="155073">I have to go... there must be another way. I have to find some way to help Songtao.</string>
  <string id="100705" soundid="155074">I can&apos;t speak now; I&apos;m trying to find a way to free Songtao.</string>
  <string id="100706">Zi Bao got away.</string>
  <string id="100708">You will regret this.</string>
  <string id="100709">You&apos;ll pay!</string>
  <string id="100710">Now I&apos;m angry! </string>
  <string id="100715">Much better.</string>
  <string id="100716">The blood burns!</string>
  <string id="100717">Be shamed!</string>
  <string id="100718">Die, coward.</string>
  <string id="100719">Die, dog.</string>
  <string id="100720">Die like a pig.</string>
  <string id="100721">Let&apos;s dance.</string>
  <string id="100722">I&apos;ll eliminate you.</string>
  <string id="100723">You&apos;re history.</string>
  <string id="100728">I&apos;m healed!</string>
  <string id="100729">I&apos;m... I&apos;m defiled!</string>
  <string id="100730">I bring death!</string>
  <string id="100741">My talents are wasted.</string>
  <string id="100742">You&apos;re barbeque.</string>
  <string id="100743">I&apos;ll break you.</string>
  <string id="100744">Die of shame.</string>
  <string id="100745">Die like a traitor.</string>
  <string id="100746">Die, garbage.</string>
  <string id="100747">For glory! </string>
  <string id="100752">I&apos;m better.</string>
  <string id="100753">Foul poison.</string>
  <string id="100754">Hah, you&apos;ve had it!</string>
  <string id="100759">My art has no effect!</string>
  <string id="100760">Fall, foul creature!</string>
  <string id="100761">Feel the pain!</string>
  <string id="100762">For the fallen!</string>
  <string id="100763">Graaah!</string>
  <string id="100764">I cannot lose!</string>
  <string id="100765">Pay attention.</string>
  <string id="100770">Ah, that&apos;s better.</string>
  <string id="100771">Poison?</string>
  <string id="100772">Despair, fool!</string>
  <string id="100775">Refreshing.</string>
  <string id="100776">My blood curdles!</string>
  <string id="100777">As it was meant to be!</string>
  <string id="100778">You blocked my attack!</string>
  <string id="100779" soundid="155176">Minister Sheng almost overslept! Judge Fang will be here any minute. Quick, out of the way! I want Fang to see me standing beside the honor gift when he enters.</string>
  <string id="100780">Fight!</string>
  <string id="100781" soundid="155178"></string>
  <string id="100782" soundid="155179">I bid you warm and humble greetings from Tien&apos;s Landing, oh great and honorable Judge. I&apos;m eager to present my report. I&apos;m sure you will find it most interesting.</string>
  <string id="100783" soundid="155180">What&apos;s that you have there for me, Sheng?</string>
  <string id="100784" soundid="155181">You have a keen and observant eye, mighty Fang. I have brought you a gift... a small token of my esteem for you.</string>
  <string id="100785">This is it!</string>
  <string id="100786">Now we see!</string>
  <string id="100787" soundid="155184">Turtle&apos;s eggs! What is the meaning of this, Sheng? You dare mock me with this... this... insult!</string>
  <string id="100788" soundid="155185">N-no... there must be some mistake....</string>
  <string id="100789" soundid="155186">I understand all too well, Sheng. These eggs are your way of getting back at me for assigning you to Tien&apos;s Landing. But *I* will have the last laugh, Sheng!</string>
  <string id="100790" soundid="155187">I banish you to Tien&apos;s Landing! Wait there until I summon you back to the Imperial City. It shouldn&apos;t take more than a decade... or two.</string>
  <string id="100791" soundid="155188">W-wait... Judge Fang... please, come back! I... I... no!!</string>
  <string id="100792" soundid="155189">You... you did this to me! You have disgraced Minister Sheng. I am doomed to remain trapped at my wretched post in Tien&apos;s Landing forever!</string>
  <string id="100793" soundid="155190">No... Minister Sheng will not accept this! Judge Fang has not heard my report yet. I will not return to Tien&apos;s Landing without giving my report!</string>
  <string id="100794" soundid="155191">I refuse to abandon the glories of the Imperial City. I simply won&apos;t leave. You can&apos;t make me. Nobody can! Minister Sheng will not be moved!</string>
  <string id="100796">More!</string>
  <string id="100798">Take this!</string>
  <string id="100803">My style is perfect!</string>
  <string id="100813">The what now?</string>
  <string id="100814">Perish, fool!</string>
  <string id="100815">Get over here.</string>
  <string id="100816">Fist meets face.</string>
  <string id="100817">One more for the road!</string>
  <string id="100818">Stand still, you!</string>
  <string id="100819">Hurry up and die!</string>
  <string id="100824">(Muffled belch)</string>
  <string id="100825">Wrong brew!</string>
  <string id="100826">That&apos;ll stain you.</string>
  <string id="100827" soundid="155241">You don&apos;t know anything about how the Imperial Arena works. Why don&apos;t you go find out?</string>
  <string id="100828" soundid="155242">Ha! I sounded like you when I first got here. Now I&apos;m finished for good. Learn about this fine Imperial Arena yourself, why don&apos;t you?</string>
  <string id="100829" soundid="155243">You think you&apos;re tough enough for the Imperial Arena, do you? Why not prove it. I&apos;ll never be allowed to fight in here again, that&apos;s for sure.</string>
  <string id="100830" soundid="155244">Guess my spot in the roster is yours if you want it. Go find Qui the Promoter if you think you can fill my shoes.</string>
  <string id="100831" soundid="155245">He&apos;s always upstairs in the third room over or so, and looking for new blood. I&apos;m taking what I have left from my winnings and leaving.</string>
  <string id="100832">What just happened?</string>
  <string id="100834">Sounds to me like you got what you deserved.</string>
  <string id="100836">You&apos;re going to take that? Get up there and stand up for yourself!</string>
  <string id="100838">Step away from me, mongrel. Your weakness disgusts me.</string>
  <string id="100872" soundid="155288">I can do no more.... I must fade. Pity those spirits that have grown twisted. You will come to know their pain when life leaves you.</string>
  <string id="100880">Outlaw</string>
  <string id="100883" soundid="155299">You should talk to the other fighters here, they&apos;ve been watching you and are getting nervous. Of course, I&apos;ll need more time than that for these preparations.</string>
  <string id="100884" soundid="155300">It&apos;s just a matter of preparing the proper documents. Why don&apos;t you kill the time by making your way out into the city? See the sights! Maybe visit the Golden Way or the Scholars&apos; Garden.</string>
  <string id="100885" soundid="155301">Actually, that reminds me: a woman was here watching your fight against Hapless Han. Dressed all in black and veiled. She seemed impressed with your preferance.</string>
  <string id="100886" soundid="155302">Just before she left, she told me to tell my new fighter that, &quot;she was still waiting to see you.&quot; She said you&apos;d know where. Sounds like quite the invitation!</string>
  <string id="100888" soundid="155304">Bai the Outcrier stands outside the arena and usually knows all sorts of interesting things that are pericollating in other parts of the city!</string>
  <string id="100889" soundid="155305">By the time you see some of the sights and get back here I should have things ready to go for your Bronze Division debut!</string>
  <string id="100890" soundid="155306">Your next fight? I&apos;d love to, but I&apos;m still arranging the details of your entry into the Bronze Division.</string>
  <string id="100891" soundid="155307">Besides, didn&apos;t you have some mysterious lady in black looking to meet you? Hardly an invitation I&apos;d turn down!</string>
  <string id="100892" soundid="155308">Go on and get some fresh air. Go see the Golden Way, pester the scholars or even bother the students at the Black Leopard School! I still need a bit more time to arrange things.</string>
  <string id="100894">What kind of preparations?</string>
  <string id="100895">I can&apos;t fight now?</string>
  <string id="101006" soundid="155434">They attacked and were overmatched. If I let them go, they might return a greater threat. You must know this simple tactic; I&apos;ve seen you training in your village.</string>
  <string id="101007">You fought without mercy. Why should I trust you?</string>
  <string id="101101" soundid="188173"></string>
  <string id="101102">Kin was made Death&apos;s Hand after you abandoned him. I&apos;ll restore his true self!</string>
  <string id="101108" soundid="155538">You might also want to keep an eye out for some small shrines that are scattered about the forest. Some of them are said to react to magic or charges of chi.</string>
  <string id="101109" soundid="155539">It is said that these shrines react when users of chi focus their inner magics upon them. They light the path for pilgrims in the darkest nights.</string>
  <string id="101110" soundid="155540">The ghosts in this forest seem to shy away from the light. It&apos;s possible that these shrines might drive them away for a time, or possibly weaken them.</string>
  <string id="101112">What is the purpose of these shrines you mentioned?</string>
  <string id="101114" soundid="155558">Talk to my acolytes at their stations in the golem press room and the Soul Extractor. These are dangerous machines, find a sharp corner Shin can crack his temple on.</string>
  <string id="101115" soundid="155559">I seen no movement in your plan to distract the press operator, clear the hall of witnesses, and stop the slave shipment arriving from outside in the Necropolis.</string>
  <string id="101116" soundid="155560">Only after all that is done will Shin be vulnerable. Of course, I cannot be involved.</string>
  <string id="101117">You found Dawn Star in discussion with Gao the Lesser, who was his usual arrogant self. Having already heard about the bandits from Master Li, Dawn Star has joined you to aid with the defense of the town.</string>
  <string id="101120">Let&apos;s talk about the plan to kill Shin.</string>
  <string id="101124">You have slain Miss Chan and her spirit no longer roams the Necropolis. Surely Shen will give you a reward for ridding him of this problem.</string>
  <string id="101125">You have slain Miss Chan and her spirit no longer roams the Necropolis.</string>
  <string id="101126">Miss Chan at Peace</string>
  <string id="101127">Return to Shen and tell him Miss Chan is at peace.</string>
  <string id="101128">You have reunited the ghost of Miss Chan with that of her son. They both now rest in peace. Surely Shen will give you that reward now for ridding him of this problem.</string>
  <string id="101129">You have reunited the ghost of Miss Chan with that of her son. They both now rest in peace.</string>
  <string id="101130">Put Merchant Bai to Rest</string>
  <string id="101131">Bring peace to Merchant Bai.</string>
  <string id="101132">Merchant Bai will not rest easy in his grave, convinced that he is being tormented even in death.</string>
  <string id="101134">Defeat Bai&apos;s Tormentors</string>
  <string id="101135">Defeat the ghosts that torment Merchant Bai.</string>
  <string id="101136">Merchant Bai is being tormented by the ghosts of the two brothers that killed him in life. Apparently they were buried in the Necropolis, as well, and they have risen to torment him. He cannot rest in his fear and anguish. He says you can find them in an underground tomb immediately to the south.</string>
  <string id="101138">Return to Merchant Bai</string>
  <string id="101139">Return to Merchant Bai with news that you have defeated his tormenters.</string>
  <string id="101140">You have defeated the ghosts of the brothers who tormented Merchant Bai. Return to him so that you can put his spirit to rest.</string>
  <string id="101142">Return to Shen</string>
  <string id="101143">Return to Shen and tell him that Merchant Bai rests in peace.</string>
  <string id="101144">Return to Shen and tell him that you have brought peace to Merchant Bai. Surely he will give you a reward for relieving him of this problem.</string>
  <string id="101145">You have brought peace to Merchant Bai and calmed his spirit.</string>
  <string id="101146">Return to Shen</string>
  <string id="101147">Return to Shen and tell him that Merchant Bai has been banished.</string>
  <string id="101148">You have banished the Spirit of Merchant Bai. Return to Shen and tell him about this so that he can reward you for getting rid of this problem.</string>
  <string id="101149">You have put down the agitated ghost of Merchant Bai. He won&apos;t roam the Necropolis anymore.</string>
  <string id="101150">Vengeance Served Cold</string>
  <string id="101151">Bring peace to Mister Ren.</string>
  <string id="101152">You have encountered the spirit of Mister Ren, who has sworn vengeance against his wife, Ren Feng. He does not seem to be able to rest until this vengeance is carried out.</string>
  <string id="101154">A Misunderstanding</string>
  <string id="101155">Bring peace to Mister Ren.</string>
  <string id="101156">You have spoken to Ren Feng, the wife of the poisoned Mister Ren. She claims that the poisoning which led to his death was accidental, and that it was just some bad fish she bought. It is doubtful that Mister Ren will believe this.</string>
  <string id="101158">Vengeance is Served</string>
  <string id="101159">Return to Mister Ren with news of his wife&apos;s death.</string>
  <string id="101160">You have killed Ren Feng, the woman Mister Ren says poisoned and murdered him. With this news, his spirit should be able to lie peaceful once more.</string>
  <string id="101161">With Ren Feng dead, Mister Ren should be able to lie peaceful once more.</string>
  <string id="101162">Return to Mister Ren</string>
  <string id="101163">Return with Ren Feng to Mister Ren&apos;s ghost.</string>
  <string id="101164">Mister Ren wouldn&apos;t believe his wife&apos;s innocence unless he heard it from her own mouth. Bring her back to him, and help her explain that his death was an accident.</string>
  <string id="101166">Return to Shen</string>
  <string id="101167">Return to Shen and tell him that Mister Ren lies peacefully once more.</string>
  <string id="101168">Return to Shen and tell him that Mister Ren&apos;s ghost lies peacefully and won&apos;t trouble him again. He should give you the reward that he has promised you.</string>
  <string id="101169">Mister Ren&apos;s ghost lies peacefully and won&apos;t rise again.</string>
  <string id="101170">Return to Shen</string>
  <string id="101171">Return to Shen and tell him that Mister Ren has been banished.</string>
  <string id="101172">The ghost of Mister Ren has been banished for good. Go back to Shen and tell him to collect the reward he promised you.</string>
  <string id="101173">Mister Ren&apos;s ghost has been put down and won&apos;t be causing any more trouble.</string>
  <string id="101174">Return to Shen</string>
  <string id="101175">Return to Shen and tell him that Mister Ren has been banished... and of his wife&apos;s untimely death.</string>
  <string id="101176">Mister Ren has been banished for good, and his annoying wife silenced as well. Mister Ren won&apos;t be coming back, and Ren Feng could be safely tossed in a discrete pit somewhere. Return and get your reward from Shen, and hope he doesn&apos;t charge you for the extra burial.</string>
  <string id="101177">Mister Ren has been banished for good, and his annoying wife was silenced, as well. Mister Ren won&apos;t be coming back, and Ren Feng can be safely tossed in a discrete pit somewhere.</string>
  <string id="101178">Vengeance Served Cold</string>
  <string id="101179">Bring peace to Mister Ren.</string>
  <string id="101180">The spirit of Mister Ren cannot rest as long as he has sworn vengeance against his wife, Ren Feng, who poisoned and killed him. He says that she lives in the Market District near the entrance to the Black Leopard School.</string>
  <string id="101182">The Operation Successful</string>
  <string id="101184">The operation was successful, and Wen Zhi&apos;s daughter has been saved. The operation had complications, but it seems that everything has turned out all right. His daughter seems to be recovering well.</string>
  <string id="101185">The operation was successful, and Wen Zhi&apos;s daughter has been saved. The operation had complications, but it seems that everything has turned out all right. His daughter seems to be recovering well.</string>
  <string id="101186">The Operation Successful</string>
  <string id="101188">Dr. An&apos;s transplant was successful, and Wen Zhi&apos;s daughter was saved using the liver her father donated. Dr. An has taken the girl as her student, and the girl is recovering well.</string>
  <string id="101189">Dr. An&apos;s transplant was successful, and Wen Zhi&apos;s daughter was saved using the liver her father donated. Dr. An has taken the girl as her student, and the girl is recovering well.</string>
  <string id="101190">Return the Elder to his Grave</string>
  <string id="101191">Find the Elder Tanner Fong and return him to his grave in the Necropolis. According to his son, he&apos;s &quot;invaded&quot; the family home.</string>
  <string id="101192">Shen has told you that the corpse of the Elder Tanner Fong has risen from its grave and wandered off, returning to his home. His son, who inherited the home, is none too pleased. He wants a refund or the corpse gone, and Shen doesn&apos;t like refunds.</string>
  <string id="101194">Remove the Elder</string>
  <string id="101195">Stop the Elder Tanner Fong&apos;s hauntings of his family home in the Market District.</string>
  <string id="101196">You spoke to the Younger Tanner Fong, who owns the property now. He wants you to get rid of the corpse of his father as quickly as possible. He&apos;ll even give you a reward for its quick disposal.</string>
  <string id="101198">The Tanners&apos; Problem</string>
  <string id="101199">Resolve the Elder Tanner Fong&apos;s problem.</string>
  <string id="101200">The Elder Tanner Fong isn&apos;t dead! His greedy son buried him while he was in a deep sleep. Now he&apos;s believed to be a ghost, and no one will come near him. The only place he has left is his home. He wants you to help him reclaim his life and confront his son.</string>
  <string id="101203">Exiled</string>
  <string id="101206">The Elder Tanner Fong has been taken in by Shen and put to work digging graves in the Necropolis. At least he&apos;ll have a few more years of productivity before he really does die.</string>
  <string id="101207">Talk to Younger Tanner Fong</string>
  <string id="101208">Speak to Younger Tanner Fong about his father&apos;s death.</string>
  <string id="101209">You have eliminated the problem by eliminating Elder Tanner Fong. His son will likely be happy with the news.</string>
  <string id="101210">With the Elder Tanner Fong no longer disputing his status as deceased, his son happily left you with a reward and then quickly hurried away.</string>
  <string id="101211">Finish Them</string>
  <string id="101212">Against foes like these, your victory should be flawless.</string>
  <string id="101213">Perhaps tired of dealing with the questions of life and death, you&apos;ve decided to take matters into your own hand.</string>
  <string id="101214">&quot;Violence only begets more violence,&quot; say the philosophers. You dealt with the Fong family problem decisively.</string>
  <string id="101217" soundid="197864">Your followers will occupy the Lotus Assassins while you challenge the Emperor in the throne room.</string>
  <string id="101220">This weapon does a large amount of damage over time. The Chi cost for Firestorm is high.</string>
  <string id="101221">These magical projectiles have the uncanny ability to track enemy ships. Each missile uses a very small amount of Chi.</string>
  <string id="101222">A temporary shield that absorbs and inflicts a moderate amount of damage. The Chi cost for Radiant Aura is moderate.</string>
  <string id="101223">This weapon produces a powerful shockwave that does moderate damage to all nearby enemy ships. The Chi cost for Tremor is moderate.</string>
  <string id="101224">This powerful weapon releases a blast that will destroy all nearby enemy ships. The Chi cost for Dragon&apos;s Wrath is extremely high.</string>
  <string id="101232" soundid="155718">Go and give the documents to Prefect Jitong. Free Chandler Ling and he will reward you.</string>
  <string id="101251">On second thought, you have to die.</string>
  <string id="101252">Talk to Soldier</string>
  <string id="101253">Soldier won&apos;t be happy that General Kao walked away unharmed, but you&apos;ll have to tell him before he&apos;ll let Qui start the fight.</string>
  <string id="101255">Soldier was irate that General Kao was allowed to walk away unharmed, but he has informed Qui that he is ready to face you.</string>
  <string id="101256" soundid="155754">This area is forbidden. Only Gao himself is allowed to enter. You must be destroyed!</string>
  <string id="101257" soundid="155755">I am Xianshi, the great elephant demon! Gao&apos;s infernal magic summoned me and bound me here to guard this room.</string>
  <string id="101258" soundid="155756">The penalty for all who enter is death. Gao&apos;s power compels me.... I must destroy you!</string>
  <string id="101259" soundid="155757">Nor I you, but the power of Gao&apos;s magic compels me. He summoned me to this place and bound me to guard this chamber.</string>
  <string id="101260" soundid="155758">The penalty for all who enter is death. I, Xianshi the great elephant demon, must crush you!</string>
  <string id="101261" soundid="155759">You lie, mortal. This place is the domain of Gao. Not even the Lotus Assassins know about it. He did not send you! </string>
  <string id="101262" soundid="155760">I will crush you!</string>
  <string id="101263">What are you?</string>
  <string id="101266">I have no quarrel with you.</string>
  <string id="101268" soundid="156391">It&apos;s Gang&apos;s acolyte. The one who dared to kill acolytes under your care, Master Shin.</string>
  <string id="101269">Uh... it&apos;s okay. Gao sent me.</string>
  <string id="101270">Prepare to die, demon!</string>
  <string id="101271" soundid="155769">Return to me when you have an idea for an appropriate accident. I don&apos;t care what it is, as long as there is a corpse for me to gloat over in the end.</string>
  <string id="101272" soundid="155770">No, that&apos;s not it. If he disappears, there is no message sent to my enemies. He must be made to look foolish. Find something else. Perhaps in the press room.</string>
  <string id="101273" soundid="155771">To succeed, everything must be in place. The hall cleared of all witnesses, the press operator distracted, and the slave shipment stopped outside in the Necropolis.</string>
  <string id="101274" soundid="155772">When all three of these are completed, Shin will be vulnerable. Killing him in the hall and transporting him to the press was a very good idea.</string>
  <string id="101275" soundid="155773">You need to get all of the witnesses out of the hall. Suspecting he was killed is fine, but if they actually see you doing it, my superiors will have to act.</string>
  <string id="101277">I examined the extractor. It could kill Shin, but it leaves no corpse.</string>
  <string id="101278">I have stopped the slave shipment from reaching the fortress.</string>
  <string id="101279">The press operator has been convinced to leave his station.</string>
  <string id="101280">I have cleared the hall of witnesses.</string>
  <string id="101281">I have stopped the slave shipment and the press operator is gone.</string>
  <string id="101282">I have stopped the slave shipment and the hall is clear of witnesses.</string>
  <string id="101283">The hall is clear of witnesses and the press operator is gone.</string>
  <string id="101285">I cleared some of the potential witnesses from the hall.</string>
  <string id="101367">According to the Rat Demon, there is some sort of powerful essence gem in the ruins of old Tien&apos;s Landing. Now you just have to find it.</string>
  <string id="101369">Lotus Assassins are using rat demons to find gems. One of the rat demons said he could feel a gem nearby, in the ruins.</string>
  <string id="101370">Find Dragon Powder and Rockets</string>
  <string id="101371" soundid="155888">I saw what you did to Third Brother. If you can beat him, I&apos;m not even going to try to fight you.</string>
  <string id="101372" soundid="155889">I saw your fight with Fourth Brother Yu... not bad, but I think I&apos;ve figured out your style. Do you want another match?</string>
  <string id="101373" soundid="155890">Simply amazing. I never thought I&apos;d see the day when Third Brother would lose a fight. Even First Brother can&apos;t defeat him.</string>
  <string id="101374" soundid="155891">I&apos;ll give a fight if you want one, but I won&apos;t be able to offer as much of a challenge as Third Brother.</string>
  <string id="101386">A young girl named Jinlin needs to retrieve an artifact from the tomb of an old emperor. She needs you to clear the tomb of ghosts first.</string>
  <string id="101387">Jinlin</string>
  <string id="101388">You tracked down Fading Moon and eliminated her. Her obvious insanity left you very little choice in the matter.</string>
  <string id="101389">Report to Captain Sen</string>
  <string id="101390">Captain Sen waits by the city gates in the Market District for you to report your success.</string>
  <string id="101392">Thanks to you, Fading Moon&apos;s fires will never again endanger the citizens of the Imperial City.</string>
  <string id="101393" soundid="155931">I guess the weapons on that flyer were active. That&apos;s certainly one way to take care of a door.</string>
  <string id="101394" soundid="173415">Some sort of magic binds this demon. I never expected Gao the Greater to be so powerful.</string>
  <string id="101395" soundid="155933">Didn&apos;t really think that through before you started messing with those controls, did you? Those weapons could have killed us!</string>
  <string id="101396" soundid="155934">Instead, you&apos;ve blown open that massive door. Only you could be that lucky.</string>
  <string id="101397" soundid="155935">I was going to try ramming that door with my head if I got bored. Oh well. Let&apos;s see what&apos;s inside!</string>
  <string id="101398" soundid="155936">That was exciting! I wonder what&apos;s inside?</string>
  <string id="101399" soundid="155937">Are you crazy? The ship nearly killed us when it fell! Not to mention the weapons firing!</string>
  <string id="101400" soundid="155938">Looks like you&apos;ve managed to &quot;open&quot; that door though. [sigh] Now I suppose you&apos;re going to want to go in and explore it.</string>
  <string id="101404" soundid="155963">Yes, you were a little blunt in your treatment of the Mold Masters. If you manage to discredit Shin in death, I will try to disguise the loss of such useful Assassins.</string>
  <string id="101407" soundid="155966">[An inactive clay golem. It is likely waiting to be activated after the Jade Golem controller, mentioned by Gang, is completed.]</string>
  <string id="101408" soundid="155967">[There is some movement among the golems stored along the wall. The machine may have kept them in stasis awaiting the Jade Golem controller.]</string>
  <string id="101410" soundid="155969">My name is Merchant Kia Jong, and I don&apos;t make a habit of angering... quick-tempered people like you. What can I do for you?</string>
  <string id="101411">The Mold Masters dismissed me and look what happened to them.</string>
  <string id="101412" soundid="155971">We now exclusively butcher slaves for this purpose. If you are lucky you will be allowed to help in the process.</string>
  <string id="101414">Damn it all!</string>
  <string id="101415">Time to pay!</string>
  <string id="101416">Suffer!</string>
  <string id="101417">Your life ends here!</string>
  <string id="101418">Taste death!</string>
  <string id="101419">You won&apos;t walk away!</string>
  <string id="101420">Death&apos;s too good for you.</string>
  <string id="101425">That&apos;s better.</string>
  <string id="101426">Cursed poisoner!</string>
  <string id="101427">Hurts, doesn&apos;t it?</string>
  <string id="101428" soundid="155987"></string>
  <string id="101430">That was useless!</string>
  <string id="101431">You stand no chance!</string>
  <string id="101432">Your life will be pain.</string>
  <string id="101433">Just give up now.</string>
  <string id="101434">It&apos;d be easier to lie down and die!</string>
  <string id="101435">We&apos;ll drink to your bones!</string>
  <string id="101436">Pathetic!</string>
  <string id="101441">Ahhh.</string>
  <string id="101442">It&apos;s in my blood.</string>
  <string id="101443">You&apos;re barely worth the effort!</string>
  <string id="101455">Clay Golem</string>
  <string id="101458">Clay Golem</string>
  <string id="101461">Clay Golem</string>
  <string id="101464">Yes, I will go in alone.</string>
  <string id="101465">No, I am not ready yet.</string>
  <string id="101477" soundid="156096">No, it has to be you! You... you&apos;re here, and someone has to help now!</string>
  <string id="101478" soundid="156097">My son was playing there, behind the arena, and he fell into the pits where the creatures are. I can&apos;t save him!</string>
  <string id="101479" soundid="156098">They took my boy and said I had to find you and lead you into an ambush or they would kill him.</string>
  <string id="101484">Let&apos;s go save your son.</string>
  <string id="101485">Let them try their little ambush. I&apos;ll kill the scum as fast as they come.</string>
  <string id="101486" soundid="156106">Don&apos;t forget his senior student. They say she&apos;s the one who fought many of those bandits.</string>
  <string id="101487" soundid="156107">I don&apos;t follow the school, which one are you talking about?</string>
  <string id="101488" soundid="156108">How could you miss her? She&apos;s the one in purple with the long hair. Must break some hearts with looks like hers.</string>
  <string id="101489" soundid="156109">How could you not know her? She&apos;s the one in the red and blue outfit with her hair always done up. I bet the young men she trains with haven&apos;t missed her.</string>
  <string id="101490" soundid="156110">What? She&apos;s the one in the deep blue outfit with those graceful long sleeves. My wife always yells at me for staring when she walks past!</string>
  <string id="101491" soundid="156111">As strong as she is beautiful, from what I hear.</string>
  <string id="101492" soundid="156112">They say she&apos;s as fast as lightning cutting across the sky when she fights.</string>
  <string id="101493" soundid="156113">From what I hear, her chi is stronger than that of any other in the school.</string>
  <string id="101494" soundid="156114">I once heard Master Li say that she was one of the best all-around fighters he&apos;d ever seen, like her style had no real weaknesses. Impressive, that.</string>
  <string id="101495" soundid="156115">Don&apos;t forget his senior student. They say he&apos;s the one who dealt with many of the bandits.</string>
  <string id="101496" soundid="156116">Wait, which one do you mean? Surely not that arrogant Gao boy?</string>
  <string id="101497" soundid="156117">Oh heavens no! No, he&apos;s the tall one with those rippling muscles and that long tail in his hair. Hard to miss, that&apos;s for sure.</string>
  <string id="101498" soundid="156118">Don&apos;t be silly! He&apos;s the one with that marvelous dragon tattoo on his back. He must have quite a few young ladies pining after him by now.</string>
  <string id="101499" soundid="156119">Are you crazed? No, he&apos;s the cute one in the blue vest with the yellow sash. Trust me, if you were a young woman in this village you&apos;d know who he was.</string>
  <string id="101500" soundid="156120">Gao? Of course not! No, he&apos;s the one in those striking robes with his hair shaved off. He&apos;s a handsome devil, that one!</string>
  <string id="101501" soundid="156121">They say he&apos;s incredibly strong and can outlast almost anyone in the school. </string>
  <string id="101502" soundid="156122">I saw him fight once, and he was quicker than the wind in spring.</string>
  <string id="101503" soundid="156123">I overheard one of the other students say that he could channel his chi like no one else they&apos;d ever seen.</string>
  <string id="101504" soundid="156124">I once heard Master Li say that he was one of most adept students he&apos;d ever seen, as if he had no real weakness while fighting</string>
  <string id="101505" soundid="166264">Dawn Star, there you are. I... I know I haven&apos;t spoken to you in a while. I saw him again last night, and I remembered what you said. I wasn&apos;t as afraid.</string>
  <string id="101506" soundid="166265">I&apos;m glad, Mrs. Jong.</string>
  <string id="101507" soundid="166266">He seemed... peaceful, if a bit... lost. But I know it&apos;s not your fault now. I am sorry for disturbing you, and for what I said before.</string>
  <string id="101508" soundid="166267">Remember Jong Jin, her son? He drowned last year after the mooring she tied let go. A sad accident. I saw his spirit and told her. She thought I was calling up ghosts.</string>
  <string id="101509" soundid="166268">Some spirits return because of trauma, to rectify something that disturbed them in life or death. They are very focused. When the pain is gone, they find rest.</string>
  <string id="101510" soundid="166269">At least, they are supposed to. Jin&apos;s spirit told his mother the accident wasn&apos;t her fault. Now he wanders, unconnected to this world and unable to pass to the next.</string>
  <string id="101511" soundid="166270">Troubled spirits can be set to rest for a time, but unless the greater problem is corrected, it seems all dead are destined to wander until they go mad.</string>
  <string id="101512" soundid="166271">I&apos;m sorry. This has been difficult. I don&apos;t want to think about how it affects... specific people. I&apos;m still not sure I should have told Mrs. Jong about her child.</string>
  <string id="101513" soundid="166272">I don&apos;t know. People just want to be left alone with their grief.</string>
  <string id="101514" soundid="166273">I guess blame is easier to understand than chance. Come on, we should go see if the students are all right.</string>
  <string id="101515" soundid="166274">Master Li will be waiting.</string>
  <string id="101516" soundid="166275">She wouldn&apos;t. She would rather blame herself than seek solace.</string>
  <string id="101517" soundid="166276">Sometimes I wonder. People can be so shallow.</string>
  <string id="101526" soundid="156147">I&apos;ll wait out front with the others if you need me. Be careful, I don&apos;t trust this situation at all.</string>
  <string id="101527" soundid="156148">This whole &quot;alone&quot; things smells fishier than week-old crab cakes. If something comes up, I&apos;ll be waiting outside with the others. Be careful!</string>
  <string id="101528" soundid="156149">This is almost sad. Am I truly so threatening to the mighty Kai Lan the Serpent? Regardless, I&apos;ll be waiting with the others if you need me.</string>
  <string id="101529" soundid="156150">Be wary. Kai Lan could either be a strong ally or your worst enemy. If anything goes wrong, I&apos;ll be waiting with the others, and not far off.</string>
  <string id="101530" soundid="156151">I don&apos;t like that they won&apos;t let me come in there with you. Be careful, and call if you need to. I&apos;ll wait with the others.</string>
  <string id="101531" soundid="156152">Be sure to come out ahead of whatever deal he offers you. I&apos;ll be with the others if you need me.</string>
  <string id="101532" soundid="156153">Suit yourself. I wouldn&apos;t keep the Serpent waiting long if I were you, but then, I value the use of my legs.</string>
  <string id="101536" soundid="156158"></string>
  <string id="101540" soundid="156162"></string>
  <string id="101542" soundid="156164"></string>
  <string id="101543">Heart of Gold</string>
  <string id="101544">Slave</string>
  <string id="101547">Slave</string>
  <string id="101551" soundid="156173">So, would you like to hear about the mission I have for you? Or did you want to have a look at the flyer parts again?</string>
  <string id="101552" soundid="156174">You are back! Would you like to hear about this mission I have for you? Or maybe look at some upgrades for your flyer?</string>
  <string id="101553" soundid="156175"></string>
  <string id="101558" soundid="156193">Come on, you louts. You&apos;ll be scrubbing the dining room floors for your part in this little altercation.</string>
  <string id="101561" soundid="156196">Damn it! Get her... and don&apos;t be gentle!</string>
  <string id="101562" soundid="156213">If you have a grievance with these... fine members of Shin&apos;s entourage, I can have nothing to do with it. Nothing.</string>
  <string id="101563" soundid="156214">I warned you not to appear too skilled. This is between you and Shin&apos;s Attendants. I just do my job. I want no part of this.</string>
  <string id="101564" soundid="156215">Go on then. Let&apos;s see how you fare. We&apos;ll need to sluice the blood out of there by the time they manage to destroy those ghosts.</string>
  <string id="101565" soundid="156216">Go on. Join your other useless acolytes in death.</string>
  <string id="101566" soundid="156217">Hrm... so, Gang has an acolyte who can fight.</string>
  <string id="101567" soundid="156218">Ghosts are mindless. I see no real skill in defeating them.</string>
  <string id="101568" soundid="156219">Yes, certainly. Against a real opponent there would be no doubt of the outcome.</string>
  <string id="101569" soundid="156220">Slink back to Master Gang. We answer to Master Shin, and if you are lucky, this is the last time you will see us.</string>
  <string id="101570" soundid="156221">Leave us, acolyte. We serve Master Shin, not your fool master.</string>
  <string id="101571" soundid="156222">So, you are the new trainer. You think you have something to show us? Master Shin has us *test* each of Gang&apos;s trainers to make sure they are skilled.</string>
  <string id="101572" soundid="156223">But not too skilled. Am I your next student? I assure you, I am more than capable of defending myself. I was made an Attendant because of my... skills.</string>
  <string id="101573" soundid="156224">Oh, don&apos;t worry about me. Worry about yourself. Let&apos;s move this fight to the Hall of Induction, so I have room to enjoy this.</string>
  <string id="101574" soundid="156225">Is that so? I would be more concerned about yourself if I were you. Let&apos;s move this fight to the Hall of Induction, so I have room to enjoy this.</string>
  <string id="101575" soundid="156226">You think to persuade us to abandon Master Shin and join Gang&apos;s pathetic faction? Then you know nothing about how true acolytes are indoctrinated.</string>
  <string id="101576" soundid="156227">Our lives belong to Master Shin. Through his guidance, we will one day ascend to serve Grand Inquisitor Jia and Death&apos;s Hand.</string>
  <string id="101577" soundid="156228">Our loyalty is absolute. We are nothing without our duty to Master Shin. Perhaps Gang is more lenient and left your mind untouched, but that is why he is weak.</string>
  <string id="101578" soundid="156229">I&apos;ll be waiting.</string>
  <string id="101579" soundid="156230">Ah, you gather the courage to return. Come to teach us something, hmm?</string>
  <string id="101580" soundid="156231">I&apos;m ready for my lesson. If you think you are good enough.</string>
  <string id="101581" soundid="156232">You... you killed Kitan. The life of an acolyte is forfeit when they walk into this place, yes, but for one of Gang&apos;s ragged minions to do this is unforgivable.</string>
  <string id="101582" soundid="156233">Do you think you can make such an insult and disguise it as a simple training mishap? You are a fool.</string>
  <string id="101583" soundid="156234">If you are ready, trainer, your next student is waiting. It is my task to make examples of Gang&apos;s acolytes who show too much promise.</string>
  <string id="101584" soundid="156235">My skills are above question. Gang is about to lose another of his pitiful acolytes. Come, let&apos;s move to the hall, and I will end this.</string>
  <string id="101585" soundid="156236">Master Shin is our guiding light. We serve his glory, and through him, we will come to serve Grand Inquisitor Jia and Death&apos;s Hand.</string>
  <string id="101586" soundid="156237">Our loyalty is absolute. You would know this if Gang properly indoctrinated his acolytes, but he does not, so he is weak.</string>
  <string id="101587" soundid="156238">On your own time, trainer. Your cowardice is as much a lesson as whatever will happen to you during our bout.</string>
  <string id="101590">You force my hand. Come, Attendants, I will fight you all.</string>
  <string id="101591">Numbers mean nothing, Attendants. I will destroy you all!</string>
  <string id="101592">Master Gang, will you not assist me?</string>
  <string id="101594">Acolyte Trainer Guang, will you assist me?</string>
  <string id="101599">[Lie] I will make certain nothing goes wrong during our bout.</string>
  <string id="101600">You better be competent. If not, you might have an *accident.*</string>
  <string id="101601">Perhaps we could come to some sort of arrangement.</string>
  <string id="101604">I&apos;ll come back later when I&apos;m ready to begin.</string>
  <string id="101608">I am ready. Come, Kai Feng, let us see how skilled you are.</string>
  <string id="101609">We do not have to fight. We can come to an agreement.</string>
  <string id="101611">I&apos;ll be ready soon enough. You can wait for now.</string>
  <string id="101619" soundid="156270">You can also seek training from Acolyte Trainer Guang. I am sure you are her superior, but she might have something of use to you.</string>
  <string id="101620" soundid="156271">I am sure I can count on you.</string>
  <string id="101621" soundid="156272">Have you not been paying attention? I cannot act directly against Master Shin! If I do, we are all dead. It is that simple.</string>
  <string id="101622" soundid="156273">Acolytes falling to other acolytes is to be expected. It is how the weak are filtered out. My actions would make it a war.</string>
  <string id="101624">Why didn&apos;t you help against Shin&apos;s Attendants?</string>
  <string id="101626" soundid="156277">An acolyte of Gang&apos;s, hmm? So am I. Let&apos;s identify what training you need by sparring for a short time.</string>
  <string id="101627" soundid="156278">Let&apos;s keep it non-lethal for now. You&apos;ll find you have enough enemies in this place. We acolytes are utterly expendable.</string>
  <string id="101628" soundid="156279">Attendant Kitan, as I said. She is with the rest of Shin&apos;s entourage by the doors to the inner chambers.</string>
  <string id="101629" soundid="156280">Your next student has been chosen for you. I did warn you that appearing too strong would put you in danger. Well, beware this next Attendant.</string>
  <string id="101630" soundid="156281">Attendant Kai Feng is waiting for you with his remaining fellows at the doors to the inner chambers. I wish you luck.</string>
  <string id="101631" soundid="156282">As I said, Attendant Kai Feng is waiting for you at the doors to the inner chamber. Be careful.</string>
  <string id="101632" soundid="156283">I have learned a number of techniques.</string>
  <string id="101633" soundid="156284">I showed my ability in the arena, and when I asked, their recruiter agreed. I have only one skill, and this was the best place to exploit it.</string>
  <string id="101634" soundid="156285">Combat. Killing. The army was too strict... the arena too tame. Here, when they want an enemy destroyed, that enemy is destroyed... sometimes family and all.</string>
  <string id="101635" soundid="156286">We are all here for one reason, and that includes you. We are killers, plain and simple. There are no Lotus Assassins with hearts of gold.</string>
  <string id="101636" soundid="156287">Goodbye. If you wish to begin your likely short career as trainer, Attendant Kitan waits with her fellows at the doors to the inner chambers.</string>
  <string id="101637" soundid="156288">Goodbye. Your next, and likely final, training partner is waiting by the inner chamber doors. Attendant Kai Feng. Do not hold back. Good luck.</string>
  <string id="101638" soundid="156289">Goodbye, acolyte.</string>
  <string id="101639" soundid="156290">You! Assist her, if you can even do that.</string>
  <string id="101640" soundid="156291">Greetings, acolyte. I believe I was supposed to be your trainer, but... given the rather remarkable deaths that have occurred, I&apos;m sure you don&apos;t need my help.</string>
  <string id="101641" soundid="156292">I still have some training techniques and resources I can share, but we may as well dispense with formality. What do you need?</string>
  <string id="101642" soundid="156293">You are either brave or foolish. I warned you that appearing too strong would make you a target of Shin&apos;s Attendants. Actually killing one will incite them further.</string>
  <string id="101643" soundid="156294">I would be very careful if you intend on continuing to train the others. They will not let the death of Kitan go unanswered.</string>
  <string id="101644" soundid="156295">What? That is your plan? I wish you luck, but I&apos;m staying well out of the way. This is going to get really ugly.</string>
  <string id="101645" soundid="156296">I marvel at your ability. You show no fear of the enemies you make. You will do well here.</string>
  <string id="101646" soundid="156297">You have no more acolytes to train for now. Is there anything else you need?</string>
  <string id="101647" soundid="156298">How can I assist you?</string>
  <string id="101648" soundid="156299">Good. Remember, no killing blows. I&apos;m sure you&apos;ll have plenty of time to practice those later.</string>
  <string id="101649" soundid="156300">Return when you are. This initial test will tell me what you need to learn. I won&apos;t train you without some idea of your capabilities. It&apos;s a waste of time.</string>
  <string id="101650" soundid="156301">Are you ready to spar? It&apos;s hard to know what you need to learn without seeing what you already know.</string>
  <string id="101651" soundid="156302">What&apos;s that? I thought I had found something special, but if that acolyte can&apos;t beat a trainer, I&apos;ll look elsewhere for a favored student.</string>
  <string id="101652" soundid="156303">Bah! Finish him off. I don&apos;t have time for this.</string>
  <string id="101653" soundid="156304">I am sorry. Master&apos;s orders.</string>
  <string id="101654" soundid="156305">Bah! Finish her off. I don&apos;t have time for this.</string>
  <string id="101655" soundid="156306">Well, you would appear to have more than a passing knowledge of combat. I could almost see some kind of flaw, but I was clearly outclassed.</string>
  <string id="101656" soundid="156307">Yes, you were! I knew this acolyte was something special, but I didn&apos;t think my trainer would be made to look like a fool!</string>
  <string id="101657" soundid="156308">You, new-blood, you will be the trainer now. When I am promoted, you will train all my acolytes.</string>
  <string id="101658" soundid="156309">You! Assist him, if you can even do that.</string>
  <string id="101659" soundid="156310">It would seem that you have taken over my duties. I will still serve as an advisor, as Master Gang ordered. There are techniques I can share.</string>
  <string id="101660" soundid="156311">In truth I did not like being a trainer. Life for any of Master Gang&apos;s acolytes is rough and short, but especially so for trainers. Master Shin sees to that.</string>
  <string id="101661" soundid="156312">My duties--your duties now--include training Master Shin&apos;s personal entourage. In the past, if a trainer was too good, Shin had that trainer killed to keep Gang weak.</string>
  <string id="101662" soundid="156313">I think one member of his entourage is a full Lotus Assassin. I have survived by appearing unimportant, and staying out of the fight between Gang and Shin.</string>
  <string id="101663" soundid="156314">You are supposed to train the Attendants in his entourage. Some need it, but if you seem too skilled, your next fight will be against the hidden Lotus Assassin.</string>
  <string id="101664" soundid="168010">If you&apos;re dead set on losing your life down in the lowest tombs, I won&apos;t stop you. I won&apos;t save you, either.</string>
  <string id="101665" soundid="156316">Besides, it wouldn&apos;t weaken Shin for long. I suppose he would be alone and more vulnerable if he had to fight right away, but he will replace them in time.</string>
  <string id="101666" soundid="156317">Accidents happen, and even the attendants in his entourage are just acolytes, and therefore are utterly expendable. There would not be much fuss.</string>
  <string id="101667" soundid="156318">However, you would probably find yourself training the hidden Lotus Assassin in the next bout. Any skilled acolytes under Gang are quickly disposed of.</string>
  <string id="101668" soundid="156319">Are you mad? Well, it doesn&apos;t matter, you must train one at a time. If you seem to be too strong a target, I&apos;m sure they will accommodate your death wish.</string>
  <string id="101669" soundid="156320">You are in a hurry to make enemies, aren&apos;t you? Very well, Master Shin has a new attendant in his entourage who is supposed to be trained. Attendant Kitan.</string>
  <string id="101670" soundid="156321">She is replacing one of the acolytes who did not return from Tien&apos;s Landing. There was no explanation. I assume he was weak and was discarded.</string>
  <string id="101671" soundid="156322">You can find her and all of the other Attendants by the doors to the inner chambers. They wait there for when Shin leaves to inspect new slave shipments.</string>
  <string id="101673">Very well. Let&apos;s spar.</string>
  <string id="101675">Goodbye.</string>
  <string id="101676">You weren&apos;t much of a trainer. I will be far better.</string>
  <string id="101680">Three more to go and Shin is helpless if called to fight.</string>
  <string id="101682">I&apos;m not ready to spar with you.</string>
  <string id="101690">I apologize for taking your position.</string>
  <string id="101693">I have access to Shin&apos;s personal entourage?</string>
  <string id="101696">Would there be an outcry if one of Shin&apos;s entourage died during training?</string>
  <string id="101698">I want to get rid of all of them. How many can I fight at once?</string>
  <string id="101699">Who am I supposed to train?</string>
  <string id="101703">What training services can you provide?</string>
  <string id="101704">How did you come to join the Assassins?</string>
  <string id="101705">What ability do you mean?</string>
  <string id="101706">You and the others were incapacitated. I did what I could.</string>
  <string id="101710" soundid="175123">Look, I didn&apos;t mean to say.... Anyway, I meant no offense to anyone, and I&apos;ll just leave it at that.</string>
  <string id="101712">Attendant Kitan</string>
  <string id="101715">Attendant Kai Feng</string>
  <string id="101718">Attendant Cohong</string>
  <string id="101721">Attendant Teng</string>
  <string id="101724">Acolyte Trainer Guang</string>
  <string id="101728">Several pages detailing the actions and transactions of the slave traders in the Imperial City. These documents clearly indicate that Chandler Ling is involved with the slave traders.</string>
  <string id="101729">Forged Slaver Documents</string>
  <string id="101730">Several pages detailing the actions and transactions of the Slave Traders in the Imperial City. These documents are cleverly doctored to falsely indicate Scholar Songtao&apos;s involvement with the Slave Traders.</string>
  <string id="101732" soundid="156392">Silence! Your lives are nothing. It is Gang&apos;s insolence that is the real insult.</string>
  <string id="101733" soundid="156393">You thought to make me vulnerable by killing my Attendants and emptying the hall? A miscalculation. I am a favored of Grand Inquisitor Jia! You will die!</string>
  <string id="101734" soundid="156394">And where are the rest of my Attendants? Delays and laziness will be repaid in blood! No one disobeys my orders!</string>
  <string id="101737">Save your breath. You and your Attendants are dead.</string>
  <string id="101738">Sign</string>
  <string id="101740">Sign</string>
  <string id="101741">Sign</string>
  <string id="101742">Sign</string>
  <string id="101743">I expected the Water Dragon to appear again.</string>
  <string id="101745">How much more of this until Dirge is restored?</string>
  <string id="101748">I can&apos;t believe a little blood could do so much.</string>
  <string id="101750">Enough of this... what&apos;s next?</string>
  <string id="101751">Mechanic Hin Goo has asked you to use your ship, the Marvelous Dragonfly, to help him with his business. The mechanic has upgrades available for your ship, as well.</string>
  <string id="101752">Mechanic Hin Goo</string>
  <string id="101753">Accept Hin Goo&apos;s First Mission</string>
  <string id="101754">Speak with Hin Goo and accept his first mission.</string>
  <string id="101756">After flying Hin Goo&apos;s first mission, he now has new upgrades for the Marvelous Dragonfly and another mission for you.</string>
  <string id="101757">Accept Hin Goo&apos;s Second Mission</string>
  <string id="101758">Speak with Hin Goo and accept his second mission.</string>
  <string id="101760">After escorting the Prefect, Mechanic Hin Goo has new upgrades for the Marvelous Dragonfly and another mission for you.</string>
  <string id="101761">Accept Hin Goo&apos;s Third Mission</string>
  <string id="101762">Speak with Hin Goo and accept his third mission.</string>
  <string id="101764">You have completed all the missions that Mechanic Hin Goo has. He still has upgrades for the Marvelous Dragonfly if you need them.</string>
  <string id="101769">Meet Jinlin at the Tomb</string>
  <string id="101770">Go to the Necropolis and find Jinlin at the tomb of the old emperor, which is in the north of the Necropolis. </string>
  <string id="101772">Jinlin has opened the door into the tomb. You must clear the tomb of ghosts and anything dangerous so that Jinlin can get the artifact for Purveyor Shouji.</string>
  <string id="101773">Clear the Spirits from the Tomb</string>
  <string id="101774">Destroy all the spirits and enemies within the tomb.</string>
  <string id="101776">Removing the artifact has caused more enemies to fill the tomb. You must defeat the enemies so you and Jinlin can get out of the tomb alive.</string>
  <string id="101777">Escape the Tomb</string>
  <string id="101778">Defeat all the enemies and escape the tomb.</string>
  <string id="101780">Jinlin has the artifact for Shouji. There was a strange riddle written on the artifact. It reads, &quot;Conductor, cog, and a bit of iron. Don&apos;t play with the tiger.&quot;</string>
  <string id="101781">Speak with Zi Bao</string>
  <string id="101782">Zi Bao, a suspected slave trader, is drinking in the Heart of the Empire Tavern.</string>
  <string id="101785">Take False Evidence to the Prefect</string>
  <string id="101788">You have sided with Cao Zeng. You must take the false evidence to Prefect Jitong and get Chandler Ling released.</string>
  <string id="101789">Take Evidence to the Prefect</string>
  <string id="101792">You have defeated Cao Zeng and learned more about the slave traders. You must take the evidence to Prefect Jitong and get Scholar Songtao released.</string>
  <string id="101793">Take False Evidence to Prefect</string>
  <string id="101794">Take Cao Zeng&apos;s false evidence to the prefect in Merchants&apos; Square in the Market District and get Chandler Ling released.</string>
  <string id="101796">You framed Scholar Songtao, who has likely been sent to the wall. Chandler Ling was released, and he paid you well for your help.</string>
  <string id="101797">Decided Not to Give Evidence</string>
  <string id="101800">Prefect Jitong refused to pay as much as you wanted for the evidence. He has decided to find someone else to help him uncover the truth behind the slave traders.</string>
  <string id="101801">Take Evidence to Prefect Jitong</string>
  <string id="101802">You must take the evidence about the slave traders to Prefect Jitong in Merchants&apos; Square in the Market District and get Scholar Songtao released.</string>
  <string id="101804">You discovered that Chandler Ling was indeed behind the slave traders. He will likely be sent to the Wall for his crimes. Scholar Songtao is free.</string>
  <string id="101806">Master Radiant wants you to defeat each of the brothers to prove that your first fight was more than just luck. Your next opponent is Third Brother Renshan.</string>
  <string id="101807">Defeat Third Brother Renshan</string>
  <string id="101808">Defeat Third Brother Renshan</string>
  <string id="101810">Third Brother is taking you to see Master Smiling Hawk.</string>
  <string id="101811">Challenge Third Brother Renshan</string>
  <string id="101814">Master Smiling Hawk wants you to kill First Brother Kai, but you have refused. Now you must defeat Third Brother Renshan.</string>
  <string id="101815">Kill First Brother Kai</string>
  <string id="101818">You have agreed to help Master Smiling Hawk. He wants you to remove First Brother Kai. You must challenge First Brother Kai to a fight and kill him.</string>
  <string id="101819">Kill First Brother Kai</string>
  <string id="101820">Challenge First Brother to a match and kill him.</string>
  <string id="101822">Master Radiant and First Brother are dead. Master Smiling Hawk has taught you a new style and rewarded you for your help, but, fearing your power, he has asked you to stay away from the Black Leopard School from now on.</string>
  <string id="101823">Defeat Third Brother Renshan</string>
  <string id="101824">Challenge Third Brother to a Fight.</string>
  <string id="101826">You have defeated Third Brother Renshan. You must next face First Brother Kai in order to prove yourself.</string>
  <string id="101827">Challenge First Brother Kai</string>
  <string id="101828">Find First Brother Kai and challenge him.</string>
  <string id="101831">Kill Master Smiling Hawk</string>
  <string id="101834">After meeting with Master Radiant, you have decided to help him by killing Master Smiling Hawk.</string>
  <string id="101835">Speak to Master Smiling Hawk</string>
  <string id="101838">After meeting with Master Radiant, you have decided to speak with Master Smiling Hawk about the situation at the Black Leopard School.</string>
  <string id="101839">Kill Master Smiling Hawk</string>
  <string id="101840">Go to Master Smiling Hawk&apos;s room and kill him.</string>
  <string id="101842">Master Smiling Hawk is dead, and First Brother Kai is now the sole master of Black Leopard School. You are free to spar with the students or purchase some rare items from First Brother Kai.</string>
  <string id="101843">Speak with Master Smiling Hawk</string>
  <string id="101844">Go to Master Smiling Hawk&apos;s room and speak with him about the situation at Black Leopard School.</string>
  <string id="101846">After speaking with Master Smiling Hawk for the second time, you have chosen to aid him by eliminating First Brother Kai and Master Radiant.</string>
  <string id="101848">Legend</string>
  <string id="101850" soundid="156521">I bring a message from my Master. You have restored one fountain, but the guardian of its seal was weak. The seal for the second fountain is not so easily claimed!</string>
  <string id="101851" soundid="156522">We shall battle in time, mortal spirit... and I shall feast upon your soul! But this is not the time or place.</string>
  <string id="101852" soundid="156523">I am the Minion of Suffering. It was I who devoured the guardian bound to this fountain and claimed the seal for my Master.</string>
  <string id="101853" soundid="156524">Seek me out, traverse the Path of Demons, and you can reclaim the seal... if you dare!</string>
  <string id="101854" soundid="156525">I agree. The demon would not reveal itself without cause.</string>
  <string id="101855" soundid="156526">Wait. Do not rush off foolishly. The demon could be trying to lure you into a trap. </string>
  <string id="101856" soundid="156527">It must have a lair around here. If we face it there, its strength will be at its greatest, but we have little choice if we are to recover the seal.</string>
  <string id="101857" soundid="156528">But there may be a way to yet overcome this demon. I know of a gem here in the monastery; a gem of great power. You could use it to help defeat this monster.</string>
  <string id="101858" soundid="156529">You alone understand the full extent of your capabilities. But the gem will augment your strength... you would be foolish to ignore it.</string>
  <string id="101859" soundid="156530">The gem has been kept here in the monastery for many generations, guarded by powerful spells that keep evil at bay. The spells persisted even after Dirge fell.</string>
  <string id="101860" soundid="156531">The demon seeks to lure us to its lair, but it may also be trying to lure us away from the gem. We must go through the opposite arch if you wish to claim the gem.</string>
  <string id="101861" soundid="156532">You are the last Spirit Monk; the wards will not keep you from the gem. But take care; its power will be like a beacon, drawing all manner of dark spirits near.</string>
  <string id="101862">Auspicious Portents</string>
  <string id="101863" soundid="156534">Perhaps it is just as well. The power of the gem must glow like a beacon here in Dirge. All manner of foul ghosts and spirits would be drawn to it.</string>
  <string id="101864" soundid="156535">Battling through such creatures may be just as difficult as facing the demon. In any case, the choice is yours.</string>
  <string id="101865" soundid="156536">You cannot join this battle. Your destiny lies in the temple at the top of the stairs!</string>
  <string id="101867">Who are you?</string>
  <string id="101868">Did you destroy this fountain&apos;s guardian?</string>
  <string id="101869">Prepare to die, demon!</string>
  <string id="101872">Well, this is obviously a trap.</string>
  <string id="101873">Quick, let&apos;s go after him!</string>
  <string id="101876">Would the gem still be here after all these years?</string>
  <string id="101877">Where can I find this gem?</string>
  <string id="101878">I don&apos;t need any help to defeat a demon!</string>
  <string id="101881">What about these spells protecting it?</string>
  <string id="101882">
Understanding the stars and the universe is a very important goal. By examining the universe, we can interpret and predict things to come. The sky is where the Great Dragon was said to dwell, and in his illustrious home we can see the signs of his effects on creation.

Of the observable phenomena, three major ones are the most auspicious: comets, the flames of the heavens, passing across the sky; eclipses, during which the power of the gods blocks the sun for brief periods; and falling stars, marking the descent of one of the Celestial Bureaucracy to the earth.</string>
  <string id="101883">Fine. Let&apos;s go get the gem.</string>
  <string id="101885">I can take care of this demon. Nothing can stop me.</string>
  <string id="101892" soundid="156565">He has no name. He is a being from neither the mortal world nor the spirit realm. He is darkness; he is suffering; he is sorrow and despair. He is evil incarnate.</string>
  <string id="101893" soundid="156566">I do not fear you, for the power of my master flows through me. I enforce his will, for all must bow down to him, in time.</string>
  <string id="101895">Who is your master?</string>
  <string id="101896">I will cleanse Dirge of this taint!</string>
  <string id="101897">Give me the seal or I will destroy you.</string>
  <string id="101899" soundid="156572">My minion is destroyed; the second seal is yours. But even that will not avail you.</string>
  <string id="101900" soundid="156573">I have feasted too long to fall to you. Too many souls, too many spirits. The pain and misery of their slaughter sustains me.</string>
  <string id="101901" soundid="156574">For twenty years, I have lingered in the shadows, growing stronger. The corruption of Dirge feeds me. It gives me power.</string>
  <string id="101902" soundid="156575">I am darkness. I am all that is unholy, all that you fear and loathe. I await you in the temple. There, you will understand my true nature and despair.</string>
  <string id="101903" soundid="156576">In all my long years of study... in all my life, I have never heard of a being of such malevolent evil as this.</string>
  <string id="101904" soundid="156577">I knew spirits and demons would overrun Dirge after the Emperor defiled it, but the corruption is far greater than I ever feared... and worse is yet to come!</string>
  <string id="101905" soundid="156578">The temple itself is the center of Dirge&apos;s corruption. The taint is at its strongest there. I shudder to think what unknown evil might await us inside.</string>
  <string id="101906" soundid="156579">The Water Dragon has faith in you, and I see you have faith in yourself. I must believe such faith is justified. In any case, we have found the seal.</string>
  <string id="101907" soundid="156580">We should return to the fountain by the courtyard gates. Restore it with the seal you took from the demon and the gates to the temple courtyard should open.</string>
  <string id="101910">Who are you?</string>
  <string id="101911">I will cleanse Dirge of this evil!</string>
  <string id="101912">I killed your minion, and I can kill you!</string>
  <string id="101916">Whatever it is, I will defeat it!</string>
  <string id="101917">At least we have the seal now.</string>
  <string id="101918">You might be afraid of what&apos;s ahead, but I&apos;m not.</string>
  <string id="101921" soundid="156594">What am I going to do? I&apos;m ruined.</string>
  <string id="101922" soundid="156595">Poor Chang. If only I hadn&apos;t sent him on such a dangerous mission... he&apos;d still be alive.</string>
  <string id="101923" soundid="156596">This can&apos;t be happening. My business is finished... I&apos;m finished.</string>
  <string id="101924" soundid="156597">I can&apos;t sell upgrades if I can&apos;t find supplies. I&apos;m ruined... finished.</string>
  <string id="101925" soundid="156598">For twenty years, I have sought to pass the wards protecting this gem. Its power calls out to me, yet the magic guarding this prize has kept me at bay. None can pass.</string>
  <string id="101926" soundid="156599">You bear the mark of the Water Dragon! You can pass through the wards... as will I, once I have devoured your spirit!</string>
  <string id="101927">The gem is mine by right. I can pass.</string>
  <string id="101928" soundid="156601">I serve my owner without hesitation. I have no taste for the lash.</string>
  <string id="101929" soundid="156602">I should not speak with you. I have no desire to incur my owner&apos;s wrath.</string>
  <string id="101930" soundid="156603">I do what I must. I cannot complain.</string>
  <string id="101931" soundid="156604">I serve as I am directed. I have no other option.</string>
  <string id="101932" soundid="156605">I used to be a free man, but that seems like a long time ago.</string>
  <string id="101933" soundid="156606">My owner is kind enough, but he still calls me &quot;property.&quot; He has my obedience, but nothing else.</string>
  <string id="101935" soundid="156608">I don&apos;t have time to talk to new recruits. Don&apos;t waste my time.</string>
  <string id="101936" soundid="156609">Scum like you crawls out of the gutter every few minutes. Go away, trash.</string>
  <string id="101937" soundid="156610">I suppose having your nose in Master Gang&apos;s backside is one way to get ahead.</string>
  <string id="101938" soundid="156611">If Master Gang hadn&apos;t shown you such favoritism, you wouldn&apos;t have gotten anywhere.</string>
  <string id="101939" soundid="156612">Ha, Shin was wasteful. Without him around, someone more... deserving can move up.</string>
  <string id="101940" soundid="156613">The way is open for my ascension now. Master Shin won&apos;t be able to keep me back anymore.</string>
  <string id="101941" soundid="156614">With all the masters gone, there&apos;s no limits to how far I can rise... or the methods with which I can deal with my opponents.</string>
  <string id="101942" soundid="156615">The masters conspired to keep us in our place, but my place is above them all!</string>
  <string id="101943" soundid="156616">I will easily surpass the petty efforts you&apos;ve put forth. I only need time.</string>
  <string id="101944" soundid="156617">You may have the ear of the masters for now, but soon it will be me they favor.</string>
  <string id="101945" soundid="156618">If the masters favored me like they do you, I would be even higher!</string>
  <string id="101946" soundid="156619">You can&apos;t expect to prove your ability when you&apos;re coddled by the masters all the time.</string>
  <string id="101947" soundid="156620">With the death of Master Shin, there is a lot of room for advancement now.</string>
  <string id="101948" soundid="156621">Someone who can stir things up as well as you is someone to keep an eye on.</string>
  <string id="101949" soundid="156622">There is no limit to how high I can climb with the masters gone. You have served a useful purpose.</string>
  <string id="101950" soundid="156623">I never liked Shin or Gang very much. They always spoke down to me. You did good work in setting this up.</string>
  <string id="101951" soundid="156624">I have been separated to reflect on my devotion.</string>
  <string id="101952" soundid="156625">There is nothing in this life except my service to Death&apos;s Hand.</string>
  <string id="101953" soundid="156626">Those who do not serve are useless trash.</string>
  <string id="101954" soundid="156627">I would give anything to be able to serve.</string>
  <string id="101955" soundid="156628">I am devoted to Death&apos;s Hand alone.</string>
  <string id="101956" soundid="156629">If permitted to serve, I would give my life as a Lotus Assassin.</string>
  <string id="101966" soundid="156639">I have no time for you, acolyte. I focus every thought on the Emperor&apos;s glorious golem army.</string>
  <string id="101967" soundid="156640">You are beneath me. Go, or risk being used as golem fodder.</string>
  <string id="101968" soundid="156641">You have proven to be more than I thought. Shin was no fool.</string>
  <string id="101969" soundid="156642">Did luck lead you to defeat Shin? New recruits are rarely so able to manipulate the masters.</string>
  <string id="101970" soundid="156643">You have proven yourself a cunning individual. That must be nurtured... or destroyed.</string>
  <string id="101971" soundid="156644">Gang and Shin let their ambition cloud their minds. It will not happen to me.</string>
  <string id="101972" soundid="156645">Keep bothering me and you won&apos;t survive being an acolyte. Your spirit could power a golem as well as any slave.</string>
  <string id="101973" soundid="156646">Lotus Assassins are far superior to you acolytes. We are trusted followers of the will of the Emperor, and will lead his golem army.</string>
  <string id="101974" soundid="156647">Shin&apos;s death has forced me to notice you. You just might survive to truly serve.</string>
  <string id="101975" soundid="156648">To be a Lotus Assassin is to serve Death&apos;s Hand. Shin has proven unworthy, as have many before him.</string>
  <string id="101976" soundid="156649">Shin and Gang were both idiots. The talent you have shown should not be wasted on such petty machinations.</string>
  <string id="101977" soundid="156650">The promise you hold should not be wasted. No matter the rank we claim, we are still under Death&apos;s Hand.</string>
  <string id="101978" soundid="156651">Return to your duties, acolyte. If you are not working to increase the Emperor&apos;s glorious golem army, you are a waste of our resources.</string>
  <string id="101979" soundid="156652">If you survive your training, then you can speak to me. Idle chatter will not delay production of the golems.</string>
  <string id="101980" soundid="156653">You seem more clever than I first thought. Of course, Shin was a fool.</string>
  <string id="101981" soundid="156654">I&apos;ll be watching you from now on. You&apos;ve shown promise.</string>
  <string id="101982" soundid="156655">New acolytes rarely impress me. You&apos;ll be one to watch in the future.</string>
  <string id="101983" soundid="156656">Your have great promise, but not all of us are as easily distracted as Gang and Shin.</string>
  <string id="101984">Speak With Lady Rento</string>
  <string id="101985">Lady Rento said she would be in the Imperial Arena if anyone needed to question her about Creative Yukong.</string>
  <string id="101987">You spoke with Lady Rento and learned that Yukong isn&apos;t actually much of a confidence man. He asked her to sponsor him as an actor. She suggested that he might be hiding in the Scholars&apos; Garden.</string>
  <string id="101988">Track Down Creative Yukong</string>
  <string id="101989">Creative Yukong could be disguised as anyone in the city, but he might give himself away by seeming out of place.</string>
  <string id="101991">You found the somewhat miserable Yukong posing as a scholar in the Scholars&apos; Garden. All that remains is deciding what to do with him.</string>
  <string id="101992">Track Down Creative Yukong</string>
  <string id="101993">According to Lady Rento, Creative Yukong is likely to be hiding in the Scholars&apos; Garden.</string>
  <string id="101995">You found the somewhat miserable Yukong posing as a scholar in the Scholars&apos; Garden. All that remains is deciding what to do with him.</string>
  <string id="101996">Eliminate Yukong</string>
  <string id="101997">Creative Yukong has a bounty on his head. Eliminating him would enable you to collect that silver.</string>
  <string id="101999">You tracked Creative Yukong down to the Scholars&apos; Garden and eliminated him, satisfying the conditions of the bounty.</string>
  <string id="102000">Aid Yukong&apos;s Escape</string>
  <string id="102001">Yukong seems a bit hapless and only wants to leave the city. There may be some way to help him.</string>
  <string id="102003">You agreed to help Creative Yukong out of the city instead of collecting his bounty. Now you just have to get him past Captain Sen.</string>
  <string id="102004">Collect Yukong&apos;s Bounty</string>
  <string id="102005">Captain Sen will be glad to hear that you have dealt with Creative Yukong. Your reward waits near the gates in the Market District.</string>
  <string id="102007">Captain Sen rewarded you for eliminating the notorious confidence man, Creative Yukong.</string>
  <string id="102008">Allow Yukong to Escape</string>
  <string id="102011">After several false starts, Creative Yukong finally managed to make his way out of the city. He should be safe now that he is away from the wrath of Lord Rento.</string>
  <string id="102012">Turn In Creative Yukong</string>
  <string id="102015">You turned in Creative Yukong after Captain Sen offered to up his bounty for more information. The bounty collected, your task is complete.</string>
  <string id="102128" soundid="158650">I doubt there are two people in the Empire that know *how* they work. It&apos;s a baffling combination of magic and artifice.</string>
  <string id="102129" soundid="158651">We may be able to do it among the three of us. I was told that they are simple to control.</string>
  <string id="102133" soundid="156815"></string>
  <string id="102134" soundid="156819">But do not fear. You will be spared this fate... for I will rend your spirit into nothingness!</string>
  <string id="102142" soundid="156827">What&apos;s this? Another spirit drawn to this place? Another ghost seeking to claim the power of the gem? Your quest will end in failure... as did mine.</string>
  <string id="102143" soundid="156828">You are bold. Do you not know my power? I could snuff out your existence like a flame. But wait! There is something different about you.</string>
  <string id="102145">The wards protect against evil... but I can pass.</string>
  <string id="102146">Out of my sight, spirit.</string>
  <string id="102149" soundid="156839">Uhkir sitakawuwir wosair yoof, praawun!</string>
  <string id="102150" soundid="156840">I did my research, acolyte. It is not as difficult as it seems. Some seem quite... eager to serve. Golems think nothing.</string>
  <string id="102151" soundid="156841">No, no, this isn&apos;t right! Destroy them!</string>
  <string id="102152" soundid="156842">You... you saw nothing of this. Nothing! I... I have to continue my research before Jia knows of my failure. I know it can work.</string>
  <string id="102155">What preparations have you made?</string>
  <string id="102158">Are you sure this is wise?</string>
  <string id="102160" soundid="156851">It looks like we have everything we need to get our flyer going again. We have to hurry if want to rescue Master Li.</string>
  <string id="102161" soundid="156852">We should head back to our camp at Tien&apos;s Landing and use the Dragonfly so we can continue on to the Imperial City.</string>
  <string id="102162" soundid="156853">You&apos;ve done well, so far. You seem to have everything you need to get that Dragonfly up into the skies again. But this quest is far from over.</string>
  <string id="102163" soundid="156854">Let&apos;s go back to the camp at Tien&apos;s Landing. The Dragonfly can take us to the Imperial City. That&apos;s where the Lotus Assassin must have taken your master.</string>
  <string id="102164" soundid="156855">It appears you have gathered everything you need to get the Marvelous Dragonfly airborne again; I guess this mission has been a success.</string>
  <string id="102165" soundid="156856">Let&apos;s get back to the camp at Tien&apos;s Landing. With the Dragonfly, we can continue on to the Imperial City and resume the search for your master.</string>
  <string id="102166" soundid="156857">Chai Ka: Your task here is done, but your greater goal is far from finished. We should go back to the camp at Tien&apos;s Landing.</string>
  <string id="102167" soundid="156858">Chai Ka: The Dragonfly can soar through the skies like a bird. Use it to journey to the Imperial City and the next stage of your quest.</string>
  <string id="102168" soundid="156859">Well, it seems you have everything you need to get your flying machine airborne again. I guess there&apos;s no reason to stay around here.</string>
  <string id="102169" soundid="156860">Why don&apos;t we go back to the camp at Tien&apos;s Landing and use that Dragonfly to head on to the Imperial City?</string>
  <string id="102170" soundid="156861">Looks like you&apos;ve smashed all your enemies around here. We need to find someone else to fight!</string>
  <string id="102171" soundid="156862">Let&apos;s go back to your camp at Tien&apos;s Landing. Use that flying machine to go to the Imperial City... they have plenty of wine, and plenty of fighting.</string>
  <string id="102179">Horse Demon</string>
  <string id="102182" soundid="156876">Don&apos;t worry, Songtao. I&apos;m doing everything I can to prove you&apos;re innocent.</string>
  <string id="102183" soundid="156877">I know you did it, Ling. It&apos;s just a matter of proving it to the minister.</string>
  <string id="102184" soundid="156878">Why would the governor want to accuse you of doing this, Songtao?</string>
  <string id="102185" soundid="156879">I&apos;m sorry... I&apos;m not being very clear. Lately I&apos;ve just been so... frustrated.</string>
  <string id="102187">Just a little silver? Forget it, I&apos;m leaving.</string>
  <string id="102189" soundid="156923"></string>
  <string id="102190" soundid="156924"></string>
  <string id="102191" soundid="156925"></string>
  <string id="102192" soundid="156926"></string>
  <string id="102193" soundid="156927"></string>
  <string id="102194" soundid="156928"></string>
  <string id="102195" soundid="156929"></string>
  <string id="102196" soundid="156930"></string>
  <string id="102197" soundid="156931"></string>
  <string id="102198" soundid="156932"></string>
  <string id="102221">You have defeated Aishi the Mournful Blade. The old man who informed you she was at the Black Leopard School said she had a considerable bounty on her head.</string>
  <string id="102222">Help Aishi</string>
  <string id="102225">After hearing her out, you have decided to aid Aishi the Mournful blade by taking her to see Captain Sen by the city gates.</string>
  <string id="102226">Collect Aishi&apos;s Bounty</string>
  <string id="102227">Captain Sen by the city gates in the Market District handles bounties, and he will likely have a bounty for Aishi the Mournful Blade.</string>
  <string id="102229">You have collected Aishi the Mournful Blade&apos;s bounty and put an end to her long history of crime and murder.</string>
  <string id="102230">Deal with Aishi the Mournful Blade</string>
  <string id="102231">Aishi the Mournful Blade has warned you to be ready before you speak with her.</string>
  <string id="102234">Track Down the Mournful Blade</string>
  <string id="102235">According to the elderly informant, Aishi the Mournful Blade is in the Black Leopard School, which lies off the Market District.</string>
  <string id="102237">Following the lead of an old man, you tracked Aishi the Mournful Blade to the Black Leopard School. She seemed reluctant to talk, and the dead body on the ground beside her suggests that she is serious in saying you should be ready before you speak with her.</string>
  <string id="102238" soundid="157101"></string>
  <string id="102239" soundid="157102"></string>
  <string id="102241" soundid="157104"></string>
  <string id="102242" soundid="157105"></string>
</tlk>