<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<tlk language="0">
    <string id="17639" soundid="41606">By all the heavens!</string>
  <string id="17640" soundid="41607">This... this is not right. Gods... gods do not bleed!</string>
  <string id="17641" soundid="41608">Forgive us, Great Dragon. Our mortal kin are ignorant, foolish, unkind. These crimes will not go unanswered.</string>
  <string id="17642" soundid="41609">You small creatures, you heard the sounds of battle, but are you truly prepared? What will become of your world if my kind fall to the same evils that plague you?</string>
  <string id="17643" soundid="178067">Your Master commands that you find her; if not to bring her back, then to teach her captor that this will not be tolerated. Gao insults your accomplishments with this action.</string>
  <string id="17644" soundid="41611">Your Master Li must be stopped. The Empire must find balance without the flow of heart-water he has unleashed.</string>
  <string id="17645" soundid="41612">The reign of Emperor Sun saw my abuse, but Sun Li the Glorious Strategist laid the plans. One could not occur without the other.</string>
  <string id="17646" soundid="41613">It was never his intent to let brother Hai rule. Had his plan initially succeeded, your Master would be Emperor, and you would have been destroyed with the others of your kind.</string>
  <string id="17647" soundid="41614">I feel as though this could absolve my father of blame, but seeing what was done here.... He was beyond my help.</string>
  <string id="17648" soundid="41615">You are a Spirit Monk, charged with guarding the order of things. You were not born to this role, but as the last, a solemn duty falls at your feet.</string>
  <string id="17649" soundid="41616">I cannot be healed. My body has been cut open, my heart removed. I should rejoin the Great Wheel, but I am defiled and cannot rest.</string>
  <string id="17650" soundid="41617">Rebirth can only come when my essence is free. To defeat your Master, you must stop the power he draws from me. Soon he will be too strong, even for you.</string>
  <string id="17652" soundid="41619">Your Master abuses the amulet he took from you. His brother did not have that luxury, so he needed to draw my essence slowly. The toll on his body was grave.</string>
  <string id="17653" soundid="41620">Emperor Sun did not have the amulet. He had to draw my essence slowly, or it would overwhelm him. Even so, it took a horrible toll on his body.</string>
  <string id="17654" soundid="41621">Your Master does not have to be so cautious. The amulet is not a source of power, but it *is* a focus.</string>
  <string id="17655" soundid="41622">He partakes of energy that mortals were never meant to hold. He laps at it greedily, expecting your return.</string>
  <string id="17656" soundid="41623">You must destroy the source of that power. You must destroy my body. When he falls, all that is mine will then rejoin my spirit. Rebirth.</string>
  <string id="17657" soundid="41624">There is no other decision to make. This desecration... we must undo it.</string>
  <string id="17658" soundid="41625">Then let it be so. Take hold of a blade, Spirit Monk, and let it strike true. Destroy the machine that maintains this abomination.</string>
  <string id="17659" soundid="41626">The Great Wheel must turn.</string>
  <string id="17661">Defeat the Spirits of your Classmates</string>
  <string id="17662" soundid="41629">It is the wisest decision. A pity such power could not have been put to constructive use.</string>
  <string id="17663" soundid="41630">A good step toward rectifying this desecration.</string>
  <string id="17664" soundid="41631">It is clear that nobody involved had the will to properly command this energy. So be it.</string>
  <string id="17665" soundid="41632">To what end? Look what has become of our Master. Look what he has been a part of.</string>
  <string id="17666" soundid="41633">Beware what you say, for you are still mortal and open to the same weaknesses he and his brothers displayed!</string>
  <string id="17667" soundid="41634">It seems that you learned your lessons in the spirit realm a little too well. Yes, blood from your mortal companions *could* be used to poison my body.</string>
  <string id="17668" soundid="41635">The energy flowing to Sun Li would be disrupted, making him vulnerable. Defeat him and my power would remain trapped in this body for you to use.</string>
  <string id="17669" soundid="41636">You could claim his place, become a god. As the blood poison waned, your power would surpass his and eventually consume my very being.</string>
  <string id="17670" soundid="41637">But the water that flows from me now sustains the Empire. If you poison my body, you poison wherever that water flows. You would taint the heart of the Empire.</string>
  <string id="17671" soundid="41638">No matter the cost? Even if you destroy that destiny? You can&apos;t truly be considering this.</string>
  <string id="17672" soundid="41639">No, I will not allow this. We would trade one tyrant for another.</string>
  <string id="17673" soundid="41640">One murderer for another? I cannot support this!</string>
  <string id="17690" soundid="115762"></string>
  <string id="17942">Dirge - Cave</string>
  <string id="17986" soundid="66115">He&apos;s freed the slaves! You&apos;ll pay for that, maggot!</string>
  <string id="17997" soundid="115763">Thank you for the opportunity to learn from you. Goodbye.</string>
  <string id="18000" soundid="38752"></string>
  <string id="18045" soundid="126631">What do you say? One match before we finish up?</string>
  <string id="18061">Zeng Sai</string>
  <string id="18067">npccbt1</string>
  <string id="18193" soundid="195354">Just kill the golem already, would you?</string>
  <string id="18272" soundid="100583">If you defeat these veterans, you will face the Ravager, our newest champion, who tore his way through the divisions to replace the now-retired Raging Ox!</string>
  <string id="18286" soundid="20814">There are those who say... but it is not important.</string>
  <string id="18287" soundid="20815">Some say that Death&apos;s Hand is collecting all the wind maps and destroying them, so that only he and his minions may travel freely about the Empire.</string>
  <string id="18357">Lotus Assassin</string>
  <string id="18360">Lotus Assassin</string>
  <string id="18363">Lotus Assassin</string>
  <string id="18366">Lotus Assassin</string>
  <string id="18372">Cannibal</string>
  <string id="18443">Paralyzing Palm</string>
  <string id="18444">Legendary Strike</string>
  <string id="18466" soundid="20816">However, I do not believe such talk. I believe firmly in the goodness, kindness, and wisdom of our Emperor and all those around him.</string>
  <string id="18467" soundid="20817">I suppose there may still be merchants in the Imperial City who have some. And they were once so widely available that there must be some here and there.</string>
  <string id="18468" soundid="20818">But I do not have any. Nor do I know anyone who has one.</string>
  <string id="18469" soundid="20819">Absolutely not! How dare you question our beloved Emperor. Absolutely not! Please stop talking to me.</string>
  <string id="18470">That&apos;s a lot to see in just a glint.</string>
  <string id="18472">Let me see your wares.</string>
  <string id="18473">Do you have anything useful? Like weapons or magical items?</string>
  <string id="18474">You don&apos;t actually have anything I&apos;d want, do you?</string>
  <string id="18475">I&apos;m done speaking with you.</string>
  <string id="18476">I&apos;ll just be going now.</string>
  <string id="18477">I have nothing to say to you.</string>
  <string id="18479">Do you sell wind maps?</string>
  <string id="18482">Tell me.</string>
  <string id="18483" soundid="136228">I have been carefully collecting this silver for years, but the death of the murderous fox is more important to me.</string>
  <string id="18484">So no one has wind maps besides Death&apos;s Hand?</string>
  <string id="18486">Then let me see your wares.</string>
  <string id="18487">I&apos;m done talking to you.</string>
  <string id="18488">Have you ever thought the Emperor might be less than good?</string>
  <string id="18489">Then let me see your wares.</string>
  <string id="18490">I&apos;m done with you.</string>
  <string id="18504">Zeng&apos;s Body</string>
  <string id="18505" soundid="108281">Be quiet, they heard me.</string>
  <string id="18506" soundid="161666">[An inactive clay golem.]</string>
  <string id="18522" soundid="20882"></string>
  <string id="18523" soundid="20883"></string>
  <string id="18524" soundid="20884">What... who... no, wait, I don&apos;t want any more trouble.</string>
  <string id="18525" soundid="20885">Yes, I can do that. Whatever you want.</string>
  <string id="18526" soundid="20886">Who? The woman? She got loose from the sack and ran into the cave. Would have been safer out here with us.</string>
  <string id="18527" soundid="20887">Gao told us to go after her, but we said no. There are... things in there. We fought one while he was in the village.</string>
  <string id="18528" soundid="20888">We refused to go after her, so Gao went himself. </string>
  <string id="18529" soundid="20889">I don&apos;t know. He just said it was very important that he get her tonight. He brought a few groups of us over for it.</string>
  <string id="18530" soundid="20890">We didn&apos;t take her; we made Gao do that himself. I know we shouldn&apos;t have let him talk us into any of this, but he doubled our pay.</string>
  <string id="18531" soundid="20891">It was just one woman. Compared to some things... well, all I&apos;ll say is that this wasn&apos;t the worst thing done by a Gao lately.</string>
  <string id="18532" soundid="20892">Look, that&apos;s all I can say. Just let me go. I won&apos;t be any more trouble for you. If I go back to Gao&apos;s father, I&apos;ll be killed as a failure.</string>
  <string id="18533" soundid="20893">By my grandfather, I won&apos;t get in your way again. I swear.</string>
  <string id="18534" soundid="20894">Thank you. You won&apos;t see me again.</string>
  <string id="18535" soundid="20895"></string>
  <string id="18536" soundid="20896">No... no. I told you all I could!</string>
  <string id="18537" soundid="20897"></string>
  <string id="18539" soundid="20899">I didn&apos;t plan any of it! I&apos;m just an extra body watching for people like you following after. He brought a few groups of us.</string>
  <string id="18540" soundid="20900">Gao! Gao the Lesser, I mean. His father would be furious if he knew, but we have to do most of what the boy says.</string>
  <string id="18541" soundid="20901">What? The Mosquito? It flies, and carries people through the air. I swear it&apos;s true!</string>
  <string id="18542" soundid="20902">You&apos;ve never seen that kind of thing out here on the borderlands, but Gao has inventors that can make all kinds of things.</string>
  <string id="18543" soundid="20903">Don&apos;t ask me to fly it, though. Gao himself carries the crystal that powers it.</string>
  <string id="18544" soundid="20904">Look, I&apos;ll tell you whatever you want. The money isn&apos;t good enough to die for. All right?</string>
  <string id="18547">Fine. Just tell me what I want to know.</string>
  <string id="18548">Where is Dawn Star?</string>
  <string id="18551">Why did he kidnap Dawn Star?</string>
  <string id="18554">What do you mean?</string>
  <string id="18556">Get out of here. I&apos;ll follow Gao into the cave.</string>
  <string id="18558">I can&apos;t take that chance. You&apos;re not going anywhere.</string>
  <string id="18560">It&apos;s all Gao&apos;s fault. How convenient. I don&apos;t believe you.</string>
  <string id="18562">I should kill you for this!</string>
  <string id="18564">Who put you up to this?</string>
  <string id="18565">What is this machine here? What does it do?</string>
  <string id="18568">You don&apos;t have any options to choose, friend.</string>
  <string id="18617" soundid="20977">If you will desist from your traitorous talk, we can speak once more about buying and selling.</string>
  <string id="18618" soundid="20978">Greetings once more! Are you ready to peruse my many fine wares?</string>
  <string id="18619">Let me see what you have.</string>
  <string id="18621">Rat Demon</string>
  <string id="18626">Rat Demon</string>
  <string id="18631">Cowardly Rat Demon</string>
  <string id="18641" soundid="127791">I can stay up as late as I want. That&apos;s good, &apos;cause I don&apos;t got no bed.</string>
  <string id="18653">The Abbot of Three Peaks Monastery has told you that his monks were murdered by a Lotus Assassin. He has discovered that the man is hiding out in the Caves. The Abbot wants revenge.</string>
  <string id="18654">Gao&apos;s Mercenary</string>
  <string id="18655" soundid="37285">Welcome, stranger. Welcome to beautiful Tien&apos;s Landing. Isn&apos;t it a glorious day? Oh, I know people complain and grumble, but honestly, I think they&apos;re overreacting.</string>
  <string id="18656" soundid="39145">Now that the Great Dam is closed, I&apos;ll bet the square is just bustling with crowds... or soon will be. Yes, things are definitely looking up for Tien&apos;s Landing.</string>
  <string id="18658" soundid="37288">When the dam was closed, people said the town was dying. But not me! I was the only one who said things would get better... and they did!</string>
  <string id="18659" soundid="37289">I have no doubt the pirates will be dealt with soon, as well. Things always look up eventually. It reminds me of an old saying my father taught me.</string>
  <string id="18660">Old Mother Kwan owned the teahouse in Tien&apos;s Landing until Three Sheets Dutong showed up with an Imperial Writ proclaiming that the teahouse was his. Dutong&apos;s story sounds suspicious and is probably worth investigating.</string>
  <string id="18661" soundid="37291">When we first heard reports of pirates raiding nearby villages, everybody said the town was doomed. But I knew things would improve, and now the pirates are gone!</string>
  <string id="18662" soundid="37292">No doubt the dam will soon be closed, too. Things always get better. It reminds me of an old saying my father taught me.</string>
  <string id="18663">Old Mother Kwan</string>
  <string id="18664" soundid="37294">The dam is closed, the pirates are gone, and life is good in Tien&apos;s Landing once again! Not that I&apos;m surprised... not at all.</string>
  <string id="18665" soundid="37295">Everybody else was all doom and gloom. Some even wanted to leave the town. But not me. I knew everything would work out... and now things are better than ever!</string>
  <string id="18667" soundid="37297">I see you are still here, honored one. I am glad to see that you are enjoying our town! Don&apos;t let the doomsayers convince you that things are not going well here!</string>
  <string id="18669" soundid="37299">The Great Dam has been opened, and the river level has dropped. Ships can&apos;t navigate the river, and nobody can fish. But I think people are overreacting.</string>
  <string id="18670" soundid="37300">Basically, we are suffering some minor inconveniences, which I am sure will soon be resolved. Still, there are a few alarmists who scream and cry that our town is dying.</string>
  <string id="18674">Investigate Dutong&apos;s Writ</string>
  <string id="18675">Speak to Dutong or the teahouse staff to learn more about Dutong&apos;s Imperial Writ.</string>
  <string id="18676">Old Mother Kwan used to own the teahouse in Tien&apos;s Landing, until Three Sheets Dutong showed up with an Imperial Writ proclaiming that the teahouse was his. Dutong&apos;s story sounds suspicious and is probably worth investigating.</string>
  <string id="18677">Steeper Yanru believes Dutong is lying about the writ. He has agreed to help you get Dutong drunk so he&apos;ll confess his crimes.</string>
  <string id="18678">Get Dutong Drunk</string>
  <string id="18679" soundid="128716">You&apos;re awake! It sounds like the army is on the move. They&apos;re on their way up the mountain!</string>
  <string id="18680" soundid="122942">Oh, yes of course. I tend to get carried away sometimes.</string>
  <string id="18681">I need to get going.</string>
  <string id="18682">Can we get back to my other questions?</string>
  <string id="18683" soundid="122945">Farther down toward the city, you&apos;ll find the Golden Way. Many wealthy people live and work there--hopefully some willing to fund one of my inventions.</string>
  <string id="18684" soundid="122946">Then there&apos;s the Market District, near where you landed earlier. Most of the city does its business there. It&apos;s an interesting place--at least, *I* think so.</string>
  <string id="18687">Speak with Yanru and convince him to send drinks to Dutong and get him drunk enough to confess.</string>
  <string id="18691" soundid="37321">Of course, with the dam open, ships can&apos;t navigate the river. So I have no supplies to make my baskets, and no customers to buy them. But am I worried? Of course not.</string>
  <string id="18692" soundid="37322">People are worried about the pirates. Sure, they raid villages and sell their captives to slavers. But they don&apos;t bother us here in Tien&apos;s Landing.</string>
  <string id="18694" soundid="37324">Now that the dam is closed, supplies will start coming back into town. In a week, two at most, I&apos;ll be able to go back to making baskets. We&apos;ll be fine until then.</string>
  <string id="18695" soundid="37325">I&apos;m always happy to talk about Tien&apos;s Landing. We may have a few minor problems, but I&apos;m sure Sheng, our Imperial Minister, will find a way to solve them.</string>
  <string id="18697" soundid="37327">A splendid question, and one in which I am particularly well versed. It is a fascinating tale that dates back to the blessed first Emperor of Jade, Sagacious Tien.</string>
  <string id="18699" soundid="37329">To honor the memory of his dream, he returned and built a summer palace in the spot where he had stopped to rest. In time, a town--this town--sprang up around the palace.</string>
  <string id="18700" soundid="37330">Well, that was long ago. Over the centuries the castle fell into ruin. But make no mistake: Tien&apos;s Landing is where he had his dream. The castle proves it.</string>
  <string id="18701">Restore Kwan&apos;s Ownership of the Teahouse</string>
  <string id="18703">Slam maneuver paralyzes</string>
  <string id="18706">[X] combo paralyzes</string>
  <string id="18707" soundid="37337">Few of the merchants have anything to sell, what with the dam being open and all. But if you head up to the square you can still get a nice view of the whole town.</string>
  <string id="18708">[A] Combo paralyzes</string>
  <string id="18709">Slam maneuver turns opponent to stone</string>
  <string id="18710">**TEMP** Clear maneuver paralyzes enemies within a 3 meter radius</string>
  <string id="18711">**TEMP** Clear maneuver paralyzes enemies within a 5 meter radius</string>
  <string id="18712">**TEMP** Clear maneuver paralyzes enemies within a 7 meter radius</string>
  <string id="18713">You have exposed Dutong&apos;s fraud and returned the teahouse to Old Mother Kwan, much to the delight of customers and staff alike.</string>
  <string id="18714">**TEMP** Clear maneuver paralyzes enemies within a 10 meter radius</string>
  <string id="18715">**TEMP** Clear maneuver paralyzes enemies within a 15 meter radius</string>
  <string id="18716">All duration effects associated with this style receive a slight duration increase.</string>
  <string id="18717">Keep Dutong&apos;s Secret</string>
  <string id="18720">Dutong admitted that he tricked Mother Kwan out of her teahouse, but you agreed to keep his secret in exchange for a pocket full of silver.</string>
  <string id="18721">Tell Mother Kwan that Dutong confessed and that the teahouse is hers again.</string>
  <string id="18722">All duration effects associated with this style receive a small duration increase.</string>
  <string id="18723">All duration effects associated with this style receive a moderate duration increase.</string>
  <string id="18724">All duration effects associated with this style receive a large duration increase.</string>
  <string id="18725">All duration effects associated with this style receive a drastic duration increase.</string>
  <string id="18732">Pending Choice</string>
  <string id="18749" soundid="37379">I think I saw him heading down to Beggar&apos;s Pier. He has a barge there. Knows the river better than anyone else in the town... a true master of his craft.</string>
  <string id="18768" soundid="85248">No more excuses. Your father was always full of excuses, too. It tires me to no end. You know what you have to do, so go do it.</string>
  <string id="18769" soundid="85249">Please, purveyor, don&apos;t send me in there. I&apos;m scared those... things will see me before I can get into the cave. Please don&apos;t make me do it.</string>
  <string id="18770" soundid="85250">I have been patient with you, Jinlin, but your father has been dead for almost a week now. It is time for you to pay off his debts.</string>
  <string id="18771" soundid="85251">Now go! Or perhaps you&apos;d prefer for you and your mother be sent to work at the Wall?</string>
  <string id="18772" soundid="85252">No! I will go. Please don&apos;t hurt my mother. I&apos;ll get the artifact for you, I promise.</string>
  <string id="18773" soundid="85253">A wise decision. You know where to find me once you have it. Do not keep me waiting, Jinlin.</string>
  <string id="18779">The Jade Empire</string>
  <string id="18780" soundid="112001">What? Why not? A slave has to know her place. If I&apos;m going to have to train these slaves myself, I should get a discount.</string>
  <string id="18781" soundid="112002">I don&apos;t want to be a slave! I just want to get out of this place!</string>
  <string id="18782" soundid="112003"></string>
  <string id="18783" soundid="112004">Get away from my daughter, you wretched man!</string>
  <string id="18784" soundid="112005">You? What are you doing here? How did you get away from the guards? Why aren&apos;t you with the rest of the slaves?</string>
  <string id="18785" soundid="112006">The guards are dead, Lun. The slaves are free, and more than a few of them are looking for you. You don&apos;t want them to find you.</string>
  <string id="18786" soundid="112007">No, this can&apos;t be! I... I have to get out of here!</string>
  <string id="18787" soundid="172548">They... they change when I talk about them. I don&apos;t think we should mention them very much any more.</string>
  <string id="18788" soundid="85268">You killed him! I&apos;ve... I&apos;ve never seen such violence! </string>
  <string id="18789" soundid="85269">Quiet, girl! A slave doesn&apos;t speak unless spoken to!</string>
  <string id="18790" soundid="85270">Hey, I know you! Mother and I met you when we were trying to get out of Tien&apos;s Landing!</string>
  <string id="18791" soundid="85271">What? This is an outrage! Do you know how long I traveled to get here? Do you know how long I spent negotiating the purchase of these slaves?</string>
  <string id="18792" soundid="85272"></string>
  <string id="18793" soundid="85273">I see you have a good nose for business, and slaves are the best business in the Empire. I&apos;ll give you the same price I was going to give Gao for this girl.</string>
  <string id="18794" soundid="85274">Excellent. Come, ladies. You will find I am a kind owner. You will only be beaten if you are bad, and my wife has promised not to lose her temper too often.</string>
  <string id="18795" soundid="85275">You would do well to curb your tongue, woman. That kind of talk will not sit well with my wife. Now, come with me. And if you give me any trouble, your daughter will pay dearly.</string>
  <string id="18796" soundid="85276">You heartless monster! I came to you for help, and you sold me to this vile, disgusting excuse for a man!</string>
  <string id="18797" soundid="85277"></string>
  <string id="18798" soundid="85278">Fight? What... do you mean?</string>
  <string id="18851" soundid="85279">What&apos;s the meaning of this? I had an agreement with Gao to purchase this girl!</string>
  <string id="18852" soundid="85280">What? This is preposterous! You would set this urchin on me with a knife? Are you mad?</string>
  <string id="18853" soundid="85281">Do I have to? I don&apos;t want to hurt anyone. Can&apos;t you just let me go?</string>
  <string id="18854" soundid="85282">I... I&apos;ll do it. If I have to.</string>
  <string id="18874" soundid="85284"></string>
  <string id="18875" soundid="172549">I... I don&apos;t know. It&apos;s like listening to the wind while people are yelling at you. The Guardian says... he says not to ask.</string>
  <string id="18906" soundid="21267">Useless marsh. I&apos;m sick of flushing out bandits just so he can chase down some farm girl. I&apos;d rather burn these reeds from the air.</string>
  <string id="18907" soundid="160083">Chai Ka: A troubling force was ejected. All is well now.</string>
  <string id="18908" soundid="160084">I am glad to see that Wild Flower appears well. It must have been a very disturbing experience.</string>
  <string id="18912" soundid="160085">No more than our own if we don&apos;t get moving.</string>
  <string id="18913" soundid="160086">Yes, while you were... elsewhere, a servant tried to warn me against entering my *own* home! We need to confront my father as soon as possible.</string>
  <string id="18923" soundid="115766">Thank you for the fight. Goodbye.</string>
  <string id="18927" soundid="21288">I swear, Dawn Star, my patience is running thin!</string>
  <string id="18928" soundid="21289">No. *No!*</string>
  <string id="18930" soundid="21291">Not you. Anyone but you! What are you doing here?</string>
  <string id="18931" soundid="21292">It seems Gao doesn&apos;t think much about anything.</string>
  <string id="18932" soundid="21293">Ha ha! I understand more than you! I did you a favor, but you are too stupid to know a good thing when you are in its grasp!</string>
  <string id="18933" soundid="21294">Being kidnapped was a good thing? You have an odd view of what it takes to impress a woman.</string>
  <string id="18934" soundid="21295">Fools! You&apos;d be dead if it wasn&apos;t for me! Everything you have is gone! My father has seen to that!</string>
  <string id="18935" soundid="21296">You&apos;ll see. Death comes from above to ferret out your hidden master and his real name!</string>
  <string id="18936" soundid="21297">Dawn Star was the only thing I wanted to save, and what thanks do I get? Nothing! So be it, I&apos;ll just kill you all and forget your pitiful little village ever existed!</string>
  <string id="18937" soundid="21298">You&apos;ll see. You&apos;ve already lost, no matter what happens here. You&apos;ll see. I&apos;ll make you see!</string>
  <string id="18938" soundid="21299">You don&apos;t have a choice! I won&apos;t let you walk away this time!</string>
  <string id="18939" soundid="21300">Good! There&apos;s no Master Li to restrict how I fight. I&apos;ll kill you in time to see the red sky over your village!</string>
  <string id="18940" soundid="21301">Then fight, and we&apos;ll see who is better outside your pretty school. Even if you win, you&apos;ve lost elsewhere.</string>
  <string id="18941" soundid="21302">It has already begun! You&apos;ll see. Death comes from above to ferret out your hidden Master and his real name!</string>
  <string id="18942" soundid="21303">You see that, Gao? That&apos;s loyalty and responsibility. Can you even understand those words?</string>
  <string id="18943" soundid="21304">An errand? I hope saving me means more than that.</string>
  <string id="18944" soundid="21305">Ha! You see! I did you a favor, but you are too stupid to know a good thing when you are in its grasp!</string>
  <string id="18951">Chasing a fool. Did you think you could get away with this?</string>
  <string id="18955">What are you talking about, Gao?</string>
  <string id="18957">What have you done, Gao?</string>
  <string id="18958">I don&apos;t want to fight you again, Gao.</string>
  <string id="18959">Let&apos;s settle this, Gao. One on one.</string>
  <string id="18960">Commoner</string>
  <string id="18961">I&apos;m getting sick of your raving, Gao.</string>
  <string id="18962">Empty threats from a beaten man.</string>
  <string id="18964">You took something very important to me. I&apos;d follow you forever.</string>
  <string id="18966">Wasting my time on another errand, and all because of you.</string>
  <string id="19028" soundid="21389">Go away.</string>
  <string id="19029" soundid="21390">You&apos;ve done it all, youngster. You&apos;ve saved an entire town. You are the hero we needed eighteen years ago. Better late than never, eh?</string>
  <string id="19033" soundid="21394">Eighteen years ago, Emperor Sun was young and flush with success from ending the drought. He began public works all over the Empire, including the Great Dam down-river.</string>
  <string id="19034" soundid="21395">The workmen came and started building it near our town. We were not engineers and so we were not sure what it would mean. Some worried that it might flood us out.</string>
  <string id="19036" soundid="21397">Most were unconcerned. After all, if there were any danger the Emperor would tell us, surely. One day, the Great Dam was finished. And the floodgates were closed.</string>
  <string id="19037" soundid="21398">The town... the town flooded. We took what we could and fled. Mothers ran about screaming for their children who had gone out to play. Children screamed for their dogs.</string>
  <string id="19038" soundid="21399">Some folks climbed to the roofs of their houses and refused to leave. We survivors straggled upriver... some collapsed from exhaustion, but the water kept rising.</string>
  <string id="19040" soundid="21401">I carried a boy and a girl. I saw another boy fall, but I couldn&apos;t carry him. Finally, I fell over too. When I woke, I found the water had stopped rising.</string>
  <string id="19041" soundid="21402">The Great Dam had created an enormous lake, and we settled our new town on the banks. The lake completely covered the ruins of our town.</string>
  <string id="19042" soundid="21403">The crewmen who manned the Great Dam would come to town sometimes, but they knew no more than we. I will go to my grave never knowing.</string>
  <string id="19044" soundid="21405">The people started a new life here. But there was much pain and sorrow. Conversations would trail off. At night you could hear women sobbing... and not a few men.</string>
  <string id="19045" soundid="21406">Finally, people stopped talking about the past, and then they refused to talk about it all together. Eventually they pretended it never happened.</string>
  <string id="19046" soundid="21407">You look like you know how to fight. You look like you can stand up for yourself. So you don&apos;t understand: We are villagers.</string>
  <string id="19047" soundid="21408">We farm and fish. We live at the mercy of the gods, nature, and the Emperor. If one or all of these masters is kind, it is good.</string>
  <string id="19048" soundid="21409">If one or all choose to be cruel, well, there&apos;s nothing we can do about it. We just have to get the fish hauled in.</string>
  <string id="19049" soundid="21410">Mm. A few months ago, the Emperor&apos;s engineers and soldiers left. They just went off in the night. Soon after, the Great Dam opened on its own.</string>
  <string id="19050" soundid="21411">There wasn&apos;t anyone around. The water drained, revealing the old ruins. Underwater these eighteen years, and now they&apos;re back.</string>
  <string id="19051" soundid="21412">I don&apos;t know what made the Great Dam open. Some say it was ghosts. They say those who died in the town don&apos;t want to be forgotten.</string>
  <string id="19053" soundid="21414">We don&apos;t know how. We are simple people, and the Great Dam is not a simple thing. They say there is magic involved in its construction.</string>
  <string id="19055" soundid="21416">Thank you for listening, youngster. Not many do anymore.</string>
  <string id="19056" soundid="21417">I don&apos;t know that you&apos;re wrong. But everyone has to make their own choices. Pray you never have to make some of the choices I have.</string>
  <string id="19060">Villager</string>
  <string id="19062" soundid="21423">Away with you then, youngster. Turn your back on Old Wei.</string>
  <string id="19063" soundid="21424">Well, well. Took care of those pirates, did you? A fine job. If only that dam were closed up. This would be a nice place to live again.</string>
  <string id="19064" soundid="21425">Well, you took care of the dam! Good job, youngster. Never thought I&apos;d be glad to see that dam closed up.</string>
  <string id="19065" soundid="21426">You again? What do you want now?</string>
  <string id="19066" soundid="21427">I may have one foot in the grave, but my mind is still sharp. Pray you can say the same when you&apos;ve seen as many years as I have, youngster!</string>
  <string id="19068" soundid="21429">Yes, youngster, I was. Still remember it like yesterday. This town, Tien&apos;s Landing, used to be where the three plateaus come together down river. It was a fine town.</string>
  <string id="19069" soundid="21430">Let&apos;s see what you have there... oh. </string>
  <string id="19070" soundid="21431">Yes, yes it&apos;s mine. She was my wife, and she didn&apos;t make it out of the rising waters.</string>
  <string id="19071" soundid="21432">I can&apos;t tell you what this means to me. After all these years, there are no words. Thank you. Thank you.</string>
  <string id="19072" soundid="21433">You would hold this hostage? I&apos;m an old man with nothing left but my memories of a better time. Don&apos;t do this.</string>
  <string id="19073" soundid="21434">I... I... very well, I will give you all I have. Take it.</string>
  <string id="19074" soundid="21435">Thank you. You are not a very nice person, but you have brought me comfort anyway.</string>
  <string id="19075" soundid="21436">What... but I... you are a monster! I have seen terrible things in my life, but you are the worst. Your ancestors are weeping with shame.</string>
  <string id="19076" soundid="21437">Eh? What do you want?</string>
  <string id="19077" soundid="21438">I&apos;m Wei. Some call me Old Wei, but that&apos;s because they don&apos;t know Old Chan. If I&apos;m old, he&apos;s ancient. He&apos;s at least a week older than me.</string>
  <string id="19078" soundid="21439">Of course, we&apos;re both pretty old compared to most of the people in Tien&apos;s Landing. Why, most of them don&apos;t even remember what it was like before the flood.</string>
  <string id="19081" soundid="141541">I know you held it until recently, but Kia Min has a knack for group fights, and she set a new bar just yesterday.</string>
  <string id="19087">Surprised you remember me, at your age.</string>
  <string id="19095">What happened?</string>
  <string id="19099">Go on.</string>
  <string id="19102">No one here will talk about the ruins.</string>
  <string id="19104">You never sought revenge for the flooding of your town?</string>
  <string id="19107">I saw the ruins on my way here. They aren&apos;t underwater.</string>
  <string id="19112">Why hasn&apos;t anyone closed the gates?</string>
  <string id="19114">Thank you for telling me your story.</string>
  <string id="19115">You peasants deserve whatever happens to you!</string>
  <string id="19117">Slave</string>
  <string id="19123" soundid="152422">We were talking about Gao earlier, but now isn&apos;t really the time to finish that conversation.</string>
  <string id="19124">Goodbye.</string>
  <string id="19125">Were you here during the flood?</string>
  <string id="19128">I found this portrait in the ruins. Is it yours?</string>
  <string id="19129">Looks familiar?</string>
  <string id="19130">At least you&apos;ll have this to remember her by. Take it.</string>
  <string id="19131">You can have it back for only a bit of silver.</string>
  <string id="19132">Well if you&apos;re going to whine, just take it.</string>
  <string id="19133">You&apos;ll treasure it more if you pay a dear price for it.</string>
  <string id="19134">And here you go. A pleasure doing business with you.</string>
  <string id="19135">Thank you for the silver. I&apos;ve decided to keep the portrait.</string>
  <string id="19136">I was just curious. I&apos;m going to keep it.</string>
  <string id="19137">So is it yours or not? I don&apos;t have all day old man.</string>
  <string id="19138">Who are you?</string>
  <string id="19141">I think I&apos;ve heard enough blather for one lifetime.</string>
  <string id="19154">Tavern Keeper</string>
  <string id="19178">In the traditional stance for the long sword, the wielder keeps their body loose, with the blade held above the head. This allows the swordsman to make long sweeping cuts, keeping his foes off balance. Wielders of the long sword move with a stylized grace, virtually dancing about the battlefield. Their blades shine in the sun as their beautiful attacks cut a deadly swath through their mesmerized foes.</string>
  <string id="19179">Long Sword</string>
  <string id="19181">Heaven</string>
  <string id="19188" soundid="127792">You sure are pretty. Just like those ladies on the corner the sailors always talk to.</string>
  <string id="19189" soundid="127793">You look lonely. You should go see those ladies the sailors always talk to. They seem real friendly.</string>
  <string id="19190">Messenger</string>
  <string id="19200">E3 Demo 1 description. STRREF 19200</string>
  <string id="19201" soundid="21616">Aw, don&apos;t be like that!</string>
  <string id="19202" soundid="21617">Yeah, we&apos;re nice guys. Don&apos;t pretend you&apos;re better than us!</string>
  <string id="19203" soundid="21618">Yeah! We don&apos;t want to be stuck in your stuck-up town either, you know!</string>
  <string id="19204" soundid="21619"></string>
  <string id="19205" soundid="21620">Yeah, you people need to relax! Have some wine with us!</string>
  <string id="19206" soundid="21621">Yeah, you need wine, sweetie!</string>
  <string id="19209" soundid="21624">Yes? What... what... do you want?</string>
  <string id="19210" soundid="21625">Kill me? Now that reminds me of my favorite song. &quot;I&apos;m a sailor fine... and I like my wine... on the water blue....&quot; Do you know the rest of the words?</string>
  <string id="19211" soundid="21626">&quot;...sleeping it off... on the water blue... I knew a sailor named....&quot; Are you sure you don&apos;t know the... the... what do you call them?</string>
  <string id="19212" soundid="21627">Yes... the words. Don&apos;t you know them?</string>
  <string id="19213" soundid="21628"></string>
  <string id="19214" soundid="21629">No, that&apos;s not the word. Word! That&apos;s the word... don&apos;t you know... the words....</string>
  <string id="19217">E3 Demo 2 Description - STRREF 19217</string>
  <string id="19218">E3 Demo 3 Description - STRREF 19218</string>
  <string id="19221" soundid="196466"></string>
  <string id="19222">Back Office</string>
  <string id="19223">Lucky Cho&apos;s Office</string>
  <string id="19224">Black Market Section</string>
  <string id="19225">Fight Office</string>
  <string id="19227">If I ever see you harassing a woman again, I will kill you.</string>
  <string id="19228">Make sense, you drunken idiot!</string>
  <string id="19229">&apos;Words.&apos;</string>
  <string id="19231">Idiot.</string>
  <string id="19232">You&apos;d better try to sleep that off.</string>
  <string id="19233">You let that one get away? I think she liked the attention.</string>
  <string id="19234">You said something about being stuck here? Why?</string>
  <string id="19236" soundid="168478"></string>
  <string id="19237" soundid="21652">Hey... honora... honor... person.</string>
  <string id="19238" soundid="21653">Yes.</string>
  <string id="19239" soundid="21654">I have to... go.</string>
  <string id="19240" soundid="21655">I am very pleased for you.</string>
  <string id="19241" soundid="21656">You have to help me.</string>
  <string id="19242" soundid="21657">Excuse me?</string>
  <string id="19243" soundid="21658">You know... you have to let me use your outhouse....</string>
  <string id="19244" soundid="21659">That is for my family only. Why don&apos;t you go back to your ship?</string>
  <string id="19245" soundid="21660">I know! I&apos;ll... go... on your sandals. Yeah, that&apos;s what I&apos;ll do....</string>
  <string id="19246" soundid="21661">Wait! Wait, stop. Very well, you can use my outhouse. Follow me.</string>
  <string id="19247" soundid="21662"></string>
  <string id="19248" soundid="21663">Hey... what are we having for dinner?  Hey, do you have a sister?</string>
  <string id="19249" soundid="21664"></string>
  <string id="19250" soundid="168479"></string>
  <string id="19253">Nothing? Impossible!</string>
  <string id="19254">For Death&apos;s Hand!</string>
  <string id="19271">Distortion Blast</string>
  <string id="19275">Distortion Wave</string>
  <string id="19312" soundid="113352">I promised to close the dam and save the town. Truth is, I wish I&apos;d never told anyone what I was going to do. I was a bit drunk when I said it. But I can&apos;t back out now!</string>
  <string id="19326" soundid="113353">Everybody thinks I&apos;m just a worthless drunk. But when I close the dam, they&apos;ll think I&apos;m a hero! I just need a few drinks to get my courage up before I go.</string>
  <string id="19342" soundid="113354">But I promised to close the dam, and I can&apos;t go back on that now. The town is counting on me. I just need another drink or two before I go.</string>
  <string id="19356" soundid="113355">[Success] Now, now... no need to get upset. I&apos;m drunk, but I&apos;m not unreasonable. If you really want to go that badly, I&apos;ll take you. You can work out some of that anger on the pirates.</string>
  <string id="19372" soundid="22016">Heard somebody took care of them pirates. Hope they got what they deserved!</string>
  <string id="19376">Kill the Spirit</string>
  <string id="19435" soundid="113495">Daoshen? He has angled for a long time for our permission to run a larger game. He&apos;s honest to a fault, but he still pulls in a fair bit of cash.</string>
  <string id="19436" soundid="113496">I was wondering if he&apos;d be resourceful enough. One of my associates has already told him of the cost involved. Are you here to deliver his payment?</string>
  <string id="19437" soundid="21852">I&apos;m a cap&apos;n.</string>
  <string id="19438" soundid="21853">You&apos;re not a captain.</string>
  <string id="19439" soundid="21854">Oh yes, I am.</string>
  <string id="19440" soundid="21855">Where&apos;s your captain&apos;s hat?</string>
  <string id="19441" soundid="21856">Well, where&apos;s *your* capn&apos; hat?</string>
  <string id="19442" soundid="21857">I&apos;m not a captain.</string>
  <string id="19443" soundid="21858"></string>
  <string id="19444" soundid="21859">Okay then.</string>
  <string id="19445" soundid="21860"></string>
  <string id="19446" soundid="189943"></string>
  <string id="19447" soundid="113498">On a single bet? That&apos;s hard to believe, but this purse is one of Daoshen&apos;s. If what you say is true, he&apos;s chosen to defy us. We&apos;ll have to make an example of him.</string>
  <string id="19452">Water Buffalo</string>
  <string id="19455">Goat</string>
  <string id="19457" soundid="113500">His payment? Good. Give it to me, and I&apos;ll send someone to go discuss the new terms of his operation. Now back to our business, yes?</string>
  <string id="19481" soundid="21896"></string>
  <string id="19510">Review the List</string>
  <string id="19511" soundid="106770">You need to talk to Qui the Promoter. He&apos;ll start you out. It&apos;ll be great to have someone new around the place.</string>
  <string id="19513" soundid="106772">Our current Emperor has not shown as much interest in the past decade or so.</string>
  <string id="19514" soundid="21929">Stop right there! I gave you two extra duty. Get back to that galley and start cleaning!</string>
  <string id="19515" soundid="21930">We don&apos;t have to listen you, Ing. You&apos;re a captain without a ship! She&apos;s nothing but a landlocked house now.</string>
  <string id="19517" soundid="21932">I will discover a way to free this ship. Until then, you had better follow orders.</string>
  <string id="19518" soundid="21933">I&apos;ve had enough of you and your orders!</string>
  <string id="19521" soundid="124878">I&apos;m afraid that wouldn&apos;t help, living one. It must be Kindly Yushan himself who does this. Our deaths are on his hands, so he must do the burial.</string>
  <string id="19523" soundid="21938">Now get back in that ship. I&apos;m your captain, understand?</string>
  <string id="19525" soundid="21940">You&apos;re still the captain... for now. But if you don&apos;t get us out of this town soon, you&apos;re going to have a mutiny on your hands. Then we&apos;ll see what&apos;s what.</string>
  <string id="19531" soundid="144607">Well, it&apos;s my life&apos;s work, that&apos;s for sure. And with the way all these spirits have been rising up, it&apos;ll probably be my death&apos;s work, as well. Eh-heheh.</string>
  <string id="19536">You found another piece of the amulet and unlocked two more gem slots.</string>
  <string id="19539" soundid="124879">I... I don&apos;t know where Yushan is now. When the flood came, I prayed he would save us. But he never showed up. Maybe he tried....</string>
  <string id="19541" soundid="124880">Questions? There is little we could tell you, big person. We are trapped here, in the ruins of the orphanage. We can&apos;t leave, and we can&apos;t rest until Kindly Yushan buries our bones.</string>
  <string id="19547" soundid="127099">True, but that can become a convenient excuse. Eventually, you may decide that even direct violence is too inefficient for someone of your strength.</string>
  <string id="19548" soundid="127100">It is a small leap from there to enforcing your will so that the crime never takes place. Suddenly, you are the oppressor, when all you wanted to do was make things right.</string>
  <string id="19549" soundid="127101">This Way of the Open Palm is not without its hidden dangers, despite the best of intentions.</string>
  <string id="19550" soundid="127102">It is the &quot;low path,&quot; the way of aggression and discord. A misunderstood path often misused by those who wish to justify a thuggish nature.</string>
  <string id="19551" soundid="127103">It is not as simple as crushing your enemies, or as mindless as terrorizing the weak. It is a mindset born of impatience, of imposing your will.</string>
  <string id="19552" soundid="127104">An evil man might ignore a plea for help because he does not care, but that shows a disconnection with the world. That is not part of the Way.</string>
  <string id="19553" soundid="127105">A man on the &quot;low path&quot; might also ignore that plea, but he would do so because that person should demonstrate they are fit to survive on their own.</string>
  <string id="19554" soundid="127106">The difference is in the details. That same man might help if the odds are unreasonable. He might also do it to incur favor. There is thought in his actions.</string>
  <string id="19556" soundid="126507">You killed her? I didn&apos;t want that! I just wanted her to leave Lan and me alone. This... this is horrible! I&apos;ve known her since we were children!</string>
  <string id="19557" soundid="126508">We grew up together; her family lived right next to mine. What am I going to tell Ai Ling&apos;s mother the next time I see her? I... I can&apos;t believe you killed her.</string>
  <string id="19560" soundid="126511"></string>
  <string id="19561" soundid="126512"></string>
  <string id="19567" soundid="126518">I guess I should thank you. I just wish there could have been some other way. I... I should go tell Ai Ling&apos;s family what happened.</string>
  <string id="19568" soundid="126519">Reward? For killing Ai Ling? You&apos;re... you&apos;re a monster! Whatever deal you had with Lan, I want no part of it! Go talk to her for your reward.</string>
  <string id="19569">Ai Ling is dead.</string>
  <string id="19570" soundid="127107">He is not a mindless killer, but he may let strength decide what course is best. That is why it is a dangerous path. It can so easily be misinterpreted.</string>
  <string id="19571" soundid="127108">You are the sum of your actions. The harmony or discord that you sow will weigh on your shoulders as surely as any physical yoke.</string>
  <string id="19572" soundid="127109">But... there can be advantages. Certain forms of attack inherently lean toward one extreme or the other. They have a rhythm that resonates within you.</string>
  <string id="19573" soundid="127110">You may find that some attacks perform better if you are... more intent on causing discord. How you use this is for you to discover and decide.</string>
  <string id="19574" soundid="127111">Who are you interested in?</string>
  <string id="19575" soundid="127112">Master Li is a private man, and I will not presume to speak for him. His interest in you surpasses the care of any master I have known. He must see great potential in you.</string>
  <string id="19577" soundid="127114">I&apos;d rather not. He is impatiently traveling the low path, and I long ago abandoned him to it. He is reckless, and he neither seeks nor wants my guidance.</string>
  <string id="19578" soundid="127115">As young as he is, Gao has impressive skill. Master Li has tried to restrain him, but I know how far he has gone. He weilds powerful energies but has the temper of a child.</string>
  <string id="19579" soundid="127116">You have seen a small part of what Gao conceals. Master Li wisely forbids such displays, but I know how far he has gone. Gao has great skill but the temper of a child.</string>
  <string id="19580" soundid="189732"></string>
  <string id="19581" soundid="127118">Master Li has taught the base of such techniques to you and others--mastering chi is important for any student here--but he also demands control.</string>
  <string id="19582" soundid="127119">Gao&apos;s father most likely tutored him. By all that I have heard, both are impatient and spoiled. They can be provoked into... explosive outbursts.</string>
  <string id="19583" soundid="127120">Only what she lets me know. A very private woman, despite spending so long in the school. You probably know her as well as anyone does.</string>
  <string id="19602">Cook Teh</string>
  <string id="19603" soundid="44582">Bah! Do you shrink from the challenge? This is how true leaders of the battlefield fight. Rise up or step aside.</string>
  <string id="19605" soundid="44583">You have offended me, fool. So be it, you&apos;ll face my full wrath in the closest location with room for proper maneuvers. Mirabelle will sit you down!</string>
  <string id="19606">Save</string>
  <string id="19620">Tien&apos;s Landing</string>
  <string id="19624">You resist me well...</string>
  <string id="19628">Sailor</string>
  <string id="19634" soundid="44584">What? Oh, this is simply a waste of my time. What could you possibly gain by my taking a switch to your hindquarters?</string>
  <string id="19641">Return to Hui</string>
  <string id="19645">Boy</string>
  <string id="19648">Fast Shin</string>
  <string id="19649">Fortunate Puzzle</string>
  <string id="19659" soundid="44585">Haven&apos;t you been schooled enough? I understand you would be upset, but this won&apos;t help matters.</string>
  <string id="19660" soundid="44586">Hrmph! You&apos;re all set on this, are you? All right, I&apos;ll have at you, but it&apos;s beyond me why you&apos;d march to the slaughter like this.</string>
  <string id="19674">Why didn&apos;t I hurt you?</string>
  <string id="19675">I won&apos;t be beaten!</string>
  <string id="19676">I&apos;ll show you!</string>
  <string id="19681">Leave without saving</string>
  <string id="19684">Save changes?</string>
  <string id="19686">Gao&apos;s Lieutenant</string>
  <string id="19687" soundid="44587">The entry hall here has walls to be up against, corners to be backed into, and floor enough on which to be down but not out. Whatever your metaphor, I&apos;ll beat it.</string>
  <string id="19688" soundid="44588">Return to me when you are ready and we will walk there together. Just to ensure that no one gets lost, or suffers an accident that would prevent a fair fight.</string>
  <string id="19689">You won&apos;t beat me!</string>
  <string id="19690">This is where you fall!</string>
  <string id="19691">Press BACK to pause combat. You can switch styles while paused.</string>
  <string id="19692" soundid="44590">Frankly, I don&apos;t know what you people are capable of.</string>
  <string id="19693" soundid="44591">What? Good. Let&apos;s get this over with so I can return to schooling the rest of your fellows.</string>
  <string id="19695">Cunning Keyi</string>
  <string id="19703" soundid="44592">I envy you. You are about to experience for the first time the skill that has forged an empire and traveled the world.</string>
  <string id="19705" soundid="44593">There will be pain as well, but I imagine it will be almost worth it.</string>
  <string id="19871" soundid="141833">Well fought, my student, but I cannot risk you against a foe like this yet.</string>
  <string id="19875" soundid="22890">Out of our way, woman! In this town we don&apos;t step aside for you... you step aside for us!</string>
  <string id="19876" soundid="22891">The peasants of this village may cower before you, but I do not. If you are smart, you will apologize for your behavior and walk away.</string>
  <string id="19877" soundid="22892">Don&apos;t tell me what to do! You think I won&apos;t hit a woman? You have to learn your place! This whole town has to learn its place!</string>
  <string id="19878" soundid="22893"></string>
  <string id="19880">Follower Gained</string>
  <string id="19884" soundid="160738">Allow me to answer that, Lord.</string>
  <string id="19885" soundid="160739">While it seems that you&apos;ve solved the problem with the forest, that doesn&apos;t mean the ghosts will simply up and leave.</string>
  <string id="19886" soundid="160740">If we&apos;re lucky, then you&apos;ve stopped things from getting worse, and time will provide the cure.</string>
  <string id="19887">Do you think this forest will be passable any time soon?</string>
  <string id="19890" soundid="22905"></string>
  <string id="19906">Superior Warrior Gem</string>
  <string id="19907" soundid="22922">You really shouldn&apos;t waste your time here in this teahouse. The Lotus Assassins are searching the ruins for the missing piece of your amulet. You must find the pieces before they do.</string>
  <string id="19916">Missing Gem</string>
  <string id="19919">This gem looks like the others used in furnaces near the Forest Shadow&apos;s temple, but it is shaped differently, as if it were designed to be mounted in a pedestal.</string>
  <string id="19924" soundid="163962">Well, it&apos;s good to see our new bounty hunter was able to bring you in. Frankly, Aishi, I thought you&apos;d fight to the death. You weren&apos;t this weak when we....</string>
  <string id="19928">Flawless Warrior Gem</string>
  <string id="19929">Superior Monk Gem</string>
  <string id="19947">Flawless Monk Gem</string>
  <string id="19948">Superior Scholar Gem</string>
  <string id="19950" soundid="23112">Twenty silver for one bowl, honored stranger, in advance. But we have other matters to discuss: I need the help of someone like you. Someone sharp and fast.</string>
  <string id="19951">Darting Lynx</string>
  <string id="19952" soundid="23114">That is what the market will bear. I&apos;m but a slave to the market forces. Now, if it wouldn&apos;t trouble you, I need the help of someone who can get things done.</string>
  <string id="19953" soundid="66400">Oh! Hello. I&apos;m sorry, I was just muttering to myself. I am in some trouble and.... Wait! You! You could help me!</string>
  <string id="19954" soundid="66401">You&apos;re clearly not from around the Imperial City, and I need someone&apos;s help most desperately, someone unaffected by the politics of this place.</string>
  <string id="19958" soundid="23120">A pleasure doing business with you.</string>
  <string id="19959" soundid="23121">It is good to talk with you again. I hope you have not forgotten my earlier business proposition regarding the Great Dam.</string>
  <string id="19960" soundid="23122">Excellent. I&apos;ll just take that; no need for any unpleasant reminders lying around.</string>
  <string id="19961" soundid="23123">Here is the silver I promised you: twenty percent of my profits to date. Now, is there anything else I can do for you?</string>
  <string id="19963" soundid="23125">It is a simple matter. The Great Dam is open, and these sailors are trapped in our town. I make a very nice amount of silver selling wine to them.</string>
  <string id="19966" soundid="23128">Greetings, stranger. I noticed you speaking with Minister Sheng. I wonder if I could have but a moment of your time.</string>
  <string id="19967" soundid="23129">I am Merchant Jiang, wineseller. I serve the community by entertaining these sailors trapped in our town. I need the help of someone with a steely eye and a steady hand. </string>
  <string id="19968" soundid="23130">I simply fill a need the best way I can. What is the crime in that? Now, you seem a capable young woman, and I really need some help.</string>
  <string id="19969" soundid="23131">We all must have our little secrets. How I conduct my trade is mine. Now, I need the help of someone with... discretion</string>
  <string id="19970" soundid="23132">Ah, you have a sharp eye. Yes, I am a merchant. However, there is nothing to see, only something to drink. I sell quality wine, and lots of it.</string>
  <string id="19971" soundid="23133">This is an excellent time to be a wine merchant. The sailors trapped in our town were on the river for quite a long time, and they had saved up massive amounts of silver.</string>
  <string id="19972" soundid="23134">I saw you speaking with Minister Sheng, worthy one. I suspect he asked you to go out to the Great Dam and close it. Am I right?</string>
  <string id="19973">None of the dead can find peace right now.</string>
  <string id="19974" soundid="23136">I want you to destroy the controls of the Great Dam, leaving it forever open. Then there will be no danger of some adventurer coming by and closing it.</string>
  <string id="19977" soundid="127291">He is greatly skilled and tutors his students intently. You especially. My school in the city was mired in politics. Not an environment that promotes diligent study.</string>
  <string id="19978" soundid="23140">Don&apos;t be so dramatic! I know that some think this river situation is fatal, but they are overreacting. They cannot adapt to the new realities.</string>
  <string id="19979" soundid="105620">The crowds won&apos;t forget that anytime soon. The Silver Division is yours now. Treat it well.</string>
  <string id="19980" soundid="39612">It is vital that we talk a moment.</string>
  <string id="19982">It&apos;s right here.</string>
  <string id="19985">What did you need again?</string>
  <string id="19990">Who are you?</string>
  <string id="19991">It seems to me that you are making a killing off the situation.</string>
  <string id="19992">Where does your wine come from? The town is cut off.</string>
  <string id="19993">Let me see your wares, merchant.</string>
  <string id="19994">What sort of help do you need?</string>
  <string id="19998">I&apos;m not going to doom this entire town!</string>
  <string id="20000">Do you have any impressions of Gao?</string>
  <string id="20001" soundid="190091">Hmm, well, if you say so. Despite Lord Rento&apos;s insistence to the contrary, I doubt he was a master criminal. Perhaps I&apos;ll just declare Yukong&apos;s bounty a dead matter.</string>
  <string id="20002">Why me?</string>
  <string id="20004">Silk Fox</string>
  <string id="20005">What&apos;ll you give me if I do this?</string>
  <string id="20006">Very well, I&apos;ll do it.</string>
  <string id="20007">I want no part of this.</string>
  <string id="20008" soundid="166108">It is time to end your meddling!</string>
  <string id="20009">Exactly how much *are* you selling your wine for?</string>
  <string id="20012">Bandit Lieutenant</string>
  <string id="20013">Twenty silver! That&apos;s outrageous!</string>
  <string id="20018">Just tell me what you want.</string>
  <string id="20020">Forest</string>
  <string id="20110">Tien&apos;s Landing</string>
  <string id="20111" soundid="23280">Hello, hello! Don&apos;t think I am ungrateful for your earlier efforts. I do, however, have much to do. Was any man ever so eternally busy as Minister Sheng?</string>
  <string id="20112" soundid="23281">You did it! How the people will sing the praises of Minister Sheng, who found, hired, and sent forth the helpful peasant who ultimately solved the problem!</string>
  <string id="20113">This bar is made of iron alloyed with nickel, producing a far stronger metal referred to by some smiths as &quot;steeled iron&quot; or simply &quot;steel.&quot;</string>
  <string id="20114">The yellow-tinged water in this vial has a strong stench, similar to that of a rotten egg.</string>
  <string id="20115">Used to treat conditions of the blood and circulation, a cow bezoar forms only in the stomach of very ill cattle. Cow bezoars are extremely rare, but many seek them for their curative nature.</string>
  <string id="20116">Kang called these gems the Eyes of the Void. They don&apos;t appear to have any conventional value, but they may produce something extraordinary if used in Lord Lao&apos;s Furnace.</string>
  <string id="20118">LL Reward Effect 1 - Focus Increase</string>
  <string id="20119">LL Reward Effect 2 - Body Increase</string>
  <string id="20120">Lord Lao&apos;s Reward Effect 3 - Spirit Increase</string>
  <string id="20121">Lord Lao&apos;s Reward Effect 4 - Conversation Skill</string>
  <string id="20122">Lord Lao&apos;s Reward Item 1</string>
  <string id="20123">Lord Lao&apos;s Reward Item 2</string>
  <string id="20124">Lord Lao&apos;s Reward Item 3</string>
  <string id="20125">Lord Lao&apos;s Reward Item 4</string>
  <string id="20126">Temp: The Magic of Lord Lao&apos;s Wondrous Furnace has increased your Focus.</string>
  <string id="20127">Temp: The Magic of Lord Lao&apos;s Wondrous Furnace has increased your Body.</string>
  <string id="20128" soundid="23297">I suppose, in theory, you could find a flyer at the pirate camp upriver. In practice, however, I doubt you would find the pirates very accommodating.</string>
  <string id="20129" soundid="112537">Welcome! It&apos;s always good to see a new face at the counter. If you&apos;ve got silver to spend, I&apos;ll be happy to help you out!</string>
  <string id="20130">Temp: The Magic of Lord Lao&apos;s Wondrous Furnace has increased your Spirit.</string>
  <string id="20131" soundid="23300">The only approach is by river. But no sane bargeman would be willing to risk such a journey. Sane people don&apos;t go looking for the pirates, they avoid them.</string>
  <string id="20132" soundid="23301">I suppose Ru the Boatswain is mad enough to take you, if he&apos;s drunk. Hmmm... yes. Ru is surely the only one who would make the trip. And then the pirates would kill you.</string>
  <string id="20134">Temp: The Magic of Lord Lao&apos;s Wondrous Furnace has increased your Spirit.</string>
  <string id="20135" soundid="112538">I&apos;m known as Thunderous Taoran, and you are my most honored customer right now, so you have all of my attention.</string>
  <string id="20136">Temp for Item reward 1 from Lord Lao: The machine has produced a pair of boots perfect for jumping over the magic snake.</string>
  <string id="20137">Temp for LL Reward Item #2: The machine has given you the scythe of destruction. Ultima 6 fans, rejoice!</string>
  <string id="20138">Temp for Reward Item 3 from LLF: The machinery of Lord Lao&apos;s Furnace has produced The Magic Pickle. You may now solve any fetch and retrieve quest instantly.</string>
  <string id="20139" soundid="83229">Gone... she&apos;s gone. They took her away, my beautiful Fen, my Flower of the Fields.</string>
  <string id="20140" soundid="23309">The humiliation! That a dread and mighty lord such as I should be reduced to answering the questions of simple folk!</string>
  <string id="20141">Sweet Poison Lyn</string>
  <string id="20142" soundid="112458">I can climb up and pull the lever easily enough. You can open the door when it&apos;s unlocked.</string>
  <string id="20143">Temp for Item reward #4 from Lord Lao&apos;s Furnace: The machinery of Lord Lao&apos;s Wondrous Furnace has produced a Widget. This could come in handy if you were playing Space Quest 4, but then again, maybe not.</string>
  <string id="20144" soundid="23313">A ship was in port when the Great Dam opened and the river drained. Now it is trapped here. The sailors behaved for a time, but now they&apos;ve gone mad with boredom.</string>
  <string id="20145" soundid="23314">I&apos;m sure Captain Ing down by the pier would offer you some sort of reward to close the Great Dam and free his vessel. That is what we in the Ministry of Harmony call a hint.</string>
  <string id="20146">A cinnabar ingot</string>
  <string id="20147">I don&apos;t think of pirates as the ingenious type.</string>
  <string id="20149">Cinnabar is the ore from which mercury is extracted. Lord Lao&apos;s Wondrous Furnace uses these ingots as its primary fuel.</string>
  <string id="20150" soundid="23319">Make your way down river, enter the ruins--to which I *did not* give you the key--and search for some way to get up to the top of the Great Dam.</string>
  <string id="20151" soundid="23320">There you should find the controls to the Great Dam. I do not know what form these controls take, but I am sure you&apos;ll figure something out. Safe and easy, no?</string>
  <string id="20155" soundid="83230">Please, my name is Hing, and you must help me. My Fen is so delicate. She will chafe under a bandit&apos;s yoke.</string>
  <string id="20163" soundid="23332">A giant among men. Superb, the best emperor ever! Surely he will soon allow me to return to the Imperial City. Surely.</string>
  <string id="20165" soundid="23334">Of course, I hold all of the Emperor&apos;s advisors in the highest esteem. Death&apos;s Hand serves the Emperor, as do we all. He is a trifle... terrifying, however.</string>
  <string id="20166" soundid="23335">Ah, I miss it so. And it misses me, I am sure. A grand place, but I fear I shall never see it again. Even the mention of the name brings sorrow to Minister Sheng&apos;s heart.</string>
  <string id="20175">Attack: Dual Axes
Support: None
The Black Whirlwind&apos;s attacks can damage spirits. 

The Black Whirlwind is a warrior of exceptional girth and immeasurable brutality. In combat, his axes gleefully plow through enemies, not stopping until the red mists fade.</string>
  <string id="20176">Attack: Long Sword
Support: Recovers your Chi
Dawn Star&apos;s attacks can damage spirits. 

Dawn Star&apos;s magical sensitivity gives her added insight into the world around her. In battle she cuts swiftly with her long sword. 

</string>
  <string id="20177">Are you trying to take credit for my exploits?</string>
  <string id="20178">Isn&apos;t there a reward?</string>
  <string id="20179">I was happy to do my duty.</string>
  <string id="20198">I need to find a flyer.</string>
  <string id="20199" soundid="112539">Always--I say always--a pleasure to see a customer return for another visit.</string>
  <string id="20202" soundid="198511"></string>
  <string id="20205" soundid="83231">We were traveling to Two Rivers. I bring goods between the farms that line the valley.</string>
  <string id="20206" soundid="112540">Help yourself to a look. Guaranteed to have something for every fan of the Imperial Arena!</string>
  <string id="20208" soundid="112541">You look like a warrior to my eye, probably not fit for the odds and sods the usual patrons might pick up.</string>
  <string id="20213" soundid="83232">I knew we were getting too close to the marshes. Why was I so foolish? Of course these thieves would strike at my beautiful Fen.</string>
  <string id="20215" soundid="112461">Inquisitor Lim has his Assassins searching for something, though what it is I couldn&apos;t say. Minister Sheng knows better than to stick his nose in the business of the Lotus Assassins.</string>
  <string id="20217" soundid="112462">I didn&apos;t want the town to panic, so I kept Lim&apos;s presence here a secret. Better the peasants think it was ghosts... a much less terrifying idea.</string>
  <string id="20219">There seems to be a lot of drunken sailors around.</string>
  <string id="20222" soundid="112463">Inquisitor Lim has his Assassins searching for something, though what it is I couldn&apos;t say. Minister Sheng knows better than to stick his nose in the business of the Lotus Assassins.</string>
  <string id="20223" soundid="112464">Directions? Are you taunting Minister Sheng? This is not the Imperial City; one could hardly get lost in a place like this. Just look around, and you&apos;ll find what you seek.</string>
  <string id="20225">Tell me again what I have to do.</string>
  <string id="20227" soundid="112472">I don&apos;t know you, but you&apos;re in here, so I know you&apos;re not common street trash. I hope, for your sake, that you have enough silver to warrant my time.</string>
  <string id="20229" soundid="112473">When you deal with me, the fullness of your purse is of concern to both of us.</string>
  <string id="20230" soundid="83233">I can&apos;t leave without her. They&apos;ll work her to death, or eat her, or worse! Can you do anything? Please?</string>
  <string id="20239">What do you think of the Emperor?</string>
  <string id="20241">What do you know about Death&apos;s Hand?</string>
  <string id="20242">Tell me about the Imperial City.</string>
  <string id="20253" soundid="23422">Must I do everything myself? Never send an Imperial soldier to do the work of a lieutenant!</string>
  <string id="20258" soundid="174446">I know that his alliance with the Lotus Assassins has reached its logical conclusion. He was a valuable ally to their order; you have done well.</string>
  <string id="20259">Gold</string>
  <string id="20269" soundid="23438">You! What are you doing here? The quarry is ours! It was ours when we lived, and it&apos;s ours when we&apos;re dead!</string>
  <string id="20270" soundid="23439">I&apos;m Yuxi. Stabber Yuxi. Everyone was afraid of me when we were alive. Toughest convict on the chain gang.</string>
  <string id="20271" soundid="23440">Then the water came. Everyone ran, no one came to help the prisoners... except Turnkey. But I know he only came to laugh at us. So... Turnkey had to die.</string>
  <string id="20272" soundid="23441">Hurt... me? Hurt me? Hahahaha! You can&apos;t hurt me! I was the toughest convict on the chain gang when I was alive!</string>
  <string id="20273" soundid="23442">I&apos;m not a fiend... and I&apos;m already dead. And now you will join us!</string>
  <string id="20274">Who are you?</string>
  <string id="20276">Stay back. I don&apos;t want to hurt you.</string>
  <string id="20277">Die, fiend!</string>
  <string id="20278" soundid="23447">Strangler Jizu smells something fresh.</string>
  <string id="20279" soundid="23448">Strangler Jizu is king in this place. Alive, king of the prisoners alive. Dead, king of the prisoners dead.</string>
  <string id="20282" soundid="23451">Water come. People leave Strangler Jizu and other prisoners to die. Water come faster. We scramble, run, claw each other.</string>
  <string id="20283" soundid="23452">Then water everywhere. But we not die. Strangler Jizu has too much hate to die.</string>
  <string id="20284" soundid="23453">Strangler Jizu is king in this place. King of the prisoners, king of the dead. Dead serve Jizu.</string>
  <string id="20285" soundid="23454">And now you join Strangler Jizu&apos;s subjects.</string>
  <string id="20286" soundid="23455">You not know? Strangler Jizu... not die.</string>
  <string id="20287">Who are you?</string>
  <string id="20291">What happened here?</string>
  <string id="20293">Who are you?</string>
  <string id="20295">Die, foul spirit!</string>
  <string id="20297" soundid="23466">Unngghh. Who&apos;s that? I can&apos;t see you.... Is somebody there? What do you want?</string>
  <string id="20298" soundid="23467">I am... I am... I think I am Turnkey Shiji? Is that right? Yes, I am Turnkey Shiji. I guard the prisoners.</string>
  <string id="20299" soundid="23468">Drowned? Yes, I remember! The water rushing in, everybody running... I went back for the prisoners. They were bad men, but no one deserves to die like that.</string>
  <string id="20300" soundid="23469">I went to free them. I freed Strangler Jizu first and then... and then... he put his hands around my throat. I couldn&apos;t breathe and he... he killed me.</string>
  <string id="20305" soundid="23474">Happened? I don&apos;t remember. This... is the quarry where the prisoners are chained up. I&apos;m Turnkey Shiji... I guard them. I remember... I remember the water rising.</string>
  <string id="20306" soundid="23475">Everyone ran, but I came back for the prisoners. I had the only key. They are bad men, but no one deserves to die like that.</string>
  <string id="20307" soundid="23476">Ghosts? I don&apos;t... ghosts? I don&apos;t remember. I am... I am... I think I am Turnkey Shiji? Is that right? Yes, I am Turnkey Shiji, and I guard the prison.</string>
  <string id="20308">Who are you?</string>
  <string id="20309">The prisoners are dead. They drowned.</string>
  <string id="20318">Never turn your back on a criminal.</string>
  <string id="20319">What happened here?</string>
  <string id="20321">You seem different than the other ghosts.</string>
  <string id="20407" soundid="105593">Hold!</string>
  <string id="20408">Yifong&apos;s daughter Fuyao was on the verge of being tortured by a pirate slave breaker in the Pirate Lair. You killed the slave breaker, but you left Fuyao in her cage, giving her a valuable lesson in self reliance.</string>
  <string id="20416">Crash Site</string>
  <string id="20434">Scholars&apos; Garden</string>
  <string id="20450">You do not have enough silver to buy the selected item.</string>
  <string id="20455">Aahh.</string>
  <string id="20457">It&apos;s toxic.</string>
  <string id="20460">Gao the Lesser</string>
  <string id="20461">Filter - All Active Quests</string>
  <string id="20462">Qui the Promoter</string>
  <string id="20467" soundid="127121">She has great skill, but a reluctance to use it. If she were to let go, she could be very powerful. Perhaps that is what she fears.</string>
  <string id="20468">Sailor</string>
  <string id="20473">Sailor</string>
  <string id="20478">Villager</string>
  <string id="20508">Lord Lao Recipe 1</string>
  <string id="20512">Lord Lao Recipe 2</string>
  <string id="20548">Sky</string>
  <string id="20549">Take a knife and kill the fat man, Fuyao. Then you go free.</string>
  <string id="20551">Prove you are strong. Kill him or be his slave!</string>
  <string id="20571">Well Lid</string>
  <string id="20573">Gate</string>
  <string id="20574" soundid="172550">Oh... okay. I won&apos;t bother you anymore then.</string>
  <string id="20575">Gate</string>
  <string id="20576">Gate of the Underworld</string>
  <string id="20577">Imperial Soldier</string>
  <string id="20579" soundid="172552">There are spirits everywhere here, in the city. Ghosts live inside of the people who remember them, just a little. Everyone has that spark... except for me...</string>
  <string id="20581">Deliver Red Silk Grass</string>
  <string id="20623">Control Room Door</string>
  <string id="20630">CUT - A strange stone token that detached from the memorial to &quot;the old master&quot; built behind master Li&apos;s house. While slightly weathered, the token is still instantly recognizable as the form of a lion&apos;s head.</string>
  <string id="20633">Character Type</string>
  <string id="20634">You are weak, girl. You deserve to be a slave!</string>
  <string id="20650" soundid="112008">Thank you, kind sir. I have my daughter back, and we are free. If I had any type of reward to give you, it would be yours.</string>
  <string id="20651" soundid="112009">We will return to Tien&apos;s Landing and tell the entire town of your great deeds. I&apos;m sure Minister Sheng will reward you for helping us.</string>
  <string id="20653">Patron</string>
  <string id="20655">[TEMP]Kungfu School Weapon</string>
  <string id="20658">[TEMP]Kungfu School Weapon Description</string>
  <string id="20746">Dawn Star</string>
  <string id="20755" soundid="143431">Despite that, it still seems the most likely place. He&apos;ll be slowed down by that load. You could still catch him if you hurry!</string>
  <string id="20765">Paralyzed</string>
  <string id="20830">Ru</string>
  <string id="20833" soundid="29121">Something&apos;s on your mind.</string>
  <string id="20841" soundid="29129">We should get back to town and be on our way.</string>
  <string id="20842" soundid="71799">What do you want? Did my son hire you to kick me out of my own home?</string>
  <string id="20843" soundid="71800">Of course I&apos;m not dead! If I were, would I be this upset about losing my house? Or breathing, for that matter?</string>
  <string id="20844" soundid="71801">Wha... what? No!</string>
  <string id="20846" soundid="24065"></string>
  <string id="20847">Two Rivers</string>
  <string id="20851">Hostel</string>
  <string id="20860">Spear</string>
  <string id="20880" soundid="129420"></string>
  <string id="20893" soundid="129421"></string>
  <string id="20895" soundid="129422">Keep going! We will meet in the school.</string>
  <string id="20896" soundid="129423"></string>
  <string id="20911" soundid="129424">Keep going! I will follow to the school.</string>
  <string id="20926" soundid="142302">What? Have you lost your mind? Well, you&apos;re about to lose your life, as well! This is unforgivable, acolyte!</string>
  <string id="20933">I&apos;m freeing the slaves. I killed the guard.</string>
  <string id="20942" soundid="129435">Do you mind? How can I enjoy the crack of bone, the screams of pain, and the glorious geysers of crimson blood down in the arena with you bothering me?</string>
  <string id="20955" soundid="129436">Or are you here to offer me your services for later? I generally prefer women, but I might branch out if a handsome man like you is willing to beg...</string>
  <string id="20957" soundid="129437">Or are you here to offer your services for later? Normally I prefer women who reek of the gutter, but I&apos;m willing to branch out... if you beg me.</string>
  <string id="20958" soundid="129438">I simply believe in exploring the darker aspects of human nature. I openly admit those hidden lustings others try to keep a shameful secret.</string>
  <string id="20976" soundid="129439">But I can see you aren&apos;t interested. So, what is your purpose here?</string>
  <string id="20977" soundid="129440">Gentle Breezes? So you&apos;re here to blackmail me with this scandal, are you? Well, my tastes are already well known at the Imperial Court.</string>
  <string id="20978" soundid="129441">Is that so? Let me guess: some sense of moral outrage at my perversions, no doubt. Well, my tastes are already well known at the Imperial Court.</string>
  <string id="20979" soundid="129442">Nobody cares about my... predilections... as long as I don&apos;t let my activities interfere with my duties as a judge.</string>
  <string id="20981" soundid="129443">My ring? But how... that harlot! I should have suspected something when she came to me willingly. Usually I have to command her presence.</string>
  <string id="20983" soundid="129444">Well, it seems you have me in an awkward position. I can&apos;t let it be known that I was foolish enough to let a whore steal my ring... I would lose my position.</string>
  <string id="20985" soundid="129445">So, what is it you want from me? Silver? An Imperial posting? What?</string>
  <string id="20986" soundid="129446">Of course. Now I understand. The Lotus Assassins are behind this, aren&apos;t they?</string>
  <string id="20993" soundid="129447">I should have known something like this would happen. They tried to bend me to their will, but I am not easily broken... or so I thought.</string>
  <string id="20996" soundid="129448">Are you proud of yourself? Bowing and scraping at the feet of your Lotus Assassin masters? Helping them to bring me down?</string>
  <string id="20997" soundid="129449">You think I&apos;m an evil man, don&apos;t you? You think my soul is rotten and corrupt. But at least I have a soul. The same cannot be said for those you now serve.</string>
  <string id="20998" soundid="129450">The Lotus Assassins destroyed me. But now that I am gone, I wonder where their attention will turn next? Keep a close watch over your shoulder... *friend.*</string>
  <string id="20999" soundid="129451">My resignation is on the table. Take it and stamp it with my Imperial Ring yourself!</string>
  <string id="21009">Slowed</string>
  <string id="21010">Healing</string>
  <string id="21011">Dazed</string>
  <string id="21017" soundid="24241"></string>
  <string id="21028">Style Information</string>
  <string id="21034" soundid="24258">You have returned, living one. Have you found Kindly Yushan? Will the orphan-master come to bury our bones?</string>
  <string id="21035" soundid="128705">That cave is home to both toad demons and ogres, and both are in a foul temper from fighting over the space. Running in there is like moving from the claws to the fangs.</string>
  <string id="21037" soundid="24261">Delightful! Give it to me! Now we can rest in peace, Bin!</string>
  <string id="21038" soundid="24262">Miao is right, we can rest now. But I fear we will not rest easy. I wish you had not done this, living one. There has been too much death already.</string>
  <string id="21039" soundid="24263">Look, Bin. Look at Yushan&apos;s eyes. Isn&apos;t he funny? Now I can play with Yushan any time I want! Now I can hurt him!</string>
  <string id="21042" soundid="24266">You have freed us, living one... though I wish you had acted differently. I am afraid of what will happen to us when we leave this world now. I&apos;m afraid of what will happen to Miao.</string>
  <string id="21043" soundid="24267">I&apos;m not afraid. I&apos;ve got Yushan to play with. And to hurt. Forever!</string>
  <string id="21046" soundid="24270"></string>
  <string id="21047" soundid="24271"></string>
  <string id="21048">Horrible Hongshi</string>
  <string id="21050" soundid="24274">Saying sorry isn&apos;t enough. You must pay. Now I get to hurt you. Forever and ever!</string>
  <string id="21051" soundid="164489">Magic styles allow you to use your Chi to control the elements, while Transformation styles allow you to assume the form of creatures or even demons.</string>
  <string id="21053" soundid="24277">Why are you here? No one ever comes to the orphanage.</string>
  <string id="21054" soundid="24278">Are you here for us to hurt?</string>
  <string id="21055">Power</string>
  <string id="21056" soundid="85320">Please... find my daughter. I can&apos;t leave without her. Please, find Fuyao and bring her back to me.</string>
  <string id="21057" soundid="24281">You can&apos;t touch us, living one. Once we lived in the orphanage, but when the waters came we became... what you see here. I am Bin, and this is Miao.</string>
  <string id="21058">Speed</string>
  <string id="21059">Range</string>
  <string id="21060" soundid="24284">Stop it, Miao! I don&apos;t like you hurting people. It&apos;s making you... strange.</string>
  <string id="21061" soundid="24285">I don&apos;t care. I don&apos;t care! Someone has to pay! Someone has to pay for what happened to us!</string>
  <string id="21062">Defense</string>
  <string id="21063">Guard</string>
  <string id="21065" soundid="24289">See, big people won&apos;t help us! They only like to hurt.</string>
  <string id="21066" soundid="24290">Just ignore her. She&apos;s gone strange because of what happened when... when the water came. We were locked in here, trapped in the orphanage with the rest of the children.</string>
  <string id="21068">Shouji</string>
  <string id="21069" soundid="24293">I should be a woman now, with kids of my own. I should have a husband and a house. Instead I have ashes and bones.</string>
  <string id="21070">I won&apos;t stand here and be lectured by a ghost!</string>
  <string id="21073">Dirge Fountain</string>
  <string id="21074" soundid="166869">I don&apos;t think we should spend our time in here chatting. Let&apos;s get what we need and get out of here.</string>
  <string id="21076" soundid="164490">I&apos;m only repeating what I&apos;ve learned in my time here, senior student, but that was one of the first things I memorized.</string>
  <string id="21077">FOUNTAIN WATER</string>
  <string id="21086" soundid="126498">Fang banished me to this remote post, seeking to slow me down. But with the town saved, it&apos;s only a matter of time until he is forced to call me back!</string>
  <string id="21088" soundid="142536">Gardening is stupid, but I like playing here. Dawn Star is nice.</string>
  <string id="21089">The Abbot&apos;s Vengeance</string>
  <string id="21091">The Cave</string>
  <string id="21093" soundid="140420">You tread dangerous ground, acolyte. Unless you plan to speed their processing in the extractor, you risk being punished for your impudence!</string>
  <string id="21094">Return to Hui in the Teahouse. She will want to know that her mission is complete, despite your setback in the ruins.</string>
  <string id="21095">The Lotus Assassins tricked Chai Ka the Heavenly Gate Guardian out of the amulet piece he was protecting, but he managed to preserve some of what was rightfully yours: a powerful gem you can add to your amulet. Return to Hui the Brave in the Teahouse and tell her what you have learned.</string>
  <string id="21096">Kill the Lotus Assassin</string>
  <string id="21097">Tell me your story again.</string>
  <string id="21098">Here is Kindly Yushan&apos;s head.</string>
  <string id="21100">It was only just.</string>
  <string id="21102">Hui has completed her sworn duty to Master Li and has gone off to resume her life now that it is once again her own.</string>
  <string id="21109">Miao seems pleased.</string>
  <string id="21111">Creative Congying</string>
  <string id="21116">Who--or what--are you?</string>
  <string id="21118">Do that again and you&apos;ll be sorry!</string>
  <string id="21119" soundid="112010">Come, Fuyao, let&apos;s go. The others are waiting for us.</string>
  <string id="21123">Calm down. Maybe I can help you.</string>
  <string id="21125">The Lotus Assassin is hiding in the caves below the monastery.</string>
  <string id="21127">The Abbot of Three Peaks Monastery has told you that his monks were murdered by a Lotus Assassin. You have found the man and gotten vengeance for the dead monks.</string>
  <string id="21128">Maybe I could help you... for a price.</string>
  <string id="21130">How did you end up like this?</string>
  <string id="21135">Return to the Abbot</string>
  <string id="21137">Teahouse</string>
  <string id="21139" soundid="150733"></string>
  <string id="21141" soundid="150735">You... you killed him! I... I can see that he was truly mad. I didn&apos;t want it to end this way, but... maybe now he can rest in peace.</string>
  <string id="21143">I am sorry. I&apos;ll repay you as soon as possible.</string>
  <string id="21164" soundid="174280">I may not know drama, but I know what I like. You sure you&apos;re not in the wrong line of work?</string>
  <string id="21165" soundid="150736">I only wish that I had had a chance to make him understand, to get him to forgive me.</string>
  <string id="21166" soundid="150737">I thank you, though, for what you tried to do. I.. I must be alone now.</string>
  <string id="21182">Pirate</string>
  <string id="21184" soundid="66156">I know you! I saw you at Tien&apos;s Landing! I&apos;m Yeung Yifong. Do you remember me? My daughter and I left town to try our luck in the wilderness.</string>
  <string id="21185" soundid="66157">We didn&apos;t get far outside the town before a flyer landed right in front of us. These pirates dragged us inside and brought us here to sell as slaves.</string>
  <string id="21192">Rope</string>
  <string id="21216" soundid="128717">Sky left a few hours ago. He said he was going to see how far up the mountain they had come. We haven&apos;t heard from him since, and I&apos;m... I&apos;m worried.</string>
  <string id="21241" soundid="81260">I&apos;m sorry, I haven&apos;t seen or heard anything. Perhaps one of the other students can help you.</string>
  <string id="21242" soundid="81261">I&apos;ll answer what I can.</string>
  <string id="21243" soundid="81262">I haven&apos;t talked to many of the newer students. The only one I have strong opinions about is Gao.</string>
  <string id="21244" soundid="81263">He and I have sparred many times. He has come dangerously close to injuring me, and I have seen his aggression hurt others.</string>
  <string id="21245" soundid="141953"></string>
  <string id="21246">I heard that you needed help opening the forest for travel again.</string>
  <string id="21274" soundid="24550">If it isn&apos;t two of Master Li&apos;s best and brightest! There&apos;s not much left for me to teach you two, so you can&apos;t be here for lessons.</string>
  <string id="21275" soundid="24551">Ah, you&apos;re cheerful today. Have you been teasing him, Dawn Star?</string>
  <string id="21277" soundid="24553">You look like you have something on your mind. What&apos;s the matter?</string>
  <string id="21279" soundid="180481">There you are! I have been hoping you would wander by.</string>
  <string id="21280">Golems are immune to Martial, Support, and Magical styles. Use Transformation or Weapon styles to defeat them, and fuel those styles with Spirit Thief. </string>
  <string id="21281" soundid="24557">That bog is full of bandits and who knows what else.</string>
  <string id="21283" soundid="180482">The Water Dragon... the Shepherd of the Dead, a goddess of rebirth. To try and steal her power; to even think it could be attempted... has any mortal ever shown such arrogance?</string>
  <string id="21284" soundid="24560">The Lesser? No. I *heard* him pass, though. Him and that foul mouth of his. He was swearing up a storm heading out of the village.</string>
  <string id="21285" soundid="24561">It sounded like he was dragging something heavy. I doubt he knows how to lift properly. I&apos;m sure he&apos;s never done a day of honest hard labor.</string>
  <string id="21286" soundid="24562">No, she hasn&apos;t been this way. I&apos;ve been testing the balance on some new practice blades that came in with Fen Do&apos;s new shipment, so I might have missed her.</string>
  <string id="21287" soundid="24563">Good luck to you.</string>
  <string id="21288" soundid="24564">Oh, there&apos;s no need for titles. Not from you two.</string>
  <string id="21289" soundid="24565">Already? I assume you dealt with them, and the rest are in for quite a surprise when they get here. Well, no time to waste.</string>
  <string id="21293" soundid="24569">Your weapon is well deserved, and you&apos;ll need it with these bandits so close.</string>
  <string id="21296" soundid="24572">That you should. Those people will be looking to you for leadership until Master Li gets back. I know you&apos;ll do well.</string>
  <string id="21297" soundid="126620">[A clay tablet like the others you previously encountered. The script is once again written in your master&apos;s hand.]</string>
  <string id="21298" soundid="126621">[Not all spirits succumb to bestial rage. A strong will can transcend death. These beings may have powers beyond any living foe, and intelligence to beguile and confuse.]</string>
  <string id="21299" soundid="126622">[All will suffer if the dead remain this way. Soon you must leave Two Rivers. Seek the source of this problem, even if it leads to the heart of the Empire.]</string>
  <string id="21303" soundid="126624">[I have old friends who may guide you, but I have old enemies, too. The cave is secure; meditate on what you see here. When you leave, all will be changed.]</string>
  <string id="21306" soundid="24582">The only thing left for you to learn is respect for others. You never can tell who might be an easily offended master of a style you don&apos;t know how to counter.</string>
  <string id="21308">Speak with Hui</string>
  <string id="21309">Speak with Hui in the teahouse. She has waited a long time to share what she knows about Master Li and your destiny.</string>
  <string id="21316">I don&apos;t have time to waste. You have something for me?</string>
  <string id="21318" soundid="180483">There are many beings that exist beyond our experience. The heavens are governed by a Celestial Bureaucracy. Each facet of existence is managed by a specialized attendant.</string>
  <string id="21319" soundid="180484">Most appear to have little influence, but some, like the Water Dragon, have a portfolio that grants exceptional status. She was said to have governance over the Great Wheel.</string>
  <string id="21320" soundid="180485">She was not a maker, but all life that ended passed her gaze before returning to the earth in another form. Sun Hai sought rebirth for his Empire at the cost of the natural order.</string>
  <string id="21322">Have you seen Gao?</string>
  <string id="21324">Have you seen Dawn Star?</string>
  <string id="21325">I&apos;ll be going now.</string>
  <string id="21326">Bandit scouts are here in Two Rivers. Master Li sent me for a weapon.</string>
  <string id="21329" soundid="173674">Would you want us to kill Fang and his guards too? Slaughter everyone? Not only does it seem excessive, but I don&apos;t think that&apos;s how Inquisitors operate.</string>
  <string id="21333">I should go see to the townsfolk now.</string>
  <string id="21342" soundid="166814">[This igniter is attached to three large firework racks via a series of fuses.]</string>
  <string id="21343" soundid="126633">I learn something every time we meet, proving that loss sometimes is the best teacher. Thank the heavens that the bruises are worth it.</string>
  <string id="21344">Unless you have something else to give me, I&apos;m finished with you.</string>
  <string id="21351" soundid="61239">Ssss! Why you have to be there, now me have to fight!</string>
  <string id="21352">Door</string>
  <string id="21360" soundid="118947">I&apos;m sure they are heartfelt.</string>
  <string id="21361" soundid="118948">You are incorrigible.</string>
  <string id="21363">You can only use this gem once. Once you place this gem on the amulet, you cannot remove it. Once its power has been used up, it will disintegrate, freeing up the slot on the amulet, once its power has been used up.</string>
  <string id="21372" soundid="180486">The Great Wheel is a way to envision the cycle of rebirth. I believe that when something dies, it is reborn as something else. After some form of assessment, of course.</string>
  <string id="21375" soundid="141801">I have a moment of power, a window to grant knowledge of a primal energy. You must choose between ice and fire, and I will grant the skill to bring them to your hands.</string>
  <string id="21376" soundid="175221">You live, but the portal was not sealed quickly enough. Defeat the maddened creatures that have followed you, or your life will once again be undone.</string>
  <string id="21377" soundid="175222">Seek your fellows. They know about your awakening and are on their way to the shelter of Dirge. Hurry, others will find you soon enough.</string>
  <string id="21378" soundid="175223">You just try and put that sticky ointment on me and I&apos;ll show you how irritable I can be!</string>
  <string id="21379" soundid="141805">He has earned my ire as well as yours. I will help if I can.</string>
  <string id="21380" soundid="141806">This seems like a personal dispute, but if the dog needs to die, so be it.</string>
  <string id="21381" soundid="141807">It doesn&apos;t matter to me! Master Li isn&apos;t here to restrict how I fight! I&apos;ll kill you both in time to see the red sky over your village!</string>
  <string id="21389">You couldn&apos;t beat me alone. Now Dawn Star is with me.</string>
  <string id="21391">You couldn&apos;t beat me alone. Now I have Zu as an ally.</string>
  <string id="21395" soundid="187853">Death&apos;s Hand should know better than to send his minions out alone.</string>
  <string id="21400" soundid="141818">I swear, one of these days I&apos;ll find a way around your guard.</string>
  <string id="21404">Gao&apos;s Mercenary</string>
  <string id="21406" soundid="188100">(Grumbling snores.)</string>
  <string id="21407">I&apos;m not perfect, it&apos;s just years of training.</string>
  <string id="21408" soundid="158233">Fine. Only one quarter of your winnings will be deducted, if you accept, that is.</string>
  <string id="21415">Ho Chong</string>
  <string id="21419" soundid="144492">That is why Death&apos;s Hand stands at the forefront of the Assassins. He draws attention, diverts criticism, while the Emperor solidifies his power.</string>
  <string id="21420" soundid="143830">If Gao killed that new student, he&apos;s a monster!</string>
  <string id="21422" soundid="141841">What *are* you? Your skills are more than this tiny village warrants, but I also see something strange... an oddity. You could be an anomaly... or a sign of who I seek.</string>
  <string id="21423" soundid="141842">A further test is needed! These mercenaries are not the only threat I command! Let us see you contend with this!</string>
  <string id="22268" soundid="69717">What is this? Weaklings, all of you!</string>
  <string id="22270" soundid="126634">You are gracious, as always. I regret that there won&apos;t be much time for such practice now that you have almost finished your training.</string>
  <string id="22271" soundid="141542">As I said, I have a special incentive for anyone who can beat her performance, but you will have to wait until she is healed before I have enough students.</string>
  <string id="22274">Jade Empire Engine (c) &amp; (p) 2002-2007 BioWare Corp. All rights reserved. BioWare Corp., the BioWare Corp. logo, BioWare and the BioWare logo, Jade Empire and the Jade Empire logo, and the Jade Empire Engine are either registered trademarks or trademarks of BioWare Corp. in the United States and/or other countries. All rights reserved. Uses Bink Video. Copyright (c) 1997-2007 by RAD Game Tools, Inc.

</string>
  <string id="22282" soundid="141543">Her wound was not mortal, but it was severe enough that I will not let her fight as she is. I suppose you could ask her if there&apos;s anything you could do to help.</string>
  <string id="22283" soundid="189733"></string>
  <string id="22284" soundid="25563">Good. The time comes when you will know all you need to. For now, keep the basics at heart.</string>
  <string id="22285" soundid="141545">Kia Min says that she is feeling well, and her wound seems to be already healing. I believe she will provide a fine challenge for you.</string>
  <string id="22286" soundid="25565">You near the end of your training, but I am still your master. You have a greater role than you know. For now, do as I say, and keep the basics at heart.</string>
  <string id="22287" soundid="25566">Dawn Star will be near her garden at the entrance to the school. Gujin will be in his shop near the village gate, up the stairs from the village square.</string>
  <string id="22288" soundid="126635">Master Li told me to pass on that you should speak to him when you have the chance. He said you could take your time, so you need not rush.</string>
  <string id="22289" soundid="126636">You have some time to wander the school and talk with other students. Smiling Mountain likely has some of the younger students available if you want to spar.</string>
  <string id="22303">Restless Spirit</string>
  <string id="22304" soundid="142599">Ah, there you are, my student. It is not like you to turn down a friendly match with Jing Woo, but you have exceeded the point where you can learn much from facing him.</string>
  <string id="22318" soundid="141546">Kia Min says that she is feeling well, though I worry about such exertions so soon after a wound. But, she knows her capabilities and would not take a foolish risk.</string>
  <string id="22319" soundid="141547">If you win this match, then I will have a special reward for you. Good fortunes.</string>
  <string id="22320" soundid="141548">I&apos;m afraid that unless Kia Min is feeling well enough to face you, I don&apos;t have enough students to allow you to do anything but tie her record.</string>
  <string id="22321" soundid="141549">There are a few, but not enough for me to set up some of the more challenging matches that I&apos;m sure you would prefer.</string>
  <string id="22322" soundid="141550">With the bandits approaching, most of the students are busy, but if you wish to limber up, I can set up a quick match. I want you at your best when the bandits arrive.</string>
  <string id="22323" soundid="141551">There will be more students available later in the day when many of their exercises have concluded.</string>
  <string id="22326" soundid="25605">Enjoy the words of your fellows. I will wait in the main hall, where we will discuss the Spirit Cave. Be certain you are ready when you come to me; your life is about to change.</string>
  <string id="22327" soundid="25606"></string>
  <string id="22353">What is this place?</string>
  <string id="22354" soundid="142261"></string>
  <string id="22355" soundid="141553"></string>
  <string id="22366" soundid="141554">Well done. As promised, here is a reward for setting a new standard. Kia Min is eager to try again, but I asked her to rest for now. She seems well, despite her earlier injury.</string>
  <string id="22367">I will do as you ask.</string>
  <string id="22369">Is that all? Am I an errand boy? I&apos;m better than that.</string>
  <string id="22370" soundid="141555">You have set a new standard and your prize is well-earned, but forgive me, my attention is elsewhere. Kia Min&apos;s injury has worsened, as you could probably see.</string>
  <string id="22371">Where can I find Dawn Star and Gujin?</string>
  <string id="22372" soundid="126637">You do not need to be so confrontational. This was merely practice. One of the few times where a loss carries no impact.</string>
  <string id="22373" soundid="126638">I didn&apos;t expect to beat you. No doubt you were focused on technique and got distracted.</string>
  <string id="22385" soundid="69718">Your defiance grows tiresome, student of Li. You must learn your place in the order of things.</string>
  <string id="22387" soundid="69719">Fools! Can you not dispose of one defiant peasant?</string>
  <string id="22389">Exit</string>
  <string id="22392">Ai Ling</string>
  <string id="22393" soundid="142601"></string>
  <string id="22394" soundid="142602"></string>
  <string id="22395" soundid="142603"></string>
  <string id="22396" soundid="142604"></string>
  <string id="22398" soundid="141707">Why does it matter? I was born by my mother and sucked at her teat like every man... well, like every man does with *his* mother.</string>
  <string id="22399" soundid="141708">Anyway, by the time I was old enough to swing an axe, my father was dead and my mother disowned me. &apos;Course, killing my father might have given her reason.</string>
  <string id="22400" soundid="141709">I think she did it out of shame. My father beat me and my brother senseless and made our lives miserable. Either way, that was the end of my childhood.</string>
  <string id="22402" soundid="141710">Ha! I wasn&apos;t brave. I was furious... and he was drunk. It was an easy fight.</string>
  <string id="22403" soundid="141711">I&apos;ve done worse since then, believe me.</string>
  <string id="22404" soundid="141712">I traveled a lot after that, begging for some things and taking the rest. Tough times, but not the worst. My axes and my wits kept me alive.</string>
  <string id="22405" soundid="141713">Yeah, yeah. I had some wits before I got them all knocked out of me. Mostly I just used my axes and my fists.</string>
  <string id="22406" soundid="141714">You&apos;d think a seven year old might be an easy target, but I soon learned just where to cut a man to make a him squeal like a pig. Ahh... those were the days.</string>
  <string id="22407" soundid="166923">Then there&apos;s merchant Fen Do. Someday, I&apos;d appreciate it if he&apos;d quit complaining that he hasn&apos;t struck it rich yet. At least he hasn&apos;t struck it elderly, I say.</string>
  <string id="22409" soundid="141557">Gao&apos;s actions were foolish. He knew he could not beat you fairly, and so he chose to catch you by surprise.</string>
  <string id="22410" soundid="141558">I hear bandits have injured Kia Min! She is a favorite pupil, and holds the record for the challenge I run. I&apos;m sure Master Li will take care of her.</string>
  <string id="22411" soundid="189735"></string>
  <string id="22412">Can we talk about Kia Min?</string>
  <string id="22415" soundid="166925">You wish to challenge the one person brave enough to get the dam closed? You&apos;re slower than I thought. No thanks, I don&apos;t need you damaged.</string>
  <string id="22416" soundid="154218">There is a place for the enforcer, the man or woman who brings death to those who have earned or otherwise deserve it. I consider that to be an honest calling.</string>
  <string id="22448">Merchant Bai will not rest easy in his grave, convinced that he is being tormented even in death.</string>
  <string id="22449">A Fearful Ghost</string>
  <string id="22451">You have encountered the spirit of Mister Ren, who has sworn vengeance against his wife, Ren Feng. He does not seem to be able to rest until this vengeance is carried out.</string>
  <string id="22466">A Vengeful Ghost</string>
  <string id="22473" soundid="69720">Very well, I will face you myself! No matter your destiny, you will fall here today!</string>
  <string id="22482">There might be another option.</string>
  <string id="22483">On second thought, death is too easy.</string>
  <string id="22485">Fawning Lacky</string>
  <string id="22488">Fawning Lacky</string>
  <string id="22491">Fawning Lacky</string>
  <string id="22498">Storm Dragon</string>
  <string id="22499">Heavenly Wave</string>
  <string id="22500">Willow</string>
  <string id="22501">Iron Palm</string>
  <string id="22533" soundid="25852">What&apos;s your pleasure?</string>
  <string id="22534" soundid="25853">Look at that camera go!</string>
  <string id="22535">Do camera demo.</string>
  <string id="22537">Never mind.</string>
  <string id="22538">Get shiny bauble.</string>
  <string id="22541">Talk to Bert</string>
  <string id="22544">Get Part A</string>
  <string id="22547">Get Part B</string>
  <string id="22550">Talk to Wuzza</string>
  <string id="22553">Talk to Ert</string>
  <string id="22556">Foo Found</string>
  <string id="22590">You&apos;re right. Forget I said anything.</string>
  <string id="22591">Did the teahouse change owners recently?</string>
  <string id="22593">Tell me more about Dutong.</string>
  <string id="22596">Give it up? What do you mean?</string>
  <string id="22597">Give me some more advice.</string>
  <string id="22600" soundid="136827"></string>
  <string id="22601">Lotus Assassin</string>
  <string id="22604" soundid="26033">Greetingsh and shalutations! Welcome to Mashter Dutong&apos;sh teahoushe! What can I do for you, my friend?</string>
  <string id="22605" soundid="26034">Whadda you want? Come to mock me? Come to laugh at the tragedy that ish the life of Three Sheetsh Dutong?</string>
  <string id="22606" soundid="26035">You! I&apos;ve sheen you around here, shkulking around. Watching me. Why ish you following me? What do you want?</string>
  <string id="22607" soundid="114564">Of course, you are the expert on demons, having faced one in the ring already. I hoped the rumors they would bring such beasts into the ring were false.</string>
  <string id="22615" soundid="116167">I thought one of the sailors trapped here might make a good husband, but they&apos;re just a bunch of drunks!</string>
  <string id="22616" soundid="43354">Hello there, traveler. Forgive my forwardness, but I noticed your arrival earlier while I was at the tavern. That flying machine of yours is truly a marvel.</string>
  <string id="22617" soundid="43355">I actually have a design for a new prototype flyer, and I hope to get funding to build it one day. The other scholars aren&apos;t interested in my inventions, though.</string>
  <string id="22618" soundid="43356">I also collect interesting magical items when I can find them. Some of them I use, and some of them I sell to fund my flyer project.</string>
  <string id="22619" soundid="43357">Me? You want to ask *me* something? Well, sure, I&apos;d be glad to help you if I can. What would you like to know?</string>
  <string id="22620">You cannot unselect a choice from a previous level.</string>
  <string id="22621">You cannot purchase this upgrade until you have bought the one before it.</string>
  <string id="22622" soundid="43360">That&apos;s right, you&apos;re new here, aren&apos;t you? Well, where should I begin? There&apos;s so much to tell you. There are several important areas here in the city.</string>
  <string id="22623" soundid="43361">Of course, there are also many different services, too. Um, I&apos;m not sure what to tell you first.</string>
  <string id="22624" soundid="43362">Sure. Well, let&apos;s see. This place is the Scholars&apos; Garden. For the most part, only stuffy old philosophers and scholars reside here.</string>
  <string id="22626" soundid="43364">You&apos;ll also find the path to the Black Leopard School there, across the river from the arena. I haven&apos;t been there, but I hear it&apos;s an interesting place to visit.</string>
  <string id="22628" soundid="43366">One of the best places in the city is the arena. Just don&apos;t tell my masters I said so. If you go to the arena, you&apos;ll also see the Heart of the Empire Tavern.</string>
  <string id="22629" soundid="43367">I&apos;m not supposed to go there... at least, not when I&apos;m studying. But it&apos;s hard to resist. It&apos;s known as the best tavern in all the Empire.</string>
  <string id="22630" soundid="43368">I actually do some of my best thinking while I&apos;m there. I like to sit in the upper rooms with a bit of wine and just look out over the city... or the arena.</string>
  <string id="22631" soundid="43369">Well, I&apos;ve got some magical items you might find interesting. You can also try Wu Pingbo. I often go to him when I need something. He&apos;s over in the Market District.</string>
  <string id="22632">Switch</string>
  <string id="22633">Switch</string>
  <string id="22634">Yellow switch</string>
  <string id="22635">Green switch</string>
  <string id="22636">Red switch</string>
  <string id="22638" soundid="43371">It&apos;s one of my guilty pleasures, I have to admit. When I was a little boy I used to dream of fighting in the arena. My uncle had other plans, however.</string>
  <string id="22639" soundid="43372">At any rate, watching those fighters compete is one of the most exhilarating experiences. You look as though you could handle yourself in the arena.</string>
  <string id="22640" soundid="43373">Of course. What do you want to know?</string>
  <string id="22641" soundid="43374">Now, there&apos;s a question you don&apos;t hear very often. Not too many people like to talk about him. In fact, if I were you, I&apos;d be careful who I ask.</string>
  <string id="22642" soundid="43375">I&apos;m not one to believe in superstitious nonsense, but I still wouldn&apos;t want to draw his attention. He&apos;s very powerful and very dangerous.</string>
  <string id="22643" soundid="43376">Some people even suggest that he has gained some control over our honorable Emperor. I find it hard to believe, but I suppose it&apos;s possible.</string>
  <string id="22644">This choice is disallowed.</string>
  <string id="22645">This choice is the prerequisite of an existing choice.</string>
  <string id="22646">I&apos;ll leave you to your drinking.</string>
  <string id="22647">Blue switch</string>
  <string id="22648">Shrine</string>
  <string id="22649" soundid="43379">A city like this always has rumors. Some people say the ghosts are angry and attacking innocent people. Another rumor suggests the Emperor is dying.</string>
  <string id="22650" soundid="43380">But I wouldn&apos;t believe any of that. Just because the Emperor hasn&apos;t been seen in a while doesn&apos;t mean he&apos;s ill. Perhaps he just wants some solitude.</string>
  <string id="22651">Shrine</string>
  <string id="22652">Let&apos;s talk about that writ you showed Mother Kwan.</string>
  <string id="22653">Shrine</string>
  <string id="22674" soundid="26103">Hello again, dearie. I hope you&apos;re having a nice time here in my--I mean, in Master Dutong&apos;s--teahouse.</string>
  <string id="22678">Blossom - test version</string>
  <string id="22681">That doesn&apos;t work, does it?</string>
  <string id="22683">Imperial Guard Captain</string>
  <string id="22684">This is going to be painful... for you.</string>
  <string id="22704">I want to ask you some questions.</string>
  <string id="22717" soundid="26146">I&apos;m watching you. Don&apos;t try anything funny.</string>
  <string id="22720" soundid="26149">Dutong says he hired me because I&apos;m big as an ox and just as smart.</string>
  <string id="22721">Three Sheets Dutong</string>
  <string id="22726" soundid="26155">What? Can&apos;t you just leave an old man in peace?</string>
  <string id="22727" soundid="26156">Why do you care? That was a long time ago. Long, long ago. All I want is to forget those days. They&apos;re gone... gone forever.</string>
  <string id="22729" soundid="127122">If you wish, but only introspection reveals true insight. I used to call the trading center of Phoenix Gate my home, but I am settled here. I have nothing to go back to.</string>
  <string id="22730" soundid="26159">A better man might have saved them. Sometimes I wonder... I wonder if I should have died with them. </string>
  <string id="22731" soundid="26160">Your threat holds little power over me. I deserve to suffer... I deserve death. I would have done it myself were I not such a coward. </string>
  <string id="22732" soundid="26161">No! Not the orphanage. The ruins are haunted! The children will be waiting for me. No!</string>
  <string id="22733" soundid="26162">You&apos;re right. I can carry this burden no longer. I must face the demons of my past and end this, one way or another. I will go with you and accept whatever fate awaits me.</string>
  <string id="22734" soundid="26163">Yes... do it! I only ask that you make it quick.</string>
  <string id="22735" soundid="26164">Sorry doesn&apos;t count for much. Sorry can&apos;t erase our mistakes. Sorry can&apos;t change the past.</string>
  <string id="22736">You used to be the orphan-master before the flood?</string>
  <string id="22737">I&apos;m taking you to the orphanage... now!</string>
  <string id="22738">What happened the day of the flood?</string>
  <string id="22741">Time to end your miserable life!</string>
  <string id="22743">If you want redemption, meet me at the orphanage.</string>
  <string id="22744">You carry them with you anyway. Now you can free yourself.</string>
  <string id="22745">You can come willingly, or I can drag you. Your choice.</string>
  <string id="22746">Then I will give you the death you deserve!</string>
  <string id="22747">I&apos;m sorry.</string>
  <string id="22748" soundid="26177">Bring me Kindly Yushan&apos;s head. If you won&apos;t do that, then go away and leave me alone.</string>
  <string id="22750" soundid="26179">You... you live? All this time, you were here. I left you to this... I&apos;m sorry. Please forgive me!</string>
  <string id="22752" soundid="26181">No, Miao. Yushan was not brought here so you could make him suffer. He must bury our bones. Then we can finally rest. </string>
  <string id="22755" soundid="26184">Yes... it&apos;s time for this to end. I... I want you to know I&apos;m sorry, Bin. I&apos;m sorry for what happened to you. I&apos;m sorry for what I did....</string>
  <string id="22758" soundid="26187">Goodbye, living one. Goodbye, forever.</string>
  <string id="22760" soundid="26189">I am so sorry...</string>
  <string id="22762">Killer Wenya</string>
  <string id="22766">Poisoned</string>
  <string id="22770">Petrified</string>
</tlk>