<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<tlk language="0">
  <string id="50670">By sabotaging the dam, you doomed the town of Tien&apos;s Landing to a long and slow death, but at least Merchant Jiang lined your pockets with silver.</string>
  <string id="50813" soundid="97439">What&apos;s that smell? Oh, that&apos;s right, it&apos;s me.</string>
  <string id="50880" soundid="93171">I&apos;m certain you understand the ethics at stake. My knowledge of their strengths and weaknesses would be a weapon in the wrong hands.</string>
  <string id="50889" soundid="93172">Pity that you are so quick to refuse the unknown.</string>
  <string id="50890" soundid="93173">My eyes may not function, but I am not blind to the world.</string>
  <string id="50891" soundid="93174">Perhaps you should talk to Qui the Promoter. He often seeks new warriors to do battle in these ancient halls.</string>
  <string id="50897">Scholars&apos; Garden</string>
  <string id="50898">Necropolis</string>
  <string id="50902">Gao&apos;s Mercenary</string>
  <string id="50935" soundid="108334">Not this time, Princess. I will be heard.</string>
  <string id="50936">Why are you leaving town?</string>
  <string id="50939" soundid="108335">Oh, fire in the eyes. How exciting.</string>
  <string id="50942">The wilderness is very dangerous.</string>
  <string id="50944">Don&apos;t leave. Perhaps I can save the town.</string>
  <string id="50946">Your cowardice endangers your daughter. Flee, peasant.</string>
  <string id="50948">Why did the Great Dam open?</string>
  <string id="50949">Lotus Assassin</string>
  <string id="50957">I don&apos;t know what you&apos;re talking about, but I&apos;ll pass regardless.</string>
  <string id="51205">The Tournament</string>
  <string id="51213" soundid="62978">You&apos;re a stranger here, aren&apos;t you? I know everyone in Tien&apos;s Landing, and I&apos;ve never seen you before! I would remember you.</string>
  <string id="51214" soundid="62979">You should turn right around and leave this town. Trust me!</string>
  <string id="51222" soundid="62987">Forgive me, great one! I meant no offense. I only meant that you should leave our town because it is doomed. I was only trying to warn you.</string>
  <string id="51224" soundid="62989">Everything in Tien&apos;s Landing is falling apart. Sheng, the local minister, is helpless to deal with all our troubles. You should get out while you can.</string>
  <string id="51230" soundid="62995">The merchants can&apos;t buy goods from the Imperial City. The traders can&apos;t sell to the outside world. The men cannot fish, and our children go hungry.</string>
  <string id="51234" soundid="124098"></string>
  <string id="51240" soundid="63005">Um, yes, I do. Why do you ask?</string>
  <string id="51241" soundid="63006">Airship? I have only heard of such things: graceful ships that sail through the air! I&apos;ve always longed to see one, but I&apos;m just a simple peasant.</string>
  <string id="51242" soundid="63007">Perhaps Minister Sheng would know something about this. He once lived in the Imperial City; I have heard the skies above it are filled with airships!</string>
  <string id="51260" soundid="63025">What few goods the merchants have are for sale there. Things are getting better now that the dam is closed, but their stores won&apos;t be fully replenished for some time. </string>
  <string id="51261" soundid="63026">What few goods the merchants have are for sale there. They have very little, however, since the town is cut off.</string>
  <string id="51269" soundid="63034">Goodbye, mighty stranger. Please forgive my earlier impertinence. It will not happen again.</string>
  <string id="51271" soundid="63036">Greetings, mighty one. I pray this humble peasant has not insulted you again? If so, I beg your forgiveness. We have enough troubles here in Tien&apos;s Landing already.</string>
  <string id="51282">Why should I leave?</string>
  <string id="51284">You can&apos;t tell me what to do, peasant!</string>
  <string id="51288">Tell me about the troubles here.</string>
  <string id="51301">Do you have your coin purse with you?</string>
  <string id="51302">I need your silver to help me save the town.</string>
  <string id="51303">I need to find a flyer or some other kind of airship.</string>
  <string id="51314" soundid="145235">I can assure you that I no longer share an allegiance with them. It was a short dalliance that ended on poor terms.</string>
  <string id="51316">I have questions about the town.</string>
  <string id="51322" soundid="145236">I will answer what I wish.</string>
  <string id="51331">Goodbye.</string>
  <string id="51371" soundid="63219">I do not have strength to answer. I am cut open, and the way to the underworld is shut. Spirits are lost with no shepherd, no guardians. You must restore us.</string>
  <string id="51376">Corpse</string>
  <string id="51377" soundid="63225">Greetings. I am the Abbot of Three Peaks Monastery. I will be giving you your sample quest today.</string>
  <string id="51378" soundid="63226">You would have come upon my plot upon arriving at the Three Peaks Monastery and finding it in mourning.</string>
  <string id="51379" soundid="63227">Upon gaining an audience with me, I would have told you that some of my monks were murdered the night before by a Lotus Assassin. The Lotus Assassin is known to be hiding in the caves below the monastery.</string>
  <string id="51380" soundid="63228">In fact, we are standing in those very caves and the villainous murderer is the Lotus Assassin at the other end of the room.</string>
  <string id="51381" soundid="63229">I have now given you the journal entry as if you were on the quest. Check your journal page before moving forward to fight the assassin and then check it again once you&apos;ve killed him.</string>
  <string id="51382" soundid="63230">After that, come and speak with me again to resolve the quest.</string>
  <string id="51383" soundid="63231">Check your journal and then kill the Lotus Assassin and check it again. Then come and speak with me to resolve the quest.</string>
  <string id="51384" soundid="63232">You have completed the quest and I will now resolve your journal entry to its completed state.</string>
  <string id="51406">You&apos;re blind. How can you sense anything?</string>
  <string id="51429" soundid="107046">I wasn&apos;t watching.</string>
  <string id="51430" soundid="141877">This day has been full for you, and you still have the cavern to face.</string>
  <string id="51431" soundid="141878">If you listen to Lin parroting the villagers&apos; stories, that place has a dark past, but I&apos;m sure Master Li wouldn&apos;t send you into unreasonable danger.</string>
  <string id="51432" soundid="141879">You are the hero of the moment! Gao claims that he dealt with hordes of bandits, but everyone else agrees that you turned aside their main attack.</string>
  <string id="51433" soundid="141880">It is good that you were here. My foolish lack of attention forced Master Li to come to my rescue and left me with a wound that will take a few weeks to heal.</string>
  <string id="51434" soundid="141881">Master Li assures me I will heal in time. It&apos;s a shame, as Smiling Mountain was teasing me just yesterday with some &quot;special prize.&quot;</string>
  <string id="51442" soundid="141882">Smiling Mountain trains students in group combat, and just yesterday, I managed to break your record for the number of opponents faced at once.</string>
  <string id="51443" soundid="141883">He teased me by saying if I could go one higher, he might have a prize for me. I suppose he might make the same offer to you, if you&apos;re up to it.</string>
  <string id="51446" soundid="141884">If I could fight, he could likely round up enough opponents for you to make a run at a new record, but I can&apos;t face anyone with this wound.</string>
  <string id="51453" soundid="140146">You are falling behind, Gang. Grand Inquisitor Jia is not happy, therefore I am not happy. If your work does not improve, I will have to stop taking credit for it.</string>
  <string id="51454" soundid="140147">The latest battalion of golems stand idle because of you. If the production of the Jade Golem is delayed again, perhaps your soul will fuel our next attempt.</string>
  <string id="51455">I&apos;ll just leave you to that then.</string>
  <string id="51456" soundid="140148">Tonight we require a shard of exceptional quality for a Jade Golem that will control the latest battalion of golems. You will oversee this in the extraction chamber.</string>
  <string id="51457" soundid="140149">You clearly deserve better than the short life of a regular acolyte. Your ability surprised me. Use it to surprise the others as well. Help me gain the power to help you.</string>
  <string id="51461">You have any more work for me?</string>
  <string id="51463">Can we talk about the city?</string>
  <string id="51465">[Intimidation] I think I deserve a little extra compensation for my work.</string>
  <string id="51468">That&apos;s it? We just forget what Zu did and move on?</string>
  <string id="51469">Then you&apos;ll join the corpses you care for!</string>
  <string id="51471" soundid="161236">You are too valuable to abandon a second time.</string>
  <string id="51475">You have heard his lies for years. Will this change anything?</string>
  <string id="51478">Whatever. I&apos;m leaving.</string>
  <string id="51483" soundid="123243">Purveyor Shouji wants me to fetch an artifact from a tomb in the Necropolis.</string>
  <string id="51492">What is this building behind you?</string>
  <string id="51497">We&apos;ll worry about that when the time comes.</string>
  <string id="51500">What is there to do around here?</string>
  <string id="51504">Magic</string>
  <string id="51505">Monster</string>
  <string id="51506">Weapon</string>
  <string id="51507">Transformation</string>
  <string id="51520" soundid="72035">He&apos;s been wandering around the house for days and with all these ghosts up and about, no one will deal with him!</string>
  <string id="51521" soundid="72036">He should have the sense to realize he&apos;s dead and stay buried!</string>
  <string id="51525" soundid="113258">Unless I&apos;ve got a sure feeling, I always go with rolling high.</string>
  <string id="51526" soundid="113259">If you&apos;re here to play, talk to Daoshen.</string>
  <string id="51527" soundid="113260">All the rich folk don&apos;t know the fun they&apos;re missing.</string>
  <string id="51528" soundid="113261">Daoshen&apos;s game is the best in the city.</string>
  <string id="51529">Messenger</string>
  <string id="51530" soundid="113263">This game&apos;s the only honest one in town.</string>
  <string id="51537" soundid="63396">People call me Lishun the Talkative, though I&apos;ve no idea why. I&apos;m actually a basket maker. In fact, I dare say I&apos;m the best basket maker in all of Tien&apos;s Landing!</string>
  <string id="51540" soundid="63399">My children only need one meal a day; after all, they&apos;re small. And my wife can take a third job, if necessary. I know things will turn around soon.</string>
  <string id="51550" soundid="63409">Can you imagine? They have no faith in the Emperor, nor in Minister Sheng, who is in charge of Tien&apos;s Landing. I am sure the cunning Sheng has a plan to save us.</string>
  <string id="51551" soundid="63410">He&apos;s in the town square, the highest point in Tien&apos;s Landing. Just follow any path leading up until you can&apos;t go any higher, and you&apos;re there.</string>
  <string id="51552" soundid="63411">Minister Sheng may not have the best reputation, but I&apos;m sure that&apos;s just gossip. I bet he&apos;s actually a smart, active man who can reassure you of our town&apos;s future.</string>
  <string id="51580">You have secured the acceptance of the Lotus Assassins and are free to enter their fortress deep within the tombs of the Necropolis. Somewhere in the inner chambers is the information against Death&apos;s Hand that Princess Lian wants.</string>
  <string id="51581">Infiltrate the Lotus Assassin Fortress</string>
  <string id="51585">Find Your New Master</string>
  <string id="51586">Despite Zu&apos;s remarks, you must still find Master Gang and see if service to him will gain you access to the inner chambers and the information the princess requires.</string>
  <string id="51587">You now bear the title of Lotus Acolyte. Gaining access to the inner chambers will be a challenge with such a lowly rank, but the princess will not take you to the palace until you have the information against Death&apos;s Hand that she needs. Zu has given a cryptic warning, but he has not clarified why he left or what he is here to do.</string>
  <string id="51591">Defeat the Rampaging Ghosts</string>
  <string id="51592">Master Gang told you to defeat some ghosts unleashed by his rival, Master Shin. Gang clearly does not expect you to survive. Return to him when you are done.</string>
  <string id="51593">Who are you?</string>
  <string id="51599">Follow Gang to the Chambers Below</string>
  <string id="51600">You are ordered to follow Master Gang to the central chambers.</string>
  <string id="51603">Construct a Spirit Shard</string>
  <string id="51604">Complete all the steps to create a spirit shard.</string>
  <string id="51608">Where can I find Minister Sheng?</string>
  <string id="51610">Kill Master Shin</string>
  <string id="51611">Complete all the steps to kill Master Shin.</string>
  <string id="51643">***TEMP YOU WON ROUND 4, NOW WIN ROUND 5</string>
  <string id="51644">***TEMP ROUND 5</string>
  <string id="51645">***TEMP  WIN ROUND 5</string>
  <string id="51647">***TEMP  YOU WON ROUND 5, NOW WIN ROUND SIX</string>
  <string id="51648">***TEMP ROUND 6</string>
  <string id="51649">***TEMP  WIN ROUND 6</string>
  <string id="51651">***TEMP YOU WON ROUND 6, AND ENTERED THE GIANT&apos;S ECHELON. NOW WIN ROUND 7.</string>
  <string id="51652">***TEMP ROUND 7</string>
  <string id="51653">***TEMP WIN ROUND 7</string>
  <string id="51655">***TEMP YOU WON ROUND 7, NOW WIN ROUND 8</string>
  <string id="51656">***TEMP ROUND 8</string>
  <string id="51657">*** TEMP WIN ROUND 8</string>
  <string id="51659">*** TEMP YOU WON ROUND 8. HONG SAYS THIS IS THE LAST ROUND AND THAT YOU ARE THE CHAMPION.</string>
  <string id="51660">***TEMP ROUND 8</string>
  <string id="51661">*** TEMP WIN ROUND 8</string>
  <string id="51663">*** TEMP YOU WON ROUND 8, NOW FIND A WAY TO FIGHT THE CHAMPION.</string>
  <string id="51664">***TEMP THE CHAMPIONSHIP</string>
  <string id="51665">*** TEMP WIN THE CHAMPIONSHIP</string>
  <string id="51667">*** TEMP YOU WON THE CHAMPIONSHIP!</string>
  <string id="51696">A custom character fits none of the predefined archetypes. You decide how the character has developed their skills and how he or she applies the lessons learned in training. A custom character begins the game with any one of the starting styles.</string>
  <string id="51712" soundid="136829">I have silver, but that money does not grant skill, not skills like yours. We need your help!</string>
  <string id="51720">Monkey</string>
  <string id="51723">School Gate</string>
  <string id="51727">You can&apos;t resist me forever!</string>
  <string id="51728" soundid="154674">Please, help my boy! He&apos;s down by the beach, east of the central square in town.</string>
  <string id="51732">Where can I find Ru the Boatswain?</string>
  <string id="51733">I&apos;ll be back after I destroy the dam.</string>
  <string id="51975" soundid="63915">You are drawn by destiny. Like water flowing... bleeding. Have you begun to question your path? It is murky... blocked, but carefully crafted.</string>
  <string id="51976" soundid="63916">You are on this path because you have been shaped... groomed... and the predators have been drawn away to let you pass. Can you see how that path winds towards your prey? </string>
  <string id="51978" soundid="144755">These demons serve the Mother, and as the Forest Shadow weakens they grow more bold. Even attacking this sacred place.</string>
  <string id="51979" soundid="63919">You are meant to learn, but not too much. To see, but not too clearly. To succeed, but not completely.</string>
  <string id="51980" soundid="63920">To control an outcome, control the beginning. It is godlike... the most arrogant action. That is what was done.</string>
  <string id="51981" soundid="63921">Unh...</string>
  <string id="51982" soundid="63922">I weaken... but listen. Endings come at their own pace. You would better serve your cause by asking where it began. Question why the path is there, not where it leads.</string>
  <string id="51983" soundid="63923">For now, look to yourself. The guardian ahead will test and teach. He is an ally... one you can trust. Find your purpose... fulfill your destiny, and we will meet again.</string>
  <string id="51985" soundid="144756">They will attack you, as well. My sisters will try to protect you, but we need your help as much as you need ours. You must reach my mistress quickly.</string>
  <string id="51986" soundid="136145">The woman directing them both was Grand Inquisitor Jia. Jia partnered with Gao the Greater and sent Inquisitor Lim here as her representative.</string>
  <string id="51993">Quit speaking in circles. Tell me something useful!</string>
  <string id="51994">Are you saying I&apos;ve been misled?</string>
  <string id="51995">I&apos;m in a ghost-filled ruin. I don&apos;t have time for this.</string>
  <string id="52000">What happened to the forest?</string>
  <string id="52001">The forest burned?</string>
  <string id="52002" soundid="136146">And because of their demands, I am forced to make flyers that they misuse. But they won&apos;t get the Marvelous Dragonfly. My special creation will not be abused.</string>
  <string id="52005">I&apos;ve heard enough of this story for now.</string>
  <string id="52050">Kia Min</string>
  <string id="52051">You didn&apos;t answer my question.</string>
  <string id="52056">How do Master Li&apos;s skills measure up to your teachers in the Imperial City?</string>
  <string id="52058" soundid="154657">The dam is downriver from us. When it was closed, it slowed the flow of the river, causing it to back up and the water level to rise.</string>
  <string id="52059" soundid="154658">But with the dam open, the water drains away too quickly and our river, the lifeblood of this town, has become a trickle. The river has no fish, and ships can&apos;t navigate it.</string>
  <string id="52060" soundid="64013">Ghosts bring wind. Wind is no friend to a river fisherman, I can tell you that.</string>
  <string id="52061" soundid="64014">One thing that is good about being a fisherman? You never see a ghost out in the middle of the river.</string>
  <string id="52062" soundid="64015">I still believe in the Emperor. He&apos;ll look after us.</string>
  <string id="52063" soundid="64016">The fisherman&apos;s life is a hard one. Don&apos;t let anyone tell you different.</string>
  <string id="52064">Why is the river so low if the dam is open?</string>
  <string id="52078">Tien&apos;s decision was made over the mid-day meal. The Flower Guardians would allow nothing else.</string>
  <string id="52082">Such a thing could only be decided in the deepest part of the night.</string>
  <string id="52106">Fang Guard</string>
  <string id="52107" soundid="128087">I surpassed his ability long ago. He&apos;s jealous, like the rest of you. You&apos;ll all see what I am capable of soon enough.</string>
  <string id="52111" soundid="164001">No, you can&apos;t mean that! They won&apos;t reach the fortress and the driver is gone. Please don&apos;t do this.</string>
  <string id="52113" soundid="142502">No, I have no interest in fighting you right now. I&apos;ll wait until it&apos;s worth it, when the whole school is watching and I can crush you slowly.</string>
  <string id="52114" soundid="142503">Master Li wants to talk to you. Do me a favor, and go talk to him. Then maybe I can actually receive some education at this school.</string>
  <string id="52117" soundid="113770">They&apos;re more riled than usual this time, but I think we can handle this. I&apos;d best get back down there.</string>
  <string id="52124">I&apos;d be happy to help.</string>
  <string id="52125">Solve your own problems, Qui. I&apos;m just here to fight my matches.</string>
  <string id="52127" soundid="113780">Oh, now, that&apos;s not good. Not good at all.</string>
  <string id="52129" soundid="145237">He is dead, and the Empire will shed no tears. He paid the price for aligning himself with Death&apos;s Hand. There is no reason to say any more than that. </string>
  <string id="52130" soundid="145238">You name the Emperor among your personal foils? You have a grand opinion of yourself. Don&apos;t be so quick to link Sun Hai to the destruction you have seen.</string>
  <string id="52131" soundid="145239">Death&apos;s Hand may still answer to him, but it is a long leap from that to assuming the Emperor approves of what the Lotus Assassins have done.</string>
  <string id="52132" soundid="145240">Both of those possibilities will be hard for people to swallow. The Emperor is the Emperor. He is above weakness or viciousness.</string>
  <string id="52133" soundid="145241">To question that is to question the nature of the Jade Empire, and I am not... not many people are willing to do that.</string>
  <string id="52135" soundid="145242">The Emperor is the foundation upon which we build. If he is weakened, we all fall.</string>
  <string id="52136" soundid="145243">There is little to tell that would affect you now. The Assassins are fanatically loyal to Death&apos;s Hand, and he uses that influence to do as he wishes.</string>
  <string id="52137" soundid="145244">He also controls the Imperial Army, but they are no longer in his favor, it seems. Mere guards in comparison to the Assassins.</string>
  <string id="52138" soundid="145245">Death&apos;s Hand was just beginning his rise to power when I left the Lotus Assassins. I do not know much more about him.</string>
  <string id="52139" soundid="145246">Goodbye, then.</string>
  <string id="52143">Student Kia&apos;s injury</string>
  <string id="52144">Chen Yi</string>
  <string id="52145">What&apos;s the nonsense supposed to mean?</string>
  <string id="52149">N/A</string>
  <string id="52150" soundid="158391">[Success] Aw, geez. Now you got me feelin&apos; all guilty about my ma!</string>
  <string id="52151" soundid="158392">[Failure] Hey, you don&apos;t know nothin&apos; about my ma! You leave her out of this!</string>
  <string id="52152" soundid="158393">[Success] A gift from his ma? Aw, geez. I guessh he probably wants it back, huh?</string>
  <string id="52153">Configuration of the Horse</string>
  <string id="52154">Configuration of the Goat</string>
  <string id="52155" soundid="158394">[Failure] So? Why should I care? I got enough to worry about with my own ma. I ain&apos;t sheen her in a long, long time.</string>
  <string id="52158" soundid="158395">[Success] Hey, you don&apos;t have to get all mad or nothin&apos;. I ain&apos;t lookin&apos; to fight you.</string>
  <string id="52159" soundid="158396">Here, take the figurine. *hic* I didn&apos;t mean to cause no trouble. I just missed my ma is all. *sniff*</string>
  <string id="52160" soundid="158397">I ain&apos;t cryin&apos;! I jusht... I jusht got shomething in my eye! *sniff* I... I gotta go back to the boat now. Come on, boys. Let&apos;sh go.</string>
  <string id="52162" soundid="158398">[Failure] You don&apos;t shcare me! You talk big, but my ma didn&apos;t raise no coward.</string>
  <string id="52164" soundid="158399"></string>
  <string id="52165" soundid="158400">Uh... okay then. *hic*</string>
  <string id="52166" soundid="64153">Stuck? Now that reminds me of my favorite song. &quot;I&apos;m a sailor fine... and I like my wine... on the water blue....&quot; Do you know the rest of the words?</string>
  <string id="52167" soundid="64154">&quot;...Making sense ...on the water blue... I knew a sailor named....&quot; Are you sure you don&apos;t know the... the... what do you call them?</string>
  <string id="52174">He was amid a mighty forest of trees that were green despite the cold.</string>
  <string id="52176">The Emperor was raking sand in the impromptu meditation garden he&apos;d ordered constructed.</string>
  <string id="52178">He stood at the edge of a vast plain, the ground covered in snow.</string>
  <string id="52180">He stood near a great river, its banks edged with frost!</string>
  <string id="52182">He stood facing a wall of mountains, the bitter winds freezing the land.</string>
  <string id="52185">The flower guardians may blossom but the warmth of spring can hide an icy heart.</string>
  <string id="52189">The lands to the north are locked in ice and snow forever.</string>
  <string id="52191">This was some time ago, yes.</string>
  <string id="52193">No, all of this happens as we speak. Lady Fourteen Flowers has the gift of prophecy!</string>
  <string id="52197">Heaven&apos;s reach is wide. Weather is not the same in all places, Puzzle.</string>
  <string id="52202">None other than Two Drops Yi Tan, his personal food taster.</string>
  <string id="52204">Any good shops in the area?</string>
  <string id="52206">He turned to the heavens themselves, as they had already turned to him.</string>
  <string id="52208">None other than myself. I am his closest confidant.</string>
  <string id="52210">He fell to the earth, to hear its spirit sing out to him.</string>
  <string id="52212">I&apos;ll go to the fortress now.</string>
  <string id="52213">I am going to do the task for the other recruiter first.</string>
  <string id="52214">He turned to no one. Emperor Tien was alone.</string>
  <string id="52219">The Horselords proved too strong for our forces.</string>
  <string id="52221">I think Sagacious Tien just got a little bored with always winning, to be frank.</string>
  <string id="52223">There was no more land to conquer.</string>
  <string id="52225">Burning fires forced our army to turn back.</string>
  <string id="52227">A shooting star traced the border of our lands.</string>
  <string id="52243" soundid="65932">Wait, don&apos;t hurt me! I was just... hey, you&apos;re no pirate. I remember the face of everyone I used to sail with, and I&apos;ve never seen you before.</string>
  <string id="52244" soundid="65933">My name&apos;s Cheung. Once I was a pirate on the river, but things were different then. We took pride in our work. We were professionals. Not like these lazy, drunken louts!</string>
  <string id="52247" soundid="65936">Pirates are hidden away all through this lair. You shouldn&apos;t have too much trouble with them. One of Gao&apos;s new captains is around. Watch out for her; she&apos;s a tough one.</string>
  <string id="52248" soundid="65937">Up near the top, you&apos;ll find the airships and Gao himself. Maybe Inquisitor Lim, too. He&apos;s so cold he could scare a spirit back to life, then scare him dead all over again.</string>
  <string id="52253" soundid="65942">I was more than just a pirate; I was captain! I robbed and pillaged up and down these waters, but I did things differently. We sailed the waters, not the skies.</string>
  <string id="52254" soundid="65943">Ha! Did you see the looks on their faces when that cannon hit them? Now they&apos;re feeding fish at the bottom of the river!</string>
  <string id="52255" soundid="65944">Gao ruined everything. I tried to tell them, but nobody listened. You&apos;d think the Lotus Assassins would have been a warning. Even a pirate knows better than to get mixed up with them.</string>
  <string id="52257" soundid="65946">The younger pirates used to look up to me. Now they treat me like dirt! They treat me worse than that slave cleaning the pier. But I&apos;m going to get even... I&apos;ll show them!</string>
  <string id="52258">What do you know about the other pirates here?</string>
  <string id="52259">Don&apos;t worry. They won&apos;t kill me.</string>
  <string id="52261">Bah. I&apos;d rather kick in the doors that keep up this secrecy.</string>
  <string id="52262" soundid="65951">That&apos;ll teach the lazy fools to leave equipment half unloaded. They don&apos;t deserve to be called pirates! Go on, give the rope a pull and give &apos;em what they got coming!</string>
  <string id="52263">Once inside, I can take care of myself.</string>
  <string id="52268" soundid="65957">Quit wasting time! Pull the rope and wipe out everyone on the pier, or go take those guard on the dock out yourself. But whatever you do, do it quick.</string>
  <string id="52270" soundid="65959">Watch yourself in this place. One minute you&apos;re on top, the next you&apos;re on the bottom, bowing and scraping.</string>
  <string id="52271" soundid="65960">Hmph! Those pirates didn&apos;t seem to give you much trouble at all. Back in my day, a pirate knew how to fight, but these young ones are soft and weak.</string>
  <string id="52273" soundid="65962">I know this island better than anyone still alive, so I&apos;m the right one to ask. What do you want to know?</string>
  <string id="52275" soundid="65964">Then Gao came with his Lotus Assassins and airships, and suddenly my ideas were old fashioned! My men turned on me, and Gao kept me around as a broken down servant.</string>
  <string id="52278" soundid="65967">Ask away, and I&apos;ll do my best to answer. Any enemy of Gao and the Lotus Assassins is a friend of mine!</string>
  <string id="52281">Who are you?</string>
  <string id="52283">Do you have somewhere safe you can go?</string>
  <string id="52286">Sounds like a good idea.</string>
  <string id="52287">I don&apos;t need fancy tricks. I&apos;m just going to hurt them.</string>
  <string id="52292" soundid="136215"></string>
  <string id="52295">Goodbye.</string>
  <string id="52297">I want to ask you some questions.</string>
  <string id="52302">I want to ask you something else.</string>
  <string id="52303">What do you know about Gao?</string>
  <string id="52307">Any idea about what I might run across in this place?</string>
  <string id="52313">If you were a pirate, how did you end up as a servant?</string>
  <string id="52317" soundid="128088">I&apos;m done with you. Go talk to your precious master. Training will not resume until he has met with you.</string>
  <string id="52318" soundid="128089">Why should I care? I have little interest in the other students here and even less for the mud farmers outside. I am here to train, nothing more.</string>
  <string id="52319" soundid="128090">You&apos;ll soon see what I am capable of. I will make sure of it.</string>
  <string id="52320" soundid="141885">What can I do for you?</string>
  <string id="52321" soundid="128092">I see how you might think that is valuable, but are these mud farmers worth the effort? I don&apos;t think so.</string>
  <string id="52322" soundid="128093">All I care about is my ability and what I want. The cares of everyone else are not my concern.</string>
  <string id="52323" soundid="128094">You&apos;ll soon see what I am capable of. Now, go talk to your precious master. He will not resume our training until he has met with you.</string>
  <string id="52331" soundid="144732">It happened again, didn&apos;t it? You saw something? I don&apos;t like the effect this place has on you. Let&apos;s get going.</string>
  <string id="52332" soundid="144733">Oh, not the best place for a lie-down. Whatever your trouble, we need to keep moving.</string>
  <string id="52333" soundid="144734">Another momentary stumble? This could become a concern if it happens many more times. Try to keep moving.</string>
  <string id="52334" soundid="144735">You fell from the sky, but despite the maddened spirits here, you will benefit. A Spirit Monk was here long ago, fleeing the destruction that orphaned you.</string>
  <string id="52335">You have accepted First Gravedigger Shen&apos;s job to put the ghosts back in their graves. He has asked you to put to rest the spirits of Miss Chan, Merchant Bai and Mister Ren. You can find them throughout the Necropolis. He offers a reward for each one you put down.</string>
  <string id="52336" soundid="128095">Bah! I don&apos;t need the respect of the weak. If they cannot protect themselves, what good are they to me? An endless, foolish road to go down.</string>
  <string id="52337" soundid="141886">This has been a busy day for us all. Is there something you need?</string>
  <string id="52341">Smiling Mountain was right, you have the temper of a child.</string>
  <string id="52344">This from someone nobody wants help from. You are barely welcome here at all.</string>
  <string id="52363" soundid="72528">Where are my manners, though? You&apos;re the Imperial Champion, and a damn fine one, I must say.</string>
  <string id="52367" soundid="72529">Glad to have the Serpent taken care of. He was going to ruin this place before long. Now, what can Three Reach Lao do for you?</string>
  <string id="52371" soundid="72530">You&apos;re one of the arena&apos;s new contestants, and Three Reach Lao always has time for you folks. Except that oaf, Soldier.</string>
  <string id="52374">J01_TOWN</string>
  <string id="52375" soundid="72531">Well, look who it is! The new Imperial Champion, out here mucking with the common folk!</string>
  <string id="52376">Bah. Li is right to fear me now. Let them come.</string>
  <string id="52381">The weak today may be strong tomorrow. I invest so I may reap.</string>
  <string id="52382" soundid="66118">Oh, certainly! We&apos;ll sit back and let you stroll upstairs to kill our leader! Would it help if we drew you a map to his room?</string>
  <string id="52383" soundid="66119">Uh... I don&apos;t think Gao would like that.</string>
  <string id="52384" soundid="66120">I wasn&apos;t serious, you idiot! We&apos;re going to kill this intruder and go back to our drinking. He&apos;s just one man; he can&apos;t beat all of us.</string>
  <string id="52385" soundid="66121">Look around. The odds are not so much in your favor. There&apos;s still a chance for you to run.</string>
  <string id="52386" soundid="66122">What are you talking about, fool?</string>
  <string id="52387" soundid="66123">You haven&apos;t noticed my partner over there watching us? He&apos;s spent his entire lifetime learning how to kill dogs like you. This is your last chance.</string>
  <string id="52388" soundid="66124">You haven&apos;t noticed my partner over there watching us? Don&apos;t let her grace and beauty fool you; she&apos;s deadly. This is your last chance to get out of here alive.</string>
  <string id="52390" soundid="66126">So the thief brought a friend? That just means you won&apos;t die alone. Attack!</string>
  <string id="52409" soundid="66145">My name is Sky. It&apos;s good to see there&apos;s someone else in this place who can&apos;t stand these slaving dogs. We make quite the pair.</string>
  <string id="52410" soundid="66146">Indeed. I find I&apos;m just not saved enough these days. Shame, that.</string>
  <string id="52411" soundid="66147">If you&apos;re going to kill me, I say we save it for a big stunt and make it worthwhile. Besides, I have something very important to accomplish before I die.</string>
  <string id="52412" soundid="66148">It was obvious you weren&apos;t with the pirates, why not deal with them quickly? There&apos;s bigger game above us.</string>
  <string id="52413" soundid="66149">Speaking of which, there&apos;s a very secure and equally intimidating gate blocking the way. If we work together, though, it will be simple to crack.</string>
  <string id="52414">Good thing I was here to save you.</string>
  <string id="52416">You dragged me into your fight!</string>
  <string id="52417">I should kill you for that little stunt!</string>
  <string id="52420">You have better insight into you opponent&apos;s weaknesses, allowing you to exploit them.</string>
  <string id="52421">You can focus your attacks better and do more damage with every strike.</string>
  <string id="52422">Info</string>
  <string id="52423" soundid="165575">He is too powerful.</string>
  <string id="52424" soundid="165576">You knew you could not beat me, exile.</string>
  <string id="52425" soundid="110014">Ya Zhen: Your return was predicted by more than Dawn Star. Assaulting the spirit realm has alerted your enemies.</string>
  <string id="52426" soundid="110015">Few things are more dangerous than the interest of the heavens.</string>
  <string id="52427" soundid="110016">Pardon the intrusion, but might I add the entire army of the Emperor to that list? Or is that too small a thing for your attention!</string>
  <string id="52428" soundid="66232">Never fear. There are people I mean to harm, but you are not one of them.</string>
  <string id="52429" soundid="66233">I will pull the lever once you are in position by the door. </string>
  <string id="52430" soundid="66234"></string>
  <string id="52435" soundid="165577">I wasn&apos;t looking for victory.</string>
  <string id="52436" soundid="110017">Such creatures are not accustomed to needing assistance, or being called on to assist. Both circumstances would likely annoy them.</string>
  <string id="52438" soundid="110018">Chai Ka: Dawn Star was not the only one aware of your return to life. Assaulting the spirit realm has alerted Sun Li.</string>
  <string id="52439" soundid="165578">Just a few seconds.</string>
  <string id="52441">How does the mechanism work?</string>
  <string id="52443">Then what happens?</string>
  <string id="52448">Area attacks are very difficult to evade. To counter them, block by holding &lt;Block&gt; without moving the left thumbstick.</string>
  <string id="52449" soundid="110019">He didn&apos;t consider us a threat. We had no way of fighting him. Just as with Sun Hai, only a Spirit Monk can face him with hope of success.</string>
  <string id="52452" soundid="110020">Unfortunately, Emperor Sun Li sensed your stirrings in the spirit realm as well, and now we are trapped.</string>
  <string id="52455">Pillar</string>
  <string id="52456">Very well. Go unlock the door.</string>
  <string id="52457">If you betray me, I&apos;ll kill you.</string>
  <string id="52459">Switching styles during combat can often make all the difference.</string>
  <string id="52460" soundid="145843">Yes, I will have my people spread rumors of your interest. Once you pass the Silver Round, the Executioner will take an interest. I&apos;m sure he will find you as impressive as I do.</string>
  <string id="52462" soundid="145845">What is the meaning of this?</string>
  <string id="52463" soundid="145846">Hello my love. Or should I call you by your rank now, Captain Sen? Surely it&apos;s been a very long time.</string>
  <string id="52465" soundid="145848">Hmm, well, if you say so. Despite Lord Rento&apos;s insistence to the contrary, I doubt he was a master criminal. Perhaps I&apos;ll just declare Yukong&apos;s bounty a dead matter.</string>
  <string id="52466" soundid="145849">What, that mercenary? Let me have a look! Ha! Would you look at that. Uncovered by a dedicated servant of the Empire!</string>
  <string id="52468" soundid="145851">That will teach me to trust one of the Empire&apos;s hounds!</string>
  <string id="52469" soundid="145852">Here&apos;s the expanded bounty. In light of his successful capture, I&apos;ll overlook that the man almost made it out of the city.</string>
  <string id="52471" soundid="71826">He thinks that with me out of the way, he has the tannery and all my money. But I&apos;ll show him yet!</string>
  <string id="52497">Master Li</string>
  <string id="52498" soundid="72532">Don&apos;t get that look, girl! Three Reach Lao is just pulling your leg. It&apos;s good to see that Serpent fellow out of here.</string>
  <string id="52500" soundid="66391">If it pleases you, stranger, this is a matter of great importance, and no one besides yourself can help me.</string>
  <string id="52501" soundid="66392">They&apos;ve made me a rich man, but they still have much silver to spend, and I have a large enough supply of wine to last many moons before my stocks run dry.</string>
  <string id="52503">No, you may not.</string>
  <string id="52506">Yes, he did.</string>
  <string id="52507">None of your business.</string>
  <string id="52508">Do you have a proposition or not?</string>
  <string id="52510" soundid="151743">Well, well. Is the Imperial City all you expected? It is quite a spectacle compared to the bulk of the Empire. The Marvelous Dragonfly performed perfectly, of course.</string>
  <string id="52511" soundid="66417">Oh surely you can spare just a moment to hear me out? I&apos;m direly in need of assistance, you see.</string>
  <string id="52512" soundid="66418">Once you change this scene, you change the very soul of the production! It&apos;s hardly my play at all if they perform it their way!</string>
  <string id="52513" soundid="66419">They&apos;ve changed it from a commentary of man&apos;s inhumanity to man to a satire of the Empire.</string>
  <string id="52514" soundid="66420">I&apos;m certain the Lotus Assassins would blame me for the satire.</string>
  <string id="52515" soundid="66421">Of course I would pay you. In fact, I&apos;d match... er... Well, this is odd.</string>
  <string id="52517" soundid="66423">It&apos;s just that there&apos;s no &quot;going&quot; rate for female actors or whatever you&apos;d be called. It&apos;s unheard of.</string>
  <string id="52518" soundid="66424">Of course there are, though I&apos;m not supposed to know it. The entire establishment turns a blind eye to them.</string>
  <string id="52519" soundid="66425">They deserve that much respect. I hear the bosom binding, pant stuffing, and whatnot is a far cry from comfortable.</string>
  <string id="52520" soundid="66426">The irony is that many of them get cast as the female roles--fresh faces, you see--leaving us with a woman playing a woman through four layers of costume. Most unsightly.</string>
  <string id="52521" soundid="66427">No. The whole situation leads to some interesting costuming challenges, I can tell you. There are female actors, but the establishment turns a blind eye to them.</string>
  <string id="52522" soundid="66428">Oh, by all the heavens I would never presume, madame. There are female actors, but the establishment turns a blind eye.</string>
  <string id="52523" soundid="66429">I, myself, have pushed long and hard for realism; &quot;verisimilitude&quot; is the word they&apos;re throwing out these days. And what better way to avoiding all that unnecessary shirt stuffing?</string>
  <string id="52524" soundid="66430">Alas, tradition often becomes a barrier blackened by short-sightedness that is not easily overcome.</string>
  <string id="52525" soundid="66431">I need that fire and that passion! That&apos;s what I need.</string>
  <string id="52526" soundid="66432">I don&apos;t think such drastic steps will be necessary. We have the desperation of directors on our side here.</string>
  <string id="52527" soundid="66433">No, that wouldn&apos;t be right at all.</string>
  <string id="52528" soundid="66434">I need you to take a role in the play and read the role the... er, original way.</string>
  <string id="52529" soundid="66435">Remember, you&apos;ll have to memorize your lines, no scripts on stage, of course. Also, make sure you read from this script.</string>
  <string id="52530" soundid="66436">I would most certainly pay you for your time.</string>
  <string id="52531" soundid="66437">I never attend my own plays, no. Much too nerve wracking. Someone goes for me. She is...very kind to do that. I heard how it went.</string>
  <string id="52532" soundid="66438">You do, do you? I have been asking around, you know.</string>
  <string id="52533" soundid="66439">The worst part is that the... ugh... commoners loved it. I&apos;m sure it will run for many turnings of the moon as their boorish faces laugh and laugh.</string>
  <string id="52534" soundid="66440">It will make vast amounts of silver, each coin falling like a weight upon my heart!</string>
  <string id="52535" soundid="66441">Perhaps as many as three!</string>
  <string id="52538">Lost Spirit</string>
  <string id="52541" soundid="151749">No, I have not had any new insights. The best option I can suggest is just to keep your eyes open. There has to be reference to them somewhere.</string>
  <string id="52542">Patron</string>
  <string id="52545">Patron</string>
  <string id="52547" soundid="151755">Certainly. It&apos;s just a flick of a switch. And I&apos;m reasonably sure the trip isn&apos;t even doing any irreparable harm.</string>
  <string id="52551">What&apos;s odd?</string>
  <string id="52552">Something the matter?</string>
  <string id="52553" soundid="151756">Well, I&apos;m judging by the smoke and the panicked state of the people that you were successful in your mission.</string>
  <string id="52554">There&apos;s NO female actors in the entire city?</string>
  <string id="52556">Sounds like a lot of unnecessary work.</string>
  <string id="52558">Do the plays only have male characters?</string>
  <string id="52560">Typical. You think women are too delicate to perform, is that it?</string>
  <string id="52563">Maybe it&apos;s time we tore down some of these traditions. What do you need me to do?</string>
  <string id="52565">If you&apos;re asking that I pretend to be a man, the answer is no.</string>
  <string id="52567">Does this mean you&apos;re not going to pay me for my help?</string>
  <string id="52573">I think it went well.</string>
  <string id="52575">I can&apos;t believe I agreed to help you.</string>
  <string id="52594" soundid="72533">Now don&apos;t get all offended, your championship; I mean no harm. Three Reach Lao is just here thanking you for getting rid of the Serpent.</string>
  <string id="52597">Search for the missing hunter.</string>
  <string id="52598">Seek out the other survivor of the temple attack. Spear has searched everywhere but the ogre cave.</string>
  <string id="52600">You have found Hunter Shau, and he&apos;s clinging to a gem which precipitated the attack at the temple. If you could get a hold of it, perhaps you can lure the creature that attacked you out of hiding.</string>
  <string id="52601">Acquire Hunter Shau&apos;s gem.</string>
  <string id="52602">You need the gem Hunter Shau&apos;s holding on to. You could just take it, but perhaps there&apos;s some way to talk him into giving it to you.</string>
  <string id="52604">You have acquired the gem Hunter Shau found at the temple. It may be a way to lure the creature that attacked the first hunting party out of hiding.</string>
  <string id="52605">Commoner</string>
  <string id="52610">Commoner</string>
  <string id="52673">Boy</string>
  <string id="52678">Girl</string>
  <string id="52683">Beggar</string>
  <string id="52684">I&apos;d like to ask you some questions about the Necropolis.</string>
  <string id="52686">Tell me about Death&apos;s Hand.</string>
  <string id="52688">Beggar</string>
  <string id="52697">Can I ask you some more questions about the arena?</string>
  <string id="52699">Certainly, go ahead.</string>
  <string id="52702">Why is the full name not commonly used any more?</string>
  <string id="52705">Does the Emperor still play an active role in the arena?</string>
  <string id="52707">How does anyone keep track of that many rules?</string>
  <string id="52710">Let&apos;s talk about something else.</string>
  <string id="52726">Throne Room</string>
  <string id="52728" soundid="162466">I have told you what you need to do. Appease one of the Lotus Assassin recruiters to gain access to their fortress.</string>
  <string id="52729">Outer Exit</string>
  <string id="52730">Inner Exit</string>
  <string id="52731">Bridge 1</string>
  <string id="52732">Tomb Door</string>
  <string id="52733">Bridge 2</string>
  <string id="52734">Water Dragon Tower</string>
  <string id="52735">Throne Room</string>
  <string id="52757" soundid="165609">I wanted nothing more than to watch this man die.</string>
  <string id="52758">Outer Exit</string>
  <string id="52759">Inner Exit</string>
  <string id="52760">Bridge 1</string>
  <string id="52761">Entrance </string>
  <string id="52762">Emperor</string>
  <string id="52771" soundid="151757">I&apos;ve made some... repairs to the Marvelous Dragonfly. It&apos;s ready to go as soon as you are. The trip to the palace will be very... quick.</string>
  <string id="52772" soundid="151758">What? Not now... I&apos;m busy with repairs on the Dragonfly. Come back later.</string>
  <string id="52773" soundid="151759">Go, explore the city. I will stay here and watch over the Marvelous Dragonfly. I have some ideas for making her even better. Go... have fun. I know I will.</string>
  <string id="52778">Seven Thunders</string>
  <string id="52779">**Temp** Seven Thuders description</string>
  <string id="52780">Black Mantis</string>
  <string id="52781">**TEMP** Description for Black Mantis style</string>
  <string id="52782">Drunken Master</string>
  <string id="52783">**TEMP** Description of Drunken Master style</string>
  <string id="52784">Leaping Tiger</string>
  <string id="52785">Martial Style
This style can complete a Harmonic Combo. 

With the vigor and speed of the animal for which this martial style was named, Leaping Tiger dazzles onlookers even as it carves up opponents. Practitioners of this Martial style focus so completely on the strength and quickness of the tiger that razor-sharp claws seem to sprout from their fists. The style&apos;s quick, leaping techniques and punishing strikes create a flurry of death that can keep even armed opponents at bay. </string>
  <string id="52786">Monkey Paw</string>
  <string id="52787">**TEMP** Description of Monkey Paw style</string>
  <string id="52788">Shooting Star</string>
  <string id="52789">**TEMP** Description of Shooting Star style</string>
  <string id="52790">Long Sword</string>
  <string id="52791">**TEMP** Description for Single Sword style</string>
  <string id="52792">White Demon</string>
  <string id="52793">Martial Style
This style can complete a Harmonic Combo. 

Many martial artists criticize the White Demon style for being slow and ponderous, but in the hands of a true master it can be one of the deadliest martial styles of all. While it lacks the crowd-pleasing panache of faster styles, White Demon&apos;s sheer power and intimidating techniques plow through opponents like an ogre in a teahouse. </string>
  <string id="52795">You cannot save during combat.</string>
  <string id="52796">Imperial Palace</string>
  <string id="52884">Silk Fox</string>
  <string id="52885">Tell me about the Lotus Assassins.</string>
  <string id="52890">Death&apos;s Hand</string>
  <string id="52893">Tell me about the Emperor&apos;s Tomb.</string>
  <string id="52902">Tell me about the ghost troubles.</string>
  <string id="52906">The Emperor</string>
  <string id="52911">Emperor First Form</string>
  <string id="52912">I&apos;ll ask some other time.</string>
  <string id="52914">I&apos;ll be going now.</string>
  <string id="52916">Master Li</string>
  <string id="52917">[Intimidation] I don&apos;t think you paid me enough for all the work I did.</string>
  <string id="52919">How are you and Tanner Fong working out?</string>
  <string id="52926">A playwright has approached you, hoping that you can help him preserve the integrity of his play. You agreed to take on a small but pivotal role in the performance.</string>
  <string id="52927">The Play&apos;s the Thing</string>
  <string id="52930" soundid="165649">It should be a straightforward task. Convince everyone to move with threats or guile. I would do it myself but I cannot act directly.</string>
  <string id="52995" soundid="67694">The Imperial City is a vast place, my friend. Be sure you don&apos;t get lost.</string>
  <string id="52996" soundid="67695">My father lived through the drought. He can attest to the marvelous change Emperor Sun Hai has brought to the Empire.</string>
  <string id="52999">Lotus Assassin</string>
  <string id="53002" soundid="67696">The Jade Empire would be in ruins if it wasn&apos;t for Emperor Sun Hai.</string>
  <string id="53003" soundid="67697">Some of the finest items you&apos;ll ever find can be bought right here in the city.</string>
  <string id="53035" soundid="105445">There must be fewer travelers for the bandits to prey on. They have to be desperate to attack the village.</string>
  <string id="53041">I must be going.</string>
  <string id="53045" soundid="158373">[Failure] No... Zhong only hurt other ox, too. Zhong is bad.</string>
  <string id="53052" soundid="112826">When you free Ling, I&apos;m sure he&apos;ll pay you and be more than happy to show you his considerable inventory of goods.... some of the best in the Empire I hear.</string>
  <string id="53056">Outlaw</string>
  <string id="53057" soundid="170259">The shrine helps you to focus on your inner voice. Your Chi and Health are replenished.</string>
  <string id="53174">Palace</string>
  <string id="53175" soundid="67446">My techniques for releasing your untapped inner energies are newer and slightly more radical, but even they benefit from a century of research and years of practice.</string>
  <string id="53176" soundid="67447">Put simply, your body possesses incredible energies, some of which can fall out of balance, putting the body at risk of disease.</string>
  <string id="53177" soundid="67448">Acupuncture releases blockages in your body&apos;s meridians--natural pathways for this energy--allowing your body to restore its balance.</string>
  <string id="53178" soundid="67449">I do not care if you consider the methodology accurate. I know the results I can produce.</string>
  <string id="53179" soundid="67450">The new schools have found ways to optimize the body&apos;s energy pathways to make you stronger than you would be normally.</string>
  <string id="53182" soundid="67453">You would have to practically abandon your pursuit of martial prowess to understand them more fully, but you have other skills to hone.</string>
  <string id="53184">Tell me some more.</string>
  <string id="53186">How does this allow you to make people stronger?</string>
  <string id="53187">Sounds like a bunch of nonsense to me.</string>
  <string id="53204" soundid="67490"></string>
  <string id="53265">Area Transition</string>
  <string id="53299">Area Transition</string>
  <string id="53305">To the Necropolis</string>
  <string id="53308">Imperial Soldier</string>
  <string id="53309">Commoner</string>
  <string id="53312">Commoner</string>
  <string id="53341" soundid="165650">The simplest task, I&apos;m sure. Tell him you are relieving him or some such. I can always claim you abused what little authority I have given you.</string>
  <string id="53362">To the Throne Room</string>
  <string id="53367">Imperial Soldier</string>
  <string id="53370">Sky</string>
  <string id="53375" soundid="110352">Gao&apos;s slaving operation found its way to my home several years ago. I was away at the time, but my daughter was there.</string>
  <string id="53384" soundid="110353">Those black-hearted bastards took my daughter, Pinmei. They killed her for resisting them. She was my only child.</string>
  <string id="53388" soundid="110354">I lost her mother when Pinmei was born, but my daughter was something precious in return. The slavers offered no such consolation.</string>
  <string id="53389" soundid="110355">It has been three years since I lost my daughter, and I have spent that time tracking down the men who took her.</string>
  <string id="53390" soundid="110356">I am many things, but broken is not one of them. The past few years have forged my grief into resolve. </string>
  <string id="53391" soundid="110357">Consider how our skills complement each other. I can get into places people would prefer I never see and out of places people would prefer I never leave.</string>
  <string id="53392" soundid="110358">There&apos;s also my knack for finding things. For instance, I was nosing around and stumbled across this.</string>
  <string id="53393" soundid="110359">Hey! That&apos;s the dust inductor I was hiding! The Dragonfly can&apos;t fly without it! It was under the floorboards in my workshop last I looked.</string>
  <string id="53394" soundid="126859">Look, I know I&apos;ve got a bad reputation. But I&apos;m looking to make a clean start. It won&apos;t be easy to change, but I&apos;m willing to try.</string>
  <string id="53395" soundid="110361">In my mind, you stand the best chance of facing down Gao&apos;s masters. We also have a far greater chance of succeeding together rather than apart.</string>
  <string id="53396" soundid="110362">Next time I hide something, I&apos;m packing explosives around it. Explosives shaped like silver bananas! Stops thieves, monkeys, and monkey thieves in one fell swoop.</string>
  <string id="53398" soundid="110364">He&apos;s full of himself, but he&apos;s talented enough to be useful. Besides, his solutions seem more practical than others our little group might offer.</string>
  <string id="53399" soundid="110365">I don&apos;t know if I trust this man, but we can&apos;t afford to turn away potential allies. Not with what lies ahead.</string>
  <string id="53400" soundid="110366">Your companion&apos;s ability to judge character is matched only by her beauty. I may not be the most constant of men, but I am true.</string>
  <string id="53401" soundid="110367">If you are planning to take on the servants of Death&apos;s Hand, you&apos;ll need all the help you can get.</string>
  <string id="53402" soundid="110368">Only if I can watch you as well. Fair is fair, after all.</string>
  <string id="53403" soundid="110369">I have nothing to hide. My motives are plain, and our causes are aligned. </string>
  <string id="53404" soundid="110370">I assure you, I will be as devoted and capable as any of your other companions.</string>
  <string id="53405" soundid="110371">Ha! If I could harness all that hot air, I could make a furnace to power the whole of the Imperial City! If you&apos;re done with all the talking, I have to go make the Dragonfly ready for some flying. </string>
  <string id="53409" soundid="111593">You still here? There&apos;s nothing more I can help you with. Can&apos;t you just leave an old pirate in peace?</string>
  <string id="53410">You won&apos;t resist me for long!</string>
  <string id="53411" soundid="165651">It must be traveling through the Necropolis now. Go outside and stop it from reaching the fortress. I don&apos;t care how you do it.</string>
  <string id="53413">How would you handle the tasks to arrange Shin&apos;s death?</string>
  <string id="53417">Healing rate increased to 8 Health per second.</string>
  <string id="53419">Healing rate increased to 12 Health per second.</string>
  <string id="53447">The witnesses in the Hall of Induction.</string>
  <string id="53448">The press operator.</string>
  <string id="53449">The slave shipment.</string>
  <string id="53450">In Inventory</string>
  <string id="53453">That&apos;s horrible!</string>
  <string id="53454">Maybe you should take some time to mourn your daughter.</string>
  <string id="53456">Minister Sheng</string>
  <string id="53462">Strref 53462</string>
  <string id="53463" soundid="93062">[Success] I always worry about silver, but I see your point.</string>
  <string id="53464" soundid="93063">[Success] Quick ears, Lucky Cho. Quick enough to catch what you missed at any rate. I will reduce my rate for this one.</string>
  <string id="53466" soundid="67799">Pretend for a moment that he asked you to close the Great Dam. He probably talked about saving the town, but I bet he offered you nothing for your services. I offer more.</string>
  <string id="53467" soundid="67800">I like the way you come right to the point. It shows that you are strong and decisive. I will answer the same way. I do not want you to close the Great Dam.</string>
  <string id="53469" soundid="67802">I am in no danger, for example. With the silver I have, I can buy my way out of this town. Any who failed to plan deserve whatever happens to them.</string>
  <string id="53470">Wok</string>
  <string id="53471" soundid="67804">If you perform this service for me, I will pay you twenty percent of my profits to date. Rest assured, it&apos;s a very substantial sum.</string>
  <string id="53472">Wok</string>
  <string id="53473" soundid="127431">Well, that&apos;s a relief. Can&apos;t have her going off and trying to rip out my eyes or something every time I go around there. I need those eyes!</string>
  <string id="53474" soundid="67807">Excellent. Now, when you destroy the controls of the Great Dam, you will no doubt come across some vital piece of equipment.</string>
  <string id="53475" soundid="67808">Bring me that vital equipment to prove that the Great Dam is truly stuck in the open position, and I will happily honor my word and pay you in full.</string>
  <string id="53476" soundid="67809">Twenty percent of my profit to date. Remember that.</string>
  <string id="53477" soundid="67810">I appreciate all you have done for me. Is there anything I can do for you?</string>
  <string id="53480" soundid="67813">As I told you before, I sell only one thing, and I doubt you&apos;d like my new prices... especially with the dam in such a state. I&apos;d rather not anger one such as you.</string>
  <string id="53481" soundid="67814">Of course, if you need something else, there are other merchants here to talk to. In that light, is there anything I can do for you?</string>
  <string id="53482" soundid="67815">Greetings. I have heard an interesting rumor. Some claim they saw an explosion atop the Great Dam. Some say the controls of the Dam have been destroyed.</string>
  <string id="53483" soundid="67816">They think that the Great Dam is now stuck open forever. Only you would know. Is this true? And do you have proof?</string>
  <string id="53484" soundid="67817">Ah... a Jade Heart. The Emperor&apos;s mages must have imbued this stone with the power to control the Great Dam. The controls will be useless without it!</string>
  <string id="53485" soundid="127432">Here&apos;s the reward I promised you.</string>
  <string id="53486" soundid="127433">Now, if you find any more, remember: I&apos;ll pay good money for you to put them back down again. So get out there and get some ghosts--er... venerated ancestors, eh-heheh.</string>
  <string id="53487" soundid="67820">Destroy the Great Dam&apos;s controls so it can never be closed. When you do, you will surely come across some sort of vital equipment.</string>
  <string id="53488" soundid="67821">Bring me that item as proof, and I will pay you twenty percent of my earnings to date... unlike the beggars of this town who ask you to help them for free. </string>
  <string id="53489" soundid="67822">Your answer is straightforward and blunt. As a businessman, I appreciate that. I will be equally blunt. I do not want you to close the Great Dam.</string>
  <string id="53493" soundid="127434">You know, you&apos;ve done a lot of good here in the Necropolis. You&apos;ve managed to clear out pretty much all of the really troublesome spirits here.</string>
  <string id="53495" soundid="127435">One spirit didn&apos;t stay here at all, though! Took up his body and left! Moved in with his son, I heard, and the son isn&apos;t pleased. He even asked me for a refund!</string>
  <string id="53497" soundid="127436">Now that was an expensive burial... I can&apos;t give refunds like that! It&apos;s bad for business, too, having my customers getting up and walking away. That&apos;s where you come in.</string>
  <string id="53498" soundid="127437">I need you to go to the tanner&apos;s in the city core and put his father back in his grave, once and for all! It&apos;s Tanner Fong. Eh-heh, there&apos;ll be an extra big reward for that one.</string>
  <string id="53503">Crashed flier</string>
  <string id="53504">Gate</string>
  <string id="53505">Let me see your wares, wineseller.</string>
  <string id="53509" soundid="127438">That area is valuable, what with all the business I&apos;ve been getting recently, and the graves need to be... uh... inspected as well, so hurry it up.</string>
  <string id="53510" soundid="127439">Ah, that one. He&apos;s mad, I tell you. Mad with fear, though of what I have no idea. You&apos;d think he&apos;d be grateful, considering what&apos;s gone on here.</string>
  <string id="53511" soundid="127440">He was murdered in an alleyway. Happens a lot in the poorer districts. They eventually caught his murderers and they were beheaded. I know. I put them in the ground myself. Dead as can be.</string>
  <string id="53517">To the Throne Room</string>
  <string id="53591">Water Dragon Spirit</string>
  <string id="53599">Lotus Elite</string>
  <string id="53600">Dishwasher Wong</string>
  <string id="53609">No Filter</string>
  <string id="53610">Martial Only</string>
  <string id="53611">Weapon Only</string>
  <string id="53612">Transformation Only</string>
  <string id="53613">Magic Only</string>
  <string id="53616" soundid="112827">Suit yourself, but it&apos;s that or we fight... and then of course, you get nothing.</string>
  <string id="53619" soundid="72037">You&apos;re here from Shen? This is his mess! He should have buried him properly!</string>
  <string id="53620">Lotus Elite</string>
  <string id="53625">Lotus Elite</string>
  <string id="53628">I&apos;m sure the play will be fine without me.</string>
  <string id="53641">Dirge Gate</string>
  <string id="53663">Dirge Fountain</string>
  <string id="53665">I&apos;ve heard enough.</string>
  <string id="53751">You successfully found and dealt with all three of the ghosts that were haunting the Necropolis and troubling First Gravedigger Shen.</string>
  <string id="53752">A Mournful Ghost</string>
  <string id="53753">Bring peace to Miss Chan. She can be found somewhere in the Necropolis. While Shen will reward you individually, he&apos;s ultimately tasked you with destroying all three of the ghosts.</string>
  <string id="53772">To the City</string>
  <string id="53781">Gentle Breezes</string>
  <string id="53782" soundid="72038">Good, good. I&apos;ll give you a reward if you just take that wretched old man out of my house so that I never have to see him again!</string>
  <string id="53784" soundid="72039">Look... I&apos;ll give you money, yes? Just take that wretched old man out of my house so that I never have to see him again!</string>
  <string id="53787" soundid="72040">He&apos;s inside. Just... just get him out of here! This is my house, and he&apos;s supposed to stay dead!</string>
  <string id="53789" soundid="150750">However, I have had some trouble attaining parts of late. My previous... associate went on a trip to retrieve valuable parts and never returned.</string>
  <string id="53795">Student</string>
  <string id="53797">Arena Creature Pens</string>
  <string id="53803">Bang Bang Chin</string>
  <string id="53813">Yituo the Guard</string>
  <string id="53814">To the Boathouse</string>
  <string id="53816">Temple Approach</string>
  <string id="53818" soundid="68354">I love living in the Imperial City. There&apos;s always something for me and my friends to do.</string>
  <string id="53819" soundid="68355">My mom says the Emperor is a great man for stopping the drought.</string>
  <string id="53820" soundid="68356">I love playing in the city. There&apos;s so many places to see.</string>
  <string id="53821" soundid="68357">I wonder if the princess used to play in the streets when she was little.</string>
  <string id="53822">Painting</string>
  <string id="53823" soundid="155900">Well, look who we have here. There&apos;s no Princess to save you this time.</string>
  <string id="53825" soundid="155901">Do you think we&apos;d forget? You can&apos;t humiliate us and just walk away.</string>
  <string id="53826" soundid="155902">Don&apos;t look at me... I can&apos;t do anything right now... not like this.</string>
  <string id="53828" soundid="155903">We&apos;ll teach you to insult a guard of the Imperial City!</string>
  <string id="53839" soundid="142086">Bearded tongue grass will make her feel the same, but it&apos;s only deadening the pain. It doesn&apos;t actually do her any good.</string>
  <string id="53841" soundid="68380">The Imperial City is the greatest. I moved here from the country; I should know.</string>
  <string id="53842" soundid="68381">I saw the Emperor once, but he was really far away, and I couldn&apos;t see through the crowd.</string>
  <string id="53843" soundid="68382">My dad says there was a drought here a long time ago, but it&apos;s hard to believe. There&apos;s water everywhere!</string>
  <string id="53844" soundid="68383">My dad bought me the best toy ever at one of the shops here in the city.</string>
  <string id="53868">Training Results</string>
  <string id="53890">Demon Form</string>
  <string id="53891">Demon Form</string>
  <string id="53892">Incisive Chorus</string>
  <string id="53893" soundid="123387">This here&apos;s a private club. Members only.</string>
  <string id="53895" soundid="123388">Why didn&apos;t you say so in the first place? Go on in. They&apos;ll unlock the door for you.</string>
  <string id="53898">Theater Play Script</string>
  <string id="53899">[TEMP] Theater Play Script Description</string>
  <string id="53901">I&apos;ll go see if there&apos;s any way to cure her wound.</string>
  <string id="53902" soundid="68442">Prepare yourself for a potential attack while I tend to my fallen student. I will return as soon as I can. We will continue our discussion when the threat is over.</string>
  <string id="53903" soundid="68443">Those who announce their important destiny before they are ready tend to meet unfortunate ends. The wise only seek attention when capable of dealing with it.</string>
  <string id="53904" soundid="131763">The ultimate goal is to prevent Minister Sheng from delivering his report to Judge Fang. How you accomplish that is up to you... and is the true essence of the test.</string>
  <string id="53905" soundid="68445">I was known as Sun Li the Glorious Strategist. I am the brother of Emperor Sun Hai.</string>
  <string id="53906" soundid="68446">I was ashamed. He seized your homeland during the Long Drought. It was an aggressive change in the Empire that would soon bring Death&apos;s Hand to power.</string>
  <string id="53908" soundid="68448">Our dead no longer drift to the underworld. They wander lost, going mad. In time they may overwhelm the living. It began when your people were destroyed.</string>
  <string id="53909" soundid="68449">You condemn without knowing all the facts. That is my fault, but I am trying to make up for it as quickly as circumstances allow.</string>
  <string id="53910" soundid="68450">We are on the edge of the Empire, and not all spirits make their presence known. We are not immune, but I kept you isolated. This information could endanger you.</string>
  <string id="53911" soundid="141887">Thank you! I&apos;m afraid that with Dawn Star missing, there won&apos;t be much opportunity to train with Smiling Mountain, but I still very much appreciate the gesture.</string>
  <string id="53912" soundid="141888">The sun breaks through the clouds when I hear news like this!</string>
  <string id="53913" soundid="68453">The first assassin found us by accident. The next attack may not be so... unfocused. To fix the world you may threaten the power of some dangerous people.</string>
  <string id="53916" soundid="141889">Heavens! I can already feel it working. That&apos;s amazing! Yes, yes, this should be perfect!</string>
  <string id="53917" soundid="126860">I suppose I can&apos;t reasonably ask for more than that, can I? Perhaps this union has potential after all.</string>
  <string id="53918">I&apos;m sure it was for a good reason, Master.</string>
  <string id="53919">I would like to challenge Kia Min&apos;s record.</string>
  <string id="53921">Why would you do that?</string>
  <string id="53923">Does it have something to do with the bandit assassin?</string>
  <string id="53924" soundid="126861">You know, I think we should get to know each other a little better... in private.</string>
  <string id="53926">Summoned Ghost</string>
  <string id="53928">Myths and legends. Start making sense.</string>
  <string id="53931">Why haven&apos;t I witnessed this?</string>
  <string id="53932" soundid="141890">The poultice must have cost you some silver. Let me repay you! What did it cost?</string>
  <string id="53933" soundid="141891">I&apos;m surprised. It&apos;s so effective I would have guessed it cost more. Here, take the silver. I give it happily.</string>
  <string id="53938" soundid="126862">[Failure] Yes, she has a lot to learn. But culture, class, and training will bring even this ornery dog to the heel.</string>
  <string id="53939" soundid="126863">Bring me to a heel? How about I bury the heel of my boot into that soft skull of your swollen head, you arrogant pig!</string>
  <string id="53940" soundid="136147">I&apos;m not Kang the Stupid. Eventually Gao is going to see me as more nuisance than asset. Plus he took my Amber Mosquitoes and ruined them through duplication.</string>
  <string id="53941">Tomb of the Dignified Collector</string>
  <string id="54209">Guard</string>
  <string id="54215">The Outlander refuses to leave the Scholars&apos; Garden, south of the Imperial City&apos;s Golden Way district.</string>
  <string id="54216">The Minister of Culture, impressed with your willingness to stand up for yourself, has asked you to help deal with an Outlander. A pompous buffoon, this foreigner has made a habit of insulting your culture.</string>
  <string id="54228" soundid="134947"></string>
  <string id="54239" soundid="160754">Ah, well, you are more than welcome. However, I must attend to the students. Enjoy your stay.</string>
  <string id="54301">I need to speak to Ai Ling about Bei.</string>
  <string id="54302">Fine. I&apos;m going.</string>
  <string id="54303" soundid="123391">You needed something, fortuitinate one?</string>
  <string id="54306" soundid="123392">Yes. I need to speak with you in private. It seems Warrior Zhang has decided to... retire.</string>
  <string id="54309" soundid="123395">I&apos;m finished here. If you&apos;re here to fight, do what they tell you.</string>
  <string id="54311" soundid="123397">Did the glint of silver get in your eye?</string>
  <string id="54313">I think we should discuss my payment first.</string>
  <string id="54314">[Intuition] Remember, your friend&apos;s freedom is at stake.</string>
  <string id="54315">[Intimidation] Give me some silver or I&apos;m leaving!</string>
  <string id="54317">Forget it then. I&apos;m leaving.</string>
  <string id="54324">Perhaps this will teach you a lesson about pestering your betters, worm!</string>
  <string id="54326" soundid="151760">Silk Fox is a princess... *the* Princess. Strange happenings indeed. Why would a princess want to run about looking like... that?</string>
  <string id="54401" soundid="150802">Excellent, I am most pleased. The prefect of Shangdang county will be glad to hear he has an escort. His ships have taken a heavy toll lately.</string>
  <string id="54402" soundid="150803">There are many raiders between here and the prefect&apos;s home, and his ship is intended more for... luxury and less for war.</string>
  <string id="54404" soundid="71827">Um... well, you see, I have friends! I can get things done!</string>
  <string id="54405" soundid="71828">I just have to get them to listen to me.</string>
  <string id="54458" soundid="151220">The nobleman was buried in one of the larger tower-tombs closer to the entrance. I tried to enter, but....</string>
  <string id="54471">Goodbye.</string>
  <string id="54567" soundid="72042">Haven&apos;t you dealt with my father yet?</string>
  <string id="54568" soundid="72043">Die? Oh.. uh... old age and all that. He was quite an old fellow... may his memory be preserved. But he was quite senile by the end, yammering on.</string>
  <string id="54584">Lotus Assassin</string>
  <string id="54587">Lotus Assassin</string>
  <string id="54590">Lotus Assassin</string>
  <string id="54593">Lotus Assassin</string>
  <string id="54596">Lotus Assassin</string>
  <string id="54599">Lotus Assassin</string>
  <string id="54602">Lotus Assassin</string>
  <string id="54605">Lotus Assassin</string>
  <string id="54609">Bell Tower</string>
  <string id="54612" soundid="71829">Hm... Hey, you could help me convince them! I could give you a good reward!</string>
  <string id="54613" soundid="71830">There wouldn&apos;t be a problem if they hadn&apos;t tried to bury me in the first place!</string>
  <string id="54614" soundid="71831">But I see where this is going. You&apos;re planning to just make me leave, is that it? Or... or something a little more permanent?</string>
  <string id="54615" soundid="71832">Uh... No need to be so hasty about that.</string>
  <string id="54616" soundid="71833">Uh... no. No. No need to get hasty on that. I never said all my problems would be solved.</string>
  <string id="54617" soundid="71834">I... um... I could make it worth your while to see that this gets sorted out in my favor.</string>
  <string id="54618" soundid="71835">Well, uh... yeah, but once we get it back from him, I&apos;ll make sure you get a good reward!</string>
  <string id="54619" soundid="71836">Well... I could offer you more.</string>
  <string id="54620" soundid="71837"></string>
  <string id="54621" soundid="71838">Say... a couple hundred silver? Enough to live comfortably for quite some time.</string>
  <string id="54622" soundid="71839">Good, good. Now let&apos;s go set that young upstart straight!</string>
  <string id="54623" soundid="71840">[Success] Well... I suppose I need your help. Take this. It&apos;s... it&apos;s all I have.</string>
  <string id="54624" soundid="71841">[Failure] I don&apos;t have any more to give. You can&apos;t take what I don&apos;t have. I&apos;ve made my offer.</string>
  <string id="54625">You&apos;re dead, you just don&apos;t know it.</string>
  <string id="54627">I&apos;m here to put you back in the ground, spirit.</string>
  <string id="54629">I don&apos;t really care about you or your son. I&apos;m being paid.</string>
  <string id="54632">Wait. Are you saying you&apos;re not dead?</string>
  <string id="54636">Why would your son try to bury you alive?</string>
  <string id="54638">Really? How? Everyone says you&apos;re dead.</string>
  <string id="54641">I&apos;m here to make sure you&apos;re not a problem to them anymore.</string>
  <string id="54644">I think it would be easier for everyone if you really were dead.</string>
  <string id="54646">So, you&apos;re saying that if you were dead for real, there wouldn&apos;t be any more problems.</string>
  <string id="54648">But your son already took everything.</string>
  <string id="54649">Your son already promised me money to get rid of you.</string>
  <string id="54651">Agreed. Let&apos;s go talk to your son.</string>
  <string id="54653">How much are we talking here?</string>
  <string id="54654">Sure, I&apos;ll take it.</string>
  <string id="54656">[Intimidation] No, give me more.</string>
  <string id="54657">No, I think it&apos;s simpler if you just die.</string>
  <string id="54660" soundid="150751">I need someone brave, someone who is a capable pilot. The missions I have are dangerous, but the rewards are worth it.</string>
  <string id="54661" soundid="150752">I will pay you good silver, and I can sell you parts for your flyer... to make it better.</string>
  <string id="54662" soundid="150753">What? Make it better! This is the finest ship of it&apos;s kind... I should know... I made it. You&apos;re just a fix-it man... what would do you know about ships?</string>
  <string id="54663" soundid="150754">I have been working on flyers since they first started appearing in the Empire. I take these rickety contraptions and make them into something amazing!</string>
  <string id="54664" soundid="150755">Rickety? There has never been a flyer more solid than the Marvelous Dragonfly! Rickety... your wits are the only thing rickety around here!</string>
  <string id="54665" soundid="150756">What? The Marvelous Dragonfly is... why do I bother? You obviously have no grasp of such things.</string>
  <string id="54667" soundid="150758">As you say. All the more reason to work with me. If your flyer is truly that good, you&apos;ll have no problems. Very few at least.</string>
  <string id="54668" soundid="150759">I have some supplies in the north provinces that I need to pick up immediately. We&apos;ve had trouble with bandits up there, so it might be tricky.</string>
  <string id="54669" soundid="150760">If you could bring me those supplies, I&apos;d have the parts necessary to upgrade your flyer. What do you say?</string>
  <string id="54670" soundid="150761">Very good! Here&apos;s your wind map; it&apos;ll show you where to go. I&apos;ll also pay extra if you get rid of those bandits plaguing the area.</string>
  <string id="54671" soundid="156181">Very impressive. Your win over Third Brother was... unexpected, to say the least. I doubt I can offer you a better challenge, but I won&apos;t decline if you ask me to fight.</string>
  <string id="54672" soundid="150763">But... I see. Well, if you change your mind, I will be here. I have nothing else to do in the meantime. Goodbye.</string>
  <string id="54678">Select Area</string>
  <string id="54682" soundid="71950"></string>
  <string id="54683" soundid="71951"></string>
  <string id="54684" soundid="71952"></string>
  <string id="54685" soundid="71953"></string>
  <string id="54689">Dawn Star</string>
  <string id="54692">Kang the Mad</string>
  <string id="54695">MAX</string>
  <string id="54696">Black Whirlwind</string>
  <string id="54704" soundid="72044">In the end, I think it was probably best he passed on, but not now that he&apos;s come back! And he&apos;s... uh... brought his body back with him. Damn ghosts.</string>
  <string id="54705">Kang</string>
  <string id="54708" soundid="136449">We have tried so hard to find a way to end the fox&apos;s attacks. She must be stopped! We thought we were close, but no.</string>
  <string id="54709" soundid="136450">Two people cannot move as quickly as one. This path is dangerous, but he was willing to brave it.</string>
  <string id="54710" soundid="136451">He may have seemed... simple to you, but he was a brave soul. He ran in the hopes of bringing us food and help, of course.</string>
  <string id="54711" soundid="136452">We are... not like her, and thus she hates us. There is no reason to a mad fox, no reason you would understand.</string>
  <string id="54712" soundid="136453">Perhaps the ghosts have driven her mad, or maybe it is her rage that changed the trees. The only way to be sure is to stop her.</string>
  <string id="54713" soundid="136454">One of us here in the inn overheard the hunter and the big man, who are now at the Forest Shadow&apos;s temple.</string>
  <string id="54714">As you drew closer to the town, the source of the black pall of smoke was apparent. Two Rivers, your home since birth, burned with an unnatural intensity.</string>
  <string id="54715" soundid="161020">It&apos;s good to see that you&apos;re back safely, Min.</string>
  <string id="54716" soundid="136457">The ghosts rage and hunger for release, and such things are rich sustenance to the Mother. </string>
  <string id="54717" soundid="136458">As her strength grew, the trees changed to reflect her glory, as did we!</string>
  <string id="54730" soundid="72045">Look, I don&apos;t have time to answer any questions with that... that ghost wandering about my house, claiming he&apos;s still alive!</string>
  <string id="54731" soundid="72046">Just... just make him go away! I don&apos;t care how you do it!</string>
  <string id="54732" soundid="72047">Have you dealt with my father yet?</string>
  <string id="54733" soundid="72048">Good. Good! I&apos;m sure we can arrange some suitable form of compensation.</string>
  <string id="54734" soundid="72049">Here we go.</string>
  <string id="54735" soundid="72050">Now remember: He was just another ghost. You did him a huge favor in pushing him on to his proper place in the afterlife.</string>
  <string id="54736" soundid="72051">Since its perfectly all right, and you only did what you had to, there&apos;s no need to mention this to anyone. </string>
  <string id="54737" soundid="72052">Private family matter, you understand.</string>
  <string id="54738" soundid="72053">Now, I have things to... attend to. I must go quickly... for mourning, you understand.</string>
  <string id="54739" soundid="150764">Have you changed your mind? My offer still stands. I will happily upgrade your flyer if you accept my mission. Do you want to retrieve the supplies for me?</string>
  <string id="54740" soundid="72055">What are you doing with HIM? You were supposed to get rid of him!</string>
  <string id="54741" soundid="72056">What the hell do we need to talk about? He&apos;s dead, and you&apos;re supposed to get rid of him!</string>
  <string id="54742" soundid="72057">I&apos;m not dead! You just convinced everyone I was so you could steal the business and my money!</string>
  <string id="54743" soundid="72058">He was as good as dead anyway! Look at him! The old fart doesn&apos;t have more than a year or two left, anyway!</string>
  <string id="54744" soundid="72059">Hey!</string>
  <string id="54745" soundid="72060">Look, this doesn&apos;t have to end badly. It could work out very well for you, in fact.</string>
  <string id="54746" soundid="72061">Just make him... disappear, and I&apos;ll reward you well. Nobody needs their *deceased* relatives coming back and making trouble for the living, now do they?</string>
  <string id="54747" soundid="72062">So what if I did! He never cared about us, anyway! All he was interested in was his business... a business I should have inherited years ago!</string>
  <string id="54748" soundid="72063">You ungrateful wretch! I raised you from when you were a snot-nosed child and this is the gratitude I get?</string>
  <string id="54749" soundid="72064">I&apos;m not leaving until I get my life back!</string>
  <string id="54750" soundid="72065">How could you do this to me? I&apos;m your father, dammit!</string>
  <string id="54751" soundid="72066">Because you never loved me! It was always you and your business! Now you&apos;re getting yours, you old bastard!</string>
  <string id="54752" soundid="72067">I... I don&apos;t know what to say. How could you think that? Since your mother passed away, you were all I had.</string>
  <string id="54753" soundid="72068">[Success] I never thought... Oh, I&apos;ve been so wrong to ignore you. How could I have neglected you like that?</string>
  <string id="54754" soundid="72069">Father....</string>
  <string id="54755" soundid="72070">I&apos;m sorry, my son. I should never have neglected you all these years. When your mother passed away, I... I just didn&apos;t know what to do.</string>
  <string id="54756" soundid="72071">I hid my own feelings away in my anger and despair. I only wish I had had the eyes to see what it did to you.</string>
  <string id="54757" soundid="72072">We&apos;ve both been so wrong, father.</string>
  <string id="54758" soundid="72073">Indeed we have, and if it weren&apos;t for this stranger, this would all have likely ended in tragedy.</string>
  <string id="54759" soundid="72074">Here is the money I promised. I shall not need the task to be carried out any longer.</string>
  <string id="54760" soundid="72075">As a token of our gratitude, my son will gladly pay you the money I had promised you.</string>
  <string id="54761" soundid="72076">Ah, yes, of course. My son will gladly pay you the money I promised.</string>
  <string id="54762" soundid="72077">Yes, of course. Here it is.</string>
  <string id="54763" soundid="72078">Of course. Here is the money I promised you. Needless to say, you won&apos;t need to carry out your task.</string>
  <string id="54764" soundid="72079">Thank you for showing us the errors of our ways, stranger. May the heavens shine upon your journeys in the future.</string>
  <string id="54766" soundid="72081">[Success] He... He... Oh father, how could I have ever done this to you?</string>
  <string id="54767" soundid="72082">No... you are right to hate me. I have been a poor father.</string>
  <string id="54768" soundid="72083">Wha... No!</string>
  <string id="54769" soundid="146538"></string>
  <string id="54770" soundid="146539"></string>
  <string id="54772" soundid="72087"></string>
  <string id="54773" soundid="72088">I want him gone. I don&apos;t care how you do it.</string>
  <string id="54774" soundid="72089">Offered you... But he has no money! He&apos;s a broke, poor beggar now! I own everything!</string>
  <string id="54775" soundid="72090">Only because you convinced everyone I was dead!</string>
  <string id="54776" soundid="72091">Grr... Fine! I&apos;ll double what he&apos;s paying you if you just get rid of him! I don&apos;t care how!</string>
  <string id="54777" soundid="72092">Wha... No!</string>
  <string id="54779" soundid="72094">Ah... good. A little... messier than I had hoped for, but... as long as no one sees the blood, no one&apos;s suspicions should be raised.</string>
  <string id="54780" soundid="72095">Now, I have to dispose of his body. I&apos;ll get Shen to come by later and pick it up.</string>
  <string id="54781" soundid="72096">Here is your money. I can&apos;t have you seen around here anymore, so please leave.</string>
  <string id="54782">Are you Tanner Fong?</string>
  <string id="54783">What old man are you talking about?</string>
  <string id="54786">Gravedigger Shen told me about him.</string>
  <string id="54788">I&apos;ll deal with him for you.</string>
  <string id="54789" soundid="150765">You&apos;ve returned. Have you reconsidered? Would you like to hear my proposal now?</string>
  <string id="54790">This isn&apos;t my problem.</string>
  <string id="54791" soundid="150766">You have returned, and in one piece, I see.</string>
  <string id="54792">You mean the dead Tanner Fong? Yeah, I&apos;m here for him.</string>
  <string id="54793" soundid="150767">Not only did you retrieve my supplies, but you made quite a dent in those bandits. For that, I&apos;ll gladly pay you extra.</string>
  <string id="54795">I haven&apos;t seen him yet.</string>
  <string id="54796">How did your father die?</string>
  <string id="54799">I&apos;d like to ask you some questions.</string>
  <string id="54801">I&apos;ll get on that right away.</string>
  <string id="54802" soundid="150768">Not bad, you brought back the supplies and you took out a few bandits on your way. You can have a little bit extra for that.</string>
  <string id="54803">I made sure he&apos;ll stay down for good.</string>
  <string id="54809" soundid="150769">Well, the bandits seemed to have their way with you, but at least you brought back the supplies. Here&apos;s your payment.</string>
  <string id="54811">He&apos;s gone to his rest now.</string>
  <string id="54812">He&apos;s dead. Where&apos;s my money?</string>
  <string id="54813">I think you two need to talk.</string>
  <string id="54815">You buried him alive!</string>
  <string id="54819">He&apos;s not dead. You tried to kill him.</string>
  <string id="54822">Come on, Elder Fong, we&apos;re leaving.</string>
  <string id="54823">Then you two have to work it out yourselves.</string>
  <string id="54826">[Intuition] Elder Fong, maybe you should have talked to your son more.</string>
  <string id="54830">You two should put the past behind you.</string>
  <string id="54835">So now that you&apos;ve made up, I&apos;m still going to get paid, right?</string>
  <string id="54841">This is melodrama... I prefer tragedy. Die!</string>
  <string id="54842">[Intuition] Younger Fong, he was just trying to support you.</string>
  <string id="54845">Oh no... I see where this is going, and I&apos;m going to have to kill both of you to stop it.</string>
  <string id="54850">We&apos;re going. *Now*.</string>
  <string id="54852">Then I guess you&apos;ll have to lose it.</string>
  <string id="54853">So, you&apos;re asking me to kill him for real.</string>
  <string id="54854">You two have to figure this out for yourselves.</string>
  <string id="54855">Then I guess Elder Fong has to die.</string>
  <string id="54856">He&apos;s offered me more than you did.</string>
  <string id="54859">No, you two have to work this out yourselves.</string>
  <string id="54860">I guess that gives you one dead old man.</string>
  <string id="54861" soundid="196236"></string>
  <string id="54865" soundid="150770">There were some great flyer parts among those supplies. Would you like to have a look at them? Or, if you&apos;d prefer, I could tell you about another mission I have for you.</string>
  <string id="54887" soundid="72600">Are you ready yet? The more I think about the information you found, the more I need answers straight from my father.</string>
  <string id="54888" soundid="72601">Well, we meet again. I&apos;ve watched your progress. It seems I underestimated you in Tien&apos;s Landing.</string>
  <string id="54889" soundid="72602">I have no doubt that you will make as much of an impact on the Imperial City.</string>
  <string id="54890" soundid="72603">I understand. Our last meeting was under... interesting circumstances. You may address me as Princess Lian the Heavenly Lily.</string>
  <string id="54891" soundid="72604">It is, as you can see, customary to bow in my presence.</string>
  <string id="54892" soundid="72605">Hmm... somehow I did not expect you to kowtow so quickly. Or maybe I just hoped you wouldn&apos;t. I get so tired of fawning servants.</string>
  <string id="54893" soundid="72606">That is why I often travel without official escort, and occasionally present myself as someone less... bridled by the rules of the court.</string>
  <string id="54894" soundid="72607">You understand why I don&apos;t go into detail here in the street, don&apos;t you? With what I have to tell you, I don&apos;t want to lose that option of disguise.</string>
  <string id="54895" soundid="72608">That would be best. I trust the servants I keep, but this is best discussed away from the open street.</string>
  <string id="54896" soundid="72609">I will not speak the location aloud. Take this note. We will meet nearby, but I must have a moment to acquire... more fitting attire.</string>
  <string id="54897" soundid="72610">Very well. We will continue speaking later. I&apos;m sure we both have questions that need answering.</string>
  <string id="54898" soundid="72611">I&apos;m certain that my entourage would prefer that this take place in private. Your gruff nature is a bit too much for them.</string>
  <string id="54899" soundid="72612"></string>
  <string id="54900" soundid="72613">Don&apos;t be too long. My message concerns your master, and time is very important.</string>
  <string id="54901" soundid="72614">I have no doubt. I have questions for you as well. Hopefully, we will both be able to find the answers we need.</string>
  <string id="54902" soundid="72615"></string>
  <string id="54903" soundid="72616">That is quite enough. We will continue this at a later time. We both have questions that we will need answered.</string>
  <string id="54904" soundid="72617">Not here. I trust my personal assistants to keep their tongues, but this matter is best discussed in private.</string>
  <string id="54905" soundid="72618"></string>
  <string id="54906" soundid="72619">The whims of a member of the Imperial Court are not your concern. There are more important things that we need to discuss in private.</string>
  <string id="54907" soundid="72620">Your explanation lies in the simple bow you have given. Everyone around me kowtows low, obeying my whims. Honest opinion is rare.</string>
  <string id="54908" soundid="72621"></string>
  <string id="54909" soundid="72622">I think you are a little too bold for your own good, but I suppose it is my fault. I go out of my way to avoid fawning servants.</string>
  <string id="54910" soundid="72623">No guise, I assure you. You have the honor of addressing Princess Lian the Heavenly Lily.</string>
  <string id="54911" soundid="72624"></string>
  <string id="54912" soundid="72625">You claim great familiarity by calling me by my childhood nickname. All who know me here address me as Princess Lian the Heavenly Lily.</string>
  <string id="54913" soundid="72626">You&apos;ve already taken the arena by storm. I should have known you were destined to make a name for yourself in the Imperial City.</string>
  <string id="54914" soundid="72627">With your entrance into the arena fights, I have no doubt that you will be quite a sensation here in the Imperial City.</string>
  <string id="54915" soundid="72628">I didn&apos;t expect you and your strange training to make it to the Imperial City. You are proving to be a very interesting person.</string>
  <string id="54916" soundid="72629">Of course, I could tell that just by looking at you. You have a... very strong presence.</string>
  <string id="54917" soundid="72630">As the Heavenly Lily I am above suspicion, but I am restrained by fawning servants. Silk Fox can go anywhere, and people are not shy about their reactions.</string>
  <string id="54918" soundid="72631">There is a thrill, of course. And it allows me to find information useful to us both. Death&apos;s Hand brought your Master Li to the palace a few days ago. I saw the flyer.</string>
  <string id="54920" soundid="165870">I can&apos;t believe you are going to kill the Forest Shadow. Do you have *any* idea how much work that will cause? There&apos;s not enough paper in the universe to cover that incident!</string>
  <string id="54923" soundid="72636">He was bound in chains. He must be powerful, but I still don&apos;t believe he is Sun Li the Glorious Strategist.</string>
  <string id="54924" soundid="72637">Sun Li died twenty years ago. Everyone was told that he and Prince Kin, the third brother, fell defending the Empire. Now it seems they may have been traitors.</string>
  <string id="54926" soundid="72639">I discovered this looking through records for information on Death&apos;s Hand. Perhaps he tried to influence Sun Li and Sun Kin before corrupting my father.</string>
  <string id="54928" soundid="72641">I could take you to the palace right now, but it would do no good. Death&apos;s Hand controls what my father hears. He must be discredited for you to succeed.</string>
  <string id="54929" soundid="72642">But... your words will fall on deaf ears unless Death&apos;s Hand is first discredited. Until then, entering the palace would just endanger you with no hope of success.</string>
  <string id="54931" soundid="72644">Death&apos;s Hand has almost total control over my father. We must find conclusive evidence of his crimes and reveal his corruption. And I know how.</string>
  <string id="54932" soundid="72645">Construction on the Wall has stopped for the first time in generations. The workers now toil in factories, building powerful creatures of stone and clay called golems.</string>
  <string id="54933" soundid="72646">Death&apos;s Hand could use these automatons to seize the Empire, and my father is oblivious. We must infiltrate the Lotus Assassins and find evidence of this treachery.</string>
  <string id="54935" soundid="72648">My father may have approved the factory without considering what it could be used for. If we just tell him my suspicions, he will dismiss them.</string>
  <string id="54936" soundid="72649">We need proof of Death&apos;s Hand&apos;s intent from the seat of his power, the Lotus Assassin fortress. It would be impossible to assault, so just walk in. They are recruiting.</string>
  <string id="54938" soundid="72651">Have any Lotus Assassins who saw your face lived to report back? I doubt it. They will not recognize you as the person who fought them in Tien&apos;s Landing.</string>
  <string id="54939" soundid="72652">They have a vague description full of guesswork that has guards holding people at random. Besides, they expect an attack, not someone trying to catch their eye.</string>
  <string id="54940" soundid="72653">I would wager that you may profit from their tasks, too. Can you see the beauty in using their own methods of recruitment to fight them? I think they deserve it.</string>
  <string id="54941" soundid="72654">There are guilds within the Lotus Assassins. Executioners look for fearsome warriors. Inquisitors are more subversive, and they look for cunning in their agents.</string>
  <string id="54943" soundid="72656">You have already proven yourself in the arena. My people will spread rumors of your interest. Return to the arena, and you will be approached by the Executioner.</string>
  <string id="54944" soundid="72657">If you prove yourself in the arena, they will notice you. My people can spread rumors of your interest. The Executioner will take a real interest when you finish the Silver Round.</string>
  <string id="54945" soundid="72658">Or, if you prefer, the Inquisitor recruiter is also seeking new people. He might be open to persuasion.</string>
  <string id="54946" soundid="72659">Death&apos;s Hand rules over the Lotus Assassins, so I take special interest in their activities. I&apos;ve had most of my life to ask questions.</string>
  <string id="54947" soundid="72660">You suspect my motives? You have no reason to doubt me. If I wanted the Lotus Assassins to find you, I could simply tell them your name.</string>
  <string id="54948" soundid="72661">Yes, my people will spread rumors of your interest and the Executioner will seek you out. I&apos;m sure he will find you as impressive as I do.</string>
  <string id="54949" soundid="72662">Or, if you prefer, court the Inquisitor. Ask Scholar Dongow in the Scholars&apos; Garden about him. I hear Dongow is closer to the assassins than he should be.</string>
  <string id="54950" soundid="72663">Ask Scholar Dongow in the Scholars&apos; Garden about him. Dongow is closer to the assassins than he should be. He will tell you where to meet the Inquisitor. </string>
  <string id="54951" soundid="72664">Or seek the Executioner. My people will spread rumors of your interest, and he will approach you in the arena. They like fighters who have passed the Silver Round.</string>
  <string id="54952" soundid="72665">Unless you want me with you, I will wait at your flying machine. You travel with such interesting peasants. I&apos;m sure I&apos;ll be entertained for hours.</string>
  <string id="54953" soundid="72666">As I said, I&apos;ve had many years to examine how they work. You have no reason not to trust me.</string>
  <string id="54954" soundid="145853">Here&apos;s your bounty, as we negotiated earlier.</string>
  <string id="54956" soundid="145854">Here&apos;s the standard bounty. Accept it with the thanks of the Empire.</string>
  <string id="54957" soundid="145855">Well, that brings an end to our pursuit of two fiends. A shame I don&apos;t have more work for someone with your skills.</string>
  <string id="54958" soundid="72671">Take advantage of the fact that they don&apos;t know you as a threat! They won&apos;t know anything is wrong until you storm their lair!</string>
  <string id="54959" soundid="72672">You have already done half the work. Your performance in the arena is more than enough to catch their eyes... if you know who to talk to.</string>
  <string id="54961" soundid="72674">The Wall was started by the first emperor, Sagacious Tien, as protection against the Horselords. The Empire has long since grown past its boundaries.</string>
  <string id="54962" soundid="72675">It is now more a spiritual monument instead of a physical barrier. Every emperor has added to it. It is a legacy that has lasted millennia.</string>
  <string id="54964" soundid="72677">Prisoners of the Empire. Hard labor reforms them, and contributing to a legacy gives them purpose. Many respected citizens once worked on the Wall.</string>
  <string id="54966" soundid="72679">A wise decision. His hold over my father is nearly absolute, but if we could show conclusive evidence of his crimes, my father would have to listen. I know how.</string>
  <string id="54967" soundid="72680">The palace is protected by the Wall, which is guarded by whole garrisons. Not even birds pass over. Dragon powder turrets are manned night and day.</string>
  <string id="54969" soundid="72682">I&apos;m sorry, but the palace is fortified beyond reason, and only the official seal of the court allows passage within. You need me, and I need you.</string>
  <string id="54971" soundid="72684">I was too young to know him. I was told that he and Prince Kin, the third brother, fell defending the Empire twenty years ago. Now it seems they may have been traitors.</string>
  <string id="54972" soundid="72685">He was bound in chains. He must be powerful... or you are. There was something familiar about him, as well.</string>
  <string id="54973" soundid="72686">Why would you say that? Is that what he told you? I&apos;m sorry, but I simply cannot believe that your Master Li is the Glorious Strategist.</string>
  <string id="54974" soundid="72687">I told you back in Tien&apos;s Landing that the Emperor, my father, is not an evil man. Death&apos;s Hand has corrupted our court, and you will help me prove it.</string>
  <string id="54975" soundid="72688">I am worth trusting. With my influence, you can enter the palace and confront my father directly about Master Li, this destiny of yours, or whatever you want.</string>
  <string id="54979" soundid="72692">No one has compassion for the troubles of a princess. I am restrained by fawning servants, but as Silk Fox I can go anywhere, and no one hides their true intentions.</string>
  <string id="54980" soundid="72693">I should have seen it coming. I suspect that we share a similar strength.</string>
  <string id="54981" soundid="72694">Why haven&apos;t I seen any activity among the Lotus Assassins yet? You should talk to the contacts I gave you.</string>
  <string id="54982" soundid="72695">Remember our arrangement? You secure the evidence of the army Death&apos;s Hand is building, and I&apos;ll get you to the palace to confront my father.</string>
  <string id="54983" soundid="72696">I&apos;m sure you are, but if you did it quicker, we would all benefit. Death&apos;s Hand grows stronger, and my father grows weaker.</string>
  <string id="54984" soundid="72697">I can&apos;t agree with this. You don&apos;t know what you are getting into. You don&apos;t know the danger they represent.</string>
  <string id="54987" soundid="72700">Really? What did you see while hiding in your swamp? I&apos;ve observed Death&apos;s Hand for years, both in the palace and elsewhere.</string>
  <string id="54988" soundid="72701">You could have four faces and a different name and wardrobe for each, and you still wouldn&apos;t understand. Death&apos;s Hand is not what he seems.</string>
  <string id="54989" soundid="72702">Then what, pray tell, is he?</string>
  <string id="54990" soundid="72703">I... don&apos;t know, but his power does not come from study or skill. He is something darker, and we should not be trying to enter his lair.</string>
  <string id="54991" soundid="72704">It sounds like Sagacious Zu wants to go back into hiding. Or perhaps the nursery. Pay no attention. Not everyone is as weak as he is.</string>
  <string id="54992" soundid="72705">You don&apos;t know what they are capable of.</string>
  <string id="54993" soundid="72706">The matter is settled. Go sulk in the corner like you&apos;re accustomed to doing.</string>
  <string id="54994" soundid="72707">This is not helping anything. Are we any closer to getting to the Lotus Assassins so this accursed woman will help us find Master Li?</string>
  <string id="54995" soundid="72708">Oh, she spits fire at last. Now I see how the child left her little village; she has some spirit in her after all.</string>
  <string id="54996" soundid="72709">And she&apos;s also right. We are no closer to finding the secret plans that Death&apos;s Hand has been making. You have to move quicker.</string>
  <string id="54997" soundid="72710">Go to the Imperial Arena to meet the Executioner, or speak with Scholar Dongow in the Scholars&apos; Garden about the Inquisitor.</string>
  <string id="54998" soundid="72711">And, surprisingly, she&apos;s right. You&apos;ve made contact with the Lotus Assassins, but haven&apos;t shown them why they need to fully accept you.</string>
  <string id="54999" soundid="72712">The Inquisitor has a task for you to prove your worth. Get to it, and show him why you should be recruited.</string>
  <string id="55000" soundid="72713">You could also seek out the Executioner in the arena. He would be interested in your skill as a combatant.</string>
  <string id="55001" soundid="72714">The Executioner wants to see you excel in the arena. Progress far enough, and he will gladly recommend that you be recruited.</string>
  <string id="55002" soundid="72715">And the Inquisitor has a task for you, as well. Appeasing one or the other will be enough for our purposes. The path is yours to choose.</string>
  <string id="55003" soundid="72716">We&apos;ve gone over this. Death&apos;s Hand is using the prisoners who should be working on the Wall to construct some sort of personal army of golems.</string>
  <string id="55004" soundid="72717">My father probably knows something, but not the true danger of it. I need to show that Death&apos;s Hand intends to seize control.</string>
  <string id="55005" soundid="72718">The Lotus Assassins act for Death&apos;s Hand. There has to be proof of his evil intent in the Lotus Assassin fortress. That is where you need to go.</string>
  <string id="55010" soundid="72723">I will answer what I can, but you have other things to do, as well.</string>
  <string id="55011" soundid="72724">Your progress is admirable, but don&apos;t become too close to the Lotus Assassins. Their power is seductive. That is how Death&apos;s Hand gained influence over my father.</string>
  <string id="55012" soundid="72725">I don&apos;t understand. You have gained the favor of the Lotus Assassins with a fair amount of ease. What else is there to speak of?</string>
  <string id="55017" soundid="72730">My father? What do you want to know that isn&apos;t already public knowledge? Emperor Sun Hai is well known and well loved.</string>
  <string id="55018" soundid="72731">Death&apos;s Hand is wearing away at that reputation, however, and I need to stop him before it goes to far. </string>
  <string id="55019" soundid="72732">He has been present for as long as I can remember, but he only rose to prominence after the end of the Long Drought.</string>
  <string id="55020" soundid="72733">My father was very caring when I was a child. Now he is cold and distant. I know Death&apos;s Hand is corrupting him somehow.</string>
  <string id="55022" soundid="72735">I wish you luck. Once you have gained the trust of the Lotus Assassins, we will plan how to proceed.</string>
  <string id="55024" soundid="72737">If you prefer, you could still seek out the Inquisitor by speaking with Scholar Dongow in the Scholars&apos; Garden.</string>
  <string id="55025" soundid="72738">But she doesn&apos;t need to worry. You&apos;ve already gained the recommendation of the Lotus Assassin Inquisitor.</string>
  <string id="55026" soundid="72739">You could also go to the arena and seek the favor of the Executioner, but it isn&apos;t necessary now. A path to the Lotus Assassin fortress is open.</string>
  <string id="55027" soundid="72740">But I&apos;m sure you can appease her. You&apos;ve already gained the recommendation of the Lotus Assassin Executioner.</string>
  <string id="55037" soundid="72750">It would still be good to get some information first. Sagacious Zu might know something. We should ask him.</string>
  <string id="55038" soundid="72751">Where... where is he?</string>
  <string id="55039" soundid="72752"></string>
  <string id="55040" soundid="72753">Well, you should be more careful of who you trust.</string>
  <string id="55041" soundid="72754">That is true. I wouldn&apos;t trust any of the ragged homeless you have collected.</string>
  <string id="55042" soundid="72755">No offense meant to those of you who are actually homeless, Dawn Star.</string>
  <string id="55043" soundid="72756">If Sagacious Zu has gone to warn the Lotus Assassins, you need to move quick. If he&apos;s just run off, he is no longer our concern.</string>
  <string id="55044" soundid="72757">Zu would not turn on us.</string>
  <string id="55046" soundid="72759">The Lotus Assassin fortress is in the far end of the Necropolis. They shouldn&apos;t give you any trouble. Just appear confident as you enter.</string>
  <string id="55050" soundid="72763">Everything is in place. I&apos;ll have my evidence against Death&apos;s Hand soon enough. Oh, and you&apos;ll have access to your Master Li as well.</string>
  <string id="55051" soundid="72764">How generous of you.</string>
  <string id="55054" soundid="72767">No, don&apos;t waste your time. If he&apos;s gone to warn the Lotus Assassins, you need to move quickly. If he&apos;s just run off, he doesn&apos;t matter.</string>
  <string id="55055" soundid="72768">If that&apos;s the case, he doesn&apos;t matter, but if he&apos;s gone to warn the Lotus Assassins, you need to move quickly.</string>
  <string id="55056" soundid="72769">You don&apos;t want too much fuss. You&apos;ll only bring the place down on yourself.</string>
  <string id="55057" soundid="72770">Sagacious Zu has knowledge of the inside. At least he seems to.</string>
  <string id="55058" soundid="72771">Oh, you&apos;re fun when you&apos;re forceful. Still, you should at least get some information about the place.</string>
  <string id="55066" soundid="72779">Thank you for listening, but I want more than caution. Neither of you understand what they are capable of.</string>
  <string id="55067" soundid="72780">You aren&apos;t doing much to add to our understanding. Go sulk in the corner, like you&apos;re accustomed to doing.</string>
  <string id="55068" soundid="72781">Scholar Dongow in the Scholars&apos; Garden will alert him to your interest. Return to your base at the flyer after you have spoken with him.</string>
  <string id="55070" soundid="72783">Keep your voice down! My name is Silk Fox. I&apos;ll have a hard time helping you if my travels outside the palace become known.</string>
  <string id="55071" soundid="72784">And your flippant attitude has to change. Death&apos;s Hand grows stronger with each moment you hesitate. </string>
  <string id="55072" soundid="72785">Hello again. I enjoy our little chats, but I don&apos;t think anything has changed since we last spoke. I still need evidence against Death&apos;s Hand to free my father.</string>
  <string id="55073" soundid="72786">Meet the Executioner in the arena, or speak with Scholar Dongow in the Scholars&apos; Garden about the Inquisitor. Hurry or you&apos;ll lose your chance to help your master.</string>
  <string id="55074" soundid="72787">Well, it looks like your contact with the Lotus Assassins will be bad for your reputation but good for our goal.</string>
  <string id="55075" soundid="72788">You spoke with both of their agents, I believe. I like that you explore all the options before making up your mind.</string>
  <string id="55076" soundid="72789">Yes? I appreciate the attention, but you have things to do. You&apos;ve made arrangements to gain the trust of the Lotus Assassins but haven&apos;t followed through.</string>
  <string id="55077" soundid="72790">So, things are looking up. You&apos;ve gained the favor of the Lotus Assassins.</string>
  <string id="55078" soundid="72791">And you&apos;ve made doubly certain of it by aiding both the Executioner and Inquisitor. Very impressive. The way to the Lotus Assassin fortress is open.</string>
  <string id="55079" soundid="72792">With the recommendation of the Inquisitor, the others will welcome you as a recruit. You can slip into the very heart of their lair.</string>
  <string id="55080" soundid="72793">With the recommendation of the Executioner, the others will welcome you as a recruit. You can slip into the very heart of their lair.</string>
  <string id="55081" soundid="72794">You must go to the Lotus Assassin fortress like we agreed. Find the evidence against Death&apos;s Hand and I will help you rescue Master Li.</string>
  <string id="55122">Forgive me, but I am not sure how to address you.</string>
  <string id="55124">Of course. Forgive me, Princess.</string>
  <string id="55127">Of course, Princess Lian. Should we talk elsewhere?</string>
  <string id="55129">Of course, Princess. At your convenience.</string>
  <string id="55131">My apologies, Princess.</string>
  <string id="55132">Don&apos;t blame them for the pampering you demand.</string>
  <string id="55134">I have many questions for you.</string>
  <string id="55136">A rendezvous with the princess! Such a scandal!</string>
  <string id="55138">What information do you have for me?</string>
  <string id="55140">Bah! You just like getting your hands dirty with commoners.</string>
  <string id="55143">A common greeting, but I require an explanation. </string>
  <string id="55145">I don&apos;t bow, and I don&apos;t know you as a princess.</string>
  <string id="55148">An interesting guise. By what name should I refer to you?</string>
  <string id="55150">Silk Fox! I could have used your help getting here!</string>
  <string id="55154">You&apos;ve changed again, Princess. Who are you now?</string>
  <string id="55161">It doesn&apos;t matter what you believe. I know it, and that&apos;s enough.</string>
  <string id="55168">I must get to the palace. What do I need to do?</string>
  <string id="55172">I&apos;ve been fighting the Lotus Assassins. How can I infiltrate them?</string>
  <string id="55173">A golem factory like you describe can&apos;t be small. What if we just identified it?</string>
  <string id="55176">I&apos;ve fought a number of them. I would be spotted.</string>
  <string id="55179">How can this be done?</string>
  <string id="55184">You know a lot about the Lotus Assassins. Why?</string>
  <string id="55186">I will go see what I can learn in the Imperial Arena.</string>
  <string id="55187">I&apos;ll ask around in the arena. I&apos;ve already proven myself there.</string>
  <string id="55190">Perhaps I will see if this Inquisitor is reasonable.</string>
  <string id="55193" soundid="145856">As I said, she confined them to the poor districts. She would have been impossible to catch in that rat&apos;s nest. More frankly, there isn&apos;t enough money to make it worth my effort.</string>
  <string id="55196">I&apos;m not interested in joining my enemy!</string>
  <string id="55197">Get on with your plan. Let&apos;s see just how ridiculous it is.</string>
  <string id="55198">Why would my arena victories help?</string>
  <string id="55199">That&apos;s ridiculous! You want me to just ask to join?</string>
  <string id="55201">Tell me about the Wall.</string>
  <string id="55204">Who does the work?</string>
  <string id="55206">Destroying Death&apos;s Hand is also a priority for me.</string>
  <string id="55208">If you won&apos;t help me now, I&apos;ll find my own way to the palace. </string>
  <string id="55211">Tell me what must be done.</string>
  <string id="55214">You didn&apos;t recognize him as family?</string>
  <string id="55216">They rightfully fear him. He is Sun Li the Glorious Strategist.</string>
  <string id="55217">He is familiar because you are related. He is Sun Li.</string>
</tlk>