<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<tlk language="0">
  <string id="107284">Lotus Assassin Camp</string>
  <string id="107285">Ruin Gate</string>
  <string id="107290" soundid="163929">He... he pushed a young boy into the river outside of town. It was fast moving and would have swept the child away, but he managed to grab hold of a rock.</string>
  <string id="107291" soundid="163930">Why indeed? In the intervening years, I&apos;ve come to believe that it was more than simple horseplay. There was a gleam in my young man&apos;s eye that I cannot forget.</string>
  <string id="107292" soundid="163931">How can you be so cold?</string>
  <string id="107293" soundid="163932">The weak often make themselves targets.</string>
  <string id="107294" soundid="163933">Whether that moment was mine or not no longer matters. I&apos;ve done far worse since, always hoping to forget what happened. As if the cries of others would drown out that child&apos;s.</string>
  <string id="107295" soundid="163934">I have followed his life since that day, as I descended into my world and he climbed the ranks in the Imperial Army.</string>
  <string id="107296" soundid="163935">That is why I have come here now. I am tired of my life, but at least I have lived it! He deserved to live as I did, but has never felt a moments remorse for his part in that day.</string>
  <string id="107297" soundid="163936">It was a gift to even begin my story.</string>
  <string id="107298">Why don&apos;t you tell me in your own words?</string>
  <string id="107299">Very little. It seems your fame&apos;s not so widespread as your ego might wish.</string>
  <string id="107303">What happened?</string>
  <string id="107306">Go on. What happened?</string>
  <string id="107307">You were in love with the town bully?</string>
  <string id="107310">If the child were stronger he wouldn&apos;t have been a victim.</string>
  <string id="107315">Who was this boy that stopped you?</string>
  <string id="107318">Now I know you&apos;re a monster. I&apos;m going to collect your bounty.</string>
  <string id="107319">I don&apos;t have time for childish love stories. Time to collect your bounty.</string>
  <string id="107320">I&apos;ve run out of patience. Tell your story to the ghosts when you join them.</string>
  <string id="107323" soundid="163981">I&apos;d love to speak with you, but Prefect Jitong gets very edgy when people question his &quot;suspects.&quot;</string>
  <string id="107324" soundid="163982">He&apos;s looking for some dedicated citizen to help him in his investigations. If you could clear this mess up, I&apos;d certainly be grateful.</string>
  <string id="107326" soundid="163984">Soon the will of the Emperor will be plain, and Death&apos;s Hand will step aside so he can enforce his glorious vision openly. Opposition will be impossible.</string>
  <string id="107327" soundid="163985">There are those that think the Emperor must serve the will of the people, but they are traitors in disguise. His glory is our glory. Death&apos;s Hand will make it so.</string>
  <string id="107329">Why does he need golems? Who would dare oppose the Emperor?</string>
  <string id="107330">Increase Speed</string>
  <string id="107339" soundid="164003">Is... is such an act necessary? I can attest how far and fast the deathly frightened can run.</string>
  <string id="107340" soundid="164004">I... see where you might need to do this, we don&apos;t want to be discovered, but it is still a distasteful act.</string>
  <string id="107341" soundid="164005">Hardly a challenge, but if it must be done, it must be done.</string>
  <string id="107343" soundid="164007">Ya Zhen: Yes, no loose ends left behind!</string>
  <string id="107344" soundid="164008">Master? Please... we just want to leave this place.</string>
  <string id="107345" soundid="164009">No! We must fight! We&apos;ve traded one villain for another!</string>
  <string id="107346">I cannot allow you to live. You might be seen escaping.</string>
  <string id="107352">Test the Outlander&apos;s Martial Skill</string>
  <string id="107354">This is too important. They must die.</string>
  <string id="107355">To the Docks</string>
  <string id="107356">Launch Room</string>
  <string id="107357">Treasure Room</string>
  <string id="107358">Control Tower</string>
  <string id="107359">To Tien&apos;s Landing</string>
  <string id="107360">Lord Yun&apos;s Camp</string>
  <string id="107361">Bridge</string>
  <string id="107363">To the Pilgrim&apos;s Rest Inn</string>
  <string id="107364">To the Forest</string>
  <string id="107365">The Pilgrim&apos;s Rest</string>
  <string id="107366">To the Caves</string>
  <string id="107367">To the Pilgrim&apos;s Rest</string>
  <string id="107368">Butcher&apos;s Room</string>
  <string id="107369">Handler&apos;s Room</string>
  <string id="107370">Bridge</string>
  <string id="107371">Mother&apos;s Room</string>
  <string id="107372" soundid="164036">I have an eye for raw talent. That helps when picking slaves, but it comes in handy in sizing up potential allies.</string>
  <string id="107373" soundid="164037">There was this woman, Cao Zeng. She was asking questions about the... you know.</string>
  <string id="107374" soundid="164038">There was a fellow nosing around upstairs, Cao Zeng. He was asking questions about... you know.</string>
  <string id="107375" soundid="164039">Is that so?</string>
  <string id="107376" soundid="164040">And so you decided to lead this investigator straight to us, did you?</string>
  <string id="107377" soundid="164041">What? No! I didn&apos;t mean to bring her down here! She must have followed me!</string>
  <string id="107378" soundid="164042">He followed me! I swear, I didn&apos;t mean to bring him here!</string>
  <string id="107379" soundid="164043">Now there&apos;s an unknown quantity in this little meeting. Just who are you?</string>
  <string id="107380" soundid="164044">Songtao? Isn&apos;t that the fool who&apos;s taking the fall for Chandler Ling? Well, you&apos;ve overheard your evidence. Too bad you won&apos;t get to tell anyone.</string>
  <string id="107381" soundid="164045">Zi Bao was a fool to bring anyone here. We can&apos;t afford anyone nosing into our affairs right now, and you&apos;ve heard too much.</string>
  <string id="107382" soundid="164046">Perhaps I can find a price that&apos;s right for you to also turn a blind eye to our little situation here. Our little enterprise gives us deep pockets.</string>
  <string id="107383" soundid="164047">That&apos;s where the real money is. Of course some are sold to private individuals with the means to purchase such... luxuries.</string>
  <string id="107384">Are you done talking? I have a slaver to kill.</string>
  <string id="107391" soundid="164297">When you&apos;re ready to see him, Master Li just went into his house. It&apos;s just over there, as always.</string>
  <string id="107394">Are you proposing an alliance of sorts?</string>
  <string id="107395">I might be interested if the offer&apos;s right.</string>
  <string id="107400">Special</string>
  <string id="107401">Chai Jin</string>
  <string id="107404" soundid="164069">They deserved a chance to celebrate, in my opinion, so I left them with a few silvers with which to enjoy themselves.</string>
  <string id="107405" soundid="164070">They took down a bandit who dared try to circle around me. That&apos;s the kind of support I need, men who watch my back but don&apos;t get in my way.</string>
  <string id="107406" soundid="164071">Besides, what&apos;s a few bandits to one of my skill? Hardly worth the time.</string>
  <string id="107407">Why didn&apos;t you have your men help? I found them drunk after the attack.</string>
  <string id="107413" soundid="164078">Oh, and I am certainly not going to tell you that the ruins can be reached by heading across the footbridge and out the west gate of town. It wouldn&apos;t be proper.</string>
  <string id="107414" soundid="164079">Perhaps I could direct you to the historic ruins of our old town, which lie across the footbridge and out the west gate. Certainly a sight worth taking in.</string>
  <string id="107415" soundid="164080">Strictly for interests&apos; sake, of course.</string>
  <string id="107416" soundid="164081">Of course, being a stranger, he&apos;d not be able to tell you that you&apos;d need to go through the ruins, which lie through the west gate. Tourists rarely know the lie of the land, you see.</string>
  <string id="107417" soundid="164082">Or that the dam lies to through the ruins, which are, in turn outside the west gate out of town. You have heard none of this from me.</string>
  <string id="107423" soundid="164093">There&apos;s one there! These beasts are everywhere. The Guardian and I will go play with them for a while. You three go stop their Mother.</string>
  <string id="107424" soundid="164094">As if this place wasn&apos;t bad enough, now we have the lunatic and the baker here for.... Wait....</string>
  <string id="107425" soundid="164095">I wondered if they would find a way to cut us off. They must move through those small tunnels. I&apos;ll go deal with them, you three eliminate the Mother.</string>
  <string id="107434">I don&apos;t have time for this! Dawn Star is missing!</string>
  <string id="107435" soundid="167876">What was life like before?</string>
  <string id="107436" soundid="164107">Master Li just went into his house. It is just over there, as always.</string>
  <string id="107437" soundid="164108"></string>
  <string id="107438" soundid="164109">A shame. I always enjoy a quick bout. I can understand you having other things on your mind, though.</string>
  <string id="107439" soundid="164110">Master Li looked a bit disappointed. Most likely he was hoping to watch us spar.</string>
  <string id="107440" soundid="164111"></string>
  <string id="107441" soundid="164112">Did you see? Master Li was watching. He may not show it, but he clearly takes pride in watching his students practice.</string>
  <string id="107442" soundid="164113">Anyway, thank you for the opportunity to face you! Always interesting to tackle the most senior student.</string>
  <string id="107450">You don&apos;t deserve peace if all you can do is hurt people.</string>
  <string id="107459">New Style Learned</string>
  <string id="107472">Black Leopard Style</string>
  <string id="107494" soundid="195357"></string>
  <string id="107497" soundid="164265">Who are you, and why are you here? You&apos;re clearly too skilled to be one of the fools hired by Prefect Jitong, so what business--or grudge--do you have with us?</string>
  <string id="107498" soundid="164266">This kind of thing can&apos;t be allowed to continue.</string>
  <string id="107499" soundid="164267">You&apos;re one of them, are you? Another fool like that Scholar Songtao, always thinking the poor are worth &quot;saving?&quot;</string>
  <string id="107500" soundid="164268">You are with Jitong? Unless he was dipped in silver recently, there&apos;s no way he could afford a warrior of your skill. Not on government pay.</string>
  <string id="107501" soundid="164269">You&apos;re better than that. You&apos;ve just shown me your strength. Any poor wretch who had the discipline to fight like you wouldn&apos;t let themselves be enslaved.</string>
  <string id="107502" soundid="164270">Someone like you deserves to work *with* me, not oppose me. I have a friend who could use your help, and I&apos;m prepared to pay for it.</string>
  <string id="107503" soundid="164271">You&apos;ve met my friend, have you? Ling&apos;s a good man, and a valuable resource, so I&apos;m not willing to let him go to jail.</string>
  <string id="107504" soundid="164272">Some generous donations to a high minister almost solved my problem, until the good Prefect decided to get in our way.</string>
  <string id="107505" soundid="164273">You can&apos;t be serious.</string>
  <string id="107506" soundid="164274">These men are as bad as the ones that destroyed our home. I hope you aren&apos;t serious about this.</string>
  <string id="107507" soundid="164275">While the silver might be lucrative, I don&apos;t think we have time for this kind of involvement.</string>
  <string id="107508" soundid="164276">Ya Zhen: Is there any commodity better than human life? Buy low, sell low, I always say.</string>
  <string id="107509" soundid="164277">An intriguing offer, but I can tell at a glance you aren&apos;t the kind of person who&apos;d be content to hang around here for too long. However....</string>
  <string id="107510" soundid="164278">You made a mistake, Bao, but I&apos;ll give you one chance to make up for it. Eliminate this pest.</string>
  <string id="107512">I&apos;m here to put an end to your slaving.</string>
  <string id="107515">Jitong asked me to help him free Songtao. That led me to you.</string>
  <string id="107518">A merchant named Chandler Ling wants me to secure his freedom.</string>
  <string id="107521">I want in on your little business.</string>
  <string id="107530" soundid="164301">My poor Bei.</string>
  <string id="107532">Ghost</string>
  <string id="107536" soundid="164307">I don&apos;t have time for visitors. You should leave before I reconsider First Brother&apos;s instructions.</string>
  <string id="107537">[Lie] I will go and deal with Smiling Hawk now.</string>
  <string id="107541" soundid="164314">I only hope that I can find some release in that freedom. I had hoped that I would have somewhere to go, but I feel no pull to the underworld.</string>
  <string id="107542" soundid="164315">Hopefully I can find my own way... somehow. Thank you for this release, great one. It is enough for now that I can fade for a time.</string>
  <string id="107545">Health Shield</string>
  <string id="107546">[TEMP] item_gem_shield_focus_II</string>
  <string id="107547">Chi Shield</string>
  <string id="107548">Shield</string>
  <string id="107549">Major Health Shield</string>
  <string id="107550">[TEMP] item_gem_shield_focus_III</string>
  <string id="107551">Major Chi Shield</string>
  <string id="107552">Major Shield</string>
  <string id="107553">Spiritform Gem</string>
  <string id="107554">Flawless Spiritform Gem</string>
  <string id="107555">Gem of Shadows</string>
  <string id="107556">Flawless Gem of Shadows</string>
  <string id="107557">Gem of Crushing</string>
  <string id="107558">Flawless Gem of Crushing</string>
  <string id="107559" soundid="188904"></string>
  <string id="107563" soundid="188905"></string>
  <string id="107567">This gem buffers your Health score, absorbing the next 25 points of damage. Once it is slotted, you cannot remove it, and it disintegrates once you use it.</string>
  <string id="107568">[TEMP] DESCRIPTION item_gem_shield_focus_II</string>
  <string id="107569">This gem buffers your Chi score, absorbing the next 25 points of Chi damage. Once it is slotted, you cannot remove it, and it disintegrates once you use it.</string>
  <string id="107570">This gem buffers all of your secondary abilities, absorbing the next 25 points of damage to any secondary ability score. Once it is slotted, you cannot remove it, and it disintegrates once you use it.</string>
  <string id="107571">This gem buffers your Health score, absorbing the next 50 points of damage. Once it is slotted, you cannot remove it, and it disintegrates once you use it.</string>
  <string id="107572">[TEMP] DESCRIPTION item_gem_shield_focus_III</string>
  <string id="107573">This gem buffers your Chi score, absorbing the next 50 points of Chi damage. Once it is slotted, you cannot remove it, and it disintegrates once you use it.</string>
  <string id="107574">This gem buffers all of your secondary abilities, absorbing the next 50 points of damage to any secondary ability score. Once it is slotted, you cannot remove it, and it disintegrates once it is used.</string>
  <string id="107575">This gem turns you into a spirit for 30 seconds. You gain all the resistances of a spirit for that time.</string>
  <string id="107576">This gem turns you into a spirit for 60 seconds. You gain all the resistances of a spirit for that time.</string>
  <string id="107577">This gem makes opponents ignore you during combat for 30 seconds.</string>
  <string id="107578">This gem makes opponents ignore you during combat for 60 seconds.</string>
  <string id="107579">This gem renders your attacks unblockable for 15 seconds.</string>
  <string id="107580">This gem renders your attacks unblockable for 30 seconds.</string>
  <string id="107582">Weak Wall</string>
  <string id="107585">Something about this strange poem made it stick in your mind.    

&quot;Configurations guided by the tiger burn bright, as the cauldron bubbles in the night.  
The cogs whirl their graceful dances, but they grow tired unless they drink of the water infused with sulphur.&quot;</string>
  <string id="107586">You found this academic leaflet and kept it. The crux of the argument reads, &quot;To think that any machine could be designed around the principles of starting motion with a tiger, of all things, is to dally with utter madness. As if this were not enough, no machine made by the hands of man can be fueled by iron infused with nickel. The resulting metal, while strong, is inert to reactions. Even application of electrical current and the introduction of chimney smoke into a mechanical cauldron, as proposed, produced no appreciable result.&quot;</string>
  <string id="107587">You found this strange excerpt from a diary; the pages were torn from the book but kept together as if they were an important secret.    

&quot;...in his ravings, my husband talked of madmen with eyes of metal and of a strange island in the skies. His words frightened me, but none more than when he clutched my arm, suddenly lucid. &apos;It&apos;s the tiger,&apos; he said, fever burning in his eyes. &apos;The tiger feeds on the stone of the cow, torn from the bovine&apos;s innards. All but the cogs are watching... waiting and active... waiting for the tiger to feed.&apos; After his recovery, my husband remembered nothing of his journeys or of his ravings, except one....&quot;</string>
  <string id="107588">A note, probably written to the author as a reminder. &quot;It will likely break the machine, but with a pair of flawless rubies, and care to leave the clappers and cauldron out of the process, the tiger might be able to manage a reconfiguration of the user instead of itself. It might be worth investigating after my preliminary studies into flight dynamics are finished. Maybe... insects!&quot;</string>
  <string id="107590">You have entered Focus mode. Focus mode slows down time. Your Focus drains constantly in this mode.</string>
  <string id="107594">DragonPowder</string>
  <string id="107595">DragonPowder</string>
  <string id="107600" soundid="169177">[The ignition pan now has powder. Pull the lever to launch the rockets.]</string>
  <string id="107601" soundid="169178"></string>
  <string id="107603" soundid="169180">[A monkey shouts at you angrily.]</string>
  <string id="107604" soundid="169181">[A few monkeys shout at you.]</string>
  <string id="107605" soundid="169182">[Several monkeys scream at you.]</string>
  <string id="107617" soundid="169194">You&apos;ve been saying that for three days, Ru. Minister Sheng&apos;s already looking for other people to close the dam, and you&apos;ll look a fool after all your boasts.</string>
  <string id="107632">No style selected</string>
  <string id="107633">Fight!</string>
  <string id="107634">This is it!</string>
  <string id="107635">Now we see!</string>
  <string id="107636" soundid="164409">Does it matter? Death&apos;s Hand himself seeks this one. Do you need any more incentive than that?</string>
  <string id="107638" soundid="166955">One of Lord Yun&apos;s men said that young woman who has been around recently helped them out.</string>
  <string id="107639" soundid="166956">A pair of hunters for Lord Yun told me the young man who has been around town helped them out.</string>
  <string id="107640" soundid="166957">Well, that&apos;s good news on a bad day, that is!</string>
  <string id="107641">Portal</string>
  <string id="107644" soundid="166961">No more pirates?</string>
  <string id="107645" soundid="166962">Ru said that fellow with the tattoos shut them down, almost single-handedly!</string>
  <string id="107646" soundid="164419">Well, there was this one time I was paid to track down a ruthless band of cutthroats. They&apos;d been terrorizing half the Empire, and nobody was willing to go after them.</string>
  <string id="107647" soundid="164420">I tracked the bandits to a hideout in the mountains. I attacked them at nightfall; they were tough, each of them as skilled as most men I&apos;d fight one on one.</string>
  <string id="107648" soundid="164421">I killed a few quickly, but they had horses and started hemming me in. Soon I was surrounded. The toughest bandit charged at me with his horse!</string>
  <string id="107649" soundid="164422">No! I Punched the horse square in the jaw, and they both went down. I fought my way through the others and got my back against a wall. There were six dead now.</string>
  <string id="107650" soundid="164423">Eventually they pushed me back through the doors of their hideout. It got so crowded I couldn&apos;t even swing my axes. The floor was slick with blood. I went down swinging.</string>
  <string id="107651" soundid="164424">Ha! They didn&apos;t have me yet. I left my axes on the floor and started snapping their necks with my bare hands. Eventually I finished them all off. Damn dirty bandits!</string>
  <string id="107652" soundid="164425">What? Oh... no... I&apos;ve never lost a fight. Well, except to you, of course.</string>
  <string id="107653" soundid="166963">I heard from Ru that that young man in the blue vest stopped them.</string>
  <string id="107654" soundid="166964">You know that fellow in the robes? Ru said it was him!</string>
  <string id="107655" soundid="166965">Ru claims that big fellow in brown wiped them out!</string>
  <string id="107656" soundid="166966">According to the boatswain, it was that young woman in blue.</string>
  <string id="107657" soundid="166967">You know the young woman in red and blue? Ru claims it was her!</string>
  <string id="107658" soundid="166968">I overheard Ru saying that lady with the long hair and wrapped arms stopped them!</string>
  <string id="107660" soundid="166970">Things aren&apos;t going to get any better until the dam closes again. That&apos;s a fact.</string>
  <string id="107661" soundid="166971">If only Minister Sheng would do something. He won&apos;t, though.</string>
  <string id="107662" soundid="166972">There&apos;s the new young woman in town, though. Maybe she&apos;ll do something.</string>
  <string id="107663" soundid="166973">Maybe that young man who arrived recently will do something. He looks trained to fight.</string>
  <string id="107665">I&apos;ll show you!</string>
  <string id="107668">So that&apos;s how you lost your first fight.</string>
  <string id="107669">That must have been painful.</string>
  <string id="107670">You got beat by a bandit on a horse?</string>
  <string id="107672">How did you escape?</string>
  <string id="107673">So, they captured you and then let you go?</string>
  <string id="107674">I can&apos;t believe you lost a fight.</string>
  <string id="107675">I thought you were telling me about the time you lost!</string>
  <string id="107676" soundid="164450">You will excuse me if I seem a bit distracted. This is a most turbulent time in the Ministry of Harmony, which, you will recall, counted Minister Sheng among its members.</string>
  <string id="107677" soundid="164451">Minister Sheng has heard that Judge Fang, the head of the Ministry, is dead! I live in terror at the thought of who his replacement might be.</string>
  <string id="107678" soundid="164452">I have heard Judge Fang--head of our illustrious Ministry--has resigned, but now I live in terror at the thought of who his replacement might be.</string>
  <string id="107679" soundid="164453">But no more! Judge Fang, one-time head of the Ministry, is gone, and his replacement is none other than... me! Minister Sheng finally gets his just reward!</string>
  <string id="107684">Such a crime against order would not go unnoticed!</string>
  <string id="107685" soundid="164459">Ha! That&apos;s a good one, and probably true. All I know is that travelling with you seems a damn sight more interesting than rotting in this forest.</string>
  <string id="107686">I can&apos;t hurt you??</string>
  <string id="107687">I&apos;m reeling from your smell.</string>
  <string id="107688">You could be useful. Glad to have you along.</string>
  <string id="107690">How does Drunken Master work again?</string>
  <string id="107693" soundid="164475">Look at that tart swinging her hips for that mercenary.</string>
  <string id="107694" soundid="164476">I should arrest that accursed tourist! Look, you spoke to a nervous scholar, and now Yukong has suddenly disappeared. Suspicious....</string>
  <string id="107697">Spirit Font</string>
  <string id="107698" soundid="164480">The last shipment of slaves were delivered smoothly enough, but now we have that accursed Prefect Jitong poking into our affairs.</string>
  <string id="107699" soundid="164481">I&apos;ve already dealt with the last shipment of slaves, and with that damned Prefect poking into our affairs we have to be extra cautious.</string>
  <string id="107700" soundid="164482">In the slave market are you? Funny how I find that a bit suspicious, especially given that we&apos;ve had run-ins several of Prefect Jitong&apos;s &quot;investigators.&quot;</string>
  <string id="107705">Chapter 2</string>
  <string id="107706">
Wherein the fall of Dirge is detailed,
The woman in black speaks of Death&apos;s Hand,
And Gao the Greater learns the fate of his son.


Two Rivers is in ruins, and Master Li has been taken captive. It is clear that this attack was carefully orchestrated and that shadowy forces have taken an interest in you and those around you. Leaving your home of twenty years, you set out after Death&apos;s Hand and his Lotus Assassins, intent on discovering the reasons behind this assault.</string>
  <string id="107715" soundid="164505">If you decide you truly don&apos;t like it, however, you can come see me after the bandits are dealt with.</string>
  <string id="107732">Is there anything else?</string>
  <string id="107734" soundid="164526">Didn&apos;t quite match what you were looking for, did it?</string>
  <string id="107735" soundid="164527">I&apos;d be happy to make an exchange for you, though it looks like you&apos;ve gotten somewhat proficient with the one you have.</string>
  <string id="107736" soundid="164528">I&apos;d hate to see you lose that experience and familiarity, and you will if you swap to a new weapon.</string>
  <string id="107737" soundid="164529">I&apos;ll admit, you don&apos;t look fully comfortable with it yet. Would you prefer the other weapon?</string>
  <string id="107738" soundid="164530">Are you sure you&apos;d like me to swap your weapon for Fortune&apos;s Favorite?</string>
  <string id="107740" soundid="164532">You can&apos;t beat the heft of a staff, but I want to make sure you&apos;re certain. A staff&apos;s what you want?</string>
  <string id="107741" soundid="164533">There you have it. Remember, when you&apos;re dealing with smiths, they&apos;ll be selling you their weapons, not offering them on exchange like your old weapon master would.</string>
  <string id="107742" soundid="164534">Enjoy your new weapon! Now, did you need anything else?</string>
  <string id="107743" soundid="164535">That&apos;s probably for the best. Always hard to get used to a new balance when you&apos;re just starting out.</string>
  <string id="107744">Could I exchange my weapon?</string>
  <string id="107747">Could I exchange my weapon for the long sword?</string>
  <string id="107748">Yes, I&apos;m sure.</string>
  <string id="107751">I would prefer Golden Star.</string>
  <string id="107752">Yes, I would like a staff.</string>
  <string id="107754">On second thought, I&apos;d rather not exchange my weapon.</string>
  <string id="107755">Chapter 3</string>
  <string id="107756">Chapter 4</string>
  <string id="107757">Chapter 5</string>
  <string id="107758">Chapter 6</string>
  <string id="107759">Chapter 7</string>
  <string id="107760">
Wherein the Imperial City is revealed,
Silk Fox reveals her station,
And the Lotus Assassins are infiltrated.


The Marvelous Dragonfly bears you away from Tien&apos;s Landing toward the Imperial City. The fall of Gao the Greater and Assassin Lim will have far-reaching consequences, and your enemy will not let your actions go unanswered. Terrible forces gather ahead, and as you draw close, they will leave their mark as surely as you have left yours.</string>
  <string id="107761">

Wherein the palace keeps its secrets,
An Emperor is met in battle,
And a Master shows his gratitude


You infiltrated and destroyed the Lotus Assassin fortress, and learned that the Emperor had full knowledge of what was held there. It was a costly endeavor, and the loss of one of your fellows casts a pall across your coming confrontation in the palace of the mighty Emperor Sun Hai.</string>
  <string id="107762">

Wherein the Water Dragon intervenes,
True history is revealed,
And the Spirit Monk legacy is reclaimed.


The defeat of Emperor Sun Hai was supposed to set things right, but with one careful blow, Master Li left you crumpled on the floor, a pawn in his carefully plotted revenge. The spirit realm stretches before you, but a beacon in the distance calls. You are not yet lost to the living.</string>
  <string id="107763">
Wherein a friend is returned to the living,
Dirge is under siege once more,
And the fate of Death&apos;s Hand is sealed.


Restoring the fountains of Dirge has allowed the Water Dragon to grant you a second chance at life. Your followers now rush to be at your side, but Sun Li also moves. He knows the threat a Spirit Monk poses. Here, at the ruins of Dirge, history will repeat itself in spectacular fashion.</string>
  <string id="107764">

Wherein the cost of war is tallied,
A Master is finally confronted,
And the fate of an Empire is decided.


You have come far, from borderland school to the ruins of Dirge, and now the fate of the Empire depends on the decisions before you. Stung by the loss of Death&apos;s Hand and the defeat of his siege force, Emperor Sun Li readies for your inevitable confrontation in the palace.</string>
  <string id="107765">Smiling Mountain, one of the combat trainers under Master Li, is offering a special reward to any student who can set a new record for the number of opponents faced at once. You might be able to earn this mysterious reward if you can help Kia Min get back into fighting form.</string>
  <string id="107766">Kia Min</string>
  <string id="107767">Ask Kia Min About Healing</string>
  <string id="107768">Kia Min must be in fighting form before you can get together enough opponents to try for Smiling Mountain&apos;s prize. Ask her if there is anything you can do to help.</string>
  <string id="107770">Kia Min can&apos;t face you in Smiling Mountain&apos;s test until she is feeling better, but she vaguely remembered a type of grass that might speed her healing.</string>
  <string id="107771">Ask Old Ming About Herbs</string>
  <string id="107772">Old Ming tends to the statue of the Emperor down by the beach. He might know a herb that is effective at binding wounds.</string>
  <string id="107774">Old Ming&apos;s memory still seems sharp after all these years. He remembered two grasses that would have similar effects in restoring Kia Min to fighting shape for Smiling Mountain&apos;s special contest. He cautioned that you should only use red silk grass, because bearded tongue grass is only a painkiller and not a true cure.</string>
  <string id="107775">Acquire a Red Silk Grass Poultice</string>
  <string id="107776">Merchant Fen Do in the town square likely has the curative red silk grass in stock.</string>
  <string id="107778">You have purchased a poultice infused with red silk grass, which Old Ming assured you would safely bind Kia Min&apos;s wounds so she could take part in Smiling Mountain&apos;s special test.</string>
  <string id="107779">Acquire a Bearded Tongue Grass Poultice</string>
  <string id="107780">While it may not be as effective, Merchant Fen Do would likely charge less for a bearded tongue grass poultice. He is at his shop in the town square.</string>
  <string id="107782">You now have a poultice infused with bearded tongue grass. The mixture may not have many curative effects, but it will at least take away the pain. This should be enough to convince Kia Min that she&apos;s able to fight in Smiling Mountain&apos;s special test.</string>
  <string id="107783">Deliver the Poultice to Kia Min</string>
  <string id="107784">Deliver the poultice to Kia Min in the school. </string>
  <string id="107786">Min was quite impressed with the effects of the poultice, and she now feels ready to fight again. If you wish to test yourself against a record level of opponents, she will happily join in Smiling Mountain&apos;s contest.</string>
  <string id="107787">Face Smiling Mountain&apos;s Challenge</string>
  <string id="107788">In order to earn Smiling Mountain&apos;s prize, you must face a record level of students. Smiling Mountain waits in the school. </string>
  <string id="107791">D: Kia Min defeated fairly.</string>
  <string id="107794">You set a new record by defeating five opponents at the same time. As your reward, Smiling Mountain taught you the training techniques he calls &quot;The Alloyed Body.&quot; Kia Min seems to be fine, thanks to the poultice you had Fen Do mix for her.</string>
  <string id="107795">D: Kia Min hurt badly.</string>
  <string id="107798">You have set a new record by defeating five opponents at the same time. The bearded tongue grass poultice lacked any real curative effect, though, and Kia Min&apos;s wound has torn open, injuring her further. Despite his obvious concern for Kia Min, Smiling Mountain has awarded you a scroll called &quot;The Alloyed Body&quot; outlining his conditioning techniques.</string>
  <string id="107801" soundid="164593">I have a little something tucked away for anyone who can best Kia Min&apos;s feat. That includes you, of course, but any attempt will have to wait until she is healed.</string>
  <string id="107804">I&apos;m in a hurry. Just show me this new stock of yours.</string>
  <string id="107806">Student</string>
  <string id="107810">A large statue dominates one of the room&apos;s in Master Li&apos;s house, likely an artifact left behind by previous masters. It seems to be a test of some kind.</string>
  <string id="107811">The Lions of Two Rivers</string>
  <string id="107812" soundid="164604">It is all right. I don&apos;t mind. But... I think that is enough for now.</string>
  <string id="107813" soundid="164605">Fair enough. All I know is that if a dog slips its leash for several months, the owners usually give up looking. Maybe this is your chance.</string>
  <string id="107814" soundid="164606">That is like suggesting the moon might give up it&apos;s chase of the stars. I have more chance of becoming emperor than of gaining my freedom.</string>
  <string id="107815" soundid="164607">You&apos;re right! I&apos;d be unleashing a monster on an unsuspecting female populace.</string>
  <string id="107818">Sky has a point, Hou. Maybe she has given up on you.</string>
  <string id="107819">If Hou were a free man, do you think you could handle the competition, Sky?</string>
  <string id="107820">Lost Spirit</string>
  <string id="107828">
Now that you have read the fully assembled Tome of Release, you know how to perform a ritual that would lift the curse from the spirits of the last few Imperial Army soldiers who still haunt Dirge. 

The ritual must be performed at the shrine dedicated to Mah Tsung the Water&apos;s Source, one of the first Spirit Monks. Elevated to the heavens for his tireless service to the Water Dragon, his influence is said to guide the invoked magic.

The last section you found, however, warns that performing the ritual at a shrine dedicated to a Heavenly Gate Guardian will summon the wrath of one of these beings. The cursed souls affected by such a ritual would be forever torn from the Wheel of Life. Their spiritual energies would be scattered to the winds, and might even affect the monk performing the ritual in some dark way.</string>
  <string id="107829">
An ancient text penned by some of the first Spirit Monks, this book has taught you how to properly focus upon the Mantra of Inspiration.

&quot;Understanding the totality of being is the only goal worth achieving, and yet it is a goal that cannot be fulfilled in any life. Still, in the striving can be found deep inspirations, and those can aid you in your search. In this paradox, the never-ending journey is made possible. 

Think upon what you have read here, and take your lessons to the meditation wheels of Divine Harmony in the temple&apos;s hallway. They will help you to find the next step upon the unending path.&quot;</string>
  <string id="107830">
There is something disturbing in the air tonight. I cannot be sure of my suspicions, but I wonder at the behavior of some of the younger monks. They seem nervous, like something is about to happen. Not long ago I spotted one of them leaving the well room off the temple, and when I asked why she was down there she could produce no reason that satisfied my fears. The look she gave me when I assigned her extra chores as penance for being distracted from her duties chilled my heart; it was filled with such menace.

Could some of the younger acolytes have discovered the secret path at the bottom of the well? Are they leaving our monastery without my permission? To what end? Troubling questions that will have to wait until tomorrow to answer.</string>
  <string id="107831">Whatever mysteries this ancient text once contained, they have been worn away by the ravages of time.</string>
  <string id="107832">Pages from the Tome of Release (1/5)</string>
  <string id="107838">A Mysterious Token</string>
  <string id="107839">There must be some explanation for the token in your possession. Perhaps the lion symbol is a clue.</string>
  <string id="107840">Behind Master Li&apos;s house, you stumbled across a small shrine dedicated to the last master of the school. When you inserted a silver coin into the collection bowl, a small token depicting a lion detached from the shrine. While its purpose remains a mystery, you kept the token.</string>
  <string id="107841">A large statue dominates one of the rooms in Master Li&apos;s house, likely an artifact left behind by previous masters. It seems to be a test of some kind. Given that the statue is in the shape of a lion, you wonder if the lion token you have in your possession is in some way related.</string>
  <string id="107842">An Ancient Test</string>
  <string id="107843">The lion statue in Master Li&apos;s house seems to be a test of reasoning of some kind. Master Li has never used it for training, but it likely still functions, if you wish to uncover its mysteries.</string>
  <string id="107846">Shatter Altar</string>
  <string id="107849">With a single mighty blow, you destroyed the altar in front of the Lion Statue. Inside, you found a collection of silver coins. You are finished with the statue.</string>
  <string id="107850">Token and complete</string>
  <string id="107853">After finding the old master&apos;s token and placing it in the lion statue, the test changed. You managed to solve this new challenge, earning a reward clearly intended for students who explored their surroundings.</string>
  <string id="107854">Playing by New Rules</string>
  <string id="107855">Whatever has changed in the statue, it still seems to function, leaving you with a mystery that begs to be solved.</string>
  <string id="107856">The lion statue in Master Li&apos;s house is clearly a test of some kind, and it seems that placing the lion token into its mouth has changed the rules in some way. Perhaps this has also changed the rewards.</string>
  <string id="107858">Your earliest memories are of the town of Two Rivers, the school you call your home, and of Master Li, the man who raised and trained you from birth. Now, as your lessons draw to a close, you can only wonder what the future has in store.</string>
  <string id="107859">A Master&apos;s Teachings</string>
  <string id="107860">Speak with Minister Sheng</string>
  <string id="107861">Minister Sheng may have some insight into the pirates and where they acquired their flyers. Speak to him in the center of town.</string>
  <string id="107864">Find a Power Source for Kang</string>
  <string id="107865">Search the ruins for the Inscrutable Power Source and bring it back to Kang.</string>
  <string id="107866">You&apos;ve acquired the Marvelous Dragonfly, but the flyer won&apos;t reach the Imperial City without an Inscrutable Power Source. Kang mentioned that the Lotus Assassins were using one in the ruins near Tien&apos;s Landing. If you bring it back to him, he can install it in the Dragonfly.</string>
  <string id="107868">Find Ru the Boatswain</string>
  <string id="107869">Ru normally spends his time in the teahouse. Seek him out.</string>
  <string id="107870">The pirates nearby are known to have flyers, but the only man foolish enough to risk traveling to their lair is Ru the Boatswain, the town drunk. You&apos;ll have to find some way to convince him to take you.</string>
  <string id="107872">Explore the Pirate Lair</string>
  <string id="107873">Explore the pirate lair to find a new flyer.</string>
  <string id="107874">Ru the Boatswain has agreed to transport you back and forth between the pirates&apos; island and the docks of Tien&apos;s Landing until you replace your crashed flyer. The pirates that hold the flyers may not be quite so helpful.</string>
  <string id="107876">A young woman named Lan has asked you to help her fiancé, a baker named Bei. Every day he gets beaten up by thugs down by the pier. Understandably, she wants someone to do something about it.</string>
  <string id="107877">The Beaten Baker</string>
  <string id="107878">Investigate Baker Bei</string>
  <string id="107879">Bei is usually down at Beggar&apos;s Pier in the southeast section of Tien&apos;s Landing.</string>
  <string id="107882">Talk to Ai Ling</string>
  <string id="107883">Ai Ling is in the boathouse of the docks district.</string>
  <string id="107884">Baker Bei told you that Ai Ling ordered the beatings. He wants you to convince her to leave him alone, and he suggested that you speak to her at the boathouse, the headquarters of her gang.</string>
  <string id="107886">Talk to Bei</string>
  <string id="107887">You could talk to Bei again and give him a chance to tell his side of the story.</string>
  <string id="107888">Ai Ling told you the only reason her thugs are picking on Bei is because he promised to marry her and then went back on his word. Considering Ai Ling&apos;s reputation, you should at least give Bei a chance to explain his side of things.</string>
  <string id="107890">Talk to Lan</string>
  <string id="107891">You could tell Lan that Bei promised to marry another woman... though she probably wouldn&apos;t take it well.</string>
  <string id="107894">Talk to Bei</string>
  <string id="107895">Bei deserves to know that his fiancée has called off the wedding.</string>
  <string id="107896">You told Lan about Bei promising to marry Ai Ling, and she didn&apos;t take the news well.</string>
  <string id="107897">Bei&apos;s proposal to Ai Ling was a harmless childhood promise, not that it matters now. Because of your actions, Lan has run off, and Bei&apos;s wedding is cancelled.</string>
  <string id="107898">Talk to Lan</string>
  <string id="107900">Ai Ling is dead, and Bei can now go about his business without fear of reprisal. You should let Lan know that Bei will be safe.</string>
  <string id="107901">Lan was a bit surprised when you told her Ai Ling was dead, but she was relieved to know that Bei was safe. Maybe the two of them will have a long and happy life.</string>
  <string id="107902">Everybody Dies</string>
  <string id="107905">Ai Ling killed Lan and Bei and then tried to kill you. Sometimes things just have to end this way.</string>
  <string id="107906">Bei and Lan Live Happily Ever After</string>
  <string id="107909">You were able to make Ai Ling see reason, and she agreed to leave Bei and Lan alone. Hopefully they&apos;ll have a long and happy life.</string>
  <string id="107910">Talk to Ai Ling</string>
  <string id="107911">You and Bei should go talk to Ai Ling and straighten everything out.</string>
  <string id="107912">Bei claims he never proposed to Ai Ling. One of them is lying, and the only way to solve this problem is by getting them both together.</string>
  <string id="107914">Ai Ling is Dead</string>
  <string id="107915">Ai Ling is dead.</string>
  <string id="107917">Ai Ling is dead, and Bei can now go about his business without fear of reprisal. You should let Lan know that Bei will be safe.</string>
  <string id="107918">Fighting Pit</string>
  <string id="107919">Creature Pens</string>
  <string id="107920">To Arena Tavern</string>
  <string id="107923">To Imperial City</string>
  <string id="107924">The Serpent&apos;s Quarters</string>
  <string id="107925">To Creature Pens</string>
  <string id="107926" soundid="164727"></string>
  <string id="107928">These bombers are heading for Two Rivers.</string>
  <string id="107929">This is a weapon powerup - fly into it!</string>
  <string id="107937">The dam is closed, and the river is rising again. The town of Tien&apos;s Landing is saved, at least from their trade concerns.</string>
  <string id="107938">The dam is closed, and the river is rising again. The town of Tien&apos;s Landing is saved, though Minister Sheng seems determined to take credit for your actions.</string>
  <string id="107939">Hui the Brave is a trusted and very loyal servant of Master Li. Upon his order, she has waited many years in Tien&apos;s Landing, preparing for your arrival. She seems eager to share what she knows, having waited so long for this moment.</string>
  <string id="107940">Hui the Brave</string>
  <string id="107941" soundid="164799">Go on, teach those bandits some manners!</string>
  <string id="107942" soundid="164800"></string>
  <string id="107943">What do you know about the Great Wheel or the Celestial Bureaucracy?</string>
  <string id="107944" soundid="164802"></string>
  <string id="107948">Acquire Your Weapon</string>
  <string id="107949">Gujin, the weapon master for your school, has a workshop north of the town square. Its location is marked on your map. You should go there and pick up a weapon to help against the bandits.</string>
  <string id="107950">The bandit threat is clearly very real; two of them have already made their way to the town square. You dealt with them, but that was only a small group. It&apos;s all the more imperative that you arm yourself before the main group arrives.</string>
  <string id="107952">Stop the Bandit Attack</string>
  <string id="107953">The bandits are all over town, but their main force has landed on the beach. Take the east gate from the main square and drive these marauders out of your home.</string>
  <string id="107954">Not long after you acquired your weapon, word arrived that the bandits&apos; main force had arrived on the beach. Master Li hasn&apos;t returned, so it falls to you to help defend the town.</string>
  <string id="107956">Return to Master Li</string>
  <string id="107957">Master Li asked to speak with you back at the school, but you have time to explore the town first.</string>
  <string id="107958">The bandits have been driven back, but their leader seemed to recognize Master Li. That recognition leaves you with many questions that only Master Li seems able to answer.</string>
  <string id="107960">Answer Gao&apos;s Challenge</string>
  <string id="107961">Gao the Lesser challenged you to single combat for the right to enter the cave beneath the school. Master Li has allowed the challenge, so facing Gao is inevitable.</string>
  <string id="107962">Master Li seemed ready to accelerate your training in light of the bandit attack, but Gao the Lesser refused to let the matter of your progress go without comment.</string>
  <string id="107964">Learn More from Master Li</string>
  <string id="107965">Master Li has asked to speak with you in his house when you are ready for your final test.</string>
  <string id="107966">You have successfully defeated Gao the Lesser, but in his pride he attacked you with a forbidden magical style.</string>
  <string id="107968">Explore the Spirit Cave</string>
  <string id="107969">Master Li asked you to explore the cave beneath the school, promising that it would make things clear.</string>
  <string id="107970">Your discussion with Master Li revealed many things: his relationship to the Emperor, your orphaning and subsequent rescue at his hands, and the truth about the restless dead. It is a lot to digest, but a mysterious cave under the school might hold answers.</string>
  <string id="107972">Exit the Spirit Cave</string>
  <string id="107973">The vortex of magical energy seems the only way out of the cave. You hope it will take you back to Master Li.</string>
  <string id="107974">After acquiring the artifact called the Dragon Amulet, you encountered several ghosts, including a mysterious female spirit who spoke in riddles. She claimed you were &quot;the last Spirit Monk,&quot; but she explained no more.</string>
  <string id="107975">After returning from the spirit cave, Master Li explained that your people, the Spirit Monks, were warriors who revered the Water Dragon. This connection led to their destruction at the hands of the Emperor, who sought to force the Water Dragon to end the Long Drought. You were the only survivor.</string>
  <string id="107976">Find Dawn Star</string>
  <string id="107977">Master Li suggested that Gao may have taken Dawn Star to the marshes outside the school. Make your way toward the town gate.</string>
  <string id="107980">Find Dawn Star</string>
  <string id="107981">It seems clear that Gao is involved in Dawn Star&apos;s disappearance. He was last spotted heading for the town gate.</string>
  <string id="107982">You have found student Si Pat murdered at the gate into town. Eyewitnesses place the blame on Gao the Lesser, who was also dragging something heavy in a sack as he went.</string>
  <string id="107984">Pursue Gao to the Marshes</string>
  <string id="107985">Gao is headed for the marshes outside of town. He must be stopped.</string>
  <string id="107986">Gao the Lesser left several men in ambush for you near the town gate. After you dealt with them, Guard Yung confirmed that Gao has already left town.</string>
  <string id="107988">A Camp to the North</string>
  <string id="107989">Head to the camp to the north, and find Dawn Star.</string>
  <string id="107990">A mysterious hermit who calls himself Sagacious Zu reluctantly directed you to a camp of men at the north end of the swamp. It seems likely that Gao took Dawn Star there.</string>
  <string id="107992">Rescue Dawn Star from Gao</string>
  <string id="107993">Track down Gao, and make sure Dawn Star is all right. They&apos;re in a cave at the north end of the marsh.</string>
  <string id="107994">One of Gao&apos;s men in the marsh told you that Dawn Star escaped and led Gao pursued into a cave just north of their encampment.</string>
  <string id="107996">Return to Two Rivers</string>
  <string id="107997">Use Gao&apos;s flyer to return to Two Rivers.</string>
  <string id="107998">Dawn Star is safe, but before he died, Gao made some ominous comments about Two Rivers.</string>
  <string id="107999">A pall of smoke in the distance served as a grim landmark as you made your way back to Two Rivers.</string>
  <string id="108000">Find Survivors</string>
  <string id="108001">There must be someone left who can tell you more about this attack. Make your way toward the school, and look for survivors.</string>
  <string id="108003">You found Jing Woo clinging to life. He told you about warriors with black hands and a leader in armor as dark as night taking Master Li away.</string>
  <string id="108004">Horse Demon</string>
  <string id="108007">It seems you are not the only one hunting a missing person in this swamp. A man named Hing has passionately implored you to rescue his Fen, the &quot;Flower of the Fields,&quot; from bandits.</string>
  <string id="108008">The Flower of the Fields</string>
  <string id="108010">To the swamp</string>
  <string id="108011">Door</string>
  <string id="108018">Spirit Cave</string>
  <string id="108019">Villager&apos;s Chest</string>
  <string id="108031">I can figure this out from here.</string>
  <string id="108035">To the Beach</string>
  <string id="108036">Town Gate</string>
  <string id="108037">You rescued a woman named Sing Wa who introduced you to Fen the Flower of the Fields, who turned out to be an admittedly much-loved water buffalo. Overjoyed, Merchant Hing thanked you profusely while his wife left you with a generous purse of silver for her rescue.</string>
  <string id="108046">I&apos;ll hurt you yet!</string>
  <string id="108047">Your spirit is mine!</string>
  <string id="108048">Join me in death!</string>
  <string id="108049">Now is your end!</string>
  <string id="108050">Die!</string>
  <string id="108051">I&apos;ll tear you apart!</string>
  <string id="108052">You are mine now!</string>
  <string id="108057">My body renews.</string>
  <string id="108058">Poison will not work on me.</string>
  <string id="108059">I&apos;ll eat your soul!</string>
  <string id="108060">I must try harder.</string>
  <string id="108061">Your death is here!</string>
  <string id="108062">I will be your doom!</string>
  <string id="108063">None escape me!</string>
  <string id="108064">My style is perfection!</string>
  <string id="108065">Die, maggot!</string>
  <string id="108066">Bow before me!</string>
  <string id="108071">I am restored.</string>
  <string id="108072">Poison won&apos;t stop me.</string>
  <string id="108073">Fear my wrath!</string>
  <string id="108074">Your style has saved you... once.</string>
  <string id="108075">My style is faultless!</string>
  <string id="108076">You will be broken!</string>
  <string id="108077">None will defeat me!</string>
  <string id="108078">Die in pain!</string>
  <string id="108079">My Master commands...</string>
  <string id="108080">For Death&apos;s Hand!</string>
  <string id="108085">My body mends.</string>
  <string id="108086">My blood is acid!</string>
  <string id="108087">Death to all who oppose!</string>
  <string id="108088">How do you resist me?</string>
  <string id="108089">Like leaves, you fall!</string>
  <string id="108090">Your power is mine!</string>
  <string id="108091">I am eternal!</string>
  <string id="108092">None shall pass!</string>
  <string id="108093">Your doom approaches!</string>
  <string id="108094">You are mine!</string>
  <string id="108099">My spirit, restored.</string>
  <string id="108100">Poison is... ineffective.</string>
  <string id="108101">I&apos;ll swallow your soul!</string>
  <string id="108102">Your defence is strong.</string>
  <string id="108103">I will destroy you!</string>
  <string id="108104">The school belongs to me!</string>
  <string id="108105">This ends here!</string>
  <string id="108106">Now you die!</string>
  <string id="108107">I am the true Master!</string>
  <string id="108108">You had your chance!</string>
  <string id="108113">I&apos;m stronger than you think!</string>
  <string id="108114">You have corrupted my body...</string>
  <string id="108115">Ha! The skill of a master!</string>
  <string id="108116" soundid="165004">[You are finished with the statue, so you leave the figurines on the altar.]</string>
  <string id="108118" soundid="165006">[Using the stand you are able to place both of the scripts for your scene side by side and compare them.]</string>
  <string id="108119" soundid="165007">[It seems you have only a few lines for this scene. They are mostly reacting to the other actor. The scene reenacts a historical moment in the formation of the Jade Empire.]</string>
  <string id="108120" soundid="165008">[There seem to be only six lines for you to remember, and on the scripts there are acting notes that should make it easy to remember the proper lines.]</string>
  <string id="108121" soundid="165009">[You examine the first page of the scripts, which covers the first three of your six lines.]</string>
  <string id="108122" soundid="165010">[Your first line seems the same in both scripts. It is simply responding to a question about the color of banners.]</string>
  <string id="108123" soundid="165011">[Your line has you commenting that white banners are flying.]</string>
  <string id="108124" soundid="165012">[The second line seems to be one of the lines that was changed between the scripts. There are two versions of it.]</string>
  <string id="108125" soundid="165013">[You are responding to a question about the time of day, and in Incisive Chorus&apos; script, you speak of the heavens sending a message at dusk and the night is coming on fast.]</string>
  <string id="108126" soundid="165014">[In the edited version, the time is mid-day, and you would speak about &quot;the Flower Guardians,&quot; an obvious dig at the Lotus Assassins.]</string>
  <string id="108127" soundid="165015">[The third line is the same in both scripts. In it, you are responding to a question about location.]</string>
  <string id="108128" soundid="165016">[As the acting notes direct, the key element lies in that a decision was reached on the edge of a great plain.]</string>
  <string id="108129" soundid="165017">[You look at the second page of the script, which contains your last three of the six lines.]</string>
  <string id="108130" soundid="165018">[This line seems to have two versions, and must have been edited when the play came to the city.]</string>
  <string id="108131" soundid="165019">[In the script written by Incisive Chorus, the theme of the heavens reaching out to Emperor Tien is explored again, and your character comments that seasons change from place to place.]</string>
  <string id="108132" soundid="165020">[In the edited version, your character comments that warmth can hide an icy heart; this comment leads to a thinly veiled condemnation of the Emperor.]</string>
  <string id="108133" soundid="165021">[This line is the same between both scripts, and the director&apos;s notes point out that you&apos;d be answering, roughly, &quot;Who did the Emperor turn to?&quot;]</string>
  <string id="108134" soundid="165022">[In the script, the Emperor turned to the heavens themselves.]</string>
  <string id="108135" soundid="165023">[The sixth line seems the same across both scripts.]</string>
  <string id="108136" soundid="165024">[Your character comments on how a shooting star traces a border across the sky.]</string>
  <string id="108137" soundid="165025">[You finish your study of the scripts.]</string>
  <string id="108138" soundid="165026">[This stand is covered with books, papers, and other elements related to a play of some sort.]</string>
  <string id="108139" soundid="165027">[You have no reason to study scripts; your role is complete.]</string>
  <string id="108142">[Read the notes for the first half of the scene.]</string>
  <string id="108143">[Read the notes for the first line.]</string>
  <string id="108145">[Read the notes for the second line.]</string>
  <string id="108148">[Read the notes for the third line.]</string>
  <string id="108150">[Read the notes for the second half of the scene.]</string>
  <string id="108151">[Read the notes for the fourth line.]</string>
  <string id="108154">[Read the notes for the fifth line.]</string>
  <string id="108156">[Read the notes for the sixth line.]</string>
  <string id="108158">[Leave the stand alone.]</string>
  <string id="108159">Bandit</string>
  <string id="108162">Bandit</string>
  <string id="108165">Bandit</string>
  <string id="108168" soundid="165056">I&apos;m so shocked, I don&apos;t know what to say. You have to keep us safe!</string>
  <string id="108169" soundid="165057">Why would bandits come here to Two Rivers?</string>
  <string id="108170" soundid="165058">What was that noise from the town square? Are people fighting?</string>
  <string id="108172">The Sickened Forest</string>
  <string id="108173">Lost Spirit</string>
  <string id="108176">Cannibals in the Inn</string>
  <string id="108179">The people at the inn seem to want nothing more than the death of the Forest Shadow, the fox spirit who serves as guardian of the Great Southern Forest. They have offered a handsome reward of silver for her death.</string>
  <string id="108180">Fox Hunt</string>
  <string id="108182">Script stand</string>
  <string id="108183">Allies or Enemies</string>
  <string id="108184">The cannibals are clearly powerful creatures if they can cloak their appearances with such ease. They would make dangerous enemies, but as flesh-eating monsters, they might be far worse as allies.</string>
  <string id="108185">The Keeper of the Pilgrim&apos;s Rest elected to reveal his true form to you. All of the people in the inn are twisted, flesh-eating cannibals, their forms normally cloaked by the magic of a greater demon they call &quot;the Mother.&quot;</string>
  <string id="108187">D: Keeper Dead</string>
  <string id="108191">D: Left in peace.</string>
  <string id="108194">The cannibals may be corrupted by a greater demon and twisted creatures that feast on the flesh of humans, but they are also generous. You parted on a wary truce with the Keeper and his followers, leaving them to pursue their goals.</string>
  <string id="108195">The Mother</string>
  <string id="108196">The cannibals won&apos;t be truly destroyed until the Mother, the demon that twisted these men into beasts, has been dealt with. She lies in wait in the caves beneath the Pilgrim&apos;s Rest Inn.</string>
  <string id="108197">After the revelation that the people of the Pilgrim&apos;s Rest had been twisted into flesh-eating monsters, you destroyed the Keeper and his followers. From what they said, however, there are far more of these creatures.</string>
  <string id="108198">You fought your way through the caves beneath the Pilgrim&apos;s Rest, eventually reaching the cavern that was home to The Mother. You defeated the disgusting beast and escaped the collapsing caves just in time.</string>
  <string id="108221">You were able to open a portal that leads to her domain. If you can track her down and kill her, the Keeper of the inn will give you a sizeable reward of silver.</string>
  <string id="108223">D: Not Kill</string>
  <string id="108226">Despite the rich reward offered by the Keeper of the Pilgrim&apos;s Rest, you refused to kill the fox, instead finding an ally in the Forest Shadow.</string>
  <string id="108227">D: Kill</string>
  <string id="108231">Track Down the Fox</string>
  <string id="108232">Pursue the Forest Shadow and destroy her.</string>
  <string id="108233">With the Keeper of the Pilgrim&apos;s Rest&apos;s offer of silver in the balance, you have decided to destroy the Forest Shadow. She escaped you, but she cannot have gone far.</string>
  <string id="108234">The Forest Shadow is dead by your hands. Her stewardship over the Great Southern Forest is over.</string>
  <string id="108235" soundid="165129">[Success] How can you be so certain? How can you believe her, after you know what she&apos;s done to me?</string>
  <string id="108236" soundid="165130">[Failure] The fish? I died from a fish? You expect me to believe such a stupid excuse?</string>
  <string id="108237" soundid="165131">[Success] Yes, you are deserving of such a reward. For showing me how wrong I was. All that was left of mine is now yours.</string>
  <string id="108238" soundid="165132">[Failure] Money? That&apos;s all this is for? Not care, not justice, but money?</string>
  <string id="108239" soundid="165133">This was all a lie! A deception so you could line your pockets at my expense!</string>
  <string id="108240" soundid="165134">No! I&apos;ll not have anything you say, nor this lying dog here! Die, the both of you!</string>
  <string id="108241">Tent</string>
  <string id="108242">[Charm] It was a bad fish that killed you, not her.</string>
  <string id="108244">[Intuition] Yes, yes. You&apos;re both wrong. Now maybe it&apos;s time to reward the person who pointed it out?</string>
  <string id="108248">To the Inner Courtyard</string>
  <string id="108249" soundid="165143">Where is my baby?</string>
  <string id="108250" soundid="165144">Please! Bring me my baby!</string>
  <string id="108251" soundid="165145">Is... is someone there?</string>
  <string id="108252" soundid="165146">Why can&apos;t I die in peace?</string>
  <string id="108253" soundid="165147">I&apos;ll have her head!</string>
  <string id="108254" soundid="165148">Vengeance will be mine!</string>
  <string id="108256">Lost Spirit</string>
  <string id="108259">Lost Spirit</string>
  <string id="108262">Lost Spirit</string>
  <string id="108266" soundid="194699"></string>
  <string id="108270">Ru&apos;s Barge</string>
  <string id="108271">Dam</string>
  <string id="108272">Path to Ruins</string>
  <string id="108273">It isn&apos;t working?!</string>
  <string id="108274">Kai Lan&apos;s command!</string>
  <string id="108275">You&apos;re meat!</string>
  <string id="108276">The arena&apos;s magic won&apos;t help you!</string>
  <string id="108277">Now you die!</string>
  <string id="108278">Kai Lan&apos;s regards, fool!</string>
  <string id="108279">You&apos;ve made your last mistake!</string>
  <string id="108284">I won&apos;t be stopped!</string>
  <string id="108285">You... you&apos;ve poisoned me?!</string>
  <string id="108286">Die, fool!</string>
  <string id="108293">Seek Out Lord Yun</string>
  <string id="108294">Tien&apos;s Landing sits not far from the edge of the Great Southern Forest. A large gate off the central square begins a path that will take you to the edge of the trees.</string>
  <string id="108295">You have heard tales of a disease affecting the Great Southern Forest, which lies just north of Tien&apos;s Landing. Lord Yun, a noble from the Imperial City, has recently arrived to find a solution. He seeks skilled warriors to aid him.</string>
  <string id="108297">Find Spear Catches Leaf</string>
  <string id="108298">Lord Yun wishes you to meet up with Spear Catches Leaf. You can find him at the temple to a fox spirit known as the Forest Shadow. To reach it, go up the hillside path and take the left fork when the path branches.</string>
  <string id="108299">In return for your help, Lord Yun has offered you a copy of a highly prized wind map that covers the skies between Tien&apos;s Landing and the Imperial City. Impressed with your skills, he has asked that you find a cure for the blight that affects his forest.</string>
  <string id="108301">Restore the Missing Crystal</string>
  <string id="108302">Spear Catches Leaf suspects the people at the inn might know where to find the missing crystal, or even have it. Track down the missing crystal and give it to Spear Catches Leaf.</string>
  <string id="108303">You made your way to the temple of the Forest Shadow and met with Spear Catches Leaf.  Spear Catches Leaf has told you that a missing crystal is key to a ritual he hopes will allow you to meet with the Forest Shadow.</string>
  <string id="108305">D: Help her</string>
  <string id="108309">D: Kill her</string>
  <string id="108313">Destroy the Mother</string>
  <string id="108314">The only way to cure the forest is to destroy the Mother, an ancient demon.</string>
  <string id="108315">The Forest Shadow was able to direct you to the real source of the Great Southern Forest&apos;s corruption: an ancient demon, long trapped by the fox spirit&apos;s magic. If you can destroy this beast, then Lord Yun&apos;s conditions should be satisfied, and his wind map should be yours.</string>
  <string id="108317">Return to Lord Yun</string>
  <string id="108318">Lord Yun promised you a copy of his wind map if you could save his lands. You should go see him and collect your reward.</string>
  <string id="108319">You destroyed the Mother and wiped out most of her cannibal followers in the process. The corruption of the Great Southern Forest should be over, and, in time, the trees should heal.</string>
  <string id="108320">Lord Yun was true to his word, and you have acquired a wind map that will take you to the Imperial City. An ancient demon has been destroyed, and the Great Southern Forest should heal in time under the care of the Forest Shadow.</string>
  <string id="108321">Return to Lord Yun</string>
  <string id="108322">Killing the Forest Shadow should have been enough to convince Lord Yun that your work is done. Go see him and collect the map.</string>
  <string id="108323">The Forest Shadow knew that anyone in the forest would sense her death when it happened. Lord Yun should be aware of your actions, and he will likely be willing to part with his wind map to the Imperial City.</string>
  <string id="108324">Whether the Forest Shadow was actually causing the blight in his lands didn&apos;t seem all that important to Lord Yun. Convinced by her death that something had changed, and assuming that it was for the better, the noble gave you a copy of a wind map to the Imperial City.</string>
  <string id="108326">The Inquisitors</string>
  <string id="108328">The Executioners</string>
  <string id="108330">The Outlander</string>
  <string id="108332">Challenge the Outlander to single combat and see if that will convince him to pack his bags once and for all.</string>
  <string id="108334">The Outlander has accepted your challenge to single combat. If you can prove yourself his superior, the Outlander might be convinced to leave, pleasing the Minister of Culture greatly.</string>
  <string id="108335">See the Minister of Culture</string>
  <string id="108336">The Outlander removed, the Minister of Culture will want to reward your efforts. He should be in the Scholars&apos; Garden.</string>
  <string id="108337">For all his conviction, Sir Roderick was unable to best your skills in combat. Admitting your superiority, the Outlander has left the Scholars&apos; Garden.</string>
  <string id="108338">Thanks to your efforts, Sir Roderick has packed up and left the Imperial City. Some semblance of peace has returned to the Scholars&apos; Garden.</string>
  <string id="108339">Totally blew debate</string>
  <string id="108342">While the debate ended with all the judges for the Outlander, he took the result as a backhanded insult. He has challenged you to personal combat.</string>
  <string id="108357">More!</string>
  <string id="108358">Take this!</string>
  <string id="108363" soundid="165294">Master, I never....</string>
  <string id="108364" soundid="165295">Oh, stuff it. It&apos;s not like I really expect you to listen. Talking just helps to keep my mind sharp.</string>
  <string id="108367">Speak to Zhong the Ox Carrier</string>
  <string id="108368">Convince Zhong the Ox Carrier to leave the teahouse.</string>
  <string id="108372">Arrogance, yes, but also audacious.</string>
  <string id="108373">Not much of a god if she fell to the Emperor&apos;s bluster.</string>
  <string id="108375" soundid="166633">I&apos;m sure the princess will not be pleased at the delay, but I&apos;m all for it. Just say the word!</string>
  <string id="108376" soundid="166634">Good luck. If you succeed at whatever it is you are doing, maybe later we can do some loops.</string>
  <string id="108377" soundid="166635">I suppose you want to go back to the palace. Just say so, and we&apos;ll fly.</string>
  <string id="108378" soundid="166636">All right, but don&apos;t be long. The others are giving me &quot;the eye.&quot;</string>
  <string id="108379" soundid="165314">Fate may have robbed me of my sight at a young age, but I can still sense the energy within your meridians. Impressive, and yet somewhat strange.</string>
  <string id="108381">According to Silk Fox, the Executioners recruit primarily from tests of skill like the Imperial Arena. Silk Fox has her people spreading word of your possible interest in joining their ranks.</string>
  <string id="108383">Become the Silver Champion</string>
  <string id="108384">Advance to become champion of the Silver Division in the Imperial Arena.</string>
  <string id="108385">Infiltrating the Executioners will not be simple. The recruiter made it clear that you would need to prove that you could advance to the top of the Silver Division in the Imperial Arena before he would accept you.</string>
  <string id="108387">Petition the Recruiter</string>
  <string id="108388">Seek out the recruiter for the Lotus Assassin Executioners and petition him for membership. He should still be in the tavern in the Imperial Arena.</string>
  <string id="108389">You have risen to the rank of Silver Champion, replacing Iron Soldier. This was the requirement set out by the recruiter for the Executioners, so you are one step closer to infiltrating their organization.</string>
  <string id="108390">Having satisfied the recruiter, you have been accepted as a new recruit into the Lotus Assassin Executioners.</string>
  <string id="108391">A spirit girl is trapped in the caves in the ruins. She is too afraid to cross the water blocking her exit from the caves.</string>
  <string id="108392">Stranded Orphan Girl</string>
  <string id="108393">Knock Down the Supports</string>
  <string id="108394">Knock down each of the supports.</string>
  <string id="108396">With the supports gone, the water has been covered with rubble. The spirit girl was able to escape the caves.</string>
  <string id="108397">Master Gang has charged you with finding a way to kill his superior, Master Shin. He must die in a way that disgraces him and does not implicate Master Gang directly.</string>
  <string id="108398">Kill Master Shin</string>
  <string id="108399">Master Gang wants you to help construct a spirit shard in the soul extraction chamber for the new lieutenant Jade Golem. There has to be a way to fulfill your duties without making the golem armies of the Lotus Assassins stronger. They will remain your enemy no matter what you learn here.</string>
  <string id="108400">Create a Spirit Shard</string>
  <string id="108435">More damage</string>
  <string id="108436">Daze recovery</string>
  <string id="108437">Display strengths</string>
  <string id="108438">Display weaknesses</string>
  <string id="108439">Lost Spirit</string>
  <string id="108442">Select/Deselect</string>
  <string id="108443">Go to the Inner Chambers</string>
  <string id="108444">Your main tasks complete, you must go to the inner chamber doors to participate in the creation of the Jade Golem. Make certain you have finished all other business in the fortress before going.</string>
  <string id="108447">Enter the Inner Chambers</string>
  <string id="108448">Proceed into the inner chambers to oversee the creation of the Jade Golem. Search for the information the princess needs to discredit Death&apos;s Hand.</string>
  <string id="108449">You have secured access to the inner chambers, where you hope to find information against Death&apos;s Hand for the princess. Sagacious Zu also revealed that he was one of the Assassins sent to kill Master Li&apos;s family, but that the child is still alive. How this information will change what comes is not yet clear.</string>
  <string id="108451">Enter the Inner Chambers</string>
  <string id="108452">Proceed into the inner chambers to oversee the creation of the Jade Golem. Search for the information the princess needs to discredit Death&apos;s Hand.</string>
  <string id="108453">You have secured access to the inner chambers, where you hope to find information against Death&apos;s Hand for the princess. Sagacious Zu also revealed that he was one of the Assassins sent to kill Master Li&apos;s family. How this information will change what comes is not yet clear.</string>
  <string id="108455">Defeat Grand Inquisitor Jia</string>
  <string id="108456">Defeat Grand Inquisitor Jia before she summons Death&apos;s Hand, and escape the collapsing fortress. </string>
  <string id="108457">Contrary to what Princess Lian claimed, you now know the Emperor is fully complicit in the actions of the Lotus Assassins. Once you have escaped the fortress, you can confront him with this information and deal with Sagacious Zu&apos;s revelation.</string>
  <string id="108459">Escape the Collapsing Fortress</string>
  <string id="108460">Do not let Sagacious Zu&apos;s sacrifice go to waste. Escape the fortress and confront the Emperor with what you know.</string>
  <string id="108462">The Emperor is fully complicit in the actions of the Lotus Assassins. Regroup at the flyer before deciding what to do with this information. You will have to deal with Sagacious Zu&apos;s revelation, as well.</string>
  <string id="108463">Find a Way to Kill and Disgrace Shin</string>
  <string id="108464">Search the fortress for some way to kill Master Shin that will also disgrace him. An embarrassing accident would be ideal.</string>
  <string id="108467">Find a Way to Kill and Disgrace Shin</string>
  <string id="108468">You might find a suitable potential accident in the golem press room.</string>
  <string id="108471">Return to Master Gang</string>
  <string id="108472">You learned that dying in the golem press would be an embarrassing way for Shin to meet his end. Tell Master Gang.</string>
  <string id="108475">Clear the Hall of Induction</string>
  <string id="108476">Remove all possible witnesses from the Hall of Induction. Convince them by guile or force.</string>
  <string id="108477">Earn Master Gang&apos;s trust by killing Master Shin in a way that disgraces him. If Shin&apos;s body is found in the golem press, he will be ridiculed for his carelessness. Shin only leaves the inner chambers to inspect new shipments of arriving slaves in the Hall of Induction. Make sure no one sees you kill him or transport his body.</string>
  <string id="108479">Remove Press Operator</string>
  <string id="108480">Convince the Lotus Acolyte operating the golem press to leave his station.</string>
  <string id="108481">Earn Master Gang&apos;s trust by killing Master Shin in a way that disgraces him. If Shin&apos;s body is found in the golem press, he will be ridiculed for his carelessness. Shin only leaves the inner chambers to inspect new shipments of arriving slaves in the Hall of Induction. Make sure no one sees you kill him or transport his body.</string>
  <string id="108483">Stop the Slave Shipment</string>
  <string id="108484">Leave the Lotus Assassin fortress to stop the slave shipment arriving from the Necropolis.</string>
  <string id="108485">Earn Master Gang&apos;s trust by killing Master Shin in a way that disgraces him. If Shin&apos;s body is found in the golem press, he will be ridiculed for his carelessness. Shin only leaves the inner chambers to inspect new shipments of arriving slaves in the Hall of Induction. Make sure no one sees you kill him or transport his body.</string>
  <string id="108487">Kill Master Shin</string>
  <string id="108488">Return to the Hall of Induction to await Master Shin. You have removed all witnesses and stopped the new slaves. Kill him there, and no one will be the wiser until his body is found in the press.</string>
  <string id="108490">Shin is dead, securing you a position closer to the heart of the Lotus Assassins. It won&apos;t be long before you are allowed entry to the inner chambers.</string>
  <string id="108491">Go to the Soul Extraction Chamber</string>
  <string id="108492">Go to the soul extraction chamber past where you fought the ghosts for Master Gang.</string>
  <string id="108495">Search the Lower Mines</string>
  <string id="108496">Use the elevator in the extraction chamber to go to the lowest mines.</string>
  <string id="108497">Sagacious Zu said there is a way to corrupt the spirit shard so you can fulfill your duties for Master Gang without increasing the strength of the golem army. He did not give details, but he said you should go to the lowest mines.</string>
  <string id="108499">Make a Corrupted Spirit Shard</string>
  <string id="108500">Take the body of Zeng Sai to the Soul Extractor, and use the controls to make a corrupted spirit shard.</string>
  <string id="108501">You fought one of the Horselord spirits that linger in the lowest mines. They are utterly chaotic, and Zu claims that a spirit shard made from the corpse the ghost was protecting will corrupt the Jade Golem. Zu also wanted proof that you were a Spirit Monk, which the ghost seemed to confirm.</string>
  <string id="108502">You fought a Horselord spirit and created a corrupted spirit shard from its corpse. That should appease your Lotus Assassin superiors without actually strengthening the golem army.</string>
  <string id="108503">Sagacious Zu left your group under mysterious circumstances, and he has been seen entering the Lotus Assassin fortress. You have yet to determine whether he is friend or foe.</string>
  <string id="108504">Sagacious Zu&apos;s Hidden Past</string>
  <string id="108505">Inner Temple</string>
  <string id="108514" soundid="165503">[The chain refuses to move. It seems like it is locked in place.]</string>
  <string id="108515" soundid="165504">[There&apos;s an indentation in the pedestal that looks like it held something until recently.]</string>
  <string id="108516" soundid="165505">[The chain seems locked in place for now. You can&apos;t budge it.]</string>
  <string id="108517">Why don&apos;t we work together after the door is opened?</string>
  <string id="108520">Visit jade.bioware.com to meet other players and discuss strategies and tricks for winning battles.</string>
  <string id="108523">How do you know your way around this place so well?</string>
  <string id="108525">Why are you here?</string>
  <string id="108526">Is this man Gao the Greater?</string>
  <string id="108530">What did he take?</string>
  <string id="108532">How do I know I can trust you?</string>
  <string id="108534">Let&apos;s talk about this plan of yours. How do we get past that door?</string>
  <string id="108536" soundid="175162">Are you getting slow in your old age, Jian?</string>
  <string id="108546" soundid="165604">The older tombs have spirits that have festered in their hatred for ages. They are not easily controlled. That is why we use slaves to power the golems now.</string>
  <string id="108547" soundid="165605">As well, the mines are simply not stable. Tombs can collapse, so we take care not to move too many golems at once, to avoid shaking the foundations of the fortress.</string>
  <string id="108548">So you believe they are dangerous?</string>
  <string id="108551" soundid="165610">It matters because he deserved to die by my hands!</string>
  <string id="108552" soundid="165611">No, that&apos;s not right. I should be thanking you. Besides, after I left you I stumbled across something just as important.</string>
  <string id="108553" soundid="165612">After I left you, I stumbled across some very interesting documents. Perhaps I spent too long pouring over them, but I couldn&apos;t resist.</string>
  <string id="108554" soundid="165613">Trust me, I didn&apos;t waste my moments. I stumbled across something very important. Evidence that changes everything.</string>
  <string id="108555" soundid="165614">Let me explain why I&apos;m here; that should clarify things. You saw with your own eyes that these pirates were collecting slaves, right?</string>
  <string id="108556" soundid="165615">True enough. I have a particular hatred for slavers.</string>
  <string id="108557" soundid="165616">My search led me here, to the lair of Gao the Greater. His men took my daughter, and I meant to even the score.</string>
  <string id="108558" soundid="165617">On my way up here, I stumbled across records that show that this goes beyond Gao. The Lotus Assassins are his primary buyers.</string>
  <string id="108559" soundid="165618">Is that so? There can be no doubt, then.</string>
  <string id="108560" soundid="165619">This goes beyond Gao the Greater. I have my vengeance, but how many others have suffered as I have because of the Lotus Assassins?</string>
  <string id="108561" soundid="165620">Do you mean to go further with this? I would join you. Only a fool would oppose the Lotus Assassins, but two fools working together stand a better chance than one.</string>
  <string id="108562" soundid="165621">It will be an honor to join you. Oh, and I stumbled across a little something on my way up here. It&apos;s probably something you need.</string>
  <string id="108563" soundid="165622">Collecting them like bad habits, are you? I hate to be pushy, but I have a right to see this through. You did steal Gao from me, after all.</string>
  <string id="108564">He&apos;s dead, why does it matter who killed him?</string>
  <string id="108567">Where have you been?</string>
  <string id="108569">If you hadn&apos;t taken your time, you might have saved me the trouble.</string>
  <string id="108571">I also saw you free some of them.</string>
  <string id="108573">Yes, of course.</string>
  <string id="108574">You know I did. Get to the point.</string>
  <string id="108576">Gao the Greater&apos;s providing them with flyers as well.</string>
  <string id="108577">I&apos;ve seen similar evidence.</string>
  <string id="108578">If you&apos;d come with me earlier you&apos;d have seen the connection firsthand.</string>
  <string id="108581">It will be good to have you along.</string>
  <string id="108582">How could you help me?</string>
  <string id="108583">I have enough fools surrounding me already.</string>
  <string id="108602">According to the Rat Demon, the Lotus Assassins are using Dragon Powder fueled rockets to clear a way to the ruins of Tien&apos;s Landing. Find the powder somewhere near their camp and then try to clear the way into the ruins.</string>
  <string id="108605">What thing will disrupt them? What do you mean?</string>
  <string id="108606">To infiltrate the Lotus Assassins you need to impress one of the recruiters. The Inquisitors favor recruits who use their brains and demonstrate cunning.</string>
  <string id="108608">Meet the Recruiter</string>
  <string id="108609">According to Scholar Dongow, the Inquisitor recruiter will meet you at the flyer docks outside the Imperial Arena in the Market District.</string>
  <string id="108610">Scholar Dongow didn&apos;t seem all that surprised when you questioned him about the Inquisitors. He agreed to set up a meeting between you and the recruiter, bringing you one step closer to infiltrating the Lotus Assassin ranks.</string>
  <string id="108611">You met with the Inquisitor recruiter, and he presented you with a test. Minister Sheng is about to give a report of the events in Tien&apos;s Landing to Judge Fang, a corrupt but untouchable senior official of the Ministry of Harmony. You must stop Sheng from delivering that report.</string>
  <string id="108612">Disgrace Sheng</string>
  <string id="108613">Hou suggested swapping the &quot;honor gift&quot; Sheng wants to give Fang with highly insulting turtle eggs. Track down Sheng at the Ministry hostel in the Golden Way.</string>
  <string id="108615">You replaced Sheng&apos;s honor gift with the highly insulting turtle eggs. Mortally offended, Fang refused to hear Minister Sheng&apos;s report. Word of what happened in Tien&apos;s Landing will not reach the Ministry of Harmony.</string>
  <string id="108616">Kill Sheng</string>
  <string id="108617">The Black Whirlwind suggested that you kill Minister Sheng. You can find Sheng at the ministry hostel in the Golden Way.</string>
  <string id="108619">You eliminated Minister Sheng, ensuring that his report would not be delivered to Judge Fang. Word of the Lotus Assassins&apos; activities in Tien&apos;s Landing will never reach the Ministry of Harmony.</string>
  <string id="108620">Kill Fang</string>
  <string id="108621">It was suggested that you should kill Fang. Fang can be found in the Heart of the Empire tavern upstairs of the Imperial Arena.</string>
  <string id="108623">With the help of Gentle Breezes, you eliminated Judge Fang, ensuring that he would never hear Sheng&apos;s report. As per the Inquisitor&apos;s wishes, word of the Lotus Assassins&apos; activities in Tien&apos;s Landing will not reach the Ministry of Harmony.</string>
  <string id="108624">Investigate Fang</string>
  <string id="108625">Dawn Star wants to deal with Judge Fang without any bloodshed. Fang can be found in the upstairs of the Imperial Arena.</string>
  <string id="108627">You met Gentle Breezes, a courtesan in Fang&apos;s employ. With her help, you acquired Judge Fang&apos;s Imperial signet ring, his seal of office. This acquisition opens up a new means of preventing Judge Fang from hearing Sheng&apos;s report.</string>
  <string id="108628">Disgrace Sheng</string>
  <string id="108629">Hou suggested swapping the &quot;honor gift&quot; Sheng wants to give Fang with highly insulting turtle eggs. Track down Sheng at the Ministry hostel in the Golden Way.</string>
  <string id="108631">You replaced Sheng&apos;s honor gift with the highly insulting turtle eggs. Mortally offended, Fang refused to hear Minister Sheng&apos;s report. Word of what happened in Tien&apos;s Landing will not reach the Ministry of Harmony.</string>
  <string id="108632">Kill Sheng</string>
  <string id="108633">The Black Whirlwind suggested that you kill Minister Sheng. You can find Sheng at the ministry hostel in the Golden Way.</string>
  <string id="108635">You eliminated Minister Sheng, ensuring that he would not deliver his report to Judge Fang. Word of the Lotus Assassins&apos; activities in Tien&apos;s Landing will never reach the Ministry of Harmony.</string>
  <string id="108636">Disgrace Fang</string>
  <string id="108637">Use Judge Fang&apos;s ring to ensure that he never hears the report. Speak to him in his private stage in the Imperial Arena&apos;s upper level.</string>
  <string id="108639">Using his signet ring, you convinced Judge Fang to step down from his position as the head of the Ministery of Harmony. This should ensure that Minister Sheng&apos;s report about Two Rivers never reaches the Ministry&apos;s collective ears.</string>
  <string id="108640">Report Back to the Inquisitor</string>
  <string id="108641">The Inquisitor will want to hear of your success. Meet him back at the flyer landing site outside the Imperial City.</string>
  <string id="108651" soundid="165750">I remember one time I was hired by two warring clans. They were going to discuss a peace treaty, and they wanted me to make sure things didn&apos;t get out of hand.</string>
  <string id="108652" soundid="165751">A bunch of fights broke out in the first few days, but after I&apos;d killed a few dozen of their clansmen, they settled down. That&apos;s when things got boring.</string>
  <string id="108653" soundid="165752">The leaders took the next *three* days to talk... and talk. If they hadn&apos;t let me dip into their wine stocks, I might have snapped sooner than I did.</string>
  <string id="108654" soundid="165753">Not really... I just helped things progress a little faster. That&apos;s all.</string>
  <string id="108655" soundid="165754">The clan leaders were agreed on peace except for one thing; Jin Lo, a beautiful clanswoman. Both leaders wanted her, and neither would give her up.</string>
  <string id="108656" soundid="165755">After five days it looked like the peace would fall apart. It looked like the two leaders were about to come to blows over Jin Lo, so I stepped in.</string>
  <string id="108657" soundid="165756">It was my job to stop them from fighting, so I cleaved the wench in two and told them to each take a half. Seemed like a good idea at the time.</string>
  <string id="108658" soundid="165757">It was easy. She was small, and my blades *are* extremely sharp. But it didn&apos;t really help, though.</string>
  <string id="108663">I certainly hope you didn&apos;t interfere with their meeting!</string>
  <string id="108665">Why couldn&apos;t they reach a peaceful agreement?</string>
  <string id="108666">I&apos;m surprised you lasted that long.</string>
  <string id="108669">You&apos;re a brute, Whirlwind! How could you do it?</string>
  <string id="108671">What happened then?</string>
  <string id="108672">Ha! Now that&apos;s thinking, Whirlwind.</string>
  <string id="108673" soundid="165772">You have? Well why haven&apos;t you dealt with the man? We can&apos;t have some confidence man running wild in the streets of the Imperial City.</string>
  <string id="108674" soundid="165773">What more do you need? You found him. Lady Rento said she would be in the Heart of the Empire in the Imperial Arena for a while if you really must know more.</string>
  <string id="108675">Mr. B0b</string>
  <string id="108676" soundid="165775">I have no one to spare, which is precisely why I&apos;ve asked you to collect his bounty for me. Surely you don&apos;t want to give up the reward? Take care of him yourself.</string>
  <string id="108678" soundid="165777">Very well. Just eliminate Yukong quickly. The man might have been tipped off to your investigation.</string>
  <string id="108679">I have found Creative Yukong.</string>
  <string id="108680">I need more information before I can deal with him.</string>
  <string id="108682">Could you send your men to arrest him?</string>
  <string id="108683" soundid="190362">He&apos;s no one to worry yourself about. You&apos;re not important enough to catch his gaze, and if you&apos;re smart, you&apos;ll keep it that way.</string>
  <string id="108684">Let me ask something else.</string>
  <string id="108686" soundid="165785">Let me level with you. I don&apos;t lose fights, and I damn well didn&apos;t expect to lose one in this forest. Then you come along and beat me handily.</string>
  <string id="108687" soundid="165786">Before you say it: no, we didn&apos;t fight to the death, and yes, you would have had a harder time had we taken things that far.</string>
  <string id="108688" soundid="165787">That part doesn&apos;t matter. What does is that I could tell I was going to lose. As far as I&apos;m concerned, you&apos;re the kind of person I could stand beside with pride.</string>
  <string id="108689" soundid="165788">Nah. So long as I&apos;m fighting and drinking--preferably at the same time--I think I can let that part where you&apos;d pay me slide.</string>
  <string id="108693">Are you sure following me won&apos;t interfere with your mercenary lifestyle?</string>
  <string id="108695">I&apos;ll kill you!</string>
  <string id="108696">Die like a dog!</string>
  <string id="108697">You&apos;ll pay!</string>
  <string id="108698">I&apos;ll avenge my son!</string>
  <string id="108699">For my son!</string>
  <string id="108700">Die in agony!</string>
  <string id="108705">I&apos;m healed!</string>
  <string id="108706">I&apos;m poisoned!</string>
  <string id="108707">Vengeance!</string>
  <string id="108708" soundid="165808">I should go now, but... I have to ask in case we never meet again. Where did you study?</string>
  <string id="108709" soundid="165809">He must have been a genius. You fight like no one I&apos;ve seen before.</string>
  <string id="108710" soundid="165810">Watching you fight... I just had to ask. Your technique is like no other I&apos;ve seen before.</string>
  <string id="108711" soundid="165811">I&apos;m sorry, I didn&apos;t mean to overstep the bounds of our relationship. I simply had to ask. Your technique is like nothing I&apos;ve seen before.</string>
  <string id="108712" soundid="165812">I&apos;ve studied the techniques of friends and foes alike.</string>
  <string id="108713" soundid="165813">No one I&apos;ve ever met fights like you do. It&apos;s subtle, but your movements bait your foes into seeing an opening that isn&apos;t there. It&apos;s like a clever trap.</string>
  <string id="108714" soundid="165814">I&apos;m sorry. I&apos;m wasting time neither of us can spare. I&apos;ll get ready and pull the lever when you&apos;re near the door. Good luck with whatever brought you to this place.</string>
  <string id="108715" soundid="165815">My question is, since it&apos;s so clear Gao was connected to the Assassins, could their order have similar associations with the whole slave market?</string>
  <string id="108716" soundid="165816">Of course, I didn&apos;t know about the direct connection at the time, but I did find some tenuous links to Gao the Greater.</string>
  <string id="108717" soundid="165817">We&apos;ll have more time to talk once we see the lay of the land in the city.</string>
  <string id="108718">I trained under Master Li of Two Rivers.</string>
  <string id="108719">Why do you ask?</string>
  <string id="108720">At the same place where I learned to mind my own business.</string>
  <string id="108721">I&apos;ve heard this kind of thing before. What&apos;s so strange about how I fight?</string>
  <string id="108722">It must be a quirk of how I was trained.</string>
  <string id="108723">Perhaps you&apos;ve just never seen a properly trained warrior.</string>
  <string id="108727">We&apos;ve already seen the connection between the two.</string>
  <string id="108733" soundid="166673">It is deep and layered. The lives of people spent in the shadow of the Wall... working, dying, never leaving. All their experiences have left marks upon it.</string>
  <string id="108734" soundid="166674">The stones echo with their passing. Sometimes, I can almost hear their voices....</string>
  <string id="108735" soundid="166675">I... I get hints, but nothing that seems useful. They are visions that are possible, or that have possibly been. They are very strong in the city, but they overlap as well.</string>
  <string id="108736" soundid="166676">It has history... ages of history, and much of it is covered in blood and misery. And not all of that is in the distant past. There are dark currents I cannot see clearly.</string>
  <string id="108737" soundid="166677">The threads of fate are woven in the city. Or will be. Does that make sense? I don&apos;t know any more.</string>
  <string id="108738" soundid="166678">Any spirits that can speak clearly are asking for help themselves. The world is upside down. It seems like there is so much more at stake than just our Master&apos;s safety.</string>
  <string id="108739" soundid="166679">I never said that. After all the time we&apos;ve know each other, you should know me better than that. It&apos;s just... so vivid in the city.</string>
  <string id="108740" soundid="166680">If that is what you want. I thought you would be interested in learning what lies beneath the Empire, but I know our troubles must take precedence.</string>
  <string id="108741" soundid="166681">I won&apos;t bring it up again.</string>
  <string id="108744" soundid="165846">They weren&apos;t too happy with my decision. Everyone turned on me. Of course, they all died, but they gave it a good effort.</string>
  <string id="108745" soundid="165847">I don&apos;t know what they were so upset about. Better a quick death by the sword than the prolonged agony of your heart being ripped from your chest and thrown to the dogs.</string>
  <string id="108751">Store Stock:</string>
  <string id="108759">Sell Price:</string>
  <string id="108761">You won&apos;t beat me!</string>
  <string id="108762" soundid="165868">But it doesn&apos;t matter who your Master is. I could take you to the palace, but Death&apos;s Hand controls what my father hears. He must be discredited for you to succeed.</string>
  <string id="108876" soundid="166049"></string>
  <string id="108877" soundid="166050"></string>
  <string id="108878" soundid="166051"></string>
  <string id="108879" soundid="166052"></string>
  <string id="108880" soundid="166053"></string>
  <string id="108887">Outlaw</string>
  <string id="108893">Bandit</string>
  <string id="108922" soundid="166099">Enough! You certainly don&apos;t fight like a minion of Death&apos;s Hand. His Lotus Assassins don&apos;t have your imagination.</string>
  <string id="108923" soundid="177719"></string>
  <string id="108926" soundid="166103">I give you this...</string>
  <string id="108930" soundid="166112">Let&apos;s get out of here. Black Whirlwind can look after himself on the way back to Tien&apos;s Landing.</string>
  <string id="108931" soundid="166113">The bun man and I&apos;ll make our way back to Tien&apos;s Landing. If you need my axes or... whatever he does, just call.</string>
  <string id="108932" soundid="166114">Well, I suppose that&apos;s it.</string>
  <string id="108933" soundid="166115">Chai Ka: I hope the Forest Shadow can rest easy now.</string>
  <string id="108934" soundid="166116">I still don&apos;t understand why you had to eliminate the Forest Shadow, but... I&apos;m sure you have your reasons.</string>
  <string id="108935" soundid="166117">I&apos;m glad we came through here. Those beasts had to be destroyed.</string>
  <string id="108936" soundid="166118">On the upside, those rocks are remarkably good at dealing with cannibals. I think they&apos;re pretty much eliminated. The inn&apos;s certainly quiet.</string>
  <string id="108937" soundid="166119">How many people can claim to the death of a fox spirit and a greater demon in the same day? At least you&apos;re thorough.</string>
  <string id="108938" soundid="166120">Cannibal or not, the Keeper still made a richer offer than the fox. I would have done things differently, but you have your reasons, I&apos;m sure.</string>
  <string id="108950">Phoenix Oil</string>
  <string id="108951">A sturdy clay vessel containing a volatile oil that burns at a very high temperature. The shape of the container allows you to pour the contents into the mixing controls in the golem press room with relative safety.</string>
  <string id="108952">Golem Spirit Shard</string>
  <string id="108953">Normally these shards are made from the concentrated spirit of an unfortunate victim of the Lotus Assassins and are used to power golems. This one is made from the chaotic spirit of an ancient Horselord. It will corrupt the Jade Golem for which it is intended.</string>
  <string id="108963" soundid="166150">A good thing, it&apos;s an uncomfortable topic really. It&apos;s not so much that I need anyone&apos;s charity, as I could just use some help around here.</string>
  <string id="108964" soundid="166151">Things could be worse, I suppose! I could be not working at all. Still I envy folks like Baker Bei. He&apos;s got Seamstress Lan to help him when things get busy, lucky dog.</string>
  <string id="108965">That&apos;s enough about your business.</string>
  <string id="108969">Tell me what you know about the Water Dragon.</string>
  <string id="108970" soundid="180501"></string>
  <string id="108971" soundid="180502"></string>
  <string id="108972" soundid="180503"></string>
  <string id="108973" soundid="180504"></string>
  <string id="108974" soundid="166161"></string>
  <string id="108975" soundid="166162"></string>
  <string id="108976" soundid="166163"></string>
  <string id="108977" soundid="166164"></string>
  <string id="108978" soundid="166165"></string>
  <string id="108979" soundid="166166"></string>
  <string id="108980" soundid="166167"></string>
  <string id="108981" soundid="166168"></string>
  <string id="108982" soundid="166169"></string>
  <string id="108983" soundid="196451"></string>
  <string id="108984" soundid="166171"></string>
  <string id="108985" soundid="196452"></string>
  <string id="108986" soundid="196453"></string>
  <string id="108987" soundid="196454"></string>
  <string id="109002">The Gem is Lost</string>
  <string id="109004" soundid="166191">Like many things in my life, it can be traced back to very bad luck on my part. As I mentioned once before, I was a master of the Drunken Master style.</string>
  <string id="109005" soundid="166192">I was the tournament champion in Phoenix Gate when things spun out of control. My need for wine took its toll on my body. There are long periods I don&apos;t even remember.</string>
  <string id="109006" soundid="166193">After one such period, I came to, having lost most of my clothes and all my money. I was destitute, and without the ability to buy more wine... I couldn&apos;t even fight!</string>
  <string id="109007" soundid="166194">Eventually I found work cleaning out creature cages at the local arena. One day I was approached by a man who remembered seeing me fight. He offered to sponsor me.</string>
  <string id="109008" soundid="166195">Just like that I was back in the ring. After climbing my way back to the top of the tournament, my sponsor told me it was time to fulfill my end of the bargain.</string>
  <string id="109009" soundid="166196">Apparently the agreement stipulated that I must marry his niece. If only I had read the agreement more closely, I could still be shoveling... dirt in the creature cages.</string>
  <string id="109010" soundid="166197">Um... no. That is a painful subject, one that brings back difficult memories. Though not for the reasons you might think.</string>
  <string id="109011" soundid="166198">For four long years my bellicose beauty insisted we try... and try... and try again to have a child. It was a most... distressing time.</string>
  <string id="109012" soundid="166199">I was so afraid of her for the first year that I could not... perform. Her screaming and chastising only made it worse. I overcame that problem, but there were others.</string>
  <string id="109013" soundid="166200">My plump plum of a bride is... a good deal larger than me. I could compare my nightly efforts akin to climbing a mountain, if only it had been that easy.</string>
  <string id="109014" soundid="166201">And there was always the fear that she would... roll. I am a small man, my delicate frame was not meant for such pressures.</string>
  <string id="109015" soundid="166202">I once lost all feeling below the waist, which perhaps was a mercy in itself. Of course, we overcame these obstacles and kept trying for four... long... years.</string>
  <string id="109016" soundid="166203">Once she decided we would not be able to conceive a child, her interests declined, thankfully. If we had succeeded, I would not have survived to see a second.</string>
  <string id="109017">Why did you marry your wife if she&apos;s so difficult?</string>
  <string id="109020">Wine is a dangerous companion.</string>
  <string id="109022">What was it you had to do?</string>
  <string id="109023">Do you have any family Hou? Any children?</string>
  <string id="109026">Um... I see. You don&apos;t have to go on if you don&apos;t want to.</string>
  <string id="109029">Okay! I think I&apos;ve heard enough.</string>
  <string id="109030" soundid="166217"></string>
  <string id="109031" soundid="166218"></string>
  <string id="109032" soundid="166219"></string>
  <string id="109033" soundid="166220"></string>
  <string id="109034" soundid="166221"></string>
  <string id="109035" soundid="166222"></string>
  <string id="109036" soundid="166223"></string>
  <string id="109037" soundid="166224"></string>
  <string id="109038" soundid="166225"></string>
  <string id="109048" soundid="166235">Senior student! Oh, excuse me, Weapon Master. I did not mean to interrupt.</string>
  <string id="109049" soundid="166236">Calm down, student. What has you so flustered?</string>
  <string id="109050" soundid="166237">The bandits! They&apos;ve already been sighted down by the beach, and they&apos;re making their way toward the town!</string>
  <string id="109051" soundid="166238">Master Li hasn&apos;t returned yet with Kia Min. I&apos;m sure he will be back before long, but we must depend on you until he returns.</string>
  <string id="109052" soundid="166239">They&apos;re making their way toward the town now. The few men in the militia weren&apos;t able to stop them.</string>
  <string id="109053" soundid="166240">I...don&apos;t know, but their ship is large. There could be many of them. You have to help, senior student.</string>
  <string id="109054" soundid="166241">If you think that is wise, I will come and do what I can!</string>
  <string id="109055" soundid="166242">I&apos;m sorry, my friend, but Student Si Pat isn&apos;t ready to face real combat. He has only just arrived. He has a big heart, but that is not enough for bandits.</string>
  <string id="109056" soundid="166243">Go to the school. Seal the gates. We will deal with this.</string>
  <string id="109057" soundid="166244">Yes, Dawn Star. I&apos;ll go now. Those gates will stay closed on my watch, you can count on it!</string>
  <string id="109058" soundid="166245">I will run to the school and seal the gates.</string>
  <string id="109059" soundid="166246">Make your way to the beach and teach these bandits a lesson! I know you can.</string>
  <string id="109060" soundid="166247">You&apos;ve done well, lad. Go back to the school now. Your friends have some new weapons they&apos;re dying to try out, I&apos;m sure.</string>
  <string id="109064">Does Master Li know they&apos;re already here?</string>
  <string id="109065">How far have they come?</string>
  <string id="109066">How many are there?</string>
  <string id="109067">Come with me, and we&apos;ll teach these bandits a lesson.</string>
  <string id="109072">Run back to the school and warn everyone else. I&apos;ll deal with these thugs.</string>
  <string id="109076">You were right to console her, even if she didn&apos;t want to hear it.</string>
  <string id="109079">Just walk away. Let her seek your help of her own accord.</string>
  <string id="109081">You should have charged for the service. Give it value, and they will want it.</string>
  <string id="109083" soundid="166293"></string>
  <string id="109084" soundid="166294"></string>
  <string id="109085" soundid="166295"></string>
  <string id="109086" soundid="166296"></string>
  <string id="109087" soundid="166297"></string>
  <string id="109088" soundid="166298"></string>
  <string id="109089">Imperial City Gates</string>
  <string id="109090" soundid="166300"></string>
  <string id="109091" soundid="166301"></string>
  <string id="109092" soundid="166302"></string>
  <string id="109093" soundid="166303"></string>
  <string id="109094" soundid="166304"></string>
  <string id="109095" soundid="166305"></string>
  <string id="109096" soundid="166306"></string>
  <string id="109097" soundid="166307"></string>
  <string id="109098" soundid="166308"></string>
  <string id="109099" soundid="166309"></string>
  <string id="109100" soundid="166310"></string>
  <string id="109101" soundid="166311"></string>
  <string id="109102" soundid="166312"></string>
  <string id="109103" soundid="166313"></string>
  <string id="109104" soundid="166314"></string>
  <string id="109105" soundid="166315"></string>
  <string id="109106" soundid="166316"></string>
  <string id="109132" soundid="166342"></string>
  <string id="109133" soundid="195380">Ya Zhen brought you here. When I destroy him, your soul *will* be lost forever.</string>
  <string id="109134">Your flyer has sustained too much damage to continue fighting.</string>
  <string id="109135">Seek out Lord Yun</string>
  <string id="109136">Silk Fox told you that Lord Yun is camped in the Great Southern Forest, which you can find by leaving through the gateway in the main square of Tien&apos;s Landing.</string>
  <string id="109138" soundid="188294"></string>
  <string id="109139" soundid="188295"></string>
  <string id="109140" soundid="188296"></string>
  <string id="109141" soundid="188297"></string>
  <string id="109142" soundid="188298"></string>
  <string id="109143" soundid="188299"></string>
  <string id="109144" soundid="188300"></string>
  <string id="109145" soundid="188301"></string>
  <string id="109146" soundid="188302"></string>
  <string id="109147" soundid="188303"></string>
  <string id="109149">Kang needs time to set the charges. Some foes will try to eliminate him; deal with them quickly if you hope to win the day.</string>
  <string id="109150" soundid="188305"></string>
</tlk>