<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<tlk language="0">
  <string id="55218">It&apos;s all your father can do to restrain him.</string>
  <string id="55219">You have to get me into the palace.</string>
  <string id="55220">I don&apos;t have time for your games. I have to rescue Master Li.</string>
  <string id="55221">You will have to prove your loyalty to me.</string>
  <string id="55228">You know nothing of strength. You are a pretender.</string>
  <string id="55230">What do I call you? Silk Fox or Princess Sun Lian?</string>
  <string id="55232">I&apos;m looking into it.</string>
  <string id="55241">Sagacious Zu will do what I say when the time comes.</string>
  <string id="55250">I want to ask more about this evidence that you want.</string>
  <string id="55253">I want to talk about you. Why has your servant given me a gift?</string>
  <string id="55257">I want to go back to my other questions.</string>
  <string id="55258">I want to talk to you about the Emperor.</string>
  <string id="55260">When did Death&apos;s Hand join your father&apos;s court?</string>
  <string id="55261">What was your father like before this began?</string>
  <string id="55262">Goodbye for now.</string>
  <string id="55278">If I did that, none of you would be here.</string>
  <string id="55293">We&apos;ll have to hunt him down!</string>
  <string id="55295">He&apos;s harmless. An old coward.</string>
  <string id="55306">Quiet, Silk Fox. He is right to advise caution.</string>
  <string id="55309">I&apos;ll do what I must regardless of you both.</string>
  <string id="55310">I will look into what the Inquisitor wants.</string>
  <string id="55313">I will see what the Executioner wants.</string>
  <string id="55314">On my own time, Princess.</string>
  <string id="55325">Death&apos;s Hand</string>
  <string id="55329" soundid="191493"></string>
  <string id="55330" soundid="191494"></string>
  <string id="55333" soundid="191497"></string>
  <string id="55334" soundid="191498"></string>
  <string id="55376" soundid="158374">[Success] Yes... master needs my muscle. How else will he get second ox in bath?</string>
  <string id="55387">Dutong fled after you exposed his lies about the Imperial Writ. Now you just need to let Old Mother Kwan know the teahouse is hers again.</string>
  <string id="55394">&lt;CUSTOM0&gt;/&lt;CUSTOM1&gt; Synergies Discovered</string>
  <string id="55398">Favorite Harmonic Combo</string>
  <string id="55439">Prefect Jitong</string>
  <string id="55457">Betrayer</string>
  <string id="55658">Scholar Songtao</string>
  <string id="55661">Chandler Ling</string>
  <string id="55664">Zi Bao</string>
  <string id="55667">Cao Zeng</string>
  <string id="55670">Betrayer</string>
  <string id="55676">Koon Kang</string>
  <string id="55693">Silk Fox</string>
  <string id="55698" soundid="127441">You&apos;d think he&apos;d be grateful with them dead and gone. But up he comes the very next day, screaming his head off. He&apos;s driving the customers away.</string>
  <string id="55700" soundid="158375">[Failure] Zhong *is* bad. Zhong not want to hurt other ox.</string>
  <string id="55701">Door</string>
  <string id="55702">Gate</string>
  <string id="55705">Master Radiant&apos;s Room</string>
  <string id="55719" soundid="126228">It is true! You have come! Because of my failure against the Lotus Assassins, I did not think to test you! I waited so long, only to endanger my task over petty pride.</string>
  <string id="55725" soundid="145247">Make your way south across the bridge and on to Tien&apos;s Landing.</string>
  <string id="55729" soundid="73723"></string>
  <string id="55730" soundid="126864">Now hold on here! I deigned to this meeting because I am, by nature, an accommodating gentleman. But I refuse to allow myself to be belittled by you and this... this....</string>
  <string id="55731" soundid="126865">What&apos;s the matter? Can&apos;t find some fancy-pants word to make you feel like a big man?</string>
  <string id="55733" soundid="126866">Thug! Rogue! Ruffian! Strumpet! Harlot!</string>
  <string id="55734" soundid="126867">One more word--just one--and my boys might take exception. It&apos;ll be fun to see how many different words we can come up with for &quot;pain.&quot;</string>
  <string id="55737">Jia</string>
  <string id="55738">ERROR: CANNOT USE FUNCTIONS TO AUTODEFINE GLOBAL VARIABLES</string>
  <string id="55745" soundid="73741">Captain, this woman is here on a personal matter of mine that does not concern you. Do I make myself clear?</string>
  <string id="55747">Dawn Star</string>
  <string id="55754" soundid="78163">Of course. You can count on me.</string>
  <string id="55755" soundid="78164">If any pirates come by and try to take my barge, I&apos;ll show &apos;em how well I use my paddle. Good luck to you in there, and if you need to leave in a hurry, just come running.</string>
  <string id="55759">So many of the pages from this tome are missing that it&apos;s impossible to tell what purpose it served, or what mysteries it held, when it was complete.</string>
  <string id="55780" soundid="73776">I&apos;ll stay here with the flyer. I&apos;ll keep her warm so she&apos;ll be ready when you want to fly us back to town.</string>
  <string id="55781" soundid="73777">But you need my help. The Dragonfly is truly marvelous... but I am sure you&apos;re going to take her into combat. She&apos;ll be injured, and you&apos;ll need someone to fix her.</string>
  <string id="55782" soundid="73778">Your friend there can&apos;t do it. You can&apos;t do it. Only I can fix her, and only I can figure out ways to upgrade her.</string>
  <string id="55783" soundid="73779">And I&apos;m glad to be here, so I can work on my... I mean, your Dragonfly. Should we go now?</string>
  <string id="55784" soundid="73780">Oh, I will! I promise. I just want to take care of my... I mean your Marvelous Dragonfly.</string>
  <string id="55788" soundid="73784">You have good fists for the hitting, but your eyes are not so good at the judging. I&apos;m no ally of Gao or his pirates. I&apos;m just more forced labor.</string>
  <string id="55789" soundid="73785">Do I build flyers? Do I build flyers? Er, yes, have you heard differently? Fantastical things, but misused by Gao and his cohorts. I have saved the best for myself.</string>
  <string id="55790" soundid="73786">If you stage a combat-related accident for Gao, like falling down a flight of punches, I&apos;ll replace the inductor on the Dragonfly and we can fly away! What do you say?</string>
  <string id="55791" soundid="73787">And once I&apos;ve seen her in action, I might even think up ways to improve her. So you really need me along. It&apos;s best for you.</string>
  <string id="55792" soundid="73788">You&apos;re still here... alive... and not in chains. I may have hitched myself to a winner. But Gao the Greater is still here, too. Give him a whack, and I can help you fly.</string>
  <string id="55793" soundid="73789">Questions are good. It means the wheels are turning. But make it quick; I never let asking get in the way of doing.</string>
  <string id="55794" soundid="73790">Is she one of the slaves? The slave breaker led a girl through this morning. I did not hear her name, but no one else has been brought by.</string>
  <string id="55795">Continue</string>
  <string id="55797" soundid="164464">Did I not mention how I dislike repeating myself? Never mind, I will explain it again. First, you must bring me with you if you intend to use the style.</string>
  <string id="55799" soundid="164465">I will throw you bottles of wine, which you must pick up. The effect will wear off, so you must keep picking up the bottles... and remember to keep me safe!</string>
  <string id="55800" soundid="73796">Oh, it&apos;s a long story.. from what I remember. Some experiments went wrong in my old workshop... explosions... a few estates burned down. Some other things happened.</string>
  <string id="55801" soundid="73797">Gao bribed some officials just as I was about to be quartered by five horses. Or would that be &quot;quinted?&quot; Regardless, he brought me here to work for him.</string>
  <string id="55802" soundid="73798">Yes, I suppose so, but if you don&apos;t mind, I&apos;ll stay with the Marvelous Dragonfly, which I have pledged to you. I won&apos;t let it fall into disrepair while you zip about the Empire.</string>
  <string id="55803" soundid="73799">Sure, he rescued me, but only to acquire my inventions and misuse them. You don&apos;t send dozens of flyers against pitiful villages. There&apos;s no elegance to a swarm.</string>
  <string id="55804" soundid="73800">Just like you don&apos;t use explosives inspired by the Great Dragon to carve a treasure chamber. A menial use of power without even a decent crater to show for it.</string>
  <string id="55805" soundid="73801">No, no, but if I offer advice, you should at least consider it. Gao ignores guidance. Listen to me, and I&apos;ll keep the Marvelous Dragonfly the best flyer in the air!</string>
  <string id="55806" soundid="73802">Just next to the launch room. I don&apos;t know how you get in or out, because it is, after all, behind a massive immobile door.</string>
  <string id="55807" soundid="73803">Absolutely. After Gao the Greater is &quot;retired,&quot; you&apos;ll have the use of my Dragonfly, and I&apos;ll come along to keep her repaired... and maybe make a change or two.</string>
  <string id="55808" soundid="73804">Master Li? No, I don&apos;t think so. I&apos;m not so good with names. Or faces. Dates are bad, too. But I remember my own handiwork. Several older flyers stopped here briefly.</string>
  <string id="55809" soundid="73805">They were full of Lotus Assassins, and one *big* Assassin in black armor who seemed to be in charge. Very big. Unpleasant look on his mask.</string>
  <string id="55811" soundid="73807">They had a prisoner with them, or so I heard, and they all seemed nervous about it. The flyers left for the Imperial City soon after. Does that help?</string>
  <string id="55813" soundid="73809">Oh, I would like to put something explody in his food, just to see if it would make him blink, because that one has dead eyes. Like he is missing something.</string>
  <string id="55814" soundid="73810">Sometimes he is here. Sometimes he is not. I don&apos;t know right now which is true. But I know he is dangerous. Very dangerous.</string>
  <string id="55815" soundid="73811">I will restate and reiterate as necessary, but I would like to get back to my tools.</string>
  <string id="55816" soundid="73812">Yes, goodbye. Go and leave me to think.</string>
  <string id="55817">I no longer need that trinket, but that apparently does not stop its misuse.</string>
  <string id="55818">I don&apos;t want your help.</string>
  <string id="55820">Very well. Glad to have you.</string>
  <string id="55822">Fine. Just remember who is in charge!</string>
  <string id="55823">I learned much about the choices I will have. She has placed a great deal of trust in me.</string>
  <string id="55826">Keep your distance, I don&apos;t trust anyone here!</string>
  <string id="55828">You build flyers?</string>
  <string id="55832">I have some questions.</string>
  <string id="55833">Have you seen a young woman named Fuyao?</string>
  <string id="55835" soundid="164466">The effect wears off quickly, but I will make sure you don&apos;t run out of wine, as long as you keep the enemies off of me. Now... watch my technique.</string>
  <string id="55836" soundid="164467">Were you drunk when I told you last time? [sigh] If you wish to use Drunken Master, bring me with you. I will throw you bottles of wine, which you must pick up.</string>
  <string id="55838" soundid="164468">The effect of the wine wears off, but I will keep a continuous supply of wine flowing, as long as you keep the enemies away from me.</string>
  <string id="55839">How did you come to be here?</string>
  <string id="55841">When I am done here, you will be free.</string>
  <string id="55842">Gao rescued you, but you want me to kill him?</string>
  <string id="55844">If I use your inventions wrong, you&apos;ll turn on me?</string>
  <string id="55845">You mentioned Gao&apos;s treasure chamber?</string>
  <string id="55846">And now you&apos;ll make things for me.</string>
  <string id="55847">Have you seen an old man named Master Li?</string>
  <string id="55849" soundid="158333"></string>
  <string id="55852">What do you know about Assassin Lim?</string>
  <string id="55854">I have other questions.</string>
  <string id="55855">Goodbye.</string>
  <string id="56599" soundid="163922">In my years in this Empire I have been a wanted criminal, a bandit, a murderer, and worse.</string>
  <string id="56601">Defend the Culture of the Jade Empire</string>
  <string id="56602">The Outlander seems convinced that your culture is lacking. It falls to you to prove him wrong.</string>
  <string id="56603">It&apos;s easy to see why the Minister of Culture wants the Outlander removed from the Scholars&apos; Garden. The man refuses to leave, and he seems determined to &quot;reform&quot; your culture, even if it takes him an eternity.</string>
  <string id="56605">Prepare for the Debate</string>
  <string id="56606">Each of the judges reacts to a particular type of debate. If you can identify what type of argument will sway their mood, you may be able to end the debate quickly. When you are ready to begin, speak to the Outlander again.</string>
  <string id="56607">In an effort to remove him from the Scholars&apos; Garden, you have challenged the Outlander to a debate. Five notables from the Scholars&apos; Garden will judge your arguments.</string>
  <string id="56609">Won debate</string>
  <string id="56612">You have countered the arguments of the Outlander through careful debate, but it will take more than skilled debate to remove him from the Scholars&apos; Garden. He has challenged you to personal combat.</string>
  <string id="56613">Lost Debate</string>
  <string id="56616">Your debating skills were not strong enough to shut down the Outlander&apos;s arguments. Perhaps a display of martial skill will change his mind about remaining in the Scholars&apos; Garden.</string>
  <string id="56617">Face the Outlander in Single Combat</string>
  <string id="56618">Speak to the Outlander when you are ready to challenge him.</string>
  <string id="56619">Ogre</string>
  <string id="56717" soundid="113297">What do you want? Do I know you?</string>
  <string id="56718" soundid="113298">Really? Lots of people know me... so what?</string>
  <string id="56720" soundid="113299">Really? I doubt you know anyone who would interest me in the least.</string>
  <string id="56721" soundid="113300">You&apos;d better have the muscle to back that up, or you&apos;ll be lying in your own blood soon enough!</string>
  <string id="56722" soundid="151761">I could make her an outfit that would disguise her as a bird... a big bird, mind you... but it might look less suspicious.</string>
  <string id="56723" soundid="151762">Those Assassins will be tougher than Gao&apos;s men. Be careful, I need you to do more test flights with my Marvelous Dragonfly.</string>
  <string id="56724" soundid="113303">Leave me alone! I have nothing to say to you, so why don&apos;t you just keep moving.</string>
  <string id="56725" soundid="113304">[Success] Yes... yes that is. More than I&apos;d see in month.</string>
  <string id="56726" soundid="169822">A lot of what we&apos;re doing here reminds me of my marriage. I&apos;ll tell you about it someday, if you have time.</string>
  <string id="56727" soundid="151764">Yes, yes... what can I do for you? Busy busy. No time for chatty chatty.</string>
  <string id="56728" soundid="151765">I&apos;ve given some thought to the strange device that I was inspired to construct. I&apos;m not sure what purpose it has yet, but it appears to be working... I think.</string>
  <string id="56729" soundid="151766">Just a few tweaks... hmm... tight fit... not sure how that will affect things. What&apos;s that... hmph... don&apos;t remember seeing that before. Just get this last....</string>
  <string id="56746">Suc 1</string>
  <string id="56779">Style Description</string>
  <string id="56816" soundid="151767">There we go. It&apos;s ready. Now we can finally find out just what it does. After I name it, of course. Nothing works right until you name it. How about... the Confoundable Minutia?</string>
  <string id="56817" soundid="151768"></string>
  <string id="56818" soundid="151769">What! Impossible... I fixed it... I checked everything... it should work. Unless... no, I did that....</string>
  <string id="56822" soundid="151770"></string>
  <string id="56823" soundid="113314">Go away. I don&apos;t want any.</string>
  <string id="56824" soundid="113315">This is my spot and I&apos;m not moving. Go get your own place.</string>
  <string id="56825" soundid="113316">Leave me alone.</string>
  <string id="56826" soundid="113317">Go find someone else to bother.</string>
  <string id="56827">No, but I know you, Zi Bao.</string>
  <string id="56828">It&apos;s who I know that matters.</string>
  <string id="56829">Watch your tongue, Zi Bao, or I&apos;ll cut it out.</string>
  <string id="56830">[Lie] Ling told me you&apos;d take me to see the slave traders.</string>
  <string id="56831">I need you to take me to see the slave traders.</string>
  <string id="56832">Take me to see the slave traders or I&apos;ll have you arrested.</string>
  <string id="56833">[Charm] How about 1,000 silver? That&apos;s a lot of money, Zi Bao.</string>
  <string id="56841">Return to Style List</string>
  <string id="56842">Lotus Assassin</string>
  <string id="56856" soundid="75395">The moment I saw you, I knew you were the fearless sort. I hoped you would offer to help. It shames me to need the help of a stranger.</string>
  <string id="56870">Shining Tusk</string>
  <string id="56881">The village of Two Rivers has been destroyed, and all who lived there are dead. The bandits behind the attack may have intended to kill you as well. How will you respond to this threat? Options have been presented to persuade local officials to join your cause, challenge the group openly, or infiltrate them on your own.</string>
  <string id="56882">The Lonely Road</string>
  <string id="56883">You have followed a trail of corrupt officials to the Golden Delta province, looking for the person that arranged the attack on your village. If you can identify him, you have the power to exact justice. He does appear to have a deep purse, however, and the option of seeking a profit from this tragedy is there if you wish.</string>
  <string id="56884">The Road Divided</string>
  <string id="56885">Someone has dared to circumvent the Emperor&apos;s rule. Working with a string of evil officials, they have corrupted the heart of the Empire. Reveal these traitors and determine where the true danger lies.</string>
  <string id="56886">Revelations</string>
  <string id="56887">Lord Lao has promised to teach you a martial style known only to the Brothers of the Northern Wind. He has asked that you find his six lost huntsmen and retrieve the pieces of his ceremonial blade broken in the Borderland Peasant Uprising. You have discovered that you may not need Lord Lao to retrieve his blade. You will have to decide if such a prize is worth betraying this trusting master.</string>
  <string id="56888">Lord Lao&apos;s Missing Legion</string>
  <string id="56889">The Black Whirlwind is the last member of the legion unaccounted for. Investigate the tales of a giant drunken warthog with axes for hands terrorizing travelers in the south. That was his mother&apos;s pet name for him.</string>
  <string id="56918" soundid="166134">That was an impressive display, acolyte. I have never seen Shin&apos;s Attendants so handily dismissed.</string>
  <string id="56967" soundid="156564">Dirge belongs to the master I serve. His strength grows; he feeds on the taint of this place. And when he is ready, he will unleash us on the mortal world!</string>
  <string id="57009" soundid="144835">Very good, acolyte, my faith in you was not misplaced. I will take that... mishap with the suspended golem as a reminder that I must always adequately reward you.</string>
  <string id="57010">Mini-game: Hit Percentage: &lt;CUSTOM0&gt;</string>
  <string id="57011">Mini-game: Success Percentage: &lt;CUSTOM0&gt;</string>
  <string id="57012">Mini-game: High Score: &lt;CUSTOM0&gt;</string>
  <string id="57020">Find a Man for Ai Ling</string>
  <string id="57021">Find an eligible bachelor in town and convince him to meet with Ai Ling.</string>
  <string id="57040">Suc 2</string>
  <string id="57068" soundid="151771">Eh, hello. I suppose the Marvelous Dragonfly is ready. We don&apos;t have to worry about landing too many more times.</string>
  <string id="57069" soundid="151772">Just make sure you are done talking to everyone. I lost the interior baffling, so you won&apos;t be able to hear a thing once we are in the air.</string>
  <string id="57070" soundid="151773">Oh, I think they know you are ready. Every eye is on you, across the whole Empire, I think.</string>
  <string id="57071" soundid="151774">We&apos;ll have to see if you are worthy of that gaze, hmm? All right, everyone in!</string>
  <string id="57072" soundid="151775">Oh no, I tend to confuse things. Yes, I know I do. This is too important for my mutterings.</string>
  <string id="57073" soundid="151776">Er, besides, the decisions that are coming... they are beyond me. You are deciding the fate of an empire.</string>
  <string id="57074" soundid="151777">My mistakes result in the occasional crater. How big a hole might you be digging, hmm?</string>
  <string id="57075" soundid="151778">Ah, whatever you wish. It&apos;s just a few more minutes of bolt-tightening to me.</string>
  <string id="57077" soundid="124211">Ho ho! Heh.</string>
  <string id="57078" soundid="151779"></string>
  <string id="57079" soundid="151780">Well, here we are. I&apos;d hoped I wouldn&apos;t have to use this entrance again.</string>
  <string id="57080" soundid="151781">Keep any pets properly collared. We wouldn&apos;t want anyone wandering off.</string>
  <string id="57084" soundid="127013">You promised to close the dam so I could take my ship and my men and leave this place. Don&apos;t you remember?</string>
  <string id="57110" soundid="124213">Master Lotus Assassin, have pity on us.</string>
  <string id="57111">Who made the extractor?</string>
  <string id="57114" soundid="140472">[The air is noticeably colder near the extractor. The machine is motionless, as if waiting silently for the next victim or corpse to be placed within.]</string>
  <string id="57116" soundid="140473">[The handle is worn smooth from use. Zu said to descend to the lowest mine to learn how to use the machine to create a shard that disrupts the Lotus Assassin plan.]</string>
  <string id="57117" soundid="140474"></string>
  <string id="57134">My style is ineffective.</string>
  <string id="57135">I will show you!</string>
  <string id="57136" soundid="113356">I&apos;m sure you could beat me black and blue, but I&apos;m so drunk, I&apos;ll barely feel it. Anyway, I promised the town I&apos;d close the dam. Gotta show &apos;em I&apos;m not some useless drunk! </string>
  <string id="57137" soundid="113357">(Sigh) I guess this means I don&apos;t have any real reason not to take you to the pirates now. I said I&apos;d take you, and I&apos;m a man of my word... mostly. </string>
  <string id="57138" soundid="113358">Good, good. I&apos;ve got lots to do before we go. Check the barge, check our supplies, sample the wine. You never want to travel with bad wine.</string>
  <string id="57139">You&apos;re not as stupid as you look.</string>
  <string id="57146">I have questions about the town.</string>
  <string id="57148" soundid="118654">The planting season was almost over, so I figured I might as well travel with him. It has been interesting.</string>
  <string id="57149" soundid="118655">His title mystifies me, except for the &quot;Magnificent Bastard&quot; portion. I&apos;m fairly certain I know how he came by that part.</string>
  <string id="57161" soundid="75398">It really isn&apos;t important. Just get that key from him, and close the Great Dam.</string>
  <string id="57163" soundid="75400">No... wait. Please. There&apos;s something different about you. You&apos;re not some peasant or simple villager like most in this town. I... I need your help.</string>
  <string id="57165" soundid="75402">I&apos;m a proud man. It&apos;s not easy to ask for another&apos;s help. But I have little choice now. I need someone to close the Great Dam for me.</string>
  <string id="57166" soundid="75403">Please, I offer a large reward for little effort! Just get the key to the ruins from Minister Sheng and close the dam so my ship and my men can leave this accursed town forever.</string>
  <string id="57169">Double Ham Style!</string>
  <string id="57170" soundid="127442">Well, that makes things easier on me, for sure. Now I can start selling those old plots again! Next time I&apos;ll just throw the bones in the river and be done with it.</string>
  <string id="57171" soundid="150708">Ha! Scourge of the South! Is that the best they could come up with? They missed your looks, too. Ha ha ha!</string>
  <string id="57172" soundid="150709">Scourge of the South... that&apos;s got a certain ring to it. Too bad they didn&apos;t get your appearance right... or perhaps it&apos;s good they didn&apos;t.</string>
  <string id="57173">He is gone.</string>
  <string id="57175" soundid="127447">Well, see if you can&apos;t do something about him quick. I&apos;m too spooked to go in that area anymore. I need those plots to... eh-heh, &quot;honor&quot; some ancestors. Eh-heheh.</string>
  <string id="57182">I&apos;ll close the dam for you.</string>
  <string id="57184">How do I get to the dam?</string>
  <string id="57187">Solve Puzzle</string>
  <string id="57188">How much would you pay to have the Great Dam closed?</string>
  <string id="57190" soundid="127448">He was buried by his wife a short while ago. I don&apos;t know what killed him. The family wouldn&apos;t talk about it. But his face was bloated like you wouldn&apos;t believe, eh-heh.</string>
  <string id="57191" soundid="127449">His wife&apos;s still around, though. She won&apos;t visit since he came up. Every time she gets near, he starts screaming incoherently, and he&apos;s out of it for days. Nothing near him is safe.</string>
  <string id="57192">Gao&apos;s Mercenary</string>
  <string id="57193">Who are you again?</string>
  <string id="57194" soundid="127451">Good riddance! Hells, it was probably his old lady that offed him in the first place, and for good reason, too, I bet. Eh-heh, it&apos;s all just business to me, you understand. </string>
  <string id="57195" soundid="127452">Well, he&apos;s one of the ones I&apos;ve had the most problems with. He&apos;s on a valuable plot, and with all the new, eh-heh, &quot;ancestors&quot; becoming venerated, land is at a premium.</string>
  <string id="57196" soundid="127453">See if you can&apos;t get him cleared up soon, will you? Maybe I&apos;ll pay a little extra for that one.</string>
  <string id="57201">Press the button to which you would like to assign the action.</string>
  <string id="57212" soundid="93715"></string>
  <string id="57250">Lord Lao&apos;s Missing Legion</string>
  <string id="57269">Imperial Soldier</string>
  <string id="57272">Imperial Soldier</string>
  <string id="57279">Lotus Assassin</string>
  <string id="57282">Horse Demon</string>
  <string id="57306" soundid="75627">Sorry, young one. I don&apos;t have time to chat. Master Dutong&apos;s got me busy steeping the tea, and he *is* the boss. You can&apos;t argue with an Imperial Writ.</string>
  <string id="57307" soundid="75628">My hero returns! Remember, you&apos;re always welcome in this teahouse as long as Old Mother Kwan is around.</string>
  <string id="57312">Clay Golem</string>
  <string id="57485">Sir Roderick has continued to malign the ways of the Jade Empire. Engage him in a duel of words to show him the error of his beliefs or get rid of him quietly. Either way he must be silenced.</string>
  <string id="57491" soundid="135350">So it&apos;s true... Master Li really is the Emperor&apos;s brother! I wish... I wish I had known.</string>
  <string id="57496" soundid="135354">Even a god is not invincible. They have their place, and it can be challenged. Sun Li could not stop the slaughter of the Spirit Monks. He fled the battle with you in his arms.</string>
  <string id="57502" soundid="177262">We should go. The task ahead will be difficult and I fear the effect it will have on us.</string>
  <string id="57503" soundid="75843">I... I served him in the Imperial Army. But right now I have things you must know, so set aside your questions and listen carefully.</string>
  <string id="57504" soundid="75844">Be calm. You can be about your other tasks soon enough. For now, I have important things to tell you, so listen well. </string>
  <string id="57505" soundid="75845">Sun Li asked me to seek a piece of a special amulet he wanted you, his prize pupil, to have. It was broken apart and scattered when the Spirit Monk temple fell.</string>
  <string id="57507" soundid="75847">He intended to--and I assume he did--give the main piece to you. Rumor placed a smaller part with a fleeing apprentice monk, but it had been some years, and the trail was cold.</string>
  <string id="57508" soundid="177263">Your perception of that time is different than mine. I thought we were very lucky to have the training we did. I still do.</string>
  <string id="57511" soundid="75851">I eventually learned the monk had fled to old Tien&apos;s Landing. He was there a year or so, but died of lingering injuries and was buried with his possessions unsorted.</string>
  <string id="57512" soundid="75852">It was rushed at the time because the new dam was due to close, and old Tien&apos;s would become a watery tomb. The amulet was beyond reach, so I came here and waited.</string>
  <string id="57513" soundid="75853">Yes, Sun Li intended you to find it; I was to tell you about it if anything happened to him. It was the last order he gave me, and I have waited years to fulfill my duty.</string>
  <string id="57514" soundid="75854">Sun Li is a great man, driven by greater goals and ideals. Sometimes his gaze is lifted so high that he does not see what is right in front of him.</string>
  <string id="57515" soundid="75855">We who serve him are sometimes forgotten; left to toil in obscurity until the time to act is thrust upon us. So it was with me, waiting for you.</string>
  <string id="57517" soundid="75857">I only know that I had to find the the piece I was tracking. I did so; it is in the ruins. You must find it before the Lotus Assassins do. You will need it to help your Master.</string>
  <string id="57528" soundid="75868">The gates leading to the ruins are locked, but Minister Sheng can give you the key. You can find him in the town square, the highest point in Tien&apos;s Landing.</string>
  <string id="57530" soundid="75870">I suspect the Minister is eager to have someone investigate the opening of the Great Dam. You can use this as an excuse to get the key and explore the ruins.</string>
  <string id="57532" soundid="75872">I am unimportant, but I promised I would aid you as best I can, so ask your questions.</string>
  <string id="57533" soundid="75873">There is little to tell. I served him years ago in the Imperial Army. I was a tracker and a soldier. I was not at Dirge when it fell, but I heard the tale of Sun Li&apos;s death.</string>
  <string id="57534" soundid="75874">I revere him as a teacher and... I revere him. Even when he ordered me to distant lands, my loyalty never wavered. But I am tired. I long for an end to my service.</string>
  <string id="57535" soundid="75875">That would be a question for him, wouldn&apos;t it? I can only say that Sun Li devoted his life to raising you to one day right the wrongs in the Jade Empire.</string>
  <string id="57536" soundid="75876">If he wanted to keep some small part of his own life and thoughts for himself, who are you to question that? Everyone must have their private side.</string>
  <string id="57537" soundid="75877">I would be honored, but as a student of Sun Li you have probably learned much of it simply by watching me. Naming it will bring it together in your mind.</string>
  <string id="57541" soundid="75881">I cannot. I have done my part. I have given Sun Li my loyalty and... devotion. Now I am empty; I have nothing left. I see an end to my long service. I welcome it.</string>
  <string id="57550" soundid="75890">Remember: Go to the ruins and claim the amulet before the Lotus Assassins do. You will need it to survive the trials that lie ahead.</string>
  <string id="57551" soundid="75891">And so I step away. I have no further part to play, and I am glad for it. Perhaps history will clear my doubts and show my time was worthwhile. I wish you luck.</string>
  <string id="57556" soundid="75896">Back again? Have you been to the ruins yet? Time is running short. If you don&apos;t find the missing piece of your amulet, the Lotus Assassins will.</string>
  <string id="57566">The Outlander&apos;s Insult</string>
  <string id="57572" soundid="135359">Li&apos;s wife was with child, his daughter born in the Imperial Palace while he was at Dirge. He never saw her. Within weeks of the siege, the Emperor had Li&apos;s family... executed.</string>
  <string id="57573" soundid="135360">Executed? Murdered! The Lotus Assassins were to cut them down... a mother and newborn child. I have no doubt that order came from Death&apos;s Hand himself!</string>
  <string id="57577" soundid="135362">He probably didn&apos;t think his family would be harmed, but even had he known, he might still have saved you. Li knows you have a destiny to fulfill. You&apos;re the last of your kind.</string>
  <string id="57578" soundid="177264">Fine. We won&apos;t talk. I&apos;m sorry I&apos;m not dealing with all of this as efficiently as you want. Let&apos;s just get back to what we need to do.</string>
  <string id="57582" soundid="135365">The natural order has been disrupted. There is much to say, but this is not the place for it. Meet me in the Teahouse. I&apos;ll tell you more about Sun Li... and how to rescue him.</string>
  <string id="57583" soundid="135366">You can trust Hui, so I don&apos;t think there&apos;s any reason for me to stick around. I&apos;ll be back at the camp if you need me.</string>
  <string id="57585" soundid="135367"></string>
  <string id="57586">How do you know Master Li, again?</string>
  <string id="57588" soundid="180500"></string>
  <string id="57589">Try to speed this up. I have other things to do.</string>
  <string id="57595">So you searched for the rest of the amulet?</string>
  <string id="57597">Could we speed this up a little bit. Where is the monk?</string>
  <string id="57601">How do they know about it?</string>
  <string id="57602">You sound regretful.</string>
  <string id="57605">Can you tell me more about the amulet?</string>
  <string id="57616">How do I get to the ruins?</string>
  <string id="57620">I have questions about you.</string>
  <string id="57621">Tell me about you and Master Li.</string>
  <string id="57623">Why has Master Li never mentioned you?</string>
  <string id="57625">Can you tell me anything else about the Spirit Thief style?</string>
  <string id="57629">I could use another fighter. Come with me.</string>
  <string id="57636">I have a lot ahead of me. I should go.</string>
  <string id="57650">Flawless Scholar Gem</string>
  <string id="57651">Body +6

This gem is of superior quality and provides an excellent bonus to your Body. </string>
  <string id="57652">Body +10

This flawless gem provides a great bonus to your Body. </string>
  <string id="57653">Spirit +6

This gem is of superior quality and provides an excellent bonus to your Spirit. </string>
  <string id="57654">Spirit +10

This flawless gem provides a powerful bonus to your Spirit. </string>
  <string id="57655">Mind +6

This gem is of superior quality and provides an excellent bonus to your Mind. </string>
  <string id="57656">Mind +10

This flawless gem provides a powerful bonus to your Mind. </string>
  <string id="57657">+ 10 Fire Resistance Gem</string>
  <string id="57658">+ 10 Ice Resistance Gem</string>
  <string id="57659">+ 10 Wood Resistance Gem</string>
  <string id="57660">+10 Earth Resistance Gem</string>
  <string id="57661">+10 Metal Resistance Gem</string>
  <string id="57662">+5 All Resistances Gem</string>
  <string id="57663">+10 All Resistances Gem</string>
  <string id="57664">[DESC]+ 10 Fire Resistance Gem</string>
  <string id="57665">[DESC]+ 10 Ice Resistance Gem</string>
  <string id="57666">[DESC]+ 10 Wood Resistance Gem</string>
  <string id="57667">[DESC]+10 Earth Resistance Gem</string>
  <string id="57668">[DESC]+10 Metal Resistance Gem</string>
  <string id="57669">[DESC]+5 All Resistances Gem</string>
  <string id="57670">[DESC]+10 All Resistances Gem</string>
  <string id="57674">Slot not used.</string>
  <string id="57806" soundid="76157">You should speak to Dutong. See if you can get him to confess to cheating Old Mother Kwan out of this teahouse.</string>
  <string id="57809">Boy</string>
  <string id="57810">Auto</string>
  <string id="57821">**TEMP** Description for Double Hammers</string>
  <string id="57822">Unique Style, Drains Chi from enemies
Does direct damage in Chi Strike mode. Spirit Thief&apos;s Power Attack inflicts damage but does not drain Chi in Chi Strike mode. 

Those most adept at manipulating chi find that even the spiritual energy of others is within their grasp. The strikes and forms of the Spirit Thief style enable practitioners to tap an enemy&apos;s vital energies and refill their own reserves. While the techniques of this style do no physical damage to its victims without being charged with the user&apos;s chi, those who face a Spirit Thief master find themselves without the resolve to put their hearts into the fight.</string>
  <string id="57823">An ancient design, the spear is a length of wood topped by a sharpened head of steel. Spears have a longer reach than most martial weapons, and a master can make use of this to keep an opponent at a distance, thereby neutralizing their attacks. The spear does not offer great defense in close quarters, but a master can often end a fight long before an opponent slips inside his reach.</string>
  <string id="57824">Spear</string>
  <string id="57827" soundid="116204">Thank you for all your help, mistress. I could not have expected more from my own sister. Your spirit is as kind and generous as that of the Emperor himself.</string>
  <string id="57828" soundid="116205">But I have nothing else to give. Please, it is a very generous dowry for a simple villager like myself. Take it... I have nothing else.</string>
  <string id="57829" soundid="116206">Don&apos;t try to defend him! He used me! He lied to me! At least I found out what he was really like before I married him, thanks to you. Here, take this. It&apos;s my dowry.</string>
  <string id="57830" soundid="116207">You&apos;re right. I am better off without him. I&apos;m... I&apos;m glad you found this out before I married him. Thank you. Here... take my dowry. I won&apos;t need it now.</string>
  <string id="57831" soundid="116208">Of course. I don&apos;t mean to sound ungrateful. I&apos;m honored that one as great as you offered to help me at all. Thank you.</string>
  <string id="57832" soundid="116209">But there isn&apos;t! My poor Bei has done nothing to these men. They attack him for no reason at all! Please, you have to help him. I beg you!</string>
  <string id="57833" soundid="116210">Please, as soon as you find out anything about this woman, let me know. It&apos;s... it&apos;s not like Bei to keep secrets from me.</string>
  <string id="57834" soundid="116211">Thank you for all you&apos;ve done. Here, take this as a sign of my appreciation: It&apos;s my dowry. I want you to have it.</string>
  <string id="57835" soundid="116212">You mean... you did this for me, and you expect nothing in return? I... I can&apos;t believe it!</string>
  <string id="57850">I&apos;ll go to the dam right now.</string>
  <string id="57857">Double Sabers</string>
  <string id="57865">Henpecked Hou</string>
  <string id="57868">Death&apos;s Hand</string>
  <string id="57871" soundid="141954"></string>
  <string id="57872" soundid="81267">Master Li cares deeply for all of us, despite his stern demeanor. Look how he came to my rescue when the bandit&apos;s spell left me wounded.</string>
  <string id="57873" soundid="81268">You told me that before. I suggested that you look for some other meaning behind it, but I don&apos;t presume to speak for Master Li.</string>
  <string id="57874" soundid="81269">I don&apos;t think that is possible. Are you sure you understood what he meant? Much of what he says is disguised in layers.</string>
  <string id="57875" soundid="81270">As he carried me back to the school, he told me that I was a rough diamond, and that this injury was the first cut of many.</string>
  <string id="57876" soundid="81271">Exactly. I could have let this shatter me, but instead I have learned a great deal about myself.</string>
  <string id="57877" soundid="81272">Perhaps you need to look for that kind of meaning in what he said.</string>
  <string id="57878" soundid="81273">I don&apos;t like your interpretation, and I still find comfort in his words.</string>
  <string id="57879" soundid="81274">I can only feed you answers that are common knowledge. Some of the other students might help you more.</string>
  <string id="57880" soundid="81275">Wen is the most widely traveled here, and Lin hasn&apos;t been able to stop talking about ghosts, which is a nice change from her talking about everyone else.</string>
  <string id="57881" soundid="81276">Yes. Goodbye.</string>
  <string id="57909" soundid="81277">Take care. Oh, and if you happen to find anything that might help this wound after you talk to Old Ming, let me know!</string>
  <string id="57910" soundid="81278">Good luck in your search.</string>
  <string id="57911" soundid="141955">Keep going! There are others in the school!</string>
  <string id="57912" soundid="81280">Goodbye.</string>
  <string id="57924" soundid="119160">Did you like it? I thought you might want a little assistance. Consider it a small token of my favor.</string>
  <string id="57926" soundid="142167">I hear your friend has gone missing. So sad. Very sad indeed.</string>
  <string id="57927" soundid="142168">More importantly, my stock has arrived. Braving roads dangerous with ghosts and bandits, a caravan runner just dropped off a load of supplies.</string>
  <string id="57928" soundid="142169">Those thugs! I can&apos;t believe they&apos;ve come so far. They&apos;re coming up from the beach.</string>
  <string id="57929" soundid="142170">Go stop them now. It&apos;s your duty as one of Master Li&apos;s students!</string>
  <string id="57930" soundid="142171">Those bandits will think twice before threatening a town protected by the likes of Master Li. They were fools to even come here.</string>
  <string id="57931" soundid="142172">The only shame is that their ship sunk. Think what we could have done with their plunder. Ahh well, that&apos;s another opportunity lost.</string>
  <string id="57932" soundid="142173">Bandits coming here? There&apos;s precious little to steal, but I suppose they suspect we&apos;re a sleepy town with no protection.</string>
  <string id="57933" soundid="142174">Luckily, we have you fine students and your master to look over us. It does my heart good to see that you&apos;re here already, prepared to defend the town.</string>
  <string id="57934" soundid="142175">A potential customer is a welcome customer!</string>
  <string id="57935" soundid="119161">I thank you for your courtesy. A woman always likes to hear when her gifts are appreciated.</string>
  <string id="57936" soundid="142176">Oh yes, I had heard that someone was injured and immediately saw the opportunity to make vast sums of... no, to make a difference, that&apos;s it.</string>
  <string id="57937" soundid="142177">Anyway, I&apos;ve checked my stocks and I only have enough ingredients to make one dose of the salve for a poultice.</string>
  <string id="57938" soundid="142178">I&apos;m not sure how much good it will do by itself. Might take a bit of the sting away.</string>
  <string id="57939" soundid="142179">Expensive stuff that. Very pricey. Hard to acquire, too. Would certainly help her wound, but I know something just as good.</string>
  <string id="57940" soundid="142180">Get her some bearded tongue grass and she&apos;ll feel better. It won&apos;t hasten the healing any, so she&apos;ll have to take it easy, but it will deaden the pain.</string>
  <string id="57941" soundid="142181">That&apos;s good stuff, and readily available to me... and you, of course, heh. Yes, it will deaden her pain perfectly.</string>
  <string id="57942" soundid="142182">She should avoid straining herself, of course. Bearded tongue grass won&apos;t heal like red silk grass does, but why spend all that money just to speed healing?</string>
  <string id="57943" soundid="142183">If you think you can justify such opulence to heal something that time would take care of, who am I to argue? I&apos;ll just need your payment to prepare the poultice.</string>
  <string id="57944" soundid="142184">Business has been slow! What am I supposed to do? Starve?</string>
  <string id="58130" soundid="123244">Good... you came. Wait here. There&apos;s a small hole in the wall... just around the side. I&apos;ll sneak in and open the door from the inside.</string>
  <string id="58131" soundid="123245">There. The ghosts are just beyond the door. They haven&apos;t noticed me... yet.</string>
  <string id="58135" soundid="123246">I was just thinking the same thing. I don&apos;t want to get any closer to those... things.</string>
  <string id="58138" soundid="123247">I think I&apos;ll just wait here for you to clear the ghosts.</string>
  <string id="58163">Kang provided you with a windmap to an unknown location. Kang seems to have no recollection of where the map could lead. Following the map should help you learn more about Kang&apos;s mysterious past.</string>
  <string id="58166">The Burning Town</string>
  <string id="58167" soundid="114434">A human here? You are not of the family! You should not be here.</string>
  <string id="58168" soundid="137121">The Lotus Assassins are very careful about such maps. They would like for the skies to be the sole property of their order and the Imperial Army.</string>
  <string id="58170" soundid="114437">The Forest Shadow is not sure of you, human, but you have earned the right to pass safely to her.</string>
  <string id="58171" soundid="114438">Beware of more demons. They grow more aggressive as our mistress weakens from the disease in the trees.</string>
  <string id="58173" soundid="114440">The sailors have all left, thanks to you! They were some of my best customers!</string>
  <string id="58265" soundid="114441">Though I suppose there will be other customers to make up for their loss now that the dam is closed. Maybe this dive will finally start to turn a profit.</string>
  <string id="58266" soundid="114442">No, no, no! You can&apos;t put all this on me anymore. You&apos;re part of this now. You and Yanru were both paid off fair and square.</string>
  <string id="58275" soundid="114443">Remember: If you tell anyone the truth, both I and Steeper Yanru will deny it. Two against one. Nobody will believe you. </string>
  <string id="58276" soundid="114444">Our business is done, so please go bother someone else. I have to get back to running *my* teahouse.</string>
  <string id="58277" soundid="114445">I thought you might try to squeeze me for a little more. As a fellow swindler, I admire the effort. But you&apos;re forgetting that we two aren&apos;t the only ones involved.</string>
  <string id="58278" soundid="114446">And I want to keep it that way. There are enough people involved already: you, me, Steeper Yanru. No sense letting anyone else in on our little secret.</string>
  <string id="58279" soundid="114447">The... the writ? Why ish you ashking about that? You want to shteal it? You want to shteal my teahoushe?</string>
  <string id="58280" soundid="114448">I&apos;m watching you! Shneaky thief. Try to shteal my teahoushe? Go on. Get out of here.</string>
  <string id="58281" soundid="114449">[Success] Yesh, you&apos;re a good friend. I can trusht you. You&apos;ll undershtand!</string>
  <string id="58282" soundid="114450">[Success] Yesh, that&apos;sh what I need to do. Confessh my shins. Then I feel better!</string>
  <string id="58283" soundid="114451">[Success] Yesh, I&apos;m a worm! A filthy shnake. I&apos;m a worthlessh, wretched worm!</string>
  <string id="58284" soundid="114452">Boss, what are you sayin&apos;? I better sober you up!</string>
  <string id="58285" soundid="114453">I heard what you said, Dutong! I knew you cheated Mother Kwan out of this place, and now we have proof! You can&apos;t get out of this now!</string>
  <string id="58343" soundid="116213">You are a true gentleman, as kind and generous as the Emperor himself. Thank you... for everything.</string>
  <string id="58480">Find the Minister&apos;s Weapon</string>
  <string id="58481">You agreed to find Minister Sheng&apos;s stolen weapon. He has committed men and resources to your effort. Seek the bandits along the Grandfather River and identify who is supporting them.</string>
  <string id="58485">Rescue Spear Catches Leaf</string>
  <string id="58519">The third of Lao&apos;s missing legion is Spear Catches Leaf. Seek him in the plains north of Tien&apos;s Landing and convince him to return.</string>
  <string id="58529">Keep your dowry. I&apos;m just happy to help.</string>
  <string id="58535">Kill Spear Catches Leaf</string>
  <string id="58536">Seek out Spear Catches Leaf in the plains north of Tien&apos;s Landing and find out what he knows. Kill him before he can warn his former master that you are coming.</string>
  <string id="58539">The Cannibal Caves</string>
  <string id="58540">Local officials have led you into a trap. These caves are filled with tainted spirits. Defeat the grotesque cannibal leader and return to Tien&apos;s Landing to show these fools the penalty for treachery.</string>
  <string id="58559">A Keg to Bait the Axeman</string>
  <string id="58582">Thank you. I was glad to help.</string>
  <string id="58583">I expected more as a reward.</string>
  <string id="58586">A bowl of wine or the right roadside alter may lure the Black Whirlwind from his hiding place. Place bowls laced with Kang&apos;s elixer of senslessness and return in the morning.</string>
  <string id="58601">Deprive a fool of his sport</string>
  <string id="58603">The Black Whirlwind may return to town if there is no more prey for him to hunt. Kill every game animal you can find in the Southern Forest.</string>
  <string id="58607">Assemble the Judges</string>
  <string id="58608">Find five judges who will adjudicate the duel of words fairly. If they are too biased, Sir Roderick will claim that the contest is pointless.</string>
  <string id="58628" soundid="77028">Praise the Emperor! Old Mother Kwan is back in charge, and I&apos;m back steeping tea where I belong. No more giving out bad advice for me!</string>
  <string id="58629" soundid="77029">I&apos;m glad we got Dutong&apos;s silver, but I feel bad for what we did to Mother Kwan. And now I&apos;m stuck giving out bad advice as a barkeep.</string>
  <string id="58653">Henpecked Hou</string>
  <string id="58687" soundid="158376">[Success] I will go... I don&apos;t want to fight anymore.</string>
  <string id="58719" soundid="142504">I have nothing to say to a dog bounding after its master. Go bother someone else.</string>
  <string id="58720">Junda</string>
  <string id="58722" soundid="77113">Go and see the mistress, human. She waits for you above.</string>
  <string id="58723" soundid="77114">Do not dally with me. She awaits you.</string>
  <string id="58724">You are unharmed?!</string>
  <string id="58725" soundid="77116">Be respectful when you speak to our mistress.</string>
  <string id="58726" soundid="77117">End the corruption.</string>
  <string id="58727" soundid="77118">You will be our salvation.</string>
  <string id="58728" soundid="77119">Be strong, human, but be swift, as well.</string>
  <string id="58729" soundid="77120">You have chosen well, human.</string>
  <string id="58730">Kang has another windmap that he thinks will lead to discovering more about his past. Though he has no idea where the map will take you, he is certain it will be dangerous.</string>
  <string id="58740">Fine. Here&apos;s the proof that Ling was involved.</string>
  <string id="58744" soundid="77135">What happened to this place? I passed through here not more than six months ago, and the trees were healthy.</string>
  <string id="58745" soundid="77136">The air feels stagnant, too. There can&apos;t be many caravan drivers willing to travel the forest in this state. Wait, what&apos;s that noise?</string>
  <string id="58760" soundid="113794">I would never do that. I&apos;d be shut down, or worse, in a heartbeat, and there&apos;s too many people who&apos;d happily report the infraction to Sweet Poison Lyn.</string>
  <string id="58761" soundid="113795">The Guild rewards those who can prove that people in my position aren&apos;t playing by their rules.</string>
  <string id="58774" soundid="180307">The loyalty you inspire is also tiresome, but I respect it. You have truly become a Spirit Monk. In another time, I would be proud of your ability.</string>
  <string id="58793">Focus mode enabled.</string>
  <string id="58797">Sailor</string>
  <string id="58800">test test</string>
  <string id="58847" soundid="77574">I&apos;ll die before one of these dwellers gets its ghostly hands on Lord Yun.</string>
  <string id="58850" soundid="142242">There is some talk of ghosts, of all things, attacking lone travelers, as well. I dismiss that kind of thing out of hand.</string>
  <string id="58851" soundid="142243">Of course that didn&apos;t stop Gao the Lesser from beating a few of them senseless. That boy enjoys causing pain.</string>
  <string id="58852" soundid="77575">Bloody forest looks like a blackened wound. Have to cut it down if it doesn&apos;t heal.</string>
  <string id="58853" soundid="77576">Guess those folk wailing about ghosts swarming the south were right.</string>
  <string id="58854" soundid="77577">I&apos;ve been in worse spots than this. Not many, but a few.</string>
  <string id="58858" soundid="106484">I thought as much before the bandit attack, but I see now that I must be prepared for anything at all times. I give it my full attention.</string>
  <string id="58860" soundid="77578">Bloody hill&apos;s caving in on itself, from the sounds of it.</string>
  <string id="58861" soundid="77579">I don&apos;t know why, but hearing all the rock shift brings a smile to my face.</string>
  <string id="58862" soundid="77580">Thought you were done for. Looks like you&apos;re a tough one.</string>
  <string id="58863" soundid="77581">The air seems clearer. Damned if I know why.</string>
  <string id="58868" soundid="77586">I can&apos;t shake the feeling the trees are watching me.</string>
  <string id="58869" soundid="77587">I just want to go home.</string>
  <string id="58870" soundid="77588">I understand Lord Yun&apos;s determination, but it will kill us all.</string>
  <string id="58871" soundid="77589">I will never see my wife again. I know this.</string>
  <string id="58872" soundid="77590">Even the earth protests this place.</string>
  <string id="58873" soundid="77591">We thought you were dead.</string>
  <string id="58874" soundid="77592">The air seems lighter now, but the ghosts are still out there. We&apos;ll stay on our guard.</string>
  <string id="58875" soundid="77593">We can&apos;t leave this place soon enough for me.</string>
  <string id="58883">Bandit</string>
  <string id="58886" soundid="124887">We have no claim on you, living one. Go, if you wish. We will not stop you.</string>
  <string id="58887" soundid="124888">Big people don&apos;t help us! Nobody helps us! They only hurt us!</string>
  <string id="58888" soundid="124889">And I must thank you, too. I have lived with this guilt for many years. Now that this is done, maybe I can finally move on with my life. Because of you.</string>
  <string id="58899">Didn&apos;t anybody try to help you?</string>
  <string id="58900">And now you&apos;re a ghost.</string>
  <string id="58906" soundid="77624">I&apos;ve tackled dangerous animals, but never ghosts.</string>
  <string id="58907" soundid="77625">Something must have happened to the Forest Shadow. This forest is sick.</string>
  <string id="58908" soundid="77626">Spear Catches Leaf, Lord Yun&apos;s lead hunter, knows this area intimately.</string>
  <string id="58909" soundid="77627">I wish you luck.</string>
  <string id="58910" soundid="77628">The shuddering earth will frighten the animals even more.</string>
  <string id="58911" soundid="77629">Something feels different in this place since the earth shook.</string>
  <string id="58912" soundid="77630">We were not sure if you would be safe.</string>
  <string id="58913" soundid="77631">If this forest does not heal, it will have to be cut down.</string>
  <string id="58924">Sky</string>
  <string id="58927">The Black Whirlwind</string>
  <string id="58931">Sagacious Zu</string>
  <string id="59158">Several spirits have pooled their energy to contact you, piercing the veil between the realm of the living and that of the dead. Cleanse the Temple of Central Harmony so they can clearly state their intent to you.</string>
  <string id="59161">Servants of the Dragon</string>
  <string id="59172">Forest</string>
  <string id="59173" soundid="167938">[Shendao flinches away from you. He remains silent, as you demanded.]</string>
  <string id="59186">You have heard rumors that there may be other survivors of the destruction of Two Rivers, your home. Seek these people out and determine how they got away.</string>
  <string id="59187">&lt;CUSTOM0&gt;</string>
  <string id="59194" soundid="83267">I thought I was saved when they killed the bandits that raided my husband&apos;s wagon, but these soldiers were no better. You have my gratitude.</string>
  <string id="59201" soundid="139465">Well, no matter... if you&apos;re looking for weapons, I have quite a good selection and reasonable rates. Would you like to see what I have for sale?</string>
  <string id="59202" soundid="139466">Here you go. There&apos;s quite a lot, so take your time.</string>
  <string id="59203" soundid="139467">Is there anything else I can do for you today?</string>
  <string id="59204" soundid="139468">Not much to tell, really. I&apos;ve been working with the school for almost twenty years, like my father did before me.</string>
  <string id="59228">Ties to Home</string>
  <string id="59229">Kang the Mad has fled the coming battle, taking his flying contraption with him. He must be found or it will take far too long to return to the Imperial City.</string>
  <string id="59230">Retrieve the Marvelous Dragonfly</string>
  <string id="59251">All attacks inflict 50% more damage.</string>
  <string id="59252">Extra attack with the fast combo.
All attacks do 20% more damage.</string>
  <string id="59253">All attacks inflict 20% more damage.
Healing rate is doubled.</string>
  <string id="59259">Pirate</string>
  <string id="59262" soundid="150710">Well, all these years together, and I never suspected you were the Scourge of the South. I&apos;m sorry, I know it&apos;s not funny... at least they didn&apos;t get your looks right.</string>
  <string id="59281">New move: Summon Dragon (Chi charged A+X )
All attacks inflict 20% more damage</string>
  <string id="59299">What would I have to do?</string>
  <string id="59300">I&apos;ll close the dam for you so the river is not so low and fast.</string>
  <string id="59302">Come with me. We might be able to explain things to him.</string>
  <string id="59303">No, not yet.</string>
  <string id="59304" soundid="150711">So, they have a name for you now. At least they didn&apos;t get your appearance right. Maybe we should find out exactly what they know.</string>
  <string id="59305" soundid="127459">Oh, well if you do find one, put it back in the ground. That&apos;s when you&apos;ll get your money, eh-heh.</string>
  <string id="59306" soundid="127460">Is there anything else?</string>
  <string id="59307" soundid="127461">Which? The elder or the younger?</string>
  <string id="59310">Gao&apos;s Mercenary</string>
  <string id="59313">Inquisitor Lim</string>
  <string id="59316">Lotus Assassin</string>
  <string id="59346">Town of Two Rivers</string>
  <string id="59402">Dispose of the Outlander</string>
  <string id="59403">Find a quiet spot to dispose of Sir Roderick. Preferably a hole somewhere large enough to fit his bulbous shape.</string>
  <string id="59406">Defeat the Nameless Hordes</string>
  <string id="59407">The Temple of Central Harmony is overrun. Cleanse it of these intruders and find out who allowed them to enter.</string>
  <string id="59410">The Four Sigils of Harmony</string>
  <string id="59411">After the garden is clear, return the four sigils to their proper places at the corners of the main hall.</string>
  <string id="59414">Seek Justice for a Fraud</string>
  <string id="59415">A traveling huckster has used the destruction of your home to solicit donations from well meaning merchants. Exact a bloody penalty for his dishonor.</string>
  <string id="59418">Get a Cut of the Action</string>
  <string id="59419">A Huckster has used your misfortune for his own profit. It is a harmless deception, just as long as you recieve the share that you deserve.</string>
  <string id="59422">Reform the Wayward Fool</string>
  <string id="59423">Convince the Huckster that has profited from your misfortune that he has dishonored himself. Help him see the error of his ways.</string>
  <string id="59426">Investigate the Impact Site</string>
  <string id="59427">The flyer may not have made it too far past the walls of the temple. Search the forest for the crash site and see if Kang survived.</string>
  <string id="59460" soundid="78496"></string>
  <string id="59463" soundid="128720">Heh... sorry for being late.</string>
  <string id="59472" soundid="142326">Well, you still have a bit of personality about you, hmm? It won&apos;t last. They strip their recruits down to the essentials. Eventually, you&apos;ll be just another mask.</string>
  <string id="59481">Press the &lt;Focus&gt; key to enter and exit Focus mode.</string>
  <string id="59494" soundid="84303"></string>
  <string id="59499" soundid="127462">Well, he was always a bit of a miser. Eh-heh, except on his burial, of course. He was wearing some very nice rings... er... well, he has a nice plot. Yeah, that&apos;s it.</string>
  <string id="59583">The Promise</string>
  <string id="59584">You&apos;ve agreed to help Ai Ling find a potential husband. The first step will be convincing an eligible bachelor to meet with her. No mean feat, considering that the meeting will take place in the headquarters of her gang.</string>
  <string id="59586" soundid="83268">Are you lying again?</string>
  <string id="59587" soundid="83269">No, dear.</string>
  <string id="59588" soundid="83270">Are you listening to me?</string>
  <string id="59589" soundid="83271">No, dear.</string>
  <string id="59590" soundid="83272">[SLAP!]</string>
  <string id="59591" soundid="83273">Fen? You have come this far for *Fen?* Did Hing send you here without even mentioning my name?</string>
  <string id="59592" soundid="83274">Oh dear. This will be unpleasant for someone.</string>
  <string id="59593" soundid="83275">I am Sing Wa. These animals made me cook for them, clean up their filth... and Hing sent you for the Flower? I will kill him.</string>
  <string id="59594" soundid="83276">No, but she is here. Oh yes, just over here. Let me present her to you.</string>
  <string id="59795">Hin Goo the Mechanic needs your services and your flyer. He asked you to retrieve some parts for him and has promised to sell you upgrades to the Marvelous Dragonfly in return. The mission will be dangerous, but it may well be worth the risk.</string>
  <string id="59803">[Step away from the fuel hopper.]</string>
  <string id="59900" soundid="83277">Fen! Come!</string>
  <string id="59901" soundid="83278"></string>
  <string id="59902" soundid="83279">Fen, my Flower! You are safe!</string>
  <string id="59903" soundid="83280">I knew this great fighter would save you. I couldn&apos;t leave without you. The cart needs your strength to pull it.</string>
  <string id="59904" soundid="83281">I am safe as well, Hing. Or did you forget I was missing?</string>
  <string id="59905" soundid="83282">Ah, there you are, my dear. I am glad you did not come to harm.</string>
  <string id="59906" soundid="83283">But you are more concerned about the ox. I see.</string>
  <string id="59907" soundid="83284">Gao? One of the soldiers said someone with that name is at a camp to the far north. Of course, he may have been speaking of someone more important.</string>
  <string id="59908" soundid="83285">Perhaps the camp goat!</string>
  <string id="59909" soundid="83286">I prayed for your safe return, dear, but the cart will not move itself.</string>
  <string id="60170">Yanwan</string>
  <string id="60174" soundid="83287">You will be lucky if I don&apos;t make you pull it while the ox rides. She is clearly important enough.</string>
  <string id="60175" soundid="83288">Come. Leave any of our stolen silver as reward for our savior. I value my own life at least that much. Someone has to.</string>
  <string id="60184">I&apos;ll get something later.</string>
  <string id="60188">Crescent Blades</string>
  <string id="60192">Doh! The thugs have killed you - StrRef #60192 </string>
  <string id="60193">Hin Goo has arranged for you to escort the Prefect of Shangdang County back to his home. The skies are filled with bandits, and the mission will be perilous, but the Prefect promises to reward you well.</string>
  <string id="60194">Hin Goo asked you to rescue his associate. In return for your aid, he will allow you to use his flyer for this one mission. The area is swarming with pirates and bandits, so you&apos;ll have to be accurate and careful.</string>
  <string id="60196" soundid="144479"></string>
  <string id="60200" soundid="180308">Physical barriers are no match for those we place in our own minds. My power has encased you in doubt, held you with the weight of your burden.</string>
  <string id="60201" soundid="180309">You and your followers are playthings. Death&apos;s Hand weakens without you, and the rest are held just as you are. You are each too weak to match my power.</string>
  <string id="60202" soundid="180487">The Celestial Bureaucracy is said to govern the heavens. Just as cities have minor officials, existence is delegated across many entities, some more grand than others.</string>
  <string id="60203">You have found some guy&apos;s sword. Switch to your sword style using your Fight Style keys. strref 60203</string>
  <string id="60204">Cannibal</string>
  <string id="60207">Cannibal</string>
  <string id="60210">Invulnerable</string>
  <string id="60211">Unlimited Chi</string>
  <string id="60235">Matchmaker</string>
  <string id="60238" soundid="93200">How dare you stand before me?</string>
  <string id="60239" soundid="93201">She was poisoned as surely as I am blind, and no one would benefit as much as her opponent of the moment.</string>
  <string id="60241" soundid="93202">Lies! By your honor as a man, do not try that with me!</string>
  <string id="60244" soundid="93203">You will not lie to me, girl!</string>
  <string id="60251" soundid="127463">He raised his son up just like him. They hated each other like you&apos;ve never seen. Maybe the son finally decided to take over the family business once and for all.</string>
  <string id="60252" soundid="93204">I have dedicated myself to the healing arts, and I know the effects of the southern black leaf extract as well as the best assassins.</string>
  <string id="60254" soundid="127464">Eh-heh, it&apos;s all the same to me, but the old man was past his prime. Like a living skeleton. If I hadn&apos;t have known him for years, I might have thought he was a ghost already!</string>
  <string id="60256" soundid="127465">Is that all you wanted to know?</string>
  <string id="60257" soundid="93206">If you think I am preaching, then I conclude my sermon now.</string>
  <string id="60258" soundid="93207">Why bother to voice an accusation in this place? Here I am a blind woman in the halls of the deaf.</string>
  <string id="60259" soundid="127466">Bright young upstart, I have to say. Taught the tanning trade by his father, the one who&apos;s risen up and gone home. Trying to make a real name for himself, too.</string>
  <string id="60262" soundid="93208">You are the Imperial Champion. Who would believe me?</string>
  <string id="60263" soundid="93209">Kai Lan controls legions of dangerous men. I know better than to sully the name of his tournament.</string>
  <string id="60264" soundid="93210">I want nothing more to do with you. Take yourself elsewhere.</string>
  <string id="60265" soundid="127467">When his father died a few days ago, he kept saying that things would change. That he was better than his father ever was, and with him out of the way, it would all be better.</string>
  <string id="60266" soundid="127468">Eh-heh, like father like son. I heard the same thing happened when the old Tanner Fong took over, too. Eh-heheh.</string>
  <string id="60269" soundid="93211">Away from my table! These tools are for healing, and they do not need your taint near them, poisoner.</string>
  <string id="60282">You&apos;re wrong, Doctor. Khana was not poisoned.</string>
  <string id="60357" soundid="117587">Don&apos;t interrupt your elders, young one. As I was saying: It was some stranger who wandered into town and saved us.</string>
  <string id="60358" soundid="117588">Some stranger? I can&apos;t believe that. What is more likely, your theory, that some lone stranger wandered into town and saved us for no reason, or my theory?</string>
  <string id="60359" soundid="117589">My theory.</string>
  <string id="60360" soundid="117590">You don&apos;t even know my theory yet.</string>
  <string id="60361" soundid="117591">I know it&apos;s yours, so I know it&apos;s wrong. My theory.</string>
  <string id="60362" soundid="117592">Here&apos;s my theory: The Emperor sent a special agent to close the dam for us. But the Emperor, he&apos;s so humble he didn&apos;t want us to know. He made the agent come in secret! </string>
  <string id="60363" soundid="117593">You really believe that? Now I *know* your mind is gone! The Emperor doesn&apos;t care about us.</string>
  <string id="60364" soundid="117594">No? Then why&apos;d he send an agent to save us? Hmph! </string>
  <string id="60366" soundid="117596">You&apos;re crazy. Times have never been better.</string>
  <string id="60367" soundid="117597">I&apos;m not crazy. I smell it in the wind. Something bad is coming.</string>
  <string id="60368" soundid="117598">How do you know? You always think you know more than me.</string>
  <string id="60369" soundid="117599">Everyone knows more than you. And I just know something bad is coming.</string>
  <string id="60370" soundid="117600">If I knew what it was, I would have said what it was. Wouldn&apos;t I?</string>
  <string id="60371" soundid="117601">I agree with the rude youngster here. You don&apos;t know what you&apos;re talking about. You&apos;re crazy.</string>
  <string id="60372" soundid="117602">The dam is closed, the river is back. We can fish, goods are coming into the town. The pirates are gone. Even Minister Sheng doesn&apos;t whine as much as usual.</string>
  <string id="60373" soundid="117603">I tell you, something bad is coming.</string>
  <string id="60374" soundid="117604">Ah, you&apos;ve just got gas.</string>
  <string id="60375" soundid="117605">Well, yes. But that&apos;s not what I&apos;m talking about. I can smell it.</string>
  <string id="60376" soundid="117606">Told you it was gas.</string>
  <string id="60377" soundid="117607">Don&apos;t interrupt your elders, young one. I got a bad feeling. Trouble&apos;s coming. It&apos;s going to be worse than the Long Drought.</string>
  <string id="60378" soundid="117608">The Long Drought? You&apos;re crazy. Was never anything worse than the Long Drought.</string>
  <string id="60379" soundid="117609">Just wait and see. Then we&apos;ll find out who&apos;s crazy.</string>
  <string id="60380" soundid="117610"></string>
  <string id="60381" soundid="117611">You&apos;ve been in the sun too long. The Long Drought was bad. This is nothing!</string>
  <string id="60382" soundid="117612">Five people died yesterday. Pirates raided one of the outlying farms, took the whole family as slaves!</string>
  <string id="60383" soundid="117613">During the Long Drought, must have been six... seven hundred... seven thousand... people died every day. That was bad, this is nothing.</string>
  <string id="60384" soundid="117614">Hush, young one. Don&apos;t interrupt your elders. We&apos;ve been sitting here talking since before your parents were born, and we ain&apos;t about to stop now.</string>
  <string id="60385" soundid="117615">If you want to listen in, fine. But pipe down. My friend&apos;s mind ain&apos;t what it used to be, and he&apos;ll lose his train of thought if you cut him off.</string>
  <string id="60386" soundid="117616">Where was I? Oh yes... you&apos;re crazy. Sure, the drought lasted ten years. But I knew Emperor Sun Hai would figure out a way to save us.</string>
  <string id="60387" soundid="117617">You knew that? Funny, I remember you sitting on that same stone, complaining that Sun Hai wasn&apos;t half the emperor his father was!</string>
  <string id="60388" soundid="117618">I never said any such thing!</string>
  <string id="60389" soundid="117619">Quit interrupting, young one! Listen to the wisdom of your elders, and you might learn something!</string>
  <string id="60390" soundid="117620">Wisdom? You don&apos;t know nothing about wisdom! You said that Sun Hai&apos;s father would have solved the drought, but you had no faith in the young buck of a son.</string>
  <string id="60391" soundid="117621">You&apos;re crazy, that&apos;s what you are. I always trusted the Emperor. After he ended the drought, I was the one cheering the loudest for him.</string>
  <string id="60392" soundid="117622">Cheered the loudest? That&apos;s just &apos;cause you were going deaf, even back then. Besides, you never even saw the Emperor!</string>
  <string id="60393" soundid="117623">How do you know? Maybe I *did* see the Emperor! Anyway, the Emperor saved us from the drought, and I&apos;m sure he&apos;ll save us now.</string>
  <string id="60394" soundid="117624">You think so? Really?</string>
  <string id="60395" soundid="117625">No. We&apos;re dead.</string>
  <string id="60396" soundid="117626">Ah, you&apos;re crazy.</string>
  <string id="60397" soundid="117627">Goodbye? Goodbye? Who was talking to him?</string>
  <string id="60398" soundid="117628">Goodbye? Goodbye? Who was talking to her?</string>
  <string id="60400" soundid="117630">You&apos;re crazy.</string>
  <string id="60401" soundid="117631">Me? You&apos;re the one kept saying the Emperor would come save us. Wasn&apos;t the Emperor in the end, though.</string>
  <string id="60402" soundid="117632">How do you know? You always think you know more than me.</string>
  <string id="60403" soundid="117633">It isn&apos;t hard. You don&apos;t know anything.</string>
  <string id="60404" soundid="117634">Hush, young one. Don&apos;t interrupt your elders! We&apos;ve been sitting here talking since before your parents were born, and we&apos;re not about to stop now.</string>
  <string id="60407">Do you ever say anything useful?</string>
  <string id="60411">I closed the dam.</string>
  <string id="60412">I know who closed the dam.</string>
  <string id="60417">What&apos;s your theory?</string>
  <string id="60421">I closed the dam!</string>
  <string id="60426">What do you think is coming?</string>
  <string id="60428">You don&apos;t know what you&apos;re talking about.</string>
  <string id="60502">Go on.</string>
  <string id="60503">You two are a complete waste of time.</string>
  <string id="60508">VFX Guy</string>
  <string id="60509">The drought sounds pretty bad.</string>
  <string id="60510">Is this all you two do? Sit here and argue?</string>
  <string id="60515">It&apos;s not good to speak ill of the Emperor.</string>
  <string id="60524">Can I ask you some questions?</string>
  <string id="60525">That&apos;s about all I can take. Goodbye.</string>
  <string id="60529" soundid="173694">It&apos;s up to you how we handle this, but remember that the Inquisitors aren&apos;t just thugs. They&apos;re more subtle.</string>
  <string id="60530">What are you two talking about?</string>
  <string id="60561" soundid="126868">You wouldn&apos;t... I don&apos;t... I mean... Ahh!!!</string>
  <string id="60667" soundid="136409">Ha! Don&apos;t make me laugh! I&apos;m looking to start a family and live a nice, quiet life. Somehow I don&apos;t see that kind of domestic tranquility in your near future.</string>
  <string id="60668" soundid="136410">You&apos;ve got that &quot;wandering hero&quot; look, and I&apos;m not interested in a husband who&apos;s going to be out traveling the Empire or saving the world.</string>
  <string id="60669">I&apos;ll marry you.</string>
  <string id="60671" soundid="136413">I... I am truly frightened about tomorrow. But I know I am safe here with you.</string>
  <string id="60672" soundid="136414">Whatever comes, thank you for showing me how to care for people. I have never been closer to anyone.</string>
  <string id="60674" soundid="160290">[You are tied to the reason why spirits wander. Many appeared after your people fell, and some are held in this cave. They are drawn to your amulet. It is ahead, waiting for you.]</string>
  <string id="60675" soundid="160291">[Be careful. It is desired by many seeking power beyond the mortal realm. I make no apology for these trials, my student. You will come to see how necessary they are.]</string>
  <string id="60679">I will never leave again.</string>
  <string id="60682" soundid="141892">Given how quickly I could feel an effect, this cure was worth it. Here, take this with my thanks.</string>
  <string id="60683" soundid="141893">That&apos;s very kind of you. I can&apos;t thank you enough.</string>
  <string id="60685" soundid="141894">It&apos;s a shame there isn&apos;t time to train with Smiling Mountain right now. I feel good enough to fight!</string>
  <string id="60686" soundid="141895">If you are interested in trying to set a new record for Smiling Mountain&apos;s special prize, whatever it is, then I&apos;ll be ready.</string>
  <string id="60687" soundid="141896">I don&apos;t think so. Some of the throbbing has faded, so I&apos;m sure it&apos;s on the road to recovery. Thank you for the offer.</string>
  <string id="60688" soundid="141897">I haven&apos;t been able to think of anything new. You should talk to Old Ming; he might have some ideas.</string>
  <string id="60689" soundid="141898">He&apos;ll probably be down by the beach making sure nothing happened to the statue of the Emperor during the bandit raid.</string>
  <string id="60690" soundid="141899">Unless you can speed up time, I&apos;m not sure there&apos;s much that can be done. Master Li has already tended to it.</string>
  <string id="60691" soundid="141900">Then again, I vaguely recall a grass or herb that hastens the healing process. Someone like Old Ming might know for sure, he&apos;s quite interested in herbs.</string>
  <string id="60692" soundid="141901">I think so, though I can&apos;t remember the name. It was some kind of rare grass, I think.</string>
  <string id="60693" soundid="141902">I don&apos;t think it&apos;s a common plant, no. The only person I can think of who might know for sure would be Old Ming.</string>
  <string id="60695" soundid="141903">I&apos;m not sure, but if you had to buy it, I&apos;d happily pay you back for the trouble you went through.</string>
  <string id="60696" soundid="141904">This wound will heal in time regardless, but I wouldn&apos;t complain if it knitted faster. All the quicker to return to my training.</string>
  <string id="60697" soundid="141905">When he&apos;s not hollering at students for making too much noise, he&apos;s usually down by the beach looking after the statue of Emperor Sun.</string>
  <string id="60698">Creative Yukong</string>
  <string id="60699" soundid="141907">If you have to buy anything, let me know what it cost and I&apos;ll pay you back happily. It would be worth it to get back to training.</string>
  <string id="60700" soundid="141908">I have expressed my concerns to Smiling Mountain, and he wisely advises me to focus on myself. If I let my anger get the better of me, I&apos;m no better than Gao.</string>
  <string id="60702" soundid="79893"></string>
  <string id="60703" soundid="127469">Well? What is it, then?</string>
  <string id="60704" soundid="127470">Of course he was dead! The family wouldn&apos;t exactly have given me a live man to bury, now would they?</string>
  <string id="60705" soundid="79896">It is too late for my wine operation, but I am a man of business, and I plan to collect payment, in one form or another!</string>
  <string id="60706" soundid="79897"></string>
  <string id="60708" soundid="127471">That would be... unprofessional. Can&apos;t have stuff like that getting around.</string>
  <string id="60709" soundid="127472">You, uh... dealt with the problem, though?</string>
  <string id="60712" soundid="79903">Hello! You do not need to speak with me. I am just Merchant Jiang&apos;s assistant. Perhaps someday I will be Merchant Shipeng, mightiest merchant of Tien&apos;s Landing!</string>
  <string id="60713" soundid="79904">But for now, I am just an assistant, not worthy of your honorable time.</string>
  <string id="60734" soundid="127473">Well, the family isn&apos;t pleased, so you should probably hurry it up. I can&apos;t say I&apos;d enjoy it either if my dead relatives came back, eh-heheh.</string>
  <string id="60779" soundid="80431">You will choose to help us, or you will die.</string>
  <string id="60780" soundid="80432">You will help, or we will have you.</string>
  <string id="60787" soundid="129990">Where did you... Ahhhh! The Spirit! She is dead and you are returned to us! The Mother be praised!</string>
  <string id="60788" soundid="80434">You are wise to serve the keeper.</string>
  <string id="60789" soundid="80435">The keeper makes us strong.</string>
  <string id="60791">Protect Kang!</string>
  <string id="60793" soundid="80439">You are too big. Your size makes you weak.</string>
  <string id="60794" soundid="80440">I see no need to speak to you. You are nothing.</string>
  <string id="60795" soundid="80441">Leave me to my food, unless you want some of it. Har!</string>
  <string id="60796" soundid="80442">Anyone want some leg with their meal? I have plenty here! Ha!</string>
  <string id="60797" soundid="80443">You shouldn&apos;t come near me unless you want my full attention.</string>
  <string id="60798" soundid="80444">I didn&apos;t order any milk, wench!</string>
  <string id="60800" soundid="80446">I do not trust you, thin-blood.</string>
  <string id="60801" soundid="80447">Decide wisely, or I will pick my teeth with your bones.</string>
  <string id="60802" soundid="129992">The caves are open, the Mother is free, and we have gathered the silver that we offered to pay you.</string>
  <string id="60803" soundid="80449">You have your duties, thin-blood. Do them!</string>
  <string id="60809" soundid="80455">Mistress, I am almost ready to return to the Imperial City. Another day and I will bring you the amulet fragment.</string>
  <string id="60810" soundid="80456">I lose confidence in you with each passing hour, Lim. You should have been back by now. Why haven&apos;t you ordered Gao to grant you one of his flyers?</string>
  <string id="60811" soundid="80457">Mistress, Gao&apos;s ships are only small flyers. They&apos;re good for short-range flights and raiding villages, but not for long journeys. That&apos;s why I haven&apos;t returned yet.</string>
  <string id="60981">Warrior&apos;s Boon</string>
  <string id="60982">Spirit Well</string>
  <string id="61090">Area Attack (Chi Strike)</string>
  <string id="61091">Attack (Chi Strike)</string>
  <string id="61093" soundid="80309">Let us begin.</string>
  <string id="61094">Show your skill with your hands, not your words.</string>
  <string id="61126" soundid="80458">Until you finish? *I* designed that Dragonfly! *I* built it, not Gao! That Dragonfly is Kang&apos;s masterpiece!</string>
  <string id="61127" soundid="80459">Silence the mad fool!</string>
  <string id="61128" soundid="80460"></string>
  <string id="61130" soundid="80462">I&apos;ve heard rumors of a spy disrupting our operations in the south, Lim. Maybe this is all too much for you to handle. Perhaps I should come out there personally.</string>
  <string id="61131">Did you say Gao was in charge?</string>
  <string id="61132" soundid="80464">That will not be necessary, Mistress. I will deal with the troublemaker here and return to the Imperial City in one day.</string>
  <string id="61133" soundid="80465"></string>
  <string id="61134" soundid="80466">You heard Mistress Jia. I can&apos;t waste any more time here. Get that flyer finished... now!</string>
  <string id="61135" soundid="80467">I... I want to be alone. I... I must grieve for my son. No one is to disturb me! No one!</string>
  <string id="61136" soundid="80468">If I can get to the Imperial City fast enough, I can give the amulet fragment to Death&apos;s Hand himself. Then, Grand Inquisitor Jia may be in for a surprise. We shall see.</string>
  <string id="61139" soundid="80471">You may have your workshop back, mad one. I suspect Gao will be preoccupied for some time, so I&apos;m in charge now. I suggest you finish your Dragonfly today!</string>
  <string id="61140" soundid="80472"></string>
  <string id="61141" soundid="80473"></string>
  <string id="61142" soundid="80474">Interruptions... who designed that Dragonfly... build something to make his sandals explode....</string>
  <string id="61143" soundid="80475"></string>
  <string id="61144" soundid="80476"></string>
  <string id="61151">How would I get to the pirate camp?</string>
  <string id="61153">Hasn&apos;t anybody tried to stop them?</string>
  <string id="61213">Chai Ka</string>
  <string id="61214" soundid="83289">Yes, dear.</string>
  <string id="61215" soundid="83290">Are you another fool who values things over lives? Careful, or you may develop some unwholesome attachments.</string>
  <string id="61217">You must slow the Imperial attack on Dirge. Destroy as many ships and ground targets as you can.</string>
  <string id="61224" soundid="127474">Eh-heh, well, you know... a few things here and there. They just sort of... fall into my hands. Eh-heheh. They don&apos;t need them anymore. Heh.</string>
  <string id="61227">Balanced</string>
  <string id="61228">Strong</string>
  <string id="61229">Fast</string>
  <string id="61230">Magic</string>
  <string id="61231" soundid="143831">This day couldn&apos;t possibly get worse.</string>
  <string id="61247">Captain Burning Sun</string>
  <string id="61250">Lotus Assassin</string>
  <string id="61253">You have recovered Minister Sheng&apos;s weapon, the Dragon Sword.</string>
  <string id="61254">Experience Jade Empire&apos;s epic story though action-packed combat and rich interactive dialog.</string>
  <string id="61256">Tien&apos;s Landing</string>
  <string id="61258">This gem temporarily prevents any drain on Health.</string>
  <string id="61259">Powered by earth spirits, this gem temporarily grants unlimited Chi.</string>
  <string id="61260">You have found a powerful protective gem called the Warrior&apos;s Boon for your amulet.</string>
  <string id="61262">You have recovered a Spirit Well gem for your Dragon Amulet.</string>
  <string id="61290" soundid="142185">[Success] I suppose it would be bad for my reputation, and you&apos;re well-known enough that word would get around. Fine, I&apos;ll knock off a bit of silver.</string>
  <string id="61291" soundid="142186">[Success] You&apos;re right, that wouldn&apos;t be just, given the circumstances. As much as I hate to do it, I can knock a few silvers off the price for you.</string>
  <string id="61292" soundid="142187">[Success] You see to the heart of the matter. I suppose I can&apos;t risk losing the sale when I have no other stock, so I will knock a few silvers off the price.</string>
  <string id="61293" soundid="142188">[Failure] I&apos;m not going to fall for that kind of word play. I&apos;ve been a merchant longer than you&apos;ve been alive. My prices are fair enough. Pay them, or move on.</string>
  <string id="61294" soundid="142189">Exactly. A wise decision, and one with a better bottom line for us both. I&apos;ll need payment in advance, of course.</string>
  <string id="61295" soundid="142190">An excellent choice! I&apos;ll mix the salve for you and prepare the poultice; it won&apos;t take a moment.</string>
  <string id="61296" soundid="142191">Time will heal her, as long as she&apos;s careful not to strain herself.</string>
  <string id="61297" soundid="119162">It is difficult for one of my rank to give gifts, even ones so simple as what I gave you. A princess is not normally allowed to show favorites.</string>
  <string id="61298" soundid="142192">Your generosity is extreme, but who am I to complain? Enjoy, and I hope it makes your friend better quickly.</string>
  <string id="61299" soundid="142193">You are the best kind of friend: generous, but frugal. Most excellent.</string>
  <string id="61300" soundid="142194">Business has been slow! What am I supposed to do? Starve?</string>
  <string id="61301" soundid="142195">[Success] I suppose it would be bad for my reputation, and you&apos;re well known enough that word would get around. Fine, I&apos;ll knock off a bit of silver.</string>
  <string id="61302" soundid="142196">[Success] You&apos;re right, that wouldn&apos;t be just, given the circumstances. As much as I hate to do it, I can knock a few silvers off the price for you.</string>
  <string id="61303" soundid="142197">[Success] You see to the heart of the matter. I suppose I can&apos;t risk losing the sale when I have no other stock, so I will knock a few silvers off the price.</string>
  <string id="61304" soundid="142198">[Failure] I&apos;m not going to fall for that kind of word play. I&apos;ve been a merchant longer than you&apos;ve been alive. My prices are fair enough. Pay them, or move on.</string>
  <string id="61305" soundid="142199">Fair enough. To be sure you aren&apos;t choosing the wrong grass, I&apos;ll go over this again with you if you change your mind.</string>
  <string id="61306" soundid="142200">To hear some of the caravan masters talk, there are problems of this type all over the Empire. I will be sure to let you know as soon as anything comes to town.</string>
  <string id="61307" soundid="142201">Two Rivers has always accepted the masters of your school as leaders, but none have taken to it with the skill, authority, or wisdom of your master.</string>
  <string id="61308" soundid="142202">Why not ask your friend there? Dawn Star knows more about the spirit realm than anyone, it seems. She&apos;s been a great help from time to time.</string>
  <string id="61309" soundid="142203">I do what I can to help, good merchant. That&apos;s all any of us can do.</string>
  <string id="61310" soundid="142204">Your friend Dawn Star might be the best person to ask. She&apos;s been a help in a few instances where there have been... issues with ghosts.</string>
  <string id="61311" soundid="83291">Yes, I&apos;ll take this filthy beast home and decide if it is allowed in the house anymore. And I&apos;ll take the ox, as well.</string>
  <string id="61312" soundid="141909">If you have questions about history or philosophy, I recommend avoiding us students. Learn about the past from those who were there.</string>
  <string id="61313" soundid="142205">One day the gods will recognize my suffering and elevate me to their ranks.</string>
  <string id="61318">I&apos;m looking for ingredients for a medicinal poultice.</string>
  <string id="61321">Old Ming suggested red silk grass to cure her wound.</string>
  <string id="61323">Do you have any bearded tongue grass?</string>
  <string id="61324" soundid="119163">Better that I give it away before Death&apos;s Hand carts it off. He has been quite brazen.</string>
  <string id="61326">I&apos;ll take the red silk grass. I want her to be able to fight safely.</string>
  <string id="61327">We negotiated a discount for red silk grass. Here&apos;s forty silver.</string>
  <string id="61328">Here&apos;s the fifty silver for red silk grass.</string>
  <string id="61329" soundid="119164">Besides, it was mine by birthright to do with as I wish. Must I always be dictated to by tradition, despite my respect for it?</string>
  <string id="61330">Surely you&apos;re not going to charge full price for a humanitarian cause?</string>
  <string id="61331">[Charm] A kind man like yourself wouldn&apos;t let a student suffer over a few silvers.</string>
  <string id="61332">[Intimidation] That girl&apos;s wound warned us of the bandits. You would dismiss that out of hand?</string>
  <string id="61333">[Intuition] How large is your profit on this herb? Large enough to justify this kind of reluctance?</string>
  <string id="61334">Forget it. I&apos;ll pay full price.</string>
  <string id="61336">As long as she thinks she&apos;s better. Give me the bearded tongue grass. </string>
  <string id="61337">We worked out a discount for the bearded tongue grass. Here&apos;s twenty silver.</string>
  <string id="61338">Here&apos;s the twenty five silver for bearded tongue grass.</string>
  <string id="61341">Surely you&apos;re not going to charge full price for a humanitarian cause?</string>
  <string id="61342">[Charm] A kind man like yourself wouldn&apos;t let a student suffer over a few silvers.</string>
  <string id="61343">[Intimidation] That girl&apos;s wound warned us of the bandits. You would dismiss that out of hand?</string>
  <string id="61344">[Intuition] How large is your profit on this herb? Large enough to justify this kind of reluctance?</string>
  <string id="61345">Forget it. I&apos;ll pay full price.</string>
  <string id="61347">I want to ask about Dawn Star&apos;s disappearance.</string>
  <string id="61348">Let&apos;s go back to my other questions.</string>
  <string id="61349">I want to ask about the others at this school.</string>
  <string id="61351" soundid="141956">I&apos;ll look to the villagers and save as many as I can. Go!</string>
  <string id="61352" soundid="119165">Sometimes I want what everyone else has: to be myself.</string>
  <string id="61353" soundid="141957"></string>
  <string id="61354">What do you think about Master Li?</string>
  <string id="61355">Master Li told me he was the Emperor&apos;s brother.</string>
  <string id="61357">One of many facets that will make you a better person.</string>
  <string id="61359">No matter how pretty the pieces, you are still diminished.</string>
  <string id="61361">Do you know much about the rest of the Empire?</string>
  <string id="61363">Goodbye for now.</string>
  <string id="61364">I&apos;ll be back when I can afford that price.</string>
  <string id="61365" soundid="119166">And to be myself I... gave you what I wished.</string>
  <string id="61366">I&apos;ll have to think about it.</string>
  <string id="61376" soundid="142251"></string>
  <string id="61377" soundid="142252"></string>
  <string id="61378" soundid="119167">Hmm. Well, you&apos;re polite, at least. Most nobles take gifts as a matter of course. Especially those from a woman.</string>
  <string id="61379" soundid="142253"></string>
  <string id="61380" soundid="142254"></string>
  <string id="61381" soundid="142255"></string>
  <string id="61387" soundid="142264"></string>
  <string id="61388" soundid="142265"></string>
  <string id="61391" soundid="188101">[It looks like Ru the Boatswain has drunk himself into a stupor. Good thing Kang has offered to let you use the Dragonfly.]</string>
  <string id="61392" soundid="119168">But the price I may pay for helping you could be greater still. I am destined for the throne, destined to rule the Empire after my father, but....</string>
  <string id="61397" soundid="142273"></string>
  <string id="61401" soundid="142277"></string>
  <string id="61407" soundid="186169">You&apos;ve made quite an impact here, getting rid of Shin *and* Gang already. I suppose you think the rest of us should beg to have you for our master now.</string>
  <string id="61408" soundid="83293">At this camp there is only me and Fen. Oh yes, I am not her, but she is here. Let me present her.</string>
  <string id="61409" soundid="83294">Flower of the Field? Hing sent you here for his Flower and did not even mention my name?</string>
  <string id="61410" soundid="186170">By coming in here and trying to leap up in rank you make the rest of us look bad. We&apos;re already being replaced by golems, we don&apos;t need you making us seem worthless.</string>
  <string id="61411" soundid="186171">Our masters look weaker than ever because of what you did. You&apos;ve made us all look bad, and we can&apos;t let that go unanswered.</string>
  <string id="61412">I&apos;d be a better master than either of those two were.</string>
  <string id="61415" soundid="142289">I have not been here that long, but even I know that Gao the Lesser despises you. You certainly taught him a lesson.</string>
  <string id="61416" soundid="83295">Do I have to slaughter that thing for you to show me some attention?</string>
  <string id="61417" soundid="142290">I just hope that you will be all right in the cavern. Master Li has forbidden anyone else to go in there, and Student Lin says that place is dangerous.</string>
  <string id="61422" soundid="119169">You are polite, at least. Too many men just take what they can, while they can. Perhaps we women are more civilized.</string>
  <string id="61424">You received:</string>
  <string id="61428" soundid="119170">True. That is the price that those in power must pay, and I do not shirk from my duty, but...</string>
  <string id="61431" soundid="143143">You are strong, but you do not know real power. *Our* strength lies in preparation.</string>
  <string id="61434">Double Axes</string>
  <string id="61440">Lotus Assassin</string>
  <string id="61466">Your Body score represents your physical hardiness and ability to withstand damage. 

Health measures your physical endurance. When Health reaches zero, you die. You can regain health by using Chi Heal, picking up red Health power-ups during battle, or meditating at Spirit fonts.</string>
  <string id="61468">Your Mind score represents your concentration and tactical awareness in combat.

Focus measures your ability to concentrate intently in battle. You use Focus when you wield weapons or enter Focus Mode to slow your enemies. You can recover Focus by picking up yellow Focus power-ups during battle, or by meditating at Focus Shrines.</string>
  <string id="61471">Your Spirit score represents your inner strength and magical power.

Chi measures your spiritual energy. You use Chi to recover Health through Chi Heal, enhance your attacks, fuel Magic styles, and power Transformation styles. You can regain Chi by picking up blue Chi power-ups during battle, meditating at Spirit fonts, or using the Spirit Thief style to steal it from enemies.</string>
  <string id="61512">Stone Immortal</string>
  <string id="61514">Ice Shard</string>
  <string id="61576">Kang</string>
  <string id="61619">Lotus Apprentice</string>
  <string id="61622" soundid="83296">No, dear.</string>
  <string id="61624">You are safe now, Fen. Hing sent me.</string>
  <string id="61643" soundid="116141">I heard the ruins are haunted by the ghosts of those that died in the flood.</string>
  <string id="61667" soundid="112325">We&apos;re sailors, we don&apos;t belong on land. If we could just get our ship back on the water, everything would be fine, but that won&apos;t happen until someone finds a way to close the dam.</string>
  <string id="61680" soundid="116142">With Old Mother Kwan back in charge, I can finally get a good cup of tea again!</string>
  <string id="61751">Tempest</string>
  <string id="61779">Lotus Assassin</string>
  <string id="61818">It&apos;s a shame this had to happen.</string>
  <string id="61820">The poultice was only a painkiller. Next time, find your *own* solutions.</string>
  <string id="61826" soundid="99433">If you want to talk about the arena, you should talk to Soldier and not me. I try to stay clear of the other fighters.</string>
  <string id="61830" soundid="99434">You must be new around here. I may not care to spend time with the people who frequent this place, but I remember faces. What do you want with me?</string>
  <string id="61831" soundid="99435">Thank you for helping Soldier and me with that little wager. We should be able to live in comfort for some time on that sum.</string>
  <string id="61834" soundid="99436">Don&apos;t get too comfortable with your Silver Division championship. Soldier will have it back from you, eventually!</string>
  <string id="61837" soundid="99437">Yes? What do you want?</string>
  <string id="61838" soundid="99438">I&apos;ve heard they sometimes recruit fighters here in the arena. Iron Soldier or the others might know the specifics, if they&apos;ll spare the time to tell you.</string>
  <string id="61856" soundid="81650"></string>
  <string id="61857" soundid="81651">A fine statue, isn&apos;t it? Too bad no one bothers to pay it proper respect but me.</string>
  <string id="61858" soundid="81652"></string>
  <string id="61859" soundid="81653">A fitting tribute to our leader, Emperor Sun, though no one else seems interested in venerating his rule.</string>
  <string id="61860" soundid="81654">I don&apos;t have the back for cleaning it properly anymore. I guess that&apos;s why they call me &quot;Old&quot; Ming.</string>
  <string id="61861" soundid="81655">Not many people seem interested in what Old Ming has to say, even if I&apos;ve been here longer than anyone.</string>
  <string id="61862" soundid="81656">Oh, yes, I heard about that. Some fool girl out walking on the overlook, wasn&apos;t it? Serves her right for not studying or meditating, I say!</string>
  <string id="61863" soundid="81657">Well, there&apos;s no accounting for youth. She probably wants something to get her moving again, so I&apos;d say you need a poultice made from red silk grass clippings. </string>
  <string id="61864" soundid="119171">Hmph... not to hear him tell it....</string>
  <string id="61865" soundid="142120">Try not to spend them all in one place unless you&apos;re trying to buy back your honor after shaming it so. Ha! Buy your respect, that&apos;s a good one.</string>
  <string id="61867" soundid="81661">I don&apos;t track every young person who flits about town. That was my wife&apos;s job, when she was alive.</string>
  <string id="61868" soundid="81662">That&apos;s not something I would know. I haven&apos;t been by the school in a long time.</string>
  <string id="61869" soundid="81663">Not in the slightest. Who knows what you young people do or where you go? Not Old Ming.</string>
  <string id="61870" soundid="81664">There is only one path out of the village, but past the fields it leads to the swamps, and I doubt she went there.</string>
  <string id="61871" soundid="81665">Not a friendly walk to make. All manner of miscreants look for shelter there.</string>
  <string id="61872" soundid="81666">Eh, if you wish, but I&apos;ve only so many years left. Give me a jostle if I nod off.</string>
  <string id="61873" soundid="81667">This place is so full of navel-gazers that it&apos;s nice to see someone looking up and out for a change.</string>
  <string id="61874" soundid="81668">That would depend on who you ask. I suspect everyone would cast a single vote for themselves.</string>
  <string id="61875" soundid="81669">Master Li is the real leader here. Everyone looks up to him, and his word passes for law around these parts. His wisdom is unquestionable.</string>
  <string id="61876" soundid="81670">He teaches a lot at the school, but Gujin the weapon master helps out a lot around town, making him probably the most well liked man around.</string>
  <string id="61877" soundid="81671">A wise and skilled man. He has kept the peace in this village for twenty years like it was set in stone.</string>
  <string id="61878" soundid="81672">I don&apos;t know. He has never talked about what transpired to bring him here, or why he arrived with you under his arm.</string>
  <string id="61879" soundid="81673">I remember he seemed quite harried at the time, but he settled in quite quickly.</string>
  <string id="61880" soundid="81674">He could see the potential of this place, I think.</string>
  <string id="61881" soundid="81675">It was so long ago... what was his name? Con Sai? Song Gan? I think that was it. He was more concerned with trade than anything else.</string>
  <string id="61882" soundid="81676">Master Li set the village on a different path. Shortly after he arrived, Song Gan left. I am not sure what became of him.</string>
  <string id="61883" soundid="119172">But true. The throne will be mine someday. Who is to say that I should live in the shadow of my father and his traditions all my life?</string>
  <string id="61884" soundid="81678">Yes, you tried to tell me that already. I&apos;m too old for games, child. Especially ones with such potentially disruptive outcomes.</string>
  <string id="61885" soundid="81679">He... said he was... Sun Li? Now child, it is not wise to lie to your elders. Especially ones not shy about boxing your ears.</string>
  <string id="61886" soundid="81680">What an odd thing to say. Sun Li. Hah! What a fuss that would cause. Twenty years unraveled.</string>
  <string id="61887" soundid="81681">It is folly to even imagine it, but if you insist.</string>
  <string id="61888" soundid="81682">Sun Li the Glorious Strategist died twenty years ago in a battle so tragic that only the Emperor knows the true details.</string>
  <string id="61889" soundid="81683">If he were alive, it would mean that the Emperor&apos;s word is questionable. For no other reason than that, it must be impossible.</string>
  <string id="61890" soundid="81684">And before you jump on it, I am well aware that Sun Li died near the time your Master Li arrived here with you.</string>
  <string id="61891" soundid="81685">Coincidence is the plaything of fox spirits. Tricks to twist the minds of mortals like us.</string>
  <string id="61892" soundid="81686">I think you&apos;re a bunch of noise-making hoodlums, no better than rabble. Then again, I think that of everyone.</string>
  <string id="61893" soundid="81687">For every Dawn Star there is a Gao. That should be enough to show my meaning.</string>
  <string id="61894" soundid="81688">If it isn&apos;t, I could talk all day and not help you.</string>
  <string id="61895" soundid="81689">Most are well liked, but as I said, there are exceptions.</string>
  <string id="61896" soundid="81690">You flatter an old man by indulging his stories more than once. I didn&apos;t think I was so interesting.</string>
  <string id="61897" soundid="81691">What would you have me speak about?</string>
  <string id="61898" soundid="81692">All my life. More years than I can remember. Very little has changed.</string>
  <string id="61899" soundid="81693">I used to grow rice. Now I live on a small stipend sent by my son. He has long since moved farther south in the Golden Delta.</string>
  <string id="61900" soundid="81694">He never comes to visit--typical--but the silver reminds me that he cares. If these bones get any more creaky, maybe I&apos;ll move down with him.</string>
  <string id="61901" soundid="81695">Good on you! History is best taught through stories. A teacher lecturing about the past is like listening to paper crumple when you want to hear a waterfall!</string>
  <string id="61902" soundid="81696">Hmm? Perhaps you think I have an affinity for spirits since I am close to becoming one myself? I&apos;m not that old yet.</string>
  <string id="61903" soundid="81697">I keep my feet toward the earth and my head as straight in the opposite direction as I can manage. I wish others were as practical.</string>
  <string id="61904" soundid="81698">I have heard many ghost stories lately. Travelers talk of roads awash in spirits. I am quicker to blame that on bowls of wine than a glut of the dead.</string>
  <string id="61905" soundid="119173">That will be meaningless if Death&apos;s Hand keeps his hold on my father&apos;s mind. I fear one day he may try to... interfere with the Imperial succession.</string>
  <string id="61906" soundid="81700">You are too young to know what it was like. A decade of thirst with all the land cracked and bare. It was worst in the great cities.</string>
  <string id="61907" soundid="81701">Riots claimed hundreds of thousands of lives. Emperor Sun Hai put all his influence toward ending the drought and saved us all, but there was a cost.</string>
  <string id="61908" soundid="119174">Or perhaps convince my father that he should be Emperor by marriage.</string>
  <string id="61909" soundid="81703">I don&apos;t know where the front line was, or the name of the enemy, but the Emperor&apos;s own brothers, Sun Kin and Sun Li, were lost.</string>
  <string id="61910" soundid="81704">As I said, the Emperor corrected whatever great offense to the heavens that had afflicted the Empire and thus ended the drought.</string>
  <string id="61911" soundid="81705">That isn&apos;t answer enough for you, I know. For the young it never is.</string>
  <string id="61912" soundid="81706">In time, you will understand that the Emperor must deal with things that you are not meant to know or comprehend.</string>
  <string id="61913" soundid="81707">I have faith in the order of things. The Emperor knows things that I am not meant to.</string>
  <string id="61914" soundid="81708">If the fisherman sends his catch to market, does the customer need to know how to fish? No, he just knows that someone else does.</string>
  <string id="61915" soundid="81709">That is the order of things. It is real, and I know it works. Ghosts and shadows are tavern tales.</string>
  <string id="61916" soundid="81710">Oh, I don&apos;t dare speak of Emperor Sun. My words can&apos;t do proper justice to his glory. He is a hero to many.</string>
  <string id="61917" soundid="81711">Ending the drought earned him great respect, even if he no longer shows his influence this far from the walls of the Imperial City.</string>
  <string id="61918" soundid="81712">I would never suggest such a thing. He must simply have greater concerns elsewhere.</string>
  <string id="61919" soundid="81713">Master Li has commented that he much prefers that Two Rivers does not get any attention. It is a sign that all is well here.</string>
  <string id="61920" soundid="81714">Goodbye. I wish you luck finding Dawn Star.</string>
  <string id="61921" soundid="81715">For now? For as long as possible. Move along.</string>
  <string id="61922" soundid="81716">I wish you well.</string>
  <string id="61923">Lina</string>
  <string id="61924" soundid="81718">Now that is not the proper tone for addressing your elders. Typical, but not the proper tone at all.</string>
  <string id="61925">If you want my respect, you&apos;re going to have to pay for it.</string>
  <string id="61927" soundid="81721">Ha! I&apos;ll say. That&apos;s the problem with youth: It&apos;s impetuous enough to charge straight on with its eyes closed and gums flapping in the breeze.</string>
  <string id="61928" soundid="81722">Oh, you&apos;ve got some spirit in you, you do! Spirit enough for an impetuous young snot who hasn&apos;t learned proper respect for elders!</string>
  <string id="61933" soundid="142510">You&apos;re finally here to talk to Master Li, are you? I certainly hope so. The old man is in there meditating, and he won&apos;t train me until he talks to you.</string>
  <string id="61934" soundid="142511">Ha! The senior student, Master Li&apos;s little lapdog, here to talk to me. My lucky, lucky day. Don&apos;t you have something more important to do?</string>
  <string id="61935" soundid="142512">You don&apos;t want my answer to that question. Go talk to one of your sandal-licking friends and let them tell you I&apos;m jealous.</string>
  <string id="61936" soundid="142513">I&apos;m sure Wen could stammer out an answer for you, something to make you feel all warm inside and just great about yourself.</string>
  <string id="61939" soundid="160207"></string>
  <string id="61941">Drunken Soldier</string>
  <string id="61942">Think carefully about how much you value your arms before you speak that way again.</string>
  <string id="61944">No, I wouldn&apos;t dishonor myself by beating a dog.</string>
  <string id="61950">Might I ask some questions?</string>
  <string id="61951">One of the students was wounded during the bandit attack.</string>
  <string id="61953" soundid="119175">Indeed we cannot. I would bite my own tongue before ever allowing that... &quot;man&quot; to touch me.</string>
  <string id="61955">Do you know anything about Dawn Star&apos;s disappearance?</string>
  <string id="61956">Are any other students missing?</string>
  <string id="61957">Have you any clue where Dawn Star would go?</string>
  <string id="61958">How many paths out of the village are there?</string>
  <string id="61960">Let&apos;s go back to my other questions.</string>
  <string id="61961">What are your thoughts on Two Rivers?</string>
  <string id="61962">Who are the important citizens?</string>
  <string id="61963">Give me your opinion.</string>
  <string id="61965">What do you know about Master Li?</string>
  <string id="61966">How did Master Li come here?</string>
  <string id="61969">Who was master before Master Li?</string>
  <string id="61972">Master Li told me he was Sun Li the Glorious Strategist.</string>
  <string id="61974">Why would it be so disruptive?</string>
  <string id="61979">How are the students viewed?</string>
  <string id="61980">What do you mean?</string>
  <string id="61982">Tell me about yourself.</string>
  <string id="61983">How long have you lived in Two Rivers?</string>
  <string id="61984">What do you do?</string>
  <string id="61986">Can we talk a bit about the past?</string>
  <string id="61987">What do you know about the spirit world?</string>
  <string id="61990" soundid="119177">You forget yourself. You should not try so hard to flatter a princess. The attentions of royalty have their own price.</string>
  <string id="61991">And yet you accept the seemingly divine end of the drought?</string>
  <string id="61992">Tell me about the Long Drought.</string>
  <string id="61994" soundid="119178">In any case, I would never allow Death&apos;s Hand such liberty. I would bite my own tongue before allowing that... &quot;man&quot; to touch me.</string>
  <string id="61996">But what really happened?</string>
  <string id="61999">You accept that, but you&apos;re too &quot;practical&quot; for ghosts?</string>
  <string id="62002">Tell me about the Emperor.</string>
  <string id="62004">Is the Emperor neglecting the borderlands?</string>
  <string id="62006">Goodbye for now.</string>
  <string id="62007">Go away and stop bothering me, you old goat.</string>
  <string id="62008">I am sorry. I spoke without thinking.</string>
  <string id="62010">It&apos;s a proper enough tone for addressing senile old fools.</string>
  <string id="62012">I&apos;m ready right now, if you dare face me.</string>
  <string id="62015" soundid="144384">Everything&apos;s lost in the translation.</string>
  <string id="62017">To the Inner Courtyard</string>
  <string id="62018">Actually, I wanted to talk to you a moment.</string>
  <string id="62019">What did I do to earn this belligerence?</string>
  <string id="62024" soundid="81818">I haven&apos;t seen or heard anything. Someone else might have time to track you students, but I don&apos;t.</string>
  <string id="62025" soundid="81819">Only one, but it passes by the swamps. You don&apos;t want to travel through there alone.</string>
  <string id="62026" soundid="81820">Too many outlaws make their home in that marsh.</string>
  <string id="62027" soundid="81821">If you wish. What do you want to know?</string>
  <string id="62028" soundid="81822">Until word of bandits, the only notable trait of this sleepy town was an unwillingness to part with its silver.</string>
  <string id="62029" soundid="81823">Who could be more important than Master Li? He is the anchor of this town, and none question his wisdom.</string>
  <string id="62030" soundid="81824">No different from anyone else. If you keep to yourself, no one bothers you.</string>
  <string id="62031" soundid="81825">Well, *you* are always asking questions. That can be tiring.</string>
  <string id="62032" soundid="81826">Although I do prefer that over Gao&apos;s posturing. He is not well liked, but his father has money, so he gets his way.</string>
  <string id="62033" soundid="81827">I&apos;ve never set my eyes beyond the horizon you can see from here. There must be someone else you could ask.</string>
  <string id="62034" soundid="81828">I send my thanks to the spirits for successful journeys just like everyone else. I don&apos;t have any special insight.</string>
</tlk>