<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<tlk language="0">
  <string id="85214">If you find your enemy is immune to a particular style, try switching to a style from a different school. </string>
  <string id="85215">The bars in the upper left-hand corner of the screen show your Health (red), Chi (blue), and Focus (yellow).</string>
  <string id="85216">Magic styles use up Chi (blue bar), while weapon styles use up Focus (yellow bar).</string>
  <string id="85217">Press &lt;Menu&gt; to see more information about your character, fighting styles, journal, map, and other options.</string>
  <string id="85218">I have some questions for you.</string>
  <string id="85219">What has your time as a hunter taught you about this forest?</string>
  <string id="85221">Do you have any idea why this forest has grown ill?</string>
  <string id="85223">Press the &lt;ChiHeal&gt; key to spend Chi and regain Health.</string>
  <string id="85224">What&apos;s the story behind this temple?</string>
  <string id="85226">Why would he be embarrassed about a temple?</string>
  <string id="85227">I&apos;d be embarrassed too, the structure is gaudy.</string>
  <string id="85229">That&apos;s enough about the forest. You mentioned philosophy earlier?</string>
  <string id="85230">What sort of philosophy would you contemplate here?</string>
  <string id="85236">Push &lt;FreeTarget&gt; to enter Free Target mode. Push it again to exit.</string>
  <string id="85239">A book icon on the left side of the screen indicates a new journal entry. </string>
  <string id="85240">Wouldn&apos;t hunting be an evil act?</string>
  <string id="85242">Switch targets by hitting &lt;NextPage&gt;.</string>
  <string id="85245">I&apos;m not sure I have the luxury of balance.</string>
  <string id="85246">Pause the game in combat by pushing &lt;CombatPause&gt;. Push it again to unpause.</string>
  <string id="85247">Once you have more than one follower, you can switch among them on the Followers screen in the Start menu.</string>
  <string id="85250">Let&apos;s go back to my questions about the forest.</string>
  <string id="85251">That&apos;s enough questions for now.</string>
  <string id="85252">Goodbye.</string>
  <string id="85253" soundid="129284">You seem tired, Dawn Star. Make sure you get some rest; our journey will only get longer, and you&apos;ve been through a great deal.</string>
  <string id="85254" soundid="129285">Thank you, Zu. I&apos;m fine. I will find time once we have set things right.</string>
  <string id="85255" soundid="129286">The *Black* Whirlwind, and I barely fit in that Spectacular Gnat of yours. It lists like a pregnant ox when I step in.</string>
  <string id="85256" soundid="129287">It is hardly his fault, you are well in excess of a normal person&apos;s size.</string>
  <string id="85257" soundid="129288">Hey, Zu, why exactly are you here? I can&apos;t quite figure you out. You&apos;re much more of a loner than any of the others.</string>
  <string id="85258" soundid="129289">And you are much more a rogue than you let on. We each have things we keep to ourselves. If I wanted you to know them, you wouldn&apos;t have to ask.</string>
  <string id="85259" soundid="129290">Dawn Star, that&apos;s a very fitting name for you. Bright, cheerful, and beautiful.</string>
  <string id="85260" soundid="129291">That&apos;s kind of you to say, Sky, but I fear it is rooted in something far darker.</string>
  <string id="85262">Silver &lt;CUSTOM0&gt;</string>
  <string id="85263">The flyer you took from Gao&apos;s men in Two Rivers proved as untrustworthy as its original owners. Pirates around the village of Tien&apos;s Landing seem to have similar devices, however, so it may be worth your time to try and seek them out.</string>
  <string id="85264">Find a New Flyer</string>
  <string id="85267" soundid="129298">Hmmm... you&apos;re a princess, eh? You don&apos;t look like any nobility I&apos;ve ever seen.</string>
  <string id="85268" soundid="129299">And what, pray tell, does nobility look like to a wine-soaked sot like you?</string>
  <string id="85269" soundid="129300">Wide-eyed and terror-stricken when I kick in their doors. But I guess that&apos;s why you live in a palace in the sky... not so easy to break those doors down.</string>
  <string id="85270" soundid="129301">What? I said she *wasn&apos;t* like the nobility I&apos;m used to. Besides... if she wanted to be pampered, she wouldn&apos;t be here. </string>
  <string id="85271" soundid="129302">I&apos;d like to know, er, Silk Fox, why do you go to the trouble to dress up like... that? As Princess, couldn&apos;t you just command that changes be made? </string>
  <string id="85272" soundid="129303">You can&apos;t understand. My place in the order of things is as much a cage as yours, but stepping down grants certain opportunities to influence that are unavailable to you.</string>
  <string id="85273" soundid="129304">What do you mean by that?</string>
  <string id="85274" soundid="129305">So... ah, Kang, how many iterations of your flyers did you make before settling on such a... safe design?</string>
  <string id="85275">You dare resist?!</string>
  <string id="85276">Die, filth!</string>
  <string id="85279" soundid="129310">The Imperial City must be somewhat bewildering to you, Dawn Star. If you need anything explained, I will be happy to assist you.</string>
  <string id="85280">You are nothing!</string>
  <string id="85281">My will prevails!</string>
  <string id="85282">Your end is here!</string>
  <string id="85283">Die now!</string>
  <string id="85284" soundid="129315">This will likely get me into trouble, but I have to ask. Is your wife really that bad, Hou? You must be... exaggerating to some degree, right?</string>
  <string id="85285" soundid="129316">I exaggerate nothing, but I will not discuss such things so close to my home here in the city. My watchful wife has habit of appearing when I least expect it.</string>
  <string id="85286" soundid="129317">It must be very difficult for you to bear such a burden, Wild Flower, to be so young and anchor such a creature. I can sense the turmoil within you.</string>
  <string id="85287" soundid="129318">Hmm... sometimes it&apos;s hard, but then the Guardian tells me it&apos;s all right, and it is! I try my best for him.</string>
  <string id="85288" soundid="129319">Kang! When will you fix your flying barrel to fit real people?</string>
  <string id="85289" soundid="129320">What is the problem, Whirlwind?  </string>
  <string id="85294">Be careful how you address the Emperor&apos;s daughter.</string>
  <string id="85297">Your life is over!</string>
  <string id="85303">I am restored!</string>
  <string id="85304">You... you poisoned me?!</string>
  <string id="85312">Your reluctance is well founded, Dawn Star.</string>
  <string id="85316">Gate</string>
  <string id="85317">Door</string>
  <string id="85318">Door</string>
  <string id="85347" soundid="152350">I promised you I wouldn&apos;t be a distraction, but I have to say something.</string>
  <string id="85350" soundid="129452"></string>
  <string id="85352">You sicken me!</string>
  <string id="85354">I want to talk about Gentle Breezes.</string>
  <string id="85356">I want you to resign your post, Fang.</string>
  <string id="85358">Your activities cost you your Imperial Ring.</string>
  <string id="85359">Breezes gave me your Imperial Ring.</string>
  <string id="85362">You&apos;re going to step down, Fang.</string>
  <string id="85363">The Lotus Assassins want you out of the picture.</string>
  <string id="85364">Give me a letter of resignation. Right now.</string>
  <string id="85367">I&apos;m proud to get a man like you out of office.</string>
  <string id="85372">Your own perversions brought this on you.</string>
  <string id="85373">Just give me your resignation.</string>
  <string id="85374" soundid="129476">You better go talk to Fang about that ring.</string>
  <string id="85375" soundid="129477">Yeah, we don&apos;t want any part of this.</string>
  <string id="85376" soundid="129478">Forget it! I won&apos;t go into details about what Fang did to the last guard he caught taking bribes, but restraints, starving dogs, and gravy on certain parts of the body were involved.</string>
  <string id="85377" soundid="129479">Fang watched the whole thing, laughing all the while. And when it was done, he went upstairs with Breezes for a little relaxation. Poor girl.</string>
  <string id="85378" soundid="129480">Thanks, champ. We appreciate it.</string>
  <string id="85379" soundid="129481">Okay. Good luck in your next fight.</string>
  <string id="85380" soundid="129482">Good idea. Come back next month. Fang might be taking appointments by then.</string>
  <string id="85381" soundid="129483"></string>
  <string id="85382" soundid="129484">Wow, the Imperial Champion! Hey, it&apos;s a real honor to have you come up here but... uh... you&apos;re going to have to back up. Please.</string>
  <string id="85383" soundid="129485">Nothing personal, but we work for Fang and he doesn&apos;t want anyone blocking his view. He comes to watch the fights, not talk to the fighters.</string>
  <string id="85384" soundid="129486"></string>
  <string id="85385" soundid="129487">Saw you out there in the ring. You got real potential. Even Fang was impressed.</string>
  <string id="85386" soundid="129488">But that doesn&apos;t mean he wants you blocking his view, so back up. He comes here to watch the fights, not talk to the fighters.</string>
  <string id="85387" soundid="129489">I guess he figures the more he talks to you, the less time you have to inflict horrible, bloody carnage on someone in the ring.</string>
  <string id="85388" soundid="129490">Normally Fang&apos;s into rough girls, but he likes them dirty, too. You&apos;re a bit too classy for his tastes. He&apos;d rather watch you in the ring than have a more intimate meeting.</string>
  <string id="85389" soundid="129491">Whoa! Back up a bit there. Judge Fang doesn&apos;t like people blocking his view of the arena.</string>
  <string id="85390" soundid="129492">Yeah, you might make him miss out on seeing someone get their nose broken. Or their leg. Or even their skull.</string>
  <string id="85391" soundid="129493">He was just saying how there hasn&apos;t been a good skull fracture for at least a week. It&apos;s put him in a foul mood.</string>
  <string id="85392" soundid="129494">Even a pretty lady like you. You might make him miss out on someone getting their nose broken. Or their leg. Or even their skull.</string>
  <string id="85393" soundid="129495">Look, we already told you, Fang doesn&apos;t want to be bothered. He just wants to relax and watch the arena fights.</string>
  <string id="85394" soundid="129496">Yeah. If he doesn&apos;t get his daily fill of blood, violence, and gore, he&apos;ll be snarly all day. And he&apos;s hard enough to work for when he&apos;s in a good mood.</string>
  <string id="85395" soundid="129497">How did you get... no, forget it. I don&apos;t want to know.</string>
  <string id="85396" soundid="129498">I wouldn&apos;t call him sick and twisted. That&apos;s an insult to sick and twisted people everywhere. Fang&apos;s on a whole other level.</string>
  <string id="85397" soundid="129499">I never used to believe the stories, but now that I&apos;m working for him, I can honestly say he&apos;s the most degenerate and perverted man in the whole Empire.</string>
  <string id="85398" soundid="129500">But he pays well. Very well. Enough so that we pretend not to see what&apos;s going on. Though I still feel bad for Breezes sometimes.</string>
  <string id="85399" soundid="129501">Gentle Breezes. She&apos;s Fang&apos;s... uh... concubine. She&apos;s over in the next room with the common folk. Fang doesn&apos;t like to be seen with her in public.</string>
  <string id="85400" soundid="129502">He doesn&apos;t mind her getting up close and personal when they&apos;re in private, though. The things she does for him...</string>
  <string id="85401" soundid="129503">Sometimes he makes us watch. Gives him an extra thrill, I guess, but I usually have to block out most of what they do. Breezes has got a stronger stomach than I do.</string>
  <string id="85402" soundid="129504">Not without an appointment. And his schedule&apos;s full for the next month. All the ministers are coming in from the outlying towns to make their reports.</string>
  <string id="85403" soundid="129505">If he&apos;s not meeting with a minister, he&apos;s relaxing here. Hoping to see somebody beaten to a quivering pulp in the ring, or maybe torn apart by one of the animals.</string>
  <string id="85404" soundid="129506">Yeah, that or he&apos;s taking a break with Breezes. Poor girl. No amount of silver is worth what she does for him.</string>
  <string id="85417">I&apos;ve got Fang&apos;s Imperial Ring.</string>
  <string id="85418">Sounds like one sick and twisted man.</string>
  <string id="85421">Who is Breezes?</string>
  <string id="85424">Can I speak to Judge Fang?</string>
  <string id="85427">Let me speak to Fang and I&apos;ll make it worth your while.</string>
  <string id="85429">I&apos;ll be going now.</string>
  <string id="85645" soundid="129880">You have come from Tien&apos;s Landing?</string>
  <string id="85646" soundid="129881">You were? This is good. I was going there, but you&apos;re coming here instead.</string>
  <string id="85648" soundid="129883">There are many ghosts here. You have to be fast to get around them and quiet or they will hear you.</string>
  <string id="85649" soundid="129884">I come from the inn, the Pilgrim&apos;s Rest. You must take a message to the town for us!</string>
  <string id="85650" soundid="129885">Things are very bad. We starve! The ghosts cut us off from everything, but we are still up there. Tien&apos;s Landing must send people to help!</string>
  <string id="85651" soundid="129886">Ugh! This poor soul has been in the forest too long. He feels... wrong, just like the air here. It&apos;s disturbing. </string>
  <string id="85652" soundid="129887">He seems... simple, as well. I wonder if the horrors of this place have touched his mind.</string>
  <string id="85653" soundid="129888">Chai Ka: This one&apos;s mind seems... unbalanced.</string>
  <string id="85654" soundid="154558">Your end is here, mortal!</string>
  <string id="85655" soundid="129890">I&apos;ve known a few fellows who sounded like this, and not one of them was right in the head.</string>
  <string id="85656" soundid="129891">If I had to guess, I&apos;d say this mongrel&apos;s mind has collapsed on itself from being trapped in this ghost-infested place.</string>
  <string id="85657" soundid="129892">Many people should come to the inn to help us. They can&apos;t let us starve!</string>
  <string id="85658" soundid="129893">You would be welcome there. They would have you for a most fun stay!</string>
  <string id="85659" soundid="129894">The inn lies above, on the path to the right.</string>
  <string id="85660" soundid="129895">The temple? No! The temple is where the ghosts are worst. It is a bad place. You should not go there. You should go to the inn.</string>
  <string id="85661" soundid="129896">No, I should... I should return to the inn. They will want to know you are coming.</string>
  <string id="85662" soundid="129897">You should come with me. I can take the message down later, and you will be safe from the Forest Shadow and her ghosts!</string>
  <string id="85663" soundid="129898">She is a wicked fox spirit! They are tricksters, all of them. The tricks she plays kill now!</string>
  <string id="85664" soundid="129899">You should stay away from her. She hurts us when we leave the inn.</string>
  <string id="85665" soundid="129900">Oh yes, they must be. She hunts us, and these ghosts hunt you, right? Isn&apos;t that the same?</string>
  <string id="85666" soundid="129901">That can&apos;t be right. She is dangerous. You should go to the inn to be kept safe. That&apos;s the only way.</string>
  <string id="85667" soundid="129902">I will go back the way I came. Knowing that there are others here, I will be all right.</string>
  <string id="85668" soundid="129903">I must go back to the inn to tell them. You should follow! The path to the right, not the left. Left goes to the temple, and the Forest Shadow will kill you!</string>
  <string id="85669" soundid="129904">Come! The inn is this way!</string>
  <string id="85670">Kang the Mad has locked the Temple Gate behind his party as a last line of defense if the mission to destroy the bridge proved to be unsuccessful.</string>
  <string id="85671">Yes, I was in Tien&apos;s Landing.</string>
  <string id="85673">Who are you?</string>
  <string id="85675">Why are you wandering alone with so many ghosts around?</string>
  <string id="85680">Where is this Pilgrim&apos;s Rest Inn?</string>
  <string id="85682">I&apos;m looking for a temple on the path above. Can you direct me?</string>
  <string id="85683">I will escort you to Tien&apos;s Landing. You can take the message yourself.</string>
  <string id="85684">I don&apos;t have time to baby-sit some simpleton. Make your own way.</string>
  <string id="85686">Tell me more about the Forest Shadow.</string>
  <string id="85688">These ghosts are the Forest Shadow&apos;s minions?</string>
  <string id="85689">Others I&apos;ve talked to seemed to think the Forest Shadow might be able to help.</string>
  <string id="85690">I should keep moving. Will you be all right in this forest?</string>
  <string id="85692">I&apos;ve had about enough of you. Go where you wish.</string>
  <string id="85695" soundid="129993">You make a wise decision, thin-blood. Our people will prosper now that you have freed us from the fox. Take this scroll and study it when you have the chance.</string>
  <string id="85697" soundid="129995">As a final gift, we give you this... cook. He is useless to us; he shivers like a leaf in winter. Remove him before his weakness infects us.</string>
  <string id="85698" soundid="129996">Ha! That is why we like you! You are practically one of us, but for all that, your blood is still thin and watery!</string>
  <string id="85699" soundid="129997">Do you see those arms? That neck? No, there is no strength to be found in this one, not for us.</string>
  <string id="85700" soundid="129998">It is said that this one knows a secret: a style rarely seen in the Jade Empire. If nothing else, you may be able to extract it from him.</string>
  <string id="85701" soundid="129999">Now go. Leave us to our plans.</string>
  <string id="85702" soundid="130000">My people, this is the treachery of the thin-bloods! Gather, and we will show this fool our true strength!</string>
  <string id="85703" soundid="130001">Gaze upon our forms and bask in our glory! You should be honored to see the true strength of the cannibals!</string>
  <string id="85704" soundid="130002">Didn&apos;t see that coming. If they&apos;re as aggressive as they are ugly, then this will get bloody fast. The faster the better!</string>
  <string id="85705" soundid="130003">Chai Ka: Cannibals. Twisted servants of a greater demon. This explains the forest&apos;s corruption.</string>
  <string id="85706" soundid="130004">It&apos;s them! Their corruption is what I have been feeling in this forest. They are... vile!</string>
  <string id="85707" soundid="130005">I&apos;m suddenly very glad I didn&apos;t order anything from the kitchen.</string>
  <string id="85709" soundid="130007">Under a demon&apos;s influence, men can twist into these things. They are cannibals, and we are in danger. Don&apos;t underestimate their strength!</string>
  <string id="85710" soundid="130008">I sense in you a kindred spirit. You know power for what it is: a tool to sweep aside those weaker than you.</string>
  <string id="85711" soundid="130009">Because of your nature, I wanted to work with you in the open. We are the powerful ones in this forest, and our majesty must spread!</string>
  <string id="85712" soundid="130010">We are sensitive to strength, and you are not like the meat out there. You speak with power and conviction. We can respect such strength.</string>
  <string id="85713" soundid="130011">Some part of you must have known that the Spirit did not detest us because we were weak humans! No, she feared our majesty!</string>
  <string id="85714" soundid="130012">Are you happy, now that you have the answer to your prying questions? No, of course not. You wish to know more. You are drawn to our majesty!</string>
  <string id="85715" soundid="130013">Intriguing, yes? Such power is hard to resist, is it not?</string>
  <string id="85716" soundid="130014">You know nothing of beauty. You know nothing at all!</string>
  <string id="85717" soundid="130015">How typical of the thin-blooded ones, to think that they can kill all that they do not understand.</string>
  <string id="85718" soundid="130016">You must understand that we are servants of a powerful demon known as the Mother, who has taught us to draw strength from human flesh!</string>
  <string id="85719" soundid="130017">The Forest Shadow imprisoned her millennia ago, but you have freed her! Our Mother will rise up and consume all who stand in her way.</string>
  <string id="85720" soundid="130018">Your kind is concerned with nothing more than silver and prizes. You are pathetic and weak willed. </string>
  <string id="85721" soundid="130019">Fine, human. You will have more than we agreed upon. We gathered the silver while you were off killing the Forest Shadow.</string>
  <string id="85722" soundid="130020">You think you can end a feud older than your petty Empire by destroying both sides?</string>
  <string id="85723" soundid="130021">Such foolish pride. With the fox dead, the Mother is free! She will consume all, and you will be first!</string>
  <string id="85724" soundid="130022">You have already killed the fox! This forest will only grow worse, no matter what you do.</string>
  <string id="85725" soundid="130023">The Mother is too strong for you. She will consume all who stand in her way, and you will be first!</string>
  <string id="85726" soundid="130024">The Forest Shadow imprisoned her millennia ago, but soon she will be free! You will help us with that, or you will die!</string>
  <string id="85727" soundid="130025">That makes two of us.</string>
  <string id="85728" soundid="130026">(Hiss.) Freaks! You are nothing but meat!</string>
  <string id="85729" soundid="130027">We have made you an offer. The bargain was vast amounts of your precious silver for the life of the Forest Shadow. Now we add your life to the deal, as well. </string>
  <string id="85730" soundid="130028">The fox holds the Mother trapped within the earth of this hill, but she can hold nothing with dying paws. </string>
  <string id="85731" soundid="130029">The dead walk the world, and the Mother can draw strength from them. That is how she reached out to us... told us of the new way.</string>
  <string id="85732" soundid="130030">The Mother grows stronger each day, but she is still trapped, and the Forest Shadow is not yet so weak as to be easily taken. She knows us instantly, so we have no surprise.</string>
  <string id="85733" soundid="130031">You are unknown. We cannot defeat her, but she cannot destroy us so easily, either. She will try to pour honey into your ears, beg for your help.</string>
  <string id="85734" soundid="130032">When her guard is down, then you will destroy her, and the Mother will be free!</string>
  <string id="85735" soundid="130033">She is a most powerful creature from a time when primal hunger ruled all of your kind. She has been trapped in this hill for centuries... trapped by the fox.</string>
  <string id="85736" soundid="130034">But as the dead grow restless, she feels their anger, their rage, and their hunger for release. They feed the Mother, and she grows strong as the ghosts flock to her.</string>
  <string id="85737" soundid="130035">She reached out to us. We are her children, and I am first among them!</string>
  <string id="85738" soundid="130036">She is the filthy fox spirit that imprisoned the Mother centuries before the Empire was born. Like all foxes, she is a trickster and thinks of herself as a judge of wrong and right.</string>
  <string id="85739" soundid="130037">She claimed this forest as hers, gloating over the imprisonment of the Mother, but she did not count on the ghosts filling her forest.</string>
  <string id="85740" soundid="130038">The Mother called to them, and their rage, their hunger for release, has restored much of her strength. The time of the fox is over!</string>
  <string id="85741" soundid="130039">You are so very stupid. What the Mother has given us is no curse! This is power!</string>
  <string id="85742" soundid="130040">We eat the flesh of your kind, and its energies make us strong! The Mother has beautified us in return for serving her.</string>
  <string id="85743" soundid="130041">You should not speak about killing the Mother. It is a sacrilege that makes our blood boil with rage!</string>
  <string id="85744" soundid="130042">What will it be? Do you value your life, or will you play the fool?</string>
  <string id="85745" soundid="130043">You just don&apos;t understand. You will!</string>
  <string id="85746" soundid="130044">You have made a very wise decision. I would suspect that you were lying to me, but only a fool would think to cross us.</string>
  <string id="85747" soundid="130045">Our offer stands firm. Go swiftly, and there may be even more than silver awaiting you.</string>
  <string id="85748" soundid="130046">Monsters? We are perfection! Allow us to demonstrate the truth!</string>
  <string id="85749" soundid="130047">Rend her flesh! Her screams should echo in the town below!</string>
  <string id="85750" soundid="130048">Tear him to pieces! We will feast tonight on those succulent flanks!</string>
  <string id="85751" soundid="130049">Where did you... Ahhhh! The Spirit! She is dead, and you are returned to us by the heavens themselves!</string>
  <string id="85752" soundid="130050">You have done us a great service, and soon we will feast... to celebrate.</string>
  <string id="85753" soundid="130051">Did she? Did she cry it out with her dying breath? Ha! The Forest Shadow is not so powerful.</string>
  <string id="85754" soundid="130052">Oh, and you shall have it. Yes, you shall have a most special reward.</string>
  <string id="85755" soundid="130053">She did deserve her death, and you... you deserve so much more.</string>
  <string id="85756" soundid="130054">I offer you a most unique chance. Look, and see the glory you have set free!</string>
  <string id="85757" soundid="130055">See us as we truly are!</string>
  <string id="85758" soundid="130056">You have a spirit to kill, do you not? We will know when she is dead, for the Mother will be free.</string>
  <string id="85759" soundid="130057">Go to the temple. Find a way to get her attention or track her down. Once you have her, tear her head from her shoulders.</string>
  <string id="85760" soundid="130058">Until you have succeeded, do not bother me unless you wish to lose an arm.</string>
  <string id="85761" soundid="130059">You know more than you need to, human.</string>
  <string id="85762" soundid="130060">Gather the cook and leave us before we grow hungry.</string>
  <string id="85763" soundid="130061">Leave before our hunger prompts us to have you for dinner.</string>
  <string id="85764" soundid="130062">I watched in awe as you dispatched those... things! Not many of your kind can deal with ghosts as easily as you did! </string>
  <string id="85765" soundid="130063">Yes, the ghosts are most dangerous. We are fortunate that they have not yet ventured inside the inn. It offers us some refuge.</string>
  <string id="85766" soundid="130064">What help could we offer to someone like you?</string>
  <string id="85767" soundid="130065">No, no, no, heavens no! You are a warrior, are you not? Bound by honor and given strength by training? Is that not the noblest of classes?</string>
  <string id="85768" soundid="130066">No apologies needed. These are stressful times for us all.</string>
  <string id="85769" soundid="130067">You are of a kind, aren&apos;t you? Clearly deserving of respect and consideration.</string>
  <string id="85770" soundid="130068">But I&apos;ve forgotten myself. Welcome to the Pilgrim&apos;s Rest, traveler. I am the Keeper, as they call me.</string>
  <string id="85772" soundid="137229">You know what I like about private clubs? The tasteful decor.</string>
  <string id="85773" soundid="137230">The Tien&apos;s Landing teahouse has a reputation as a rough place. Should be entertaining.</string>
  <string id="85774" soundid="137231">Stranded sailors make for rich courtesans. At this rate, these ladies will own half the town before long.</string>
  <string id="85777" soundid="130075">Tell me, did you happen to come across one of us on your way up here? We sent him not long ago to search for help.</string>
  <string id="85780" soundid="135877">Oh, nothing that matters now. It was a fool&apos;s hope to think I might learn anything.</string>
  <string id="85781" soundid="135878">I am tasked with safeguarding any lands that I own, and this land is far from safe. To admit failure would be... unfortunate for my house.</string>
  <string id="85783" soundid="130081">It was the Forest Shadow! She has taken another from us!</string>
  <string id="85787" soundid="137237">Too far to jump. We&apos;ll have to find another way.</string>
  <string id="85788" soundid="130086">We are a long way from the Imperial City here. The tax collector&apos;s arms are only so long, you know.</string>
  <string id="85789" soundid="130087">There can be no other way. The Forest Shadow must die... to save us and cure this forest.</string>
  <string id="85793">Gem of Pure Flame</string>
  <string id="85799">Gem of Freezing</string>
  <string id="85801" soundid="130099">You must join us for dinner. You would be a most welcome addition!</string>
  <string id="85802" soundid="130100">The Mother? Nothing. Nothing at all. You should not speak nonsense when the Forest Shadow is still alive!</string>
  <string id="85803" soundid="130101">Did he? How... unfortunate. We should have tipped him into his own pot weeks ago!</string>
  <string id="85804" soundid="130102">You truly wish to know? Your mind will not rest until you have an answer?</string>
  <string id="85805" soundid="130103">You are lucky that I sense such great strength from you. Had you dealt with those ghosts out front with less efficiency, I would tear your throat out.</string>
  <string id="85806" soundid="130104">But, please, allow me to reveal all that you wish to see. Let me show you the truth!</string>
  <string id="85807" soundid="130105">We shall forget this moment, then, shall we? Do you wish to know anything else?</string>
  <string id="85808" soundid="130106">This is the mad fox&apos;s place. I shudder to dwell too long on the subject, but I will answer what I can.</string>
  <string id="85809" soundid="130107">The forest has been ailing for some time now, but things have been especially bad over the past month.</string>
  <string id="85810" soundid="130108">It has been most unpleasant for us. No new visitors grace our tables with their presence.</string>
  <string id="85811" soundid="130109">I do not know. Maybe the fox spirit that claims to protect this place has diseased it, or perhaps she is just too weak to fight another disease.</string>
  <string id="85812" soundid="130110">I don&apos;t care what happens to her, so long as my people... those of us at the inn, I mean, stay safe.</string>
  <string id="85813" soundid="130111">I have heard that the Pilgrim&apos;s Path stays open to the town of Tien&apos;s Landing.</string>
  <string id="85814" soundid="130112">One day, when the time is right, we shall make our way down there. Tien&apos;s Landing is full of so many people.</string>
  <string id="85815" soundid="130113">I do, as well. This forest is an uncomfortable topic for us all.</string>
  <string id="85816" soundid="130114">Many travelers know the name of the Pilgrim&apos;s Rest, and before long, so will many more.</string>
  <string id="85817" soundid="130115">It is an old name. The route you climbed used to be called the Pilgrim&apos;s Path, thanks largely to the temple near here, and other small shrines.</string>
  <string id="85818" soundid="130116">Here, at the hill&apos;s summit, the pilgrims would stay and contemplate what they had seen during their climb. </string>
  <string id="85819" soundid="130117">This place was known as the Pilgrim&apos;s Rest long before the inn was constructed.</string>
  <string id="85820" soundid="130118">Of course. This whole forest belongs to Lord Yun, does it not? He expects this place to pay him a &quot;tribute.&quot; He doesn&apos;t call it that, but we know the truth.</string>
  <string id="85821" soundid="130119">Mark me. Lord Yun will have his share of the proceeds from this place before long. His fair share.</string>
  <string id="85822" soundid="130120">Surviving? Simple. You can still find meat if you know where to look, and is meat not the heart of any good dish?</string>
  <string id="85823" soundid="130121">The sick trees and ghosts, yes, they keep us from the animals. You make a good point, but still, we saw this coming, did we not?</string>
  <string id="85824" soundid="130122">Of course, of course. Those are important for the blood, are they not? They keep it rich and fresh.</string>
  <string id="85825" soundid="130123">We have supplies. It always pays to be prepared.</string>
  <string id="85826" soundid="130124">Of course.</string>
  <string id="85827" soundid="130125">There must be some way to trap the fox. We will find it somehow.</string>
  <string id="85829" soundid="175977">Hold! That&apos;s enough.</string>
  <string id="85830">Follow through on your end of the deal, and we part in peace, keeper.</string>
  <string id="85833">I&apos;ll take him off your hands.</string>
  <string id="85834">He&apos;ll find a way to be useful to me, or he will die.</string>
  <string id="85836">Keep and eat him. He&apos;s no use to either of us.</string>
  <string id="85839">You&apos;ve gathered the silver? Good, because I&apos;m going to destroy you, as well.</string>
  <string id="85849">My nature made you want to reveal yourself?</string>
  <string id="85851">What magic allowed you to cloak yourself so?</string>
  <string id="85853">Majesty? You are disgusting!</string>
  <string id="85855">I don&apos;t know what you are, but you clearly need to die.</string>
  <string id="85858">Do what you wish; I&apos;m only here for my reward.</string>
  <string id="85859">Knowing what you are, the price of my aid has just gone up.</string>
  <string id="85861">This forest has seen enough meddling by demons and spirits. It&apos;s your turn to die.</string>
  <string id="85864">I see I was wrong. Destroying you will be my atonement.</string>
  <string id="85867">Why should I help you?</string>
  <string id="85868">I&apos;m having trouble feeling threatened by a group of freaks.</string>
  <string id="85872">Why not do this yourself? Why do you need my help?</string>
  <string id="85874">I&apos;m still not sure why you&apos;re turning to me.</string>
  <string id="85875">You admit that I am your superior?</string>
  <string id="85877">Tell me more about the Mother.</string>
  <string id="85880">Tell me about the Forest Shadow.</string>
  <string id="85883">What if I killed the Mother? Would that free you from this curse?</string>
  <string id="85886">I have made my decision.</string>
  <string id="85887">You must be destroyed. There&apos;s no other answer.</string>
  <string id="85889">[Lie] I should go find the Spirit now.</string>
  <string id="85891">I will aid you, but I expect to be repaid for my trouble.</string>
  <string id="85892">You&apos;re flesh-eating cannibals! I will never aid you monsters.</string>
  <string id="85897">The Spirit claimed she wasn&apos;t behind the ghosts in this forest.</string>
  <string id="85899">Your celebrations be damned. I&apos;m here for my reward.</string>
  <string id="85901">Spirits have no place manipulating us. She deserved her death.</string>
  <string id="85907">I&apos;m surprised anyone&apos;s still alive up here.</string>
  <string id="85909">It would have been easier with help.</string>
  <string id="85911">My kind? You mean to offend me?</string>
  <string id="85912">You meant no offense. I apologize for taking what was not there.</string>
  <string id="85914">Grovel some more, and I might not kill you.</string>
  <string id="85917" soundid="137244">Don&apos;t ask me how I know, but there&apos;s trouble ahead.</string>
  <string id="85921" soundid="164088">We should move. There could be....</string>
  <string id="85922" soundid="164089">There&apos;s one there! Are they coming out of the walls? I&apos;ll go make sure they aren&apos;t trying to cut us off! You deal with the Mother!</string>
  <string id="85923" soundid="164090">It&apos;s funny how this cave felt less crowded before Whirlwind arrived. Wait, what&apos;s....</string>
  <string id="85924" soundid="164091">Where did that rascal come from? Those small tunnels in the walls? Look, you three go ahead and deal with &quot;Mother.&quot; I&apos;ll make sure we don&apos;t get completely cut off.</string>
  <string id="85930">The man you sent to bring aid from Tien&apos;s Landing was killed.</string>
  <string id="85931">The simpleton? He died at the hands of a fox spirit.</string>
  <string id="85932" soundid="164092">Chai Ka: There are more. Many many more.</string>
  <string id="85933" soundid="137672">Nice place here. Government officials get the best warehouses to sleep in.</string>
  <string id="85934" soundid="137673">If this place is still looking to collect what I owe them, there could be trouble.</string>
  <string id="85937" soundid="137676">If I had to live here for more than a day, I&apos;d throw myself off the nearest cliff.</string>
  <string id="85938">Where would a humble innkeeper get that kind of money?</string>
  <string id="85939">Why are you so positive that she has to die?</string>
  <string id="85940" soundid="137677">The entire place is crumbling! Unless we want to be buried here, we&apos;d better hurry!</string>
  <string id="85942" soundid="161033">It sounds like they were being cautious. Perhaps if you go ask them more specifically about the crystal, they&apos;ll realize that we&apos;re just here to help.</string>
  <string id="85943">Tell me again how Drunken Master style works.</string>
  <string id="85944" soundid="161035">All signs point to the inn, and even if they didn&apos;t mention this missing crystal before, they will have to explain themselves if you confront them about it directly.</string>
  <string id="85945">When I was at the inn, they talked about some plan they had to &quot;deal&quot; with the fox.</string>
  <string id="85947">I&apos;ll go back to the inn and ask them about the missing crystal.</string>
  <string id="85956">I&apos;m not that easily beaten.</string>
  <string id="85957">You... fight dirty!</string>
  <string id="85958">What is the Mother?</string>
  <string id="85959">The cook called you &quot;twisted servants of the Mother.&quot;</string>
  <string id="85961">There&apos;s something wrong in this inn. What&apos;s really going on?</string>
  <string id="85965">You&apos;re right. I&apos;ll find more answers in the forest than I will here.</string>
  <string id="85966">Answer some questions for me about this area.</string>
  <string id="85967">How long has the forest been like this?</string>
  <string id="85969">What is causing the blight in the trees?</string>
  <string id="85971">Do you know of any routes out of the forest?</string>
  <string id="85973">I want to discuss another subject.</string>
  <string id="85974">Tell me more about this inn.</string>
  <string id="85975">How did this place earn its name?</string>
  <string id="85978">Is this inn the property of Lord Yun?</string>
  <string id="85980">With the forest in this state, how have you been surviving?</string>
  <string id="85981">How can you hunt with the forest in its current state?</string>
  <string id="85983">What of rice or vegetables? With no caravans, where do you find them?</string>
  <string id="85985">Let&apos;s talk about something else.</string>
  <string id="85986">I have to go and deal with this forest.</string>
  <string id="85987" soundid="130285">You left more destruction and shattered lives behind you than my wife shopping for a new hat!</string>
  <string id="85988" soundid="130286">I&apos;m clearly going crazy, but I wanted to be here. This... thing, mother, whatever... it has to be destroyed.</string>
  <string id="85989" soundid="130287">Why did you bring the cook? The next time you want things slaughtered, bring me! It&apos;s what I do best.</string>
  <string id="85990" soundid="130288">Spear Catches Leaf told me to look after you while you were in this forest, so let&apos;s see what we can do about this &quot;mother&quot; thing. Sounds like you&apos;ll need all the help you can get.</string>
  <string id="85991" soundid="130289">There&apos;s no way you&apos;re going down there without us. I came here to help you deal with this... &quot;Mother&quot; thing. Spear Catches Leaf told me to look after you, so here I am.</string>
  <string id="85992" soundid="163641">Eh? It&apos;s not like they need any of that anymore! Eh-heh, feel some compassion for them, do you? Maybe you don&apos;t have what it takes to do my job.</string>
  <string id="85993" soundid="130291">Yes, well... it&apos;s obvious you two are fine on your own. I&apos;ll just wait here.</string>
  <string id="85994" soundid="130292">Oh no you don&apos;t! We&apos;ll all go together. Besides, I need you to keep the wine flowing. I&apos;m always more dangerous when I&apos;m drunk.</string>
  <string id="85995" soundid="130293">Well, there&apos;s no turning back now. Who knows how many more cannibals are down there? When you&apos;re ready, let&apos;s finish this Mother off.</string>
  <string id="86001" soundid="163642">Then you&apos;re no better than me! We both just do the best we can with what we&apos;re given, so let&apos;s just leave it at that.</string>
  <string id="86014" soundid="144736">He carried a piece of your amulet. It was separated, broken apart, so your enemies could not find it easily. You have the first piece. It trains your abilities now.</string>
  <string id="86029" soundid="138152">You are weak and impure! You cannot stop the Mother or her people! Die now!</string>
  <string id="86030" soundid="138153">Lies! You are not cannibal or changing like these new ones. You are food!</string>
  <string id="86032">I&apos;m the one who will stop this sickness from spreading.</string>
  <string id="86086" soundid="144737">The second piece fell here with its minder, hidden until waters receded. A guardian protects it, waiting to test and serve you. The third piece awaits discovery in a distant lair.</string>
  <string id="86104">Don&apos;t mind me, I&apos;m just passing through.</string>
  <string id="86105">I am one of your kind!</string>
  <string id="86106" soundid="162511">This is a chance to isolate the leader of the troops! Death&apos;s Hand thinks that he and a group of Assassins will enter the temple unopposed, but I have a surprise.</string>
  <string id="86107" soundid="162512">I set traps... remember how I asked Kang for some of his explosive casks? The Assassins will be destroyed, and Death&apos;s Hand will be yours alone.</string>
  <string id="86160" soundid="130458">This should be fun. If there&apos;s enough of the little guys down there, this could be better than that time I stormed the Fortress of Seven Gates by myself!</string>
  <string id="86163">Dragon Powder</string>
  <string id="86164" soundid="130462">You have come this far. Impressive.</string>
  <string id="86165" soundid="130463">The Water Dragon may wish for you to find her, but I will not lie down and die, even if your death dooms us all.</string>
  <string id="86166" soundid="130464">My death will free the Mother. You... fool.</string>
  <string id="86167" soundid="130465">Neither of us has time to waste, but there is time to talk.</string>
  <string id="86168" soundid="130466">You must destroy my ancient enemy, the Mother. She has infected the people of the inn with her magic and twisted them into monsters. </string>
  <string id="86169" soundid="130467">They infest the caves beneath the Pilgrim&apos;s Rest and will defend their mistress to the death.</string>
  <string id="86170" soundid="130468">If you&apos;re thinking to learn our tricks, you will be disappointed. I&apos;ll happily tell you more of my kind if you wish, though.</string>
  <string id="86171">Dragon Powder</string>
  <string id="86172" soundid="130470">One of my kind might approach you as a wizened sage and ask for aid in studying an ancient artifact. Your response would determine the reaction.</string>
  <string id="86173" soundid="130471">You might expect this generosity to be rewarded, and many who think they are dealing with the fox take exactly this approach. They are fools.</string>
  <string id="86174" soundid="130472">To give without temperance encourages charlatans, liars, and thieves. Had you given that offer to me, I would have taken all you had to teach you a lesson.</string>
  <string id="86175" soundid="130473">Then you would be rewarded in some small way. Perhaps the artifact would be genuine, or the fox would offer you some information she had &quot;learned&quot; from the artifact.</string>
  <string id="86176" soundid="130474">Your response was proper, as you balanced your wealth with the &quot;sage&apos;s&quot; need, but did not do so foolishly.</string>
  <string id="86177" soundid="130475">As someone who had just come into more wealth than you could possibly need, you would be made to suffer in some way.</string>
  <string id="86179" soundid="130477">The fox has a nose for people&apos;s character, and we judge by their intentions as much as their actions.</string>
  <string id="86180" soundid="130478">No. Unlike many of my younger sisters, I am anchored to this place. More free to act upon your world than most spirits because of my connection to the trees.</string>
  <string id="86181" soundid="130479">The Mother is the dark balance to my lighter influence. You will find that most anchors are like that; the heavens maintain balance in all things.</string>
  <string id="86182" soundid="130480">It likely depends on what a fox has done to you. How easy to paint the persecutor as evil and the benefactor as good.</string>
  <string id="86183" soundid="130481">So long as we stay in our place, we foxes are merely servants of heaven. We fill a role few would envy.</string>
  <string id="86184" soundid="130482">Every class of spirit or demon is ordered by the Celestial Bureaucracy. We have our roles and powers, but we also have desires and personalities.</string>
  <string id="86185" soundid="130483">Some rebel against the will of heaven itself and follow their own hearts. Not all of those who do so are &quot;evil&quot; as you&apos;d define it, but they are certainly defiant.</string>
  <string id="86186" soundid="130484">Of course. What do you need?</string>
  <string id="86187" soundid="130485">A most ancient tale, and one long forgotten by your kind. The Mother tried to corrupt this forest once before and failed, leaving herself weakened.</string>
  <string id="86188">Student remains</string>
  <string id="86195">Chi +10

The Spirit Monks have long used the meditation wheels lining the entryway of Dirge&apos;s inner temple to aid their meditations. Three of the wheels spun freely during your meditations, and your spirit feels more in tune with your heritage as a result.</string>
  <string id="86196" soundid="191964"></string>
  <string id="86197" soundid="191965"></string>
  <string id="86200" soundid="191968">The natural order has been disrupted. There is much to say, but first, I was instructed to impart some very specific knowledge. Your Master was very clear.</string>
  <string id="86201" soundid="191969">Zu is an honorable man. Not a good man, perhaps, but an honorable one. Now, to your training; a brief description will reinforce in your mind the style you saw me use.</string>
  <string id="86203" soundid="191970">Certain lessons had to be withheld until you were ready for the attention they will bring. Sun Li taught me so that I would teach you. I must train you in Spirit Thief.</string>
  <string id="86204" soundid="191971">Magic and weapons tire you. Draw on them too much and you could be left defenseless. Spirit Thief restores your chi and focus, prolonging your ability to fight or ignore wounds.</string>
  <string id="86209" soundid="191972">It is especially useful when enemies are immune to basic martial attacks, when you *must* use magic or weapons. Spar with me. I was directed to test you personally.</string>
  <string id="86210" soundid="191973">Magic and weapons tire you. Draw on them too much and you could be left defenseless. Spirit Thief restores your chi, prolonging your ability to fight or ignore wounds.</string>
  <string id="86211" soundid="191974">Magic and weapons tire you. Draw on them too much and you could be left defenseless. Spirit Thief restores you, prolonging your ability to fight or ignore wounds.</string>
  <string id="86212" soundid="191975">It is time to continue your training, and I am honored to add to the basics that Sun Li instilled. A brief description should reinforce the style you saw me use.</string>
  <string id="86213" soundid="191976">Well done. You are quick to learn, as Sun Li said you would be. Speak with me in the Teahouse. We have much to discuss about your master, and how to find him.</string>
  <string id="86214" soundid="130512">As you wish.</string>
  <string id="86215" soundid="130513">Of course.</string>
  <string id="86216" soundid="130514">Shall I send you to the portal back to my temple, or would you prefer to walk among these islands a bit longer?</string>
  <string id="86217" soundid="130515">Breathe deeply. You will find yourself in other places where the air is less pure soon enough.</string>
  <string id="86218" soundid="130516">Time is of the essence. Go safely.</string>
  <string id="86220">What do I need to do to aid you again?</string>
  <string id="86222">Can I ask you some things about fox spirits?</string>
  <string id="86223">I keep hearing about the foxes&apos; tricks. Can you give me an example?</string>
  <string id="86224" soundid="191977">Use Spirit Thief to restore yourself, then you can attack or heal yourself.</string>
  <string id="86225">What if I offered as much money as the &quot;sage&quot; needed?</string>
  <string id="86228">Suppose I gave the &quot;sage&quot; some funds and demanded results. What then?</string>
  <string id="86231">If I turned this &quot;sage&quot; away, what would happen?</string>
  <string id="86234">Are most of your kind tied to nature in some way?</string>
  <string id="86236">Are fox spirits good or evil?</string>
  <string id="86238">What about those who don&apos;t stay in their place?</string>
  <string id="86240">Let&apos;s change the subject.</string>
  <string id="86241">Tell me about the history of your struggle with the Mother.</string>
  <string id="86242">I am always ready to learn.</string>
  <string id="86247">You presume to teach me?</string>
  <string id="86248">Shouldn&apos;t we talk about the Water Dragon or rescuing Master Li?</string>
  <string id="86251">Sagacious Zu</string>
  <string id="86258" soundid="191995"></string>
  <string id="86273">Let&apos;s move on to something else.</string>
  <string id="86274">I should go deal with the inn.</string>
  <string id="86276">I will walk.</string>
  <string id="86277">Send me back to the portal.</string>
  <string id="86278" soundid="144768"></string>
  <string id="86281" soundid="137684">You know, it looks a lot smaller from the outside.</string>
  <string id="86282" soundid="137685">This is no way to treat an honored foe. A clean death is reward for a good fight lost.</string>
  <string id="86283" soundid="137686">That wasn&apos;t so hard. A shame we have to kill him, he was great at supplying us enemies!</string>
  <string id="86315">Door</string>
  <string id="86316" soundid="144769"></string>
  <string id="86320" soundid="137693">This place is too pretty for my tastes. Where is the stench of old blood and young wine that should hang in the air like the ghost of yesterday&apos;s supper?</string>
  <string id="86321" soundid="137694">Now this place suits my tastes. This floor is no stranger to blood and bile.</string>
  <string id="86322" soundid="137695">I hope they serve more than just tea in there.</string>
  <string id="86327" soundid="137700">This place stinks of the dead... moldy, soggy, rust-up-my-axes dead.</string>
  <string id="86329">Door</string>
  <string id="86330">Door</string>
  <string id="86331">Door</string>
  <string id="86332">Door</string>
  <string id="86333">Door</string>
  <string id="86334">Boulders</string>
  <string id="86335">Boulders</string>
  <string id="86336">Rocks</string>
  <string id="86343">Rocks</string>
  <string id="86344">Rocks</string>
  <string id="86345">Rocks</string>
  <string id="86347">Secret Door</string>
  <string id="86348">Large Boulder</string>
  <string id="86356">Rail Rock 2</string>
  <string id="86357">Golem Press</string>
  <string id="86358">Crane Operation</string>
  <string id="86359">Columns</string>
  <string id="86362">Material Select</string>
  <string id="86592">Hunter</string>
  <string id="86595" soundid="131185">What can I do for the arena&apos;s champion?</string>
  <string id="86596" soundid="131187">No, no! You have sided with the Spirit! We had thought her dead, but her stink is on you!</string>
  <string id="86597" soundid="131188">You will pay for your lies! You will suffer for your deception!</string>
  <string id="86598" soundid="131189">You fool! You do not know our true nature! You know nothing of the power we possess! Look upon us now, and see your doom!</string>
  <string id="86599" soundid="131190">This is what you have turned away from! And for what? A fox?</string>
  <string id="86604" soundid="190046">Do not feel bad, she is responsible for her own health and accidents in the ring can happen. I just pray that my decision to let the two of you spar has not crippled her.</string>
  <string id="86611">Spirit Thief is very important. It does no damage, but transfers chi from the enemy to you. If you run out of chi, use spirit thief to restore your abilities. With Spirit Thief you can use magic styles or healing almost indefinitely!</string>
  <string id="86613">Use Spirit Thief to drain all of Hui&apos;s chi, restoring your own!</string>
  <string id="86688" soundid="135879">If I&apos;m lucky, I would lose my lands. If not, my life could very well be forfeit.</string>
  <string id="86689" soundid="135880">What did you need to know?</string>
  <string id="86690" soundid="135881">In the past, you could make your way out of Tien&apos;s Landing through a different path and travel along a highway to reach the city.</string>
  <string id="86697" soundid="135882">That route has been closed for some time now. Even if we cleared it, the forest and highway are plagued with spirits.</string>
  <string id="86698" soundid="135883">Even I had to make my way here using a flyer from the Imperial City. The land route is closed for all intents and purposes.</string>
  <string id="86699" soundid="135884">I certainly came here by flyer. It was the only way.</string>
  <string id="86746">Henpecked Hou</string>
  <string id="86749">Black Whirlwind</string>
  <string id="86763">Pirate Guard</string>
  <string id="86768" soundid="131427">The trees began to blacken when the ghosts appeared. I&apos;m certain the two are connected. What worries me is that the Forest Shadow may somehow be involved.</string>
  <string id="86770">Once you gain a level, remember to press the &lt;Menu&gt; key to level your character up.</string>
  <string id="86820" soundid="131479">Nice job. I&apos;d spit on Fang&apos;s corpse, but he&apos;s not worth the effort. Too bad about his guards, though. They really weren&apos;t that bad.</string>
  <string id="86821" soundid="131480">I... I appreciate this, you know. Fang was... he was evil. Pure evil. He kept me blinded with silver, and I just never realized how horrible my life was.</string>
  <string id="86822" soundid="131481">Well... that is a lot of silver. And I&apos;d love to get out from under Fang&apos;s boot heel.</string>
  <string id="86823" soundid="131482">I&apos;ll help you. You wanted Fang dead, right?</string>
  <string id="86824" soundid="131483">It&apos;d be easier to kill him. Fang&apos;s reputation is already as dirty as it can get. As long as it doesn&apos;t get in the way of his job, everybody just turns a blind eye.</string>
  <string id="86825" soundid="131484">Well, every document Judge Fang approves has to be stamped with his Imperial Ring. Losing the ring is a major offense.</string>
  <string id="86826" soundid="131485">And if it was revealed he lost the ring during one of his sexual escapades... even Fang wouldn&apos;t want that to come out.</string>
  <string id="86827" soundid="131486"></string>
  <string id="86828" soundid="131487">What are you doing here, Breezes? You know I don&apos;t like it when people see us together in public.</string>
  <string id="86829" soundid="131488">Don&apos;t be mad, my mighty and manly Fang. I was just hoping we could go upstairs for a bit. I&apos;ve got a treat for you. Here&apos;s a hint: they&apos;re silk.</string>
  <string id="86830" soundid="131489">I&apos;m surprised you&apos;re so eager after last night. I&apos;m glad to see you&apos;re finally becoming more receptive to my... special needs.</string>
  <string id="86831" soundid="131490"></string>
  <string id="86832" soundid="131491">Well done, Breezes... if a little tame for my tastes. I think tonight you should wear the blindfold. I have some interesting surprises in store for you.</string>
  <string id="86833" soundid="131492">I... I can hardly wait, oh great and virile Fang.</string>
  <string id="86834" soundid="131493"></string>
  <string id="86835" soundid="131494">Here&apos;s the ring. Fang will do anything to keep people from finding out he lost it to a whore... even if it means resigning his post.</string>
  <string id="86836" soundid="131495">Show the ring to his guards and they&apos;ll let you through. I better disappear for a while, but make sure you tell him where you got it. He&apos;ll be sorry he ever touched me!</string>
  <string id="86837" soundid="131496">Good, that&apos;s what I like to hear. But we can&apos;t do it here in front of everyone. We need someplace more private. Like the animal pens down below.</string>
  <string id="86838" soundid="131497">An exotic locale should excite him. I&apos;ll lure him down there, then you follow. </string>
  <string id="86839" soundid="131498">If you&apos;re lucky, the guards won&apos;t notice you slip down after us, but I don&apos;t know. Those men are well paid to look after Fang.</string>
  <string id="86840" soundid="131499"></string>
  <string id="86841" soundid="131500">Breezes, I&apos;m surprised. I thought you&apos;d be avoiding me after last night. You didn&apos;t seem to enjoy it very much.</string>
  <string id="86842" soundid="131501">Uh... no, great and mighty Fang. I... I liked it. In fact, I was hoping we could try it again. Right now. Down below.</string>
  <string id="86843" soundid="131502">In the animal pens? Oh, Breezes... you are such a filthy girl!</string>
  <string id="86844" soundid="131503"></string>
  <string id="86845" soundid="131504">Fang, hold on a moment. I have a special surprise for you.</string>
  <string id="86846" soundid="131505">How unexpected, Breezes. You&apos;re not usually the type to come up with new activities for us. What sort of filthy thing do you have in mind down here?</string>
  <string id="86847" soundid="131506">You like pain, so you should love this, Fang! I&apos;ve brought you someone who&apos;s going to make sure you suffer for what you&apos;ve done to me!</string>
  <string id="86848" soundid="131507">Hey, what are you doing down here? What&apos;s going on?</string>
  <string id="86849" soundid="131508">Attack, you fools! The whore has led us into a trap!</string>
  <string id="86850" soundid="131509">Don&apos;t worry about that. One thing I&apos;ve learned from my time with Fang is how to block things out.</string>
  <string id="86851" soundid="131510">Judge Fang won&apos;t like it, but the worst he can do is rough me up a little tonight. The bastard might do that anyway... or make me rough him up. Sometimes that&apos;s worse.</string>
  <string id="86852" soundid="131511">I hate him! He&apos;s a vile, repulsive deviant! He likes to hurt. When things are bad, a man like that leaves scars. Emotional and physical.</string>
  <string id="86853" soundid="131512">Look, I&apos;ve been around. I know people do strange and disturbing things behind locked doors. But nothing like this.</string>
  <string id="86854" soundid="131513">There&apos;s no act too brutal or shameful for Judge Fang. He&apos;s into all sorts of things, and he&apos;s no stranger to pain. I know that all too well.</string>
  <string id="86855" soundid="131514">I&apos;ve thought about quitting. Every night. But I heard what happened to the last girl who tried to leave Fang. He&apos;s not the kind of man you just walk away from.</string>
  <string id="86856" soundid="131515">He... he sees me as a possession. *His* possession. He&apos;s not just going to let me go. He&apos;s got the wealth and power to find me wherever I run.</string>
  <string id="86857" soundid="131516">I&apos;m stuck with Judge Fang until he&apos;s tired of me. I&apos;ve come to accept that. It&apos;s a hard, grim fact, but at least he pays well.</string>
  <string id="86858" soundid="131517">Go ahead. It&apos;s not like I&apos;m going to tell you anything that isn&apos;t common knowledge.</string>
  <string id="86859" soundid="131518">Fang&apos;s head of the Ministry of Harmony, so he controls taxes and executions across the Empire. That makes him a very rich and powerful man.</string>
  <string id="86860" soundid="131519">Even the Lotus Assassins are wary of Judge Fang. Probably because they know he&apos;s just as vile and corrupt as they are. All the rumors about him are true.</string>
  <string id="86861" soundid="131520">He&apos;s the most infamous degenerate in the Imperial City... and I work for him.</string>
  <string id="86862" soundid="131521">Good, let me rest. I&apos;ve got a feeling I&apos;m in for a long night tonight.</string>
  <string id="86863" soundid="131522">Now that he&apos;s dead, I finally realize what I have become... what he made me. I just... I just hope I can put all this behind me.</string>
  <string id="86864" soundid="131523">Yeah, you&apos;re right. I think... I think things are going to work out. Thank you.</string>
  <string id="86865" soundid="131524">Once a whore, always a whore, is that it? You&apos;re nothing but a heartless bastard! You&apos;re no better than Fang!</string>
  <string id="86866" soundid="131525">Don&apos;t judge me! If you were starving on the street, you&apos;d sell your body just like I had to! You&apos;re no better than I am, you heartless bitch!</string>
  <string id="86867" soundid="131526">What? No... you can&apos;t kill me. Not now. Not when I&apos;m finally free of Fang! No... no!</string>
  <string id="86868" soundid="131527">I&apos;m not really in the mood for company. Judge Fang wanted to try something special last night, and I still haven&apos;t quite recovered yet.</string>
  <string id="86869" soundid="131528">Sorry, big boy. I&apos;m not open for business. Judge Fang&apos;s got me on his payroll, and he doesn&apos;t like me taking customers on the side.</string>
  <string id="86870" soundid="131529">Forget it, lady. I stick with male clients, and right now I&apos;m on Judge Fang&apos;s payroll. He doesn&apos;t like me branching out to make money on the side.</string>
  <string id="86871" soundid="131530">Unless you&apos;re into something twisted. Then he might want to watch. Fang&apos;s always looking for some new perversion to make his little soldier stand at attention.</string>
  <string id="86872" soundid="131531">My name is Gentle Breezes, but everyone just calls me Breezes now. I guess you lose your gentle side when you spend too many nights with Judge Fang.</string>
  <string id="86873" soundid="131532">Fang&apos;s my... benefactor, if you know what I mean. I do all the things that make him happy. Filthy, nasty things. But at least that sick bastard pays well.</string>
  <string id="86874" soundid="131533">Judge Fang&apos;s the head of the Ministry of Harmony. He&apos;s sitting in the next room with his guards. Likes to come and watch the arena fights.</string>
  <string id="86875" soundid="131534">The blood and beatings in the ring get his fever burning for later. Sometimes that bastard takes it out on me. Other times he makes me take it out on him.</string>
  <string id="86876" soundid="131535">He doesn&apos;t seem to care either way. There are few things more twisted than Judge Fang&apos;s idea of a fun night.</string>
  <string id="86877" soundid="131536">Get rid of him? What do you mean? Remove him from office or... something else?</string>
  <string id="86878" soundid="131537">Really? I was hoping you wanted to kill him. The world would be a better place with that disgusting pig dead and buried!</string>
  <string id="86879" soundid="131538">Good! I hate that disgusting pig. Nobody knows the depths of his perversions better than I. The world will be a better place when he&apos;s dead and buried. </string>
  <string id="86880" soundid="131539">But as much as I want to see his bloated corpse floating in the gutter... Fang is a dangerous man and he keeps my pockets lined with silver.</string>
  <string id="86881" soundid="131540">I hope Fang gets what he deserves, but you&apos;ll have to do it without my help.</string>
  <string id="86882" soundid="131541">[Success] It would be nice to get rid of him. No more debasing myself for that repulsive toad.</string>
  <string id="86883" soundid="131542">[Failure] No. Even if I was willing to give up all that silver, if Fang finds out, he&apos;ll make sure I spend the rest of my days begging for death. It&apos;s not worth the risk.</string>
  <string id="86884" soundid="131543">[Success] You&apos;re right. He&apos;s treated me worse than a dog. It&apos;s time he learned I&apos;m still strong enough to stand up to him!</string>
  <string id="86885" soundid="131544">[Success] Don&apos;t... don&apos;t hurt me. Fang&apos;s already hurt me too many times and I won&apos;t let him hurt me again!</string>
  <string id="86886" soundid="131545">[Failure] You think threats will work on me? You obviously don&apos;t know the depths of Fang&apos;s creativity.</string>
  <string id="86889">[Intimidation] Help me with Fang, and I won&apos;t break your legs.</string>
  <string id="86891">Here&apos;s nine hundred silver if you help me.</string>
  <string id="86893">No. I just want to ruin him.</string>
  <string id="86894">There&apos;s got to be some way to bring him down.</string>
  <string id="86896">Bring me the ring and I&apos;ll blackmail him into resigning.</string>
  <string id="86907">Let&apos;s just kill him.</string>
  <string id="86908">Yes. I want him dead.</string>
  <string id="86911">Don&apos;t worry about the guards. I can handle them.</string>
  <string id="86912">Lure him down there. I&apos;ll follow you.</string>
  <string id="86916">Some enemies are so powerful that they are immune to certain types of attacks. If an enemy seems immune to the style you&apos;re using, try switching to a different type of style (Martial, Support, Weapon, Magic, or Transformation).</string>
  <string id="86923">Fine. Forget I said anything.</string>
  <string id="86924">I want to ask you some questions.</string>
  <string id="86925">You don&apos;t like Fang much, do you?</string>
  <string id="86928">Why do you work for him?</string>
  <string id="86931">I want to ask you something else.</string>
  <string id="86932">Tell me more about Judge Fang.</string>
  <string id="86935">Goodbye.</string>
  <string id="86936">The past is behind you. You&apos;ve got a fresh start now.</string>
  <string id="86938">Right. You&apos;ll bed the next guy who flashes a few coins at you.</string>
  <string id="86941">Sorry, but I don&apos;t leave witnesses behind.</string>
  <string id="86945">Who are you?</string>
  <string id="86947">Who is Judge Fang?</string>
  <string id="86950">I want you to help me get rid of Fang.</string>
  <string id="86951">I want to ruin his career.</string>
  <string id="86953">I want him dead.</string>
  <string id="86956">[Intuition] With Fang gone you can finally be free.</string>
  <string id="86958">[Charm] Fang has to pay for how he&apos;s treated you.</string>
  <string id="86961" soundid="173931"></string>
  <string id="86962" soundid="173932">I... I think we should go back to the Temple. And quickly, before those flyers drop more Lotus Assassins.</string>
  <string id="86963">What were you saying before about the forest?</string>
  <string id="86969">You hear things?</string>
  <string id="86983">I already know the forest is haunted.</string>
  <string id="86984">To Swamp Cave</string>
  <string id="86985">Swamp Bridge</string>
  <string id="86986" soundid="131650">Ahhhhhhh!</string>
  <string id="86987" soundid="131651">Ahhhhhhh!</string>
  <string id="86988" soundid="131652">Haha! This is a *good* fight! More!</string>
  <string id="86991" soundid="131655">That almost hurt! You&apos;re going to regret that!</string>
  <string id="86992" soundid="131656">Is this supposed to be a challenge?</string>
  <string id="86993" soundid="131657">Keep it away from me!</string>
  <string id="86994" soundid="131658">Kill it! Kill it!</string>
  <string id="86995" soundid="131659">Is that it? Is that it? You call that a punch?</string>
  <string id="86996" soundid="131660">Oh, I know you didn&apos;t aim that kick at me!</string>
  <string id="87001" soundid="131665">I... I&apos;m sorry. I had no choice. He.. he promised me my daughter back if I helped him, and you... you are no better than those we fight.</string>
  <string id="87002" soundid="138432">That name... means nothing. I am the will of the Emperor. I am Death&apos;s Hand. Sun Li commands that you die. I must obey.</string>
  <string id="87003" soundid="131667">Good, you are here. The trap is set, the signal sent. It&apos;s all up to you now.</string>
  <string id="87004" soundid="131668">He&apos;s an arrogant one. I doubt he&apos;d consider the possibility that my loyalty to you would be stronger than my fear of him. The bell was the signal. He&apos;ll be here.</string>
  <string id="87005" soundid="131669">Thank you for this opportunity, by the way. I could never face Death&apos;s Hand myself, but I want to make him pay for thinking I would be so weak.</string>
  <string id="87006">Standing Stones</string>
  <string id="87007">Ruined Gazebo</string>
  <string id="87008" soundid="131672">Very good, Sky, you have proven a useful tool.</string>
  <string id="87009" soundid="131673">Guess again, you slab of rot.</string>
  <string id="87011" soundid="138433"></string>
  <string id="87012">Trap? Signal? Have I forgotten something?</string>
  <string id="87015">To Swamp</string>
  <string id="87016">Toad Cave</string>
  <string id="87018" soundid="138434"></string>
  <string id="87019">Sky! What have you done!</string>
  <string id="87020" soundid="138435">I am reborn again and again. I am the will of the Emperor. I am Death&apos;s Hand. Sun Li commands that you die. I must obey.</string>
  <string id="87021" soundid="131685">Your allies are not as strong as you thought, and neither are you. My master tires of your resistance.</string>
  <string id="87022">Blocked Tunnel</string>
  <string id="87023" soundid="131687">The will of the master guides me. The strength of the dragon empowers me. I cannot be defeated. I must obey.</string>
  <string id="87024" soundid="131688">You know nothing about me, about what I endure. Your fists will not defeat me. Not while I must obey.</string>
  <string id="87025">Your master is not here. What do you want, Prince Kin?</string>
  <string id="87027">Then fight as you must, but you will not defeat me.</string>
  <string id="87028">Ogre Cave</string>
  <string id="87030">I have lost too much to you and your master. No more!</string>
  <string id="87031">You are a shell, a shadow. Let us see how fearsome you are!</string>
  <string id="87032">Didn&apos;t I leave you buried in the dirt somewhere?</string>
  <string id="87033">I don&apos;t fear you. All you can do is kill me, and I&apos;ve already been there.</string>
  <string id="87082" soundid="165542">Oh, I don&apos;t know. They&apos;re good with knots.</string>
  <string id="87090" soundid="165543">Coming from you, that&apos;s a tempting offer. I&apos;m a fool to turn you down, but I think what I&apos;ve come here to do is something I must do alone.</string>
  <string id="87094" soundid="131764">Do not expect any help from the Lotus Assassins with this task. You will have to prove you can succeed on your own before we will even consider you for our organization.</string>
  <string id="87095" soundid="131765">There will be no questions. I have already given you all the information you need to succeed. Now you are on your own.</string>
  <string id="87096" soundid="131766">Perhaps, perhaps not. In any case, I wish you luck in your endeavor.</string>
  <string id="87097" soundid="131767">Remember, don&apos;t let Sheng give his report to Judge Fang. We will be watching you from afar. Once you have completed your task, I will meet you back here.</string>
  <string id="87099" soundid="131769">You know, far be it from me to presume, but I have an idea of how we might be able to solve this problem.</string>
  <string id="87100" soundid="131770">My glorious wife&apos;s third cousin is a minor official in the Ministry of Harmony. I know a little something of the way Judge Fang conducts his business.</string>
  <string id="87101" soundid="131771">Yes, of course, I do not mean to incur your wrath but... it&apos;s only that I know something of the way the Ministry of Harmony does business.</string>
  <string id="87102" soundid="131772">All of Fang&apos;s ministers bring him an honor gift when they go to see him... an offering given as a sign of respect. A... a bribe, some might call it.</string>
  <string id="87103" soundid="131773">If we replace Sheng&apos;s honor gift with something insulting--rare turtle eggs, for example--Fang would be so outraged he&apos;d refuse to even listen to Sheng&apos;s report!</string>
  <string id="87104" soundid="131774">It&apos;s true. A gift of turtle eggs would be as insulting as a box of manure. Even more so because they are so difficult to track down, whereas manure is somewhat common.</string>
  <string id="87105" soundid="144094">That is the beauty of what Sun Hai has done. He has taken the raw material of the Empire and extracted something useful.</string>
  <string id="87106" soundid="131776">I admit there are still some details yet to be worked out, but acquiring the eggs is easy. I have some here that you can simply have.</string>
  <string id="87107" soundid="131777">We should just kill Sheng. Nice and simple. Kill his guards, too.</string>
  <string id="87108" soundid="131778">Yes. And while we&apos;re at it, we could kill Fang. And his guards, too. Unleash rivers of blood in the streets, all in the service of the Lotus Assassins!</string>
  <string id="87109" soundid="131779">Now that is how you interrupt the bureaucratic process! I&apos;m all for it!</string>
  <string id="87110" soundid="131780">I am no coward, but there is already more blood on my hands than I can ever wash clean. You know this.</string>
  <string id="87111" soundid="131781">I have no plan for you... no easy answer. But working with the Lotus Assassins is a bad idea. No good can ever come of it.</string>
  <string id="87112" soundid="131782">We really don&apos;t have any choice, Zu. It&apos;s the only way we&apos;ll ever rescue Master Li. But I don&apos;t like the idea of causing trouble for Sheng.</string>
  <string id="87113" soundid="131783">Maybe you&apos;re right, Dawn Star. I just hope that in the end we don&apos;t sacrifice everything for the sake of one man, even if he is your... your beloved Master Li.</string>
  <string id="87114" soundid="131784">My spies tell me that Judge Fang has resigned. Is this true?</string>
  <string id="87115" soundid="131785">However, you did take the shortest path to accomplish your goal. Killing Sheng is a task more suited to a back-alley thug than an Inquisitor.</string>
  <string id="87116" soundid="131786">I&apos;ve been out spying on the Lotus Assassins. We&apos;re trying to draw their attention, and I wanted to see if it was working.</string>
  <string id="87117" soundid="131787">I&apos;m happy to report our bait has snagged a fish. The Inquisitors have taken notice of us. In fact, one of their representatives is on his way here now.</string>
  <string id="87118" soundid="131788">You were spying on an Inquisitor, and he didn&apos;t notice you? Impossible! What&apos;s really going on, Sky? Where were you?</string>
  <string id="87119" soundid="131789">It&apos;s like I told you before: I was spying on the Lotus Assassins. At great personal risk, I might add! Instead of interrogating me, you could show me some gratitude.</string>
  <string id="87120" soundid="131790">The Inquisitors are masters of espionage and intrigue, Sky. They would have seen you tailing them. They would have seen you and killed you!</string>
  <string id="87121" soundid="131791">You underestimate me. I can be quite invisible when necessary. I followed the Inquisitor for some time without him being aware of my presence.</string>
  <string id="87122" soundid="131792">Then I slipped away and rushed on ahead to warn you he was coming. I didn&apos;t want him to catch us in the middle of anything incriminating... like this argument.</string>
  <string id="87123" soundid="131793"></string>
  <string id="87124" soundid="131794"></string>
  <string id="87125" soundid="131795">But your point is well taken. You have shown some inkling of promise merely by drawing our attention... but that alone is hardly proof of your worth.</string>
  <string id="87126" soundid="131796">Obviously we require some type of test, some proof of loyalty before any can join. You must prove yourself useful to us before we will even consider you.</string>
  <string id="87127" soundid="131797">Such confidence must be the mark of great skill... or foolish bravado. Rest assured, we will determine which in due course. </string>
  <string id="87128" soundid="131798">There is a small problem I intended to deal with. A minor annoyance, but one that should prove a good test of your value to our organization.</string>
  <string id="87129" soundid="131799">Judge Fang of the Ministry of Harmony has made a habit of openly defying our order. In the past we have tolerated him, as few pay his accusations any heed.</string>
  <string id="87130" soundid="131800">Judge Fang has a rather... unsavory... reputation. Because of his degenerate appetites, most have dismissed his warnings out of hand. Until now.</string>
  <string id="87131" soundid="131801">A certain Minister named Sheng is coming to make his annual report. Sheng has information about certain... activities... of our group we wish to keep from the public.</string>
  <string id="87132" soundid="131802">If Judge Fang learns of these activities from Sheng&apos;s report, he may have enough evidence to cause real problems for us. We would have to take drastic action.</string>
  <string id="87135">I&apos;ll pass any test you dream up!</string>
  <string id="87139">So what&apos;s changed?</string>
  <string id="87140">Why bother with him, then?</string>
  <string id="87143">You want me to kill Sheng?</string>
  <string id="87144">You want me to kill Judge Fang?</string>
  <string id="87145">You want me to steal that report?</string>
  <string id="87147">What do you want me to do?</string>
  <string id="87150">I will not fail you.</string>
  <string id="87151">Wait, I have some questions.</string>
  <string id="87153">This will be easy.</string>
  <string id="87156">Spirit Font</string>
  <string id="87157">What&apos;s your plan?</string>
  <string id="87159">Forget it.</string>
  <string id="87162">Turtle eggs? Are you serious?</string>
  <string id="87164">Where are we going to find turtle eggs?</string>
  <string id="87165">I&apos;ll keep that in mind.</string>
  <string id="87166" soundid="144095">But through all this, a threat remained: a traitorous sibling and a hidden protege. We did not know a face or a name, but we knew what they would need.</string>
  <string id="87167">That&apos;s a stupid plan.</string>
  <string id="87171">I think Zu was being sarcastic.</string>
  <string id="87172">So what&apos;s your plan, Zu?</string>
  <string id="87173">What&apos;s the matter, Zu? Scared of a little blood?</string>
  <string id="87177" soundid="139384">Her name, they said, was a testament to her ability to move between the trees in utter silence, observing all that happened in this place without ever being detected.</string>
  <string id="87180">A good question. Where did you go, Sky?</string>
  <string id="87182">Relax. Sky told us where he was.</string>
  <string id="87183">Knock it off! The Inquisitor could be here any minute.</string>
  <string id="87184" soundid="156838">Watch and learn.</string>
  <string id="87186">He&apos;s right. Just drop it.</string>
  <string id="87187">This isn&apos;t over, Sky.</string>
  <string id="87188">Enough. I think I hear someone coming.</string>
  <string id="87194">How can I prove my worth, honorable Master?</string>
  <string id="87195">What do you want me to do?</string>
  <string id="87197">The Lotus Assassins don&apos;t want Fang to see that report.</string>
  <string id="87200">What are you suggesting?</string>
  <string id="87201">You want me to kill Judge Fang?</string>
  <string id="87256">Ministry Hostel</string>
  <string id="87257" soundid="166111">Let&apos;s go. I&apos;m sure Hou can make his way back to Tien&apos;s Landing. Even if there&apos;s more cannibals about, he&apos;s too skinny to eat.</string>
  <string id="87259">The Golden Way</string>
  <string id="88130" soundid="135885">You should really make your way out of this place. This once lovely forest is lost, I think. The ghosts have made it unfit for the rest of us.</string>
  <string id="88131" soundid="135886">Help me? That&apos;s certainly a kind offer, but I&apos;m not sure that anyone....</string>
  <string id="88132" soundid="135887">I would highly recommend that course of action. This place is not safe, even for one of your considerable skills.</string>
  <string id="88148" soundid="135888">Wait a moment. You don&apos;t look like a pilgrim or one of the poor folk trying to escape Tien&apos;s Landing. Would it be out of line to inquire as to what brought you here?</string>
  <string id="88149" soundid="135889">Lotus Assassins? You have picked a dangerous quarry. Compounding the problem, they likely took him to the Imperial City.</string>
  <string id="88150" soundid="135890">The Imperial City, is it? How interesting. You find yourself in a tricky predicament. There are few ways to reach the capital from here. Air would be your best bet.</string>
  <string id="88178" soundid="135891">Trust me when I say that there is no safe land route to the north. This path is barely passable, and the forest is crawling with ghosts. </string>
  <string id="88179" soundid="135892">Even caravans employing skilled warriors have been forced to turn back under these ghosts&apos; assaults. I could only reach Tien&apos;s Landing by using my flyer.</string>
  <string id="88180" soundid="135893">The new supplies and men that are being gathered were going to be used to restore the highway.</string>
  <string id="88198" soundid="134090">The same power that held the outer gates shut keeps these locked, as well. We must restore the nearby fountain to open them.</string>
  <string id="88201" soundid="137704">Never trust a thief. You think they&apos;re on your side, but they&apos;ll slit your throat and take your silver.</string>
  <string id="88203" soundid="137706">Now *that* was a fight! I hope there&apos;s more where those came from.</string>
  <string id="88204" soundid="137707">Ah, treasure! My one true love... other than wine... and killing... and so on.</string>
  <string id="88206">Gate</string>
  <string id="88213">Door</string>
  <string id="88214">Door</string>
  <string id="88232" soundid="137735">Here is the source as she was laid open. She is a trophy representing all that we accomplished. Her power bleeds to feed an Empire.</string>
  <string id="88233" soundid="137736">Brother Li awaits. The first battle was to test your resolve and abilities. He is ever the Glorious Strategist.</string>
  <string id="88258" soundid="137761">I can&apos;t believe they&apos;ve moved so quickly. We need your weapon. Gujin will be in his shop north of the main stairs.</string>
  <string id="88259" soundid="137762">I can hear fighting to the east! We have to push these bandits back off the beach!</string>
  <string id="88260" soundid="137763">There&apos;s something... not right. This place feels all wrong. The forest is the same, but it&apos;s stronger here.</string>
  <string id="88261" soundid="137764">This is nightmarish... we have to finish this any way we can.</string>
  <string id="88263" soundid="137766">The forest had a mournful feeling to it, but there&apos;s none of that here. If this is the Forest Shadow&apos;s home, she can&apos;t be behind the sickness in the trees.</string>
  <string id="88266" soundid="137769">Look at this place... so many people. This truly is the heart of the Empire.</string>
  <string id="88267" soundid="137770">The busy streets are almost overwhelming. It is hard to keep focused on what we need to do.</string>
  <string id="88268" soundid="137771">Is... is this a school? It is so much bigger than what we had in Two Rivers.</string>
  <string id="88269" soundid="137772">Shouldn&apos;t visiting ministers have more... dignified accommodations?</string>
  <string id="88270" soundid="134162">This... this cannot be! Is it really possible? I... I sense the mark of the Water Dragon upon you. You have returned!</string>
  <string id="88271" soundid="134163">You don&apos;t recognize me? No, of course not. You were just an infant when you were taken from us.</string>
  <string id="88272" soundid="134164">I am the spirit of Abbot Song, slain many years ago by the Glorious Strategist. Before my death, I was the head of the Spirit Monk order... your order.</string>
  <string id="88273" soundid="134165">Master Li? He is Sun Li the traitor! How out of balance the world has become when one of our order believes Sun Li to be his Master!</string>
  <string id="88274" soundid="134166">I am. I was. But I only led them to defeat and destruction. I failed in my duty to protect the Water Dragon... a duty I would one day have passed to you.</string>
  <string id="88275" soundid="134167">Yes, this is Dirge, once the home of the Spirit Monks, a holy order devoted to serving the Water Dragon... now reduced to tainted ruins.</string>
  <string id="88276" soundid="134168">You are a Spirit Monk, born here in Dirge and cleansed in the sacred fountains. You were an infant the day the Emperor and Sun Li attacked our monastery.</string>
  <string id="88277" soundid="134169">I tried to save you from the slaughter, only to lose you to Li when he ripped you from the arms of your dying guardian.</string>
  <string id="88278" soundid="134170">I can only imagine what lies and distortions he told you about Dirge, your heritage, and his own role in events here. But now, you deserve to hear the truth.</string>
  <string id="88280" soundid="134172">Thirty years ago, the Long Drought struck the land. For a decade, crops withered and died. Starving people across the Empire demanded that something be done.</string>
  <string id="88281" soundid="134173">Despite his position, Emperor Sun Hai could not alter the natural order. He demanded that his brother, the Glorious Strategist, concoct a plan to rectify this insult.</string>
  <string id="88285" soundid="138810">[With the seal restored, this fountain is now cleansed.]</string>
  <string id="88289" soundid="144738">These three pieces are physical, but there is one more. It cannot be found, only earned. This final piece is all that will save you in the end.</string>
  <string id="88290" soundid="134182">The soldiers of the Imperial Army swarmed over us, too many to count. My Spirit Monks fought bravely, but I knew the battle was lost.</string>
  <string id="88291">Rubble 1</string>
  <string id="88292">Portal</string>
  <string id="88293">Pillar</string>
  <string id="88294">Pillar</string>
  <string id="88295">Pillar</string>
  <string id="88296">Pillar</string>
  <string id="88298">Villager</string>
  <string id="88301" soundid="163499"></string>
  <string id="88304">The Land of Spirits</string>
  <string id="88305">The Abbot knows of a gem of power located in the western section of the inner courtyard, near the old residences. You will need it to confront the strange presence that now corrupts Dirge. It is likely guarded by many spirits, but the benefits outweigh the risks.</string>
  <string id="88306">Gem of Power</string>
  <string id="88307">Find the Abbot in Dirge</string>
  <string id="88308">Find Abbot Song in Dirge and seek his help.</string>
  <string id="88309">The Water Dragon confirmed Master Li&apos;s betrayal. He used you to acquire the power he and his brother stole. In the gap between Sun Hai&apos;s death and Sun Li claiming power, the Water Dragon was able to bring your spirit to Dirge. You must try to find Abbot Song, one of the Spirit Monks trapped in Dirge. He will help restore the Water Dragon to the point where she can restore you to life.</string>
  <string id="88311">Restore the Fountains of Dirge</string>
  <string id="88312">Find and destroy the guardians, and restore each of the fountains.</string>
  <string id="88313">Abbot Song has joined you. He told of how the fountains of Dirge were corrupted by his fellow monks, allowing Sun Li and the Emperor to overrun the temple. You must defeat the guardians and then restore each of the fountains. This will restore some of the Water Dragon&apos;s power so she can restore you to life.</string>
  <string id="88315" soundid="134207">The guardian of this fountain is destroyed... and I weep for her. She was once one of our order, but, lured by Li&apos;s promises of wealth and power, she betrayed us.</string>
  <string id="88316" soundid="134208">This... thing... is the corrupted spirit of Xian Wu. During the attack, she and several other Spirit Monks betrayed us by tainting the holy fountains with human blood.</string>
  <string id="88317" soundid="134209">The seals on the fountains were broken, and the Water Dragon was crippled. If not for this betrayal, Dirge would never have fallen. Li must have known this.</string>
  <string id="88318" soundid="134210">Long before the attack, Li sent spies to bribe some of our... weaker members. When they tainted the fountains, the power sustaining us against the army vanished.</string>
  <string id="88319" soundid="134211">Xian Wu&apos;s betrayal is... a great shame. I knew her well and considered her a friend. I never imagined she could turn on me like this.</string>
  <string id="88320" soundid="134212">We Spirit Monks are guided by honor and duty; these values are ingrained in us from birth. I never imagined one of our own could betray us.</string>
  <string id="88321" soundid="134213">After the battle, the Emperor executed Xian Wu and the others, and he used the power of the Water Dragon to bind their spirits to the fountains.</string>
  <string id="88322" soundid="134214">Their crime was terrible, but they did not deserve this fate. They suffered endless torment from which they could never escape. Such is the power of the binding.</string>
  <string id="88323" soundid="134215">The binding is a sacred ritual of the Spirit Monks. We can draw on the power of the Water Dragon to bind a spirit to us. It is one of our tools for shepherding the dead.</string>
  <string id="88324" soundid="134216">Even before Dirge was befouled, there were ghosts in the world. Some spirits would become lost in their journey here or refuse to let go of the mortal world and go mad.</string>
  <string id="88325" soundid="134217">If we found one of these restless ghosts, we could bind it to us and bring it to Dirge. Then we would release the spirit so the Water Dragon could lead it into the afterlife.</string>
  <string id="88326" soundid="134218">The binding is a great gift from the Water Dragon, if used properly. But the power can be abused. The Emperor bound the traitors not to himself, but to a place.</string>
  <string id="88327" soundid="134219">A spirit can never escape such a binding. It feels an inexorable pull, but it has nowhere to go. It feels a compulsion to obey, but it is never given a command.</string>
  <string id="88328" soundid="134220">The spirit twists and corrupts, and in its agony, it goes mad. Binding a spirit to a place is a terrible crime for our order. The only thing worse is binding a living creature.</string>
  <string id="88329" soundid="134221">Binding the living condemns them to a fate worse than death. It forces the subject to obey and robs them of their free will. As a Spirit Monk, you must never do such a thing.</string>
  <string id="88330" soundid="134222">The ability to bind spirits comes from the essence of the Water Dragon inside you. You may not have the power now, but one day you will be able to call upon it when needed.</string>
  <string id="88331" soundid="134223">But this is not the time for lessons or instruction. The guardian is dead, but you must place the seal on the fountain for it to be fully restored.</string>
  <string id="88332" soundid="134224">You have nothing to fear here. Though many dangerous beings dwell in Dirge, these monks and soldiers cannot harm you.</string>
  <string id="88333" soundid="134225">The monks and soldiers who fell during the battle are trapped here in Dirge, caught in a never-ending war. They fight, they fall, only to rise and fall again.</string>
  <string id="88334" soundid="134226">I have tried to help my brethren in this battle, but they neither see nor hear me. I cannot aid or lead them. Even in death, I fail them... just as I did in life.</string>
  <string id="88335" soundid="134227">I cannot say. Perhaps because I was the abbot of this monastery. Or maybe because of my death and what happened shortly after.</string>
  <string id="88336" soundid="134228">I made many mistakes during the attack. I was not prepared for the treachery from within, and it led to our downfall. Even after my death, I made poor choices.</string>
  <string id="88337" soundid="134229">Li cut me down on the steps of the temple. My body fell, and my spirit rose. Powerless, I fled toward the outer courtyard while the battle still raged.</string>
  <string id="88338" soundid="134230">I wanted to see if you had escaped. Instead, I saw Li take you... and I found myself trapped out here. The Emperor had sealed the gates behind me.</string>
  <string id="88339" soundid="134231">My spirit cannot leave Dirge. None of the spirits here can leave. For twenty years I have been trapped in the outer courtyard, unable to pass through the gates.</string>
  <string id="88340" soundid="134232">Maybe if I had been inside, I could have saved the Spirit Monks from this endless war. Or maybe I would have been caught up in it with them. I cannot say.</string>
  <string id="88341" soundid="134233">My hope is that the restoration of the fountain will allow the gates to open. Perhaps inside we can find a way to restore Dirge and free my brethren from this curse.</string>
  <string id="88342" soundid="134234">I cannot say what fate lies ahead. But after twenty years, your return gives me reason to hope once more. </string>
  <string id="88343" soundid="134235">Li has trained you in his own image: selfish and oblivious to the suffering of others. Yet I know the Water Dragon believes in you, and I will not lose hope. Not now.</string>
  <string id="88344" soundid="134236">The second fountain is here, but the seal is missing! This could only be possible if the guardian bound to this fountain has been destroyed.</string>
  <string id="88345" soundid="134237">This is... troubling. I feel a foul taint here. Something worse than the corruption of the Emperor. Something older... something not of this realm.</string>
  <string id="88346" soundid="134238">The guardians were powerful beings. Whatever destroyed them must be even stronger... perhaps some monstrosity drawn to this realm by the corruption of Dirge.</string>
  <string id="88347" soundid="134239">Bravery often comes from ignorance. If I am afraid, it is only because I know enough to realize what we may be up against.</string>
  <string id="88348" soundid="134240">There are unnamed things barred from entering both the mortal world and the spirit realm. But with the Water Dragon gone, such a being may have crossed into Dirge.</string>
  <string id="88349" soundid="134241">Such a creature would be drawn to the corruption of the fountain. It must have destroyed the guardian and hidden the seal so the fountain could never be restored.</string>
  <string id="88350" soundid="134242">The creature would not go far... wait! Do you feel that? Something is coming.</string>
  <string id="88351" soundid="196855">Yes? Is there something you need?</string>
  <string id="88358" soundid="134250">Yes? Is there something you need? I will gladly do all that I can to help you restore the fountains of Dirge.</string>
  <string id="88359" soundid="134251">The fountains were tainted with human blood, which shattered their seals. The blood that stained them is gone. Replacing the seals should restore them.</string>
  <string id="88364" soundid="156920"></string>
  <string id="88365" soundid="134257">Only that you should do as the Water Dragon asked and try to restore the fountains of Dirge.</string>
  <string id="88366" soundid="134258">I know the monastery well. If there are questions you wish to ask in your quest to restore the fountains, I will do my best to answer them.</string>
  <string id="88367" soundid="134259">The amulet is an artifact of great power, though few truly understand its nature. What do you wish to know?</string>
  <string id="88368" soundid="134260">The amulet is a powerful tool, but it is only a tool. When you were first learning to unleash the power within you, the amulet helped you to focus your mind and energy.</string>
  <string id="88369" soundid="134261">But you are a Spirit Monk. The power of the Water Dragon was always in you, not in the amulet. Now you are strong enough to draw on that power without the amulet.</string>
  <string id="88370" soundid="134262">You no longer need the amulet, but Li has a use for it. Li&apos;s brother Sun Hai consumed the Water Dragon&apos;s power, but without the amulet it was a long and slow process.</string>
  <string id="88371" soundid="134263">Even after twenty years, he was not strong enough to defeat you. Had the Lotus Assassins brought him enough pieces of the amulet, he would have been far more powerful.</string>
  <string id="88372" soundid="134264">But Sun Li has the amulet, making him far more dangerous. With it, he can draw on the Water Dragon&apos;s power much faster. Unless you stop him soon, he will become invincible.</string>
  <string id="88373" soundid="134265">I did not want the amulet to fall into the hands of our enemy. When I realized the battle was lost, I shattered it into several pieces.</string>
  <string id="88374" soundid="134266">I gave the pieces to my apprentices and told them to flee to the farthest reaches of the Empire. The core of the amulet was given to the young monk who fled with you.</string>
  <string id="88375" soundid="134267">I knew the core alone would be enough for you to start discovering your true power, but anyone else would need to find all the pieces to use the amulet.</string>
  <string id="88376" soundid="134268">I will do my best to answer whatever questions you might have.</string>
  <string id="88377" soundid="134269">I would be honored to help you learn more about our order and your legacy.</string>
  <string id="88378" soundid="134270">I will try my best to explain the glorious mysteries of the god we serve.</string>
  <string id="88379" soundid="134271">You are probably right. We must restore the Water Dragon&apos;s power before Sun Li gains full command of her powers.</string>
  <string id="88393" soundid="134285">There is no way through the gates. The Emperor sealed them twenty years ago. Now they keep me from entering my own monastery.</string>
  <string id="88394" soundid="134286">If we can restore the fountain, the gates may open for us.</string>
  <string id="88398" soundid="134290">You must restore the fountain before these doors will open.</string>
  <string id="88475" soundid="137773">Remember Jing Woo back in Two Rivers? He talked of fighting in the Imperial Arena one day. He would have done well.</string>
  <string id="88478" soundid="137776">This city has so many wonders. I never dreamed of such a place.</string>
  <string id="88479" soundid="144739">Easy there. You fell flat on your face after the fight. Are you prone to that sort of thing?</string>
  <string id="88480" soundid="138238">[Nothing happens.]</string>
  <string id="88481" soundid="138239">[The statue erupts in a loud burst of energy. Clearly you have done something momentous. You feel different.]</string>
  <string id="88482" soundid="135896">They&apos;re quite common around the Imperial City. The trick is to obtain a wind map that allows you to navigate the air currents over large distances.</string>
  <string id="88483" soundid="135897">Acquiring that chart was a hard fought battle, I can assure you. The Lotus Assassins keep a tight rein on those precious documents.</string>
  <string id="88484" soundid="135898">Indeed, though you would also need a flyer with enough fuel to manage the trip. Those are in precious short supply in this area of the Empire.</string>
  <string id="88485" soundid="135899">Then again, you seem resourceful, and I believe resourceful people find ways to get things done.</string>
  <string id="88486" soundid="135900">Perhaps you could get something done for me. If so, I might be persuaded to foolishly risk the Lotus Assassins&apos; wrath by making a copy of one of their precious maps.</string>
  <string id="88487" soundid="135901">The only flyers I know of in this region are flown by a group of pirates near Tien&apos;s Landing.</string>
  <string id="88488" soundid="135902">I&apos;m not sure where they get the resources to make raids from the air, but I am quite sure that they&apos;d object if you tried to borrow one of their airships.</string>
  <string id="88489" soundid="135903">Someone in Tien&apos;s Landing probably knows more about them. Perhaps that Minister... Sheng, is it? He must at least be aware of their activities.</string>
  <string id="88490" soundid="135904">You clearly don&apos;t understand the value of a wind map. I don&apos;t have it on me in this rough camp.</string>
  <string id="88491" soundid="135905">If you take that map, and I cannot return it to the Assassins, I&apos;m a dead man already. Threaten me if you will; I prefer a quick death to what they would do to me. </string>
  <string id="88492" soundid="135906">I am willing to risk a copy because we share the blame, and you would have as much to lose as I, were the assassins to learn of this arrangement.</string>
  <string id="88493" soundid="135907">The deal is simple. Find out why my land sickens--why it is home to so many ghosts--and you will have your map.</string>
  <string id="88494" soundid="135908">No bartering, no record of this discussion. A simple agreement between a Lord and a highly skilled woman.</string>
  <string id="88495" soundid="135909">No negotiation, no contracts to sign, just an agreement between gentlemen.</string>
  <string id="88496" soundid="135910">Then you are out one very precious map. Unless my luck changes, then I am also out one forest. You may as well hear the tale of this place before you refuse.</string>
  <string id="88497" soundid="135911">Two things threaten the entire length and breadth of this forest: The trees blacken with disease, and ghosts flock to this place like no other in the Empire.</string>
  <string id="88498" soundid="135912">I suspect that these things are related and, more importantly, that they&apos;re related to a fox called the Forest Shadow.</string>
  <string id="88499" soundid="135913">She is a powerful being, one my father considered the guardian of this forest.</string>
  <string id="88500" soundid="135914">If this place is filled with ghosts, then I suspect that it is either because of or in spite of her.</string>
  <string id="88501" soundid="135915">Just that. She is a fox spirit, and thus one of heaven&apos;s tricksters. The fox can take on the forms of men and women and will often do so to test us.</string>
  <string id="88502" soundid="135916">Personally, I don&apos;t think they have any right to deceive us, but my father felt that our family&apos;s good fortune came from just such a test passed long ago by an ancestor.</string>
  <string id="88503" soundid="135917">Some sort of ancient alliance, in which she was guardian of the forest while we owned the land in the world of men.</string>
  <string id="88504" soundid="135918">She is a powerful spirit that has long been an ally of my family. Personally, I&apos;ve had little to do with her.</string>
  <string id="88505" soundid="135919">My father and his father before him, however, felt strongly that she should be revered. They considered her the true guardian of this forest.</string>
  <string id="88506" soundid="135920">No one really knows. It&apos;s out of character for a fox spirit, that I can assure you. They normally test men&apos;s worth and pass judgment.</string>
  <string id="88507" soundid="135921">At first I wondered if this disease and these ghosts are a test for me, but that doesn&apos;t feel right. Not like this.</string>
  <string id="88508" soundid="135922">I think something is wrong with the Forest Shadow, and I want you to find her and figure out what is happening. Once we know that, we&apos;ll have a clear idea of what we face.</string>
  <string id="88509" soundid="135923">A noble sentiment, but when I look upon these trees, I&apos;m afraid that you may have to destroy her. See what you can learn first. Then we will act if it is necessary.</string>
  <string id="88510" soundid="135924">I would prefer not, but if it is necessary, do what you think is right. She has been an ally to my family in the past, but I do not hold with the worship of tricksters.</string>
  <string id="88511" soundid="135925">Make your way up this ancient trail, and when you come to a fork, take the left path. That will lead you to a temple built long ago in the Forest Shadow&apos;s honor.</string>
  <string id="88514" soundid="183011">If we can stop the bandits quickly, we can keep everyone safe. </string>
  <string id="88515" soundid="137780">I... do not like this place. Even compared to the rest of the Necropolis this is a dark and troubled place.</string>
  <string id="88518" soundid="137783">I sense so much pain here; it is almost overwhelming. Whatever they do here is monstrous.</string>
  <string id="88520" soundid="137785">This... this cannot be. How can this be allowed?</string>
  <string id="88521" soundid="137786">It&apos;s... almost over. I don&apos;t think there&apos;s anything left in the Empire for us to battle through.</string>
  <string id="88522" soundid="137787">Everyone was so scared, and I still am. That sorcerer seemed far too interested in you and Master Li.</string>
  <string id="88523" soundid="137788">No... it&apos;s all gone. Why did Gao&apos;s father do this? Why are his men here?</string>
  <string id="88524" soundid="137789">The school... everything is gone. Quickly, there have to be survivors! They can&apos;t all have fallen. They can&apos;t! </string>
  <string id="88528" soundid="137793">A second floor? I&apos;m surprised a town this small can support such a large teahouse.</string>
  <string id="88529" soundid="137794">Be careful in here. I don&apos;t relish the idea of fighting my way out of this place.</string>
  <string id="88530" soundid="137795">This teahouse must be popular. It seems like quite a prominent structure.</string>
  <string id="88531" soundid="137796">These docks remind me of the fishermen in Two Rivers. A shame we will never see them again.</string>
  <string id="88533" soundid="137798">There is something dangerous beyond these gates. The spirits here are... troubled.</string>
  <string id="88535" soundid="137800">There is much suffering in this quarry. So many lives lost.</string>
  <string id="88536" soundid="137801">This must be the guardian the Lotus Assassin spoke of.</string>
  <string id="88538" soundid="137803">Water has covered old Tien&apos;s Landing once again, but there is much it will not wash away.</string>
  <string id="88539" soundid="137804">Be careful in here. This could be a trap.</string>
  <string id="88541" soundid="137806">Look at that flyer... it&apos;s beautiful. The Marvelous Dragonfly is the perfect name.</string>
  <string id="88543" soundid="137808">This forest is so troubled. We were well-sheltered in Two Rivers to not see any of this.</string>
  <string id="88550" soundid="137815">Remind me again why I encouraged you to fight these cannibals? My wife&apos;s right, I am a shortsighted fool.</string>
  <string id="88554" soundid="137819">No other place in the Empire can compare to the Imperial City. I love the peaceful bustle of commerce... and the absence of my wife.</string>
  <string id="88555" soundid="137820">Ah, the smell of success. My sweet lily would prefer that *I* smell of sweat and yeast, instead.</string>
  <string id="88560" soundid="137825">The garden is a beautiful place, but there&apos;s only a title&apos;s difference between a scholar and a fool who won&apos;t shut up.</string>
  <string id="88562" soundid="137827">It&apos;s times like this when the thought of seeing my wife again actually gives me hope.</string>
  <string id="88563" soundid="137828">Somehow I always pictured the golems being pieced together... like a puzzle.</string>
  <string id="88564" soundid="137829">Jia seems like a reasonable woman. Of course, I only have my wife as a comparison.</string>
  <string id="88566" soundid="137831">They say spirits can sense your fear. I fear they knew I was coming before we left the city.</string>
  <string id="88569" soundid="137834">I know I&apos;ve said this before... but this time I really do have a bad feeling about this.</string>
  <string id="88570" soundid="137835">No man alive was meant to see this... or would want to.</string>
  <string id="88571" soundid="137836">What are you waiting for? Kill him quickly, or we&apos;ll all be dead.</string>
  <string id="88575">Who are you?</string>
  <string id="88576">Are you Abbot Song?</string>
  <string id="88577">Stay back, spirit!</string>
  <string id="88579">The Glorious Strategist? You mean Master Li?</string>
  <string id="88581">So you&apos;re the leader of the Spirit Monks?</string>
  <string id="88583">What are you talking about?</string>
  <string id="88584">Where am I? Is this Dirge?</string>
  <string id="88587">No... that&apos;s not true. Master Li rescued me.</string>
  <string id="88588">Li claimed he was the one who saved me.</string>
  <string id="88589">I guess my whole life has been a lie.</string>
  <string id="88590" soundid="144740">In the what? Your Master taught you some interesting things. Come on, we need to move our camp somewhere that no ghosts attack.</string>
  <string id="88591" soundid="144741">You saw a vision? Strange that I could not make it out. Strong spirits are usually quite clear to me. Please tell me if you have any more.</string>
  <string id="88592" soundid="145249">Ah, you found your way. Good. I decided there wasn&apos;t much point in staying with the flyer. It&apos;s not going to get much worse, in my opinion.</string>
  <string id="88594" soundid="144743">Very well. Where you choose to take a nap is your business.</string>
  <string id="88595" soundid="144744">I... I guess we should. I just wish I knew what was going on.</string>
  <string id="88600">What happened when they attacked Dirge?</string>
  <string id="88601">How did he defeat Water Dragon?</string>
  <string id="88604">The Emperor must have been mad to think this was acceptable.</string>
  <string id="88606">Confront the Minion of Suffering</string>
  <string id="88607">Find the Minion of Suffering and confront him.</string>
  <string id="88608">The corruption of Dirge has allowed something malevolent to take up residence in the temple. The Minion of Suffering awaits you in the cave to the east. You must find and destroy the creature to regain the missing seal that will restore the second fountain. Once Dirge is restored the Water Dragon can restore you to life.</string>
  <string id="88610">Destroy the Abomination in the Temple</string>
  <string id="88611">Go to the temple and confront the Abomination that resides there.</string>
  <string id="88612">The way to the temple courtyard is open. Enter the temple and confront the Abomination that has corrupted Dirge. When this malevolent presence is purged, the Water Dragon will have enough power to restore you to life.</string>
  <string id="88613">Dirge is restored, the Spirit Monks have been freed from their bonds, and the Water Dragon has restored your physical form. Sun Li awaits you.</string>
  <string id="88614">Find the Gem</string>
  <string id="88615">Search in the western section of the inner courtyard for the gem.</string>
  <string id="88617">You have found the gem that the abbot mentioned. Once you purge the corruption that has infected Dirge the Water Dragon will restore you to life.</string>
  <string id="88618">Return to game.</string>
  <string id="88619" soundid="163527">We should get back to Two Rivers. Master Li needs to be told about what Gao said.</string>
  <string id="88620" soundid="163528">We have to find Master Li. There have to be survivors.</string>
  <string id="88634" soundid="163545">A manual of regimented conditioning will serve you well. Red meat, constitutionals, and union suit calisthenics. You&apos;re never so fit as when the johns are long.</string>
  <string id="88635">Who was she?</string>
  <string id="88636">This woman was once a Spirit Monk?</string>
  <string id="88637">So she betrayed you?</string>
  <string id="88640">What happened to Xian Wu?</string>
  <string id="88641">And you never suspected anything?</string>
  <string id="88642">Why didn&apos;t you mention this before?</string>
  <string id="88644">You were a fool to trust them.</string>
  <string id="88646">Sounds like they got what they deserved.</string>
  <string id="88647">That&apos;s awful!</string>
  <string id="88648">What&apos;s so bad about the binding?</string>
  <string id="88649">I don&apos;t understand. How did he bind their spirits?</string>
  <string id="88652">So the Emperor did this to Xian Wu?</string>
  <string id="88653">I still don&apos;t see why this is so bad.</string>
  <string id="88656">We can bind living people, too?</string>
  <string id="88657" soundid="192577"></string>
  <string id="88658">Can you teach me how to bind the living?</string>
  <string id="88661">What&apos;s going on here?</string>
  <string id="88662">Are these the spirits of those who died in the attack?</string>
  <string id="88664">Don&apos;t blame yourself.</string>
  <string id="88665">Why aren&apos;t you caught up in this battle?</string>
  <string id="88667">You weren&apos;t much of a leader, were you?</string>
  <string id="88670">So you can&apos;t get back into the temple?</string>
  <string id="88671">Why didn&apos;t you follow Li?</string>
  <string id="88672">So you ran like a coward, and now you can&apos;t get back?</string>
  <string id="88675">Dirge will be restored, Abbot Song. I swear it.</string>
  <string id="88676">All I care about is getting back to the land of the living.</string>
  <string id="88677">They couldn&apos;t harm me anyway.</string>
  <string id="88678">So what destroyed the guardian?</string>
  <string id="88679">Maybe we have an ally in here.</string>
  <string id="88680">Good. One less thing to worry about.</string>
  <string id="88682">You mean a demon?</string>
  <string id="88683">Whatever it is, I&apos;ll destroy it!</string>
  <string id="88684">Are you saying you&apos;re scared?</string>
  <string id="88687">Don&apos;t worry. We&apos;ll find it.</string>
  <string id="88688">So what do we do now?</string>
  <string id="88689">Just tell me where it is so I can kill it!</string>
  <string id="88691" soundid="158171">I don&apos;t know much, but I saw one lift a stone no human could move. It looked immensely armored. The Lotus Assassin fortress seems the center of production.</string>
  <string id="88693">Tell me what you know about golems.</string>
  <string id="88698">How am I supposed to restore the fountains?</string>
  <string id="88699" soundid="156921"></string>
  <string id="88700" soundid="156922"></string>
  <string id="88701">Do you have any advice for me?</string>
  <string id="88702">I want to ask you some questions.</string>
  <string id="88703">I want to know more about my amulet.</string>
  <string id="88704">I saw Li take it from me. How can I still use it?</string>
  <string id="88706">If the power was mine, what does the amulet do?</string>
  <string id="88707">If the amulet is only a focus, why did Li take it from me?</string>
  <string id="88710">Why is it so powerful?</string>
  <string id="88711">Why were pieces of the amulet scattered across the Empire?</string>
  <string id="88714">I want to ask you something else.</string>
  <string id="88715">I&apos;m curious about the Spirit Monks and Dirge.</string>
  <string id="88716">You said I was born here at Dirge?</string>
  <string id="88717">What did the Spirit Monks do, exactly?</string>
  <string id="88718">Tell me more about Dirge.</string>
  <string id="88719">Tell me more about the Water Dragon.</string>
  <string id="88720">What was the Water Dragon the god of, exactly?</string>
  <string id="88721">How did the Emperor take her power?</string>
  <string id="88722">Can she really bring me back to life?</string>
  <string id="88723">I think we should move on.</string>
  <string id="88729" soundid="189584"></string>
  <string id="88731" soundid="189586"></string>
  <string id="88732" soundid="135933">Once there, find my hunter Spear Catches Leaf, if he still lives. He claimed to remember some sort of ritual that my forebears used to contact the Forest Shadow.</string>
  <string id="88733" soundid="135934">Remember that you want to go to the temple by the left fork when you reach the branch up above.</string>
  <string id="88734" soundid="135935">If you go to the right, you can find the Pilgrim&apos;s Rest Inn, an establishment I technically own but have very little to do with.</string>
  <string id="88735" soundid="135936">One of my hunters usually collects the taxes from them on my behalf.</string>
  <string id="88736" soundid="135937">It is impossible to miss. The temple is an impressive structure, carved into the rock itself.</string>
  <string id="88737" soundid="135938">You may, but I would find it unlikely. To call this area the safest part of the forest is misleading. The ghosts are numerous and vicious.</string>
  <string id="88738" soundid="135939">How would simple travelers and innkeepers survive when surrounded and cut off by these ghosts?</string>
  <string id="88739" soundid="135940">What else would aid you?</string>
  <string id="88740" soundid="135941">Ask him yourself, he&apos;s right there.</string>
  <string id="88741" soundid="135942">Perhaps the question is about your take on me, Lord?</string>
  <string id="88742" soundid="135943">Spear Catches Leaf is one of the best men I know. He&apos;s skilled and wise, and I can trust him, which is more than I will say for most. Beyond that, ask him yourself.</string>
  <string id="88743" soundid="135944">Spear Catches Leaf is one of my best men, and I&apos;m worried that I sent him to his doom. He insisted that he try this ritual, though.</string>
  <string id="88744" soundid="135945">To keep him safe, I sent another mercenary up with him. A hulking fellow who seemed more than adept with his axes.</string>
  <string id="88745" soundid="135946">This mercenary lacked your grace, poise, manners, and likely much of your skill, but then he had the good graces to work for the traditional pay: silver.</string>
  <string id="88746" soundid="135947">If the Forest Shadow is responsible, then you must find some way to stop her. Given her centuries-old connection to this forest, I expect we&apos;ll know in some way.</string>
  <string id="88747" soundid="135948">If she is not the cause, then we can only pray that she knows more about things than us. Hopefully you will be able to learn the truth from her.</string>
  <string id="88748" soundid="135949">Then you may still be able to learn something if Spear Catches Leaf was successful in reaching her first. If not, then we are both out of luck.</string>
  <string id="88749" soundid="135950">The same way I can be sure you&apos;ll hold up your end of things. I have something you need, and vice versa.</string>
  <string id="88750" soundid="135951">If you prove capable of curing this forest, I&apos;d be a fool to deny you your just reward out of spite, wouldn&apos;t I?</string>
  <string id="88751" soundid="135952">I don&apos;t fancy dying any time soon, and without your reward, you&apos;d not only be capable, but justified in murdering me where I stand.</string>
  <string id="88752" soundid="135953">That&apos;s true. I&apos;ll tell you whatever I can.</string>
  <string id="88756">Trainer: Smiling Mountain</string>
  <string id="88757">It is all a matter of training.</string>
  <string id="88759">Not many people have my skills.</string>
  <string id="88761">Are these ghosts a major problem?</string>
  <string id="88764">I&apos;m curious about this place. Will you answer a few questions?</string>
  <string id="88765">What is this area?</string>
  <string id="88768">How long have you been having problems with ghosts?</string>
  <string id="88771">Why are you camped here?</string>
  <string id="88774">What did you think you might learn by camping here?</string>
  <string id="88775">Why wouldn&apos;t you want to return to the city?</string>
  <string id="88777">Let&apos;s go back to my other questions.</string>
  <string id="88778">Is there any route from here to the Imperial City?</string>
  <string id="88781">Did you just say you have a flyer near here?</string>
  <string id="88783">That&apos;s enough of these questions for now.</string>
  <string id="88784">There&apos;s something else I wanted to ask.</string>
  <string id="88785">Perhaps there&apos;s some way I can help you.</string>
  <string id="88787">I&apos;ll take your advice and go back to Tien&apos;s Landing.</string>
  <string id="88789">I&apos;m trailing a group of Lotus Assassins who took my master.</string>
  <string id="88791">I am seeking a route to the Imperial City.</string>
  <string id="88795" soundid="138240">Examine your world from all angles and you will see the interconnectedness of all things. Even that which is humble can be the key to greater things.</string>
  <string id="88796" soundid="138241">[The sphere grows dim.]</string>
  <string id="88797">Where did you acquire a flyer?</string>
</tlk>