<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<tlk language="0">
  <string id="103462" soundid="158890">I do not mind waiting, but if you are only pretending to have an interest, then what is the point?</string>
  <string id="103463" soundid="158891">[Success] It is gratifying to hear you say so. I never meant to be a distraction. I have just always found the company of close friends very comforting in difficult times.</string>
  <string id="103464" soundid="158892">[Failure] No, I understand what you are unwilling to say. This isn&apos;t the time for personal concerns, even among old friends.</string>
  <string id="103465" soundid="158893">No, I didn&apos;t have anything pressing on my mind, although your company is always welcome. We seem so far from anything familiar.</string>
  <string id="103466" soundid="158894">Strange enemies, troubling plots; I will be glad when we can leave this place to find Master Li.</string>
  <string id="103467" soundid="158895">We should get in this Marvelous Dragonfly and go after Master Li&apos;s captors! Talk to Kang, and he will get us on our way.</string>
  <string id="103468" soundid="158896">Zu made it quite clear what we must do. We need a wind map, and we need a flyer. The longer we take, the farther away Master Li gets.</string>
  <string id="103469" soundid="158897">If that is your wish.</string>
  <string id="103470" soundid="158898">I do not like the area around this place, around Tien&apos;s Landing. There is rot here, deep in the heart of it. There are secrets, and there has been much suffering.</string>
  <string id="103471" soundid="158899">Maybe I just feel this way because of what happened at the school or what I fear will happen to Master Li. I just know we must be careful.</string>
  <string id="103472" soundid="158900">I will... but I cannot help worrying, or thinking about what has happened to Master Li.</string>
  <string id="103473" soundid="158901">Yes, of course. I am glad you are strong in the face of all the death and destruction we&apos;ve seen.</string>
  <string id="103474" soundid="158902">You weren&apos;t there. Neither of us knows what really went on. How can you say it wasn&apos;t the best course?</string>
  <string id="103475" soundid="158903">I... I know that, but he must have tried to do something... I don&apos;t know.</string>
  <string id="103476" soundid="158904">The lives of our friends are already lost. Master Li&apos;s life is still in jeopardy. How many others will come to depend on you? I fear your burden, not your ability.</string>
  <string id="103477" soundid="158905">I am glad to hear you say it. We must keep our heads clear to survive this. Is there anything else I can do for you?</string>
  <string id="103478" soundid="158906">We can&apos;t always choose such things. We can neither escape nor ignore what we are meant to do. I&apos;m sorry, is there something else we can talk about?</string>
  <string id="103479" soundid="158907">Be well, my friend.</string>
  <string id="103480" soundid="158908"></string>
  <string id="103481" soundid="158909">I don&apos;t think now is a good time to discuss things. I&apos;d rather not die in here, if you don&apos;t mind.</string>
  <string id="103482" soundid="158910">We should focus on getting to Jia. We can discuss things after we&apos;ve done that.</string>
  <string id="103483" soundid="158911">I suppose it is good that the Lotus Assassin Executioner accepted you. I wish I felt better about that.</string>
  <string id="103484" soundid="158912">Will you be heading to the Lotus Assassin fortress soon? When you are through there, the princess will take us to the palace.</string>
  <string id="103485" soundid="158913">At least, that&apos;s what she promised.</string>
  <string id="103486" soundid="158914">You&apos;ve appeased both of the Lotus Assassin recruiters. What else could we possibly need to do?</string>
  <string id="103487" soundid="158915">I dread the answer, but is there something the Inquisitor wants you to do as well?</string>
  <string id="103488" soundid="158916">Do we still need to finish that unpleasant business with Sheng, or can you just proceed to the fortress?</string>
  <string id="103489" soundid="158917">Yes? What do you need? I&apos;d like to get that business with Minister Sheng out of the way.</string>
  <string id="103490" soundid="158918">She worries about the poor minister, a man she would despise in any other circumstance.</string>
  <string id="103491" soundid="158919">Be careful in the Lotus Assassin fortress. They may not know you are an enemy, but they can still be dangerous.</string>
  <string id="103492" soundid="158920">Hurry to the palace. I hate it that Master Li is trapped there. Who knows what the Emperor is doing with him.</string>
  <string id="103493" soundid="158921">My father will explain. Death&apos;s Hand is behind this. You will see.</string>
  <string id="103494" soundid="158922">The Imperial City... I&apos;d always heard how impressive it was. The stories didn&apos;t do it justice.</string>
  <string id="103495" soundid="158923">I feel like I&apos;m a long way from home, and I don&apos;t even know where home is anymore.</string>
  <string id="103496" soundid="158924">If you want to go to the palace, you will have to talk to Princess Lian. She&apos;s the one who controls that path.</string>
  <string id="103497" soundid="158925">I can still have the map ready if you want to fly anywhere else, but we should get to the palace as soon as we have taken care of everything.</string>
  <string id="103498" soundid="158926">Very well, but let&apos;s not take too long. Master Li is waiting for us to rescue him.</string>
  <string id="103499" soundid="158927">Very well. I&apos;ll have the map ready.</string>
  <string id="103500" soundid="158928">Do you have time for me now? We should have spoken some time ago. If you do not wish me to burden you with my... attention, all you need to do is say so.</string>
  <string id="103501" soundid="158929">[Success] Thank you for that. This has been a difficult journey, and it is good to know such... close friends are thinking of me</string>
  <string id="103502" soundid="158930">I want to talk about what we have seen in the Imperial City. You are becoming more than a friend, and I value your perception.</string>
  <string id="103503" soundid="158931">[Failure] I see myself as only a distraction to you. Perhaps after all of this is done we can... I don&apos;t know.</string>
  <string id="103504" soundid="158932">I will keep my feelings to myself unless it is of the utmost importance. I don&apos;t want to distract from our rescue of Master Li.</string>
  <string id="103505" soundid="158933">[Success] I am sorry to distract you so, but it has been a burden for me, as well. </string>
  <string id="103506" soundid="158934">[Success] I am sorry. I know that you are doing your best. This is difficult for me, as well.</string>
  <string id="103507" soundid="158935">If that is the case, I will remain quiet unless discussing the most basic of our concerns. I... I&apos;m sorry I wasted your time... and mine.</string>
  <string id="103508" soundid="158936">I&apos;m sorry. I was foolish to disturb you in the first place, and it&apos;s indulgent of me to waste your time now. I just want... I&apos;m not sure what I want.</string>
  <string id="103509" soundid="158937">Rest assured that I know you have no interest in my personal concerns. I tried to speak with you a number of times, but you just put it off too long.</string>
  <string id="103510" soundid="158938">I will not bother you with this again, I promise that.</string>
  <string id="103511" soundid="158939">It is a bit late for that, and we have... more pressing concerns. Please, let&apos;s just get back to finding Master Li.</string>
  <string id="103512" soundid="158940">Do you really have an interest? I accepted your word before, but it seems you may have... exaggerated your concern.</string>
  <string id="103513" soundid="158941">If you don&apos;t want to pay attention to my... personal concerns, you need only say. We were content as friends.</string>
  <string id="103514" soundid="158942">[Success] I know I shouldn&apos;t need such assurances, but I do appreciate hearing you say such things. You are a great comfort in troubling times.</string>
  <string id="103515" soundid="158943">[Failure] Perhaps you didn&apos;t mean it, but that doesn&apos;t change much. We should just focus on the task at hand.</string>
  <string id="103516" soundid="158944">I don&apos;t mean to distract you. I just wanted someone familiar around me for a moment, if only to reassure me that we are still in the Empire I thought I knew.</string>
  <string id="103517" soundid="158945">I have long dreamed of reaching the Imperial City, but now that I have, under these circumstances, I am more overwhelmed than ever.</string>
  <string id="103518" soundid="158946">But that&apos;s what is bothering me. We can&apos;t be a long way from home, because our home is gone.</string>
  <string id="103519" soundid="158947">I can no longer say that what I see is strange or foreign, because I have lost what I would have compared it to. I am the one out of place now.</string>
  <string id="103520" soundid="158948">I... I would like that. To know you will be there, no matter what... I&apos;ve never had that stability. At least, not before joining the school.</string>
  <string id="103521" soundid="158949">As a child, I was marked by ill omens, apparently named for them. The people in Two Rivers were polite, but many did not hide the discomfort I caused them.</string>
  <string id="103522" soundid="158950">How do you deal with being able to sense the spirit world when people make such absurd conclusions?</string>
  <string id="103523" soundid="158951">That is horrible, but... I see what you mean. That is where they got their fear from in the first place, from tales of witch women and sorcerers. </string>
  <string id="103524" soundid="158952">I... did not expect this conversation to take this turn, but I still feel better. I am not quite comfortable with it yet, but I begin to see what has made you so strong.</string>
  <string id="103525" soundid="158953">I would like to continue this later. As always, I have much to think about after speaking with you.</string>
  <string id="103526" soundid="158954">I always just felt like a victim... but perhaps, like now, I was just out of place. Is that what you mean? I should feel superior because they did not understand me?</string>
  <string id="103527" soundid="158955">I... I cannot change who I am, I know. Perhaps I just have to let all of that go. It will not be easy.</string>
  <string id="103528" soundid="158956">But I do feel that you have given me a strength I did not have before. I... very much appreciate your support.</string>
  <string id="103529" soundid="158957">We should continue this discussion later. I have much to think about, and our work here has only just begun.</string>
  <string id="103530" soundid="158958">The Imperial City. I never dreamed I would reach it.</string>
  <string id="103531" soundid="158959">All right. What did you want to ask?</string>
  <string id="103532" soundid="158960">I suppose that is a reflex of mine. I cannot be excluded if I don&apos;t belong to begin with. That is why I did not participate much while at the school.</string>
  <string id="103533" soundid="158961">Get tough? I am quite capable of defending myself physically. Are you suggesting I harden my heart more than it already is? I already feel like an outsider.</string>
  <string id="103534" soundid="158962">What good is there in pointless rage? I have no desire to spend my days growing bitter over things I can&apos;t change.</string>
  <string id="103535" soundid="158963">[Success] I... I appreciate what I think you are saying, but the sentiment is so harsh. I don&apos;t want to become like the people who pushed me aside.</string>
  <string id="103536" soundid="158964">[Failure] No, it would be weak to fall into that kind of thinking just to protect myself from people who think exactly that way.</string>
  <string id="103537" soundid="158965">I&apos;m not sure what you are suggesting is all that healthy. Perhaps... perhaps we are not as similar as I thought.</string>
  <string id="103538" soundid="158966">I am sorry. I don&apos;t mean to distract you. I shouldn&apos;t be opening these old wounds while we have so much to do.</string>
  <string id="103539" soundid="158967">There was a time when I was more inclined to that kind of thought, but the stability of the school helped me find some measure of peace. </string>
  <string id="103540" soundid="158968">I suppose that is best. We should focus on the job ahead... and nothing else.</string>
  <string id="103541" soundid="158969">[Success] Perhaps I do, but how can I rationalize away my concern for others? I spent a long time suffering people who did the same to me.</string>
  <string id="103542" soundid="158970">[Success] I should stand up for myself more, I know that, but I don&apos;t want to become like the people who pushed me aside.</string>
  <string id="103543" soundid="158971">I don&apos;t want to seem ungrateful for her help, but having Silk Fox here is causing me some concern.</string>
  <string id="103544" soundid="158972">I mean, she is the daughter of the Emperor, and we do not know his role in Master Li&apos;s capture. Can she be trusted?</string>
  <string id="103545" soundid="158973">To you, perhaps, but not to me. I think I am perceived as a rival, but no one has told me what the game is.</string>
  <string id="103546" soundid="158974">She delights in taunting me, as though I were a child. If she is with us, why such hostility?</string>
  <string id="103547" soundid="158975">The Princess? The daughter of the Emperor is jealous of me? I think the size of our task has addled your senses.</string>
  <string id="103548" soundid="158976">What could I possibly have that would make her jealous? What does a woman from the borderlands have that the Princess herself does not?</string>
  <string id="103549" soundid="158977">W-what?</string>
  <string id="103550" soundid="158978">I&apos;m sorry. You caught me off guard for a moment.</string>
  <string id="103551" soundid="158979">Well that is... just foolish. Isn&apos;t it?</string>
  <string id="103552" soundid="158980">I am not! Why would you suggest that? And why did you smirk?</string>
  <string id="103553" soundid="158981">Are you... are you trying to pit us against each other? Does it amuse you to see people compete for your affection...?</string>
  <string id="103554" soundid="158982">Your affection... did I just say that? Well... damn you for being right.</string>
  <string id="103555" soundid="158983">You have always been a good friend to me, but I never meant... I mean, I couldn&apos;t....</string>
  <string id="103556" soundid="158984">No. No, I should have more control over this. This is too uncertain. You can&apos;t manipulate me into admitting something like this.</string>
  <string id="103557" soundid="158985">Not when you could leave whenever you want.</string>
  <string id="103558" soundid="158986">I prefer to have more control over myself, and as much control over what goes on around me as possible.</string>
  <string id="103559" soundid="158987">Silk Fox, or whatever she wants to be called, is an unknown I can&apos;t compensate for. I can&apos;t stay in balance if I don&apos;t know what she represents.</string>
  <string id="103560" soundid="158988">You and I, we talk and share thoughts, but she... forces me to consider where that might lead, both good and bad. I&apos;m not ready for that.</string>
  <string id="103561" soundid="158989">Don&apos;t you dare! Oh, you tease so much! I don&apos;t know what to do with you. You have become so different since we left Two Rivers.</string>
  <string id="103562" soundid="158990">Or perhaps it is me. For all the trouble we face, I feel like a weight is lifting.</string>
  <string id="103563" soundid="158991">I suppose it does. Strange that you are becoming more adept at reading my moods than I am.</string>
  <string id="103564" soundid="158992">I think we will have a great deal more to discuss in the coming days. I am... looking forward to it.</string>
  <string id="103565" soundid="158993">Until then, thank you for being so understanding. Master Li was right. You are special.</string>
  <string id="103566" soundid="158994">Then we are at an impasse, and I don&apos;t know how to get around it. I think... I think I am not ready for this.</string>
  <string id="103567" soundid="158995">Don&apos;t juggle your words. I am not amused by it. You know very well what I mean. It&apos;s probably at the front of your mind all the time, for all I know.</string>
  <string id="103568" soundid="158996">What? What do you mean?</string>
  <string id="103569" soundid="158997">Well, I would... I would.... I don&apos;t know. I... I&apos;m not used to thinking about that. I always felt that what came next was in someone else&apos;s hands.</string>
  <string id="103570" soundid="158998">I&apos;ve never been given that kind of choice before.</string>
  <string id="103571" soundid="158999"></string>
  <string id="103572" soundid="159000">[Success] I... I deserve not to be cast aside. I deserve better.</string>
  <string id="103573" soundid="159001"></string>
  <string id="103574" soundid="159002">[Failure] Be quiet! Just let me think. I don&apos;t like... I don&apos;t like what you are trying to do. You want me to lash out, to fight pain by giving it. I won&apos;t.</string>
  <string id="103575" soundid="159003">Why are you doing this? What are you trying to make me be? This isn&apos;t who I am.</string>
  <string id="103576" soundid="159004">I&apos;m sorry. I&apos;ve had enough. If you need anything for our current task, I will help, but I don&apos;t want to talk about this anymore.</string>
  <string id="103577" soundid="159005"></string>
  <string id="103578" soundid="159006">[Success] I... I can&apos;t justify it. I look at how much I fear and I can&apos;t.</string>
  <string id="103579" soundid="159007">I should... I should fight more. I should spit more. I should slap the princess in her smirking face, and I should... I should....</string>
  <string id="103580" soundid="159008">I should look at you without fear of what might happen, because if I grow to need you and you *leave,* ancestors help me, you will regret it.</string>
  <string id="103581" soundid="159009">Am I? Perhaps you should worry if you are worthy of mine. That is what you wish, isn&apos;t it? That I assert myself?</string>
  <string id="103582" soundid="159010">I did not intend for this to go as far as it has this quickly. I am startled by what you bring out in me. I need time to think.</string>
  <string id="103583" soundid="159011">You have introduced me to some interesting ideas. I thank you for that. I think I have been weak for too long.</string>
  <string id="103584" soundid="159012">Perhaps it is time that others started worrying about me. I thought striking back would lower me, but I don&apos;t know anymore.</string>
  <string id="103585" soundid="159013"></string>
  <string id="103586" soundid="159014"></string>
  <string id="103587" soundid="159015">[Success] They deserve... they deserve the worst I can imagine for making me weak.</string>
  <string id="103588" soundid="159016"></string>
  <string id="103589" soundid="159017">It is clear we have very different views about what is going on here. I&apos;m not sure I want to continue this. In fact, I am very sure.</string>
  <string id="103590" soundid="159018">If you wish something related to the task at hand, I will be happy to assist. Beyond that, I think we are done.</string>
  <string id="103591" soundid="159019">The situation is *useful?* Is that what I am here for? To be used? Will I be cast aside when you are done?</string>
  <string id="103592" soundid="159020">This is how it starts, you know. Soon there will be whispers and strange looks. I&apos;ve seen that before. I don&apos;t want to be a part of this.</string>
  <string id="103593" soundid="159021">So you don&apos;t trust her fully, but you invite her into our midst? I&apos;m not sure I understand that, especially when she is so confrontational.</string>
  <string id="103594" soundid="159022">We are much closer to finding our Master, but the path you are forced to take worries me, and I don&apos;t think the princess shares my concern.</string>
  <string id="103595" soundid="159023">We have faced these Lotus Assassins in small numbers before, but this is something different.</string>
  <string id="103596" soundid="159024">That is not what I meant. Hordes can be overcome. They are never the endless threat they appear to be.</string>
  <string id="103597" soundid="159025">What concerns me is how you have walked in their steps to fool them. I am... growing accustomed to you. I don&apos;t want to see this change you.</string>
  <string id="103598" soundid="159026">I have always respected your resolve, but there are dangers other than death. When you walk in the shadow of the enemy, you risk taking their shape.</string>
  <string id="103599" soundid="159027">You fought through the arena with your honor intact, but the Lotus Assassins will press you to commit far more vicious acts.</string>
  <string id="103600" soundid="159028">I don&apos;t want to win if it claims the good in you. What right do we have to harmony if we sacrifice what we believe to get it?</string>
  <string id="103601" soundid="159029">I know you won&apos;t, but it still does my heart good to hear it. The more I know about you, the more I want you to stay as you are.</string>
  <string id="103602" soundid="159030">It would be a shame for something to happen when we are... becoming close.</string>
  <string id="103603" soundid="159031">We will talk again. I... know everything will work out just fine.</string>
  <string id="103604" soundid="159032">What? It is very unlike you to say that. This is a different side of you from the one you have let me see so far.</string>
  <string id="103605" soundid="159033">How can you make a rightful claim to victory if, in the end, you are no better than the enemy we worked to defeat?</string>
  <string id="103606" soundid="159034">Yes, I suppose I should. It would appear that you already have.</string>
  <string id="103607" soundid="159035">You are very different from the boy I met at the school. Perhaps I am changing as well. I&apos;m sorry to have wasted your time. It won&apos;t happen again.</string>
  <string id="103608" soundid="159036">What? I suppose all that I know is what you have let me see. I thought I was getting close to your true self. Was I mistaken?</string>
  <string id="103609" soundid="159037">And if you sacrifice all the good that is in you, what then?</string>
  <string id="103610" soundid="159038">I don&apos;t dare judge you, but some of what I saw in the arena worried me. If you can act as you did, what will the Lotus Assassins bring out?</string>
  <string id="103611" soundid="159039">You found a way to appease the Lotus Assassins while sparing Minister Sheng. Will you be able to hide your honor when in their midst?</string>
  <string id="103612" soundid="159040">Minister Sheng paid the price for you to gain the favor of the Lotus Assassins. Who else will you be willing to sacrifice?</string>
  <string id="103613" soundid="159041">You embarrass me with such forward questions, but I think like that, as well. It bothers me that you risk so much to walk in the shadow of the enemy.</string>
  <string id="103614" soundid="159042">I see the necessity of walking in their steps to fool them, but I am... growing accustomed to you, and I don&apos;t want to see this change you.</string>
  <string id="103615" soundid="159043">It seems like such a long path, but we are getting closer to Master Li and those who took him. I am concerned about what is coming.</string>
  <string id="103616" soundid="159044">After all, the lair of the Lotus Assassins may hold a tempting power.</string>
  <string id="103617" soundid="159045">Nor should you. I know your strength, and how you place yourself above all others. You have shown how effective your way of thinking can be.</string>
  <string id="103618" soundid="159046">What? No, that isn&apos;t it at all. You have shown me that I shouldn&apos;t worry so much about the method so long as we approve of the result.</string>
  <string id="103619" soundid="159047">Ha! I have the utmost confidence in you. You have shown me what strength can be drawn from thinking of yourself first.</string>
  <string id="103620" soundid="159048">I know that if there is any power to be taken from the Lotus Assassins, you will take it. I am not concerned about that. Any help would be useful to us, despite the source.</string>
  <string id="103621" soundid="159049">I am more concerned that their presentation might be... seductive. You will not forget that our mission is to free our master, will you?</string>
  <string id="103622" soundid="159050">I knew you would stay true to our cause. If we turn the powers of our enemy against them, more the better.</string>
  <string id="103623" soundid="159051">It would be good to see someone else suffer for a change.</string>
  <string id="103624" soundid="159052">Why would this change surprise you? You showed me how fruitless it was to try and meet cruelty with grace. If that applies to my life, it certainly applies here.</string>
  <string id="103625" soundid="159053">If the methods of the Lotus Assassins bring us strength, you should use them. If you don&apos;t, and we lose Master Li again, you, not our enemy, will be the target of my anger.</string>
  <string id="103626" soundid="159054">Do I? I suppose I don&apos;t have the patience to let people change on their own anymore, but not many deserved it.</string>
  <string id="103627" soundid="159055">You helped me to see that, and I am grateful, even if it is taking me a while to get used to this darker view of the world.</string>
  <string id="103628" soundid="159056">As long as you stay with me, I know everything will work out just fine. I&apos;ve changed because of you... for you.</string>
  <string id="103629" soundid="159057">I&apos;m... I&apos;m glad. I won&apos;t lose you, or the chance to save Master Li. I can&apos;t.</string>
  <string id="103630" soundid="159058">Can we... get back to the task at hand? There will be time to speak about this later, when we get this hateful world back to normal.</string>
  <string id="103631" soundid="159059">I just want this to be over so we can... build new lives.</string>
  <string id="103632" soundid="159060">I was a fool. You made that clear the last time we talked. I was trying to find peace while making excuses for the behavior of others.</string>
  <string id="103633" soundid="159061">I tried to effect change by example, only I didn&apos;t know how to react when bad things continued to happen. Now I know better.</string>
  <string id="103634" soundid="159062">Our enemies should be served back whatever they throw at us. Make them reap what they sow. Our cause is too worthy to do otherwise.</string>
  <string id="103635" soundid="159063">This isn&apos;t what you wanted? Why convince me of this if it isn&apos;t to your liking?</string>
  <string id="103636" soundid="159064">[Success] I didn&apos;t think I was. When you wanted me to be stronger, I thought you meant like the Princess. Her concerns are all that matter to her.</string>
  <string id="103637" soundid="159065">I don&apos;t want to see the world like that, like I have to be as cold as those we fight. I don&apos;t want to think that you are like that.</string>
  <string id="103638" soundid="159066">What right do we have to win, if we can&apos;t tell ourselves from the enemy? I know my heart isn&apos;t like that. I want to believe yours isn&apos;t, either.</string>
  <string id="103639" soundid="159067">I... I need some time to think. Thank you for this. I feel as though I have turned away from a very dark path.</string>
  <string id="103640" soundid="159068">[Failure] What good does this admission do me? I am tired of trying to be what others want and of being cast aside when I fail.</string>
  <string id="103641" soundid="159069">W-what? But this was what you wanted, wasn&apos;t it? For me to give back the pain directed at me? Why convince me of this, if it will only drive you away?</string>
  <string id="103642" soundid="159070">I... I can&apos;t do this anymore. I tried to be what you wanted, but it isn&apos;t enough. I don&apos;t know who I am, or who you want me to be.</string>
  <string id="103643" soundid="159071">I think... I think I need to let this go. Master Li should be our focus. This only clouds my eyes... and my heart.</string>
  <string id="103644" soundid="159072">If you need anything, I will be here, but I don&apos;t think these talks are helping. Maybe... when everything is done. I&apos;m sorry for wasting your time.</string>
  <string id="103645" soundid="159073">If you subjugated the whole of their order, that would be very useful to us, indeed. I wouldn&apos;t be against that. We could use them to our advantage against their leaders.</string>
  <string id="103646" soundid="159074">It is just about time, isn&apos;t it? The Emperor or Death&apos;s Hand or whoever can only keep us from our Master for so long.</string>
  <string id="103647" soundid="159075">So much has happened to get us here: our hard work, the loss of Sagacious Zu. I am looking forward to having our questions answered.</string>
  <string id="103648" soundid="159076">I... also don&apos;t want to worry about you anymore. What if you are next to fall?</string>
  <string id="103649" soundid="159077">I think I trust you now, but I am not sure what should come next. This seems like such an uncertain time to be making plans for the future.</string>
  <string id="103650" soundid="159078">You have a very odd way of twisting a sentiment. How should I react to such a &quot;comfort?&quot; It is, I suppose, better than nothing.</string>
  <string id="103651" soundid="159079">Listen to me. I think I am used to this new life, laughing about the danger we will face, about whether we will survive. Is this what &quot;normal&quot; has become?</string>
  <string id="103652" soundid="159080">I feel selfish for trying to find peace while this war of ours continues. If... when we free Master Li, that will be the more appropriate time for this.</string>
  <string id="103653" soundid="159081">I doubt you need any more incentive, but I am glad I have that effect.</string>
  <string id="103654" soundid="159082">Now it is just up to the princess to keep her word, and we can end this. Everything will be all right again. I know it.</string>
  <string id="103655" soundid="159083">Don&apos;t mistake my caution for reluctance. I have come to see how important you are to me, but... I&apos;m sorry, I need to know that this will be over soon.</string>
  <string id="103656" soundid="159084">If the princess keeps her word, we can leave for the palace when you are ready. Then it will feel like the end is near, like we can go home.</string>
  <string id="103657" soundid="159085">We are very close to our goal now, aren&apos;t we? I am growing impatient for answers. We have pushed against the walls blocking our way, and it&apos;s about time we broke through.</string>
  <string id="103658" soundid="159086">After suffering so much and losing Sagacious Zu, I think this Emperor owes us a great deal.</string>
  <string id="103659" soundid="159087">I think we are owed time to be safe together. If you were the next to fall, I would never forgive you.</string>
  <string id="103660" soundid="159088">That sounds more like a war cry than a sign of affection, but I suppose I should expect nothing less. Everything is a matter of strength to you.</string>
  <string id="103661" soundid="159089">As long as your boasts match your action, I will be happy. I am looking forward to something for the first time in a great while. I know you will not disappoint.</string>
  <string id="103662" soundid="159090">Smirk all you like, but the threat is real. I feel selfish pushing for what I want while this war of ours is ongoing, but I will have no such reservations when it is done.</string>
  <string id="103663" soundid="159091">I am looking forward to something for the first time in a great while. You should not disappoint me.</string>
  <string id="103664" soundid="159092">What? But this is what you wanted, isn&apos;t it? You said I needed to put myself first. Why convince me of this if it would only drive you away?</string>
  <string id="103665" soundid="159093">It is too late for apologies. I need consistency, and I am not finding it with you. </string>
  <string id="103666" soundid="159094">I should hope so. I&apos;m still a stranger in my own skin. If I don&apos;t encourage you to succeed, what good are the changes I have tried to make?</string>
  <string id="103667" soundid="159095">Let&apos;s just get this over with. Once we rescue Master Li, we can turn our minds to more... pleasing thoughts.</string>
  <string id="103668" soundid="159096">That is really not necessary right now, although I do enjoy the attention. We have come so far together. Thank you for that.</string>
  <string id="103669" soundid="159097">I&apos;ve only been here as long as you have. I doubt I have any information you would find useful.</string>
  <string id="103670" soundid="159098">So much has happened... so much death. Sagacious Zu&apos;s sacrifice weighs on my mind.</string>
  <string id="103671" soundid="159099">Now I understand why he was so troubled. It wasn&apos;t cowardice that led to his exile from the Lotus Assassins, it was conscience.</string>
  <string id="103672" soundid="159100">He must have wanted to oppose them, even if he didn&apos;t realize it at first, but that would have meant his superiors were wrong, a far graver thing than just being evil.</string>
  <string id="103673" soundid="159101">What must it be like, to be so devoted that it was easier to imagine a deficiency in himself than to confront the truth of the Emperor&apos;s evil?</string>
  <string id="103674" soundid="159102">We have to make sure this can never happen again. I know we will. We have to.</string>
  <string id="103675" soundid="159103">Hurry to the palace. I can&apos;t bear to think of Master Li remaining in the hands of this Emperor a moment longer.</string>
  <string id="103676" soundid="159104">And yet, he still did what he thought he must. We can&apos;t let that action be for nothing.</string>
  <string id="103677" soundid="159105">He was flawed, as we all are, but he still managed to do what he thought he must. We can&apos;t let that action be for nothing. </string>
  <string id="103678" soundid="159106">Sagacious Zu seemed very certain that Death&apos;s Hand is no normal opponent. He was also very deliberate in his actions, like he knew the fight was inevitable.</string>
  <string id="103679" soundid="159107">I don&apos;t like it, but you have to get as close to the Lotus Assassins as you can to gain access to their fortress.</string>
  <string id="103680" soundid="159108">That&apos;s what the Princess wants, and she is our passage to the palace.</string>
  <string id="103681" soundid="180318">Grr... he presumes to trap us, too. He is too strong to fight alone, but you can use the strength of your followers. What else are they good for?</string>
  <string id="103682" soundid="159110">Let&apos;s get what we need and get out of here. Just do whatever your &quot;master&quot; wants so we can get into the inner chambers of the fortress.</string>
  <string id="103684" soundid="159112">As much as I think it is foolishly dangerous, you need to go to the Lotus Assassin fortress and find the information the Princess needs.</string>
  <string id="103685" soundid="159113">Very well, but we should get that business with Minister Sheng out of the way.</string>
  <string id="103686" soundid="159114">Don&apos;t go too far. I&apos;d get lost in this city. I know it.</string>
  <string id="103687" soundid="159115">This is all so much to absorb. I would appreciate your counsel if you have time to speak privately.</string>
  <string id="103688" soundid="159116">Are you ready to go? You said that we needed to deal with Sheng, and I don&apos;t want to leave the matter too long.</string>
  <string id="103689" soundid="159117">Yes? I like to think that we can take time to talk about... important things.</string>
  <string id="103690" soundid="159118">What did you want to talk about?</string>
  <string id="103691" soundid="159119"></string>
  <string id="103692" soundid="159120">Don&apos;t look at me. It is bad enough I feel your will within my mind. I don&apos;t want to see your face.</string>
  <string id="103693" soundid="159121">My eyes may do as you command, but they will hold no affection for you.</string>
  <string id="103694" soundid="159122">No, don&apos;t make me suffer this. What we shared was... was a lie! Do not shame me further.</string>
  <string id="103695" soundid="159123">I care for you.</string>
  <string id="103696" soundid="159124">I would turn my head in shame if my body would let me. Will the Empire itself be forced to look at you in the same way?</string>
  <string id="103697" soundid="159125">Just... just go.</string>
  <string id="103698" soundid="159126">[Dawn Star obediently remains quiet.]</string>
  <string id="103699" soundid="159127">You can make me do what you want, but you will never again have what I once freely gave.</string>
  <string id="103700" soundid="159128">Do not mock me now by claiming my feelings are a surprise. You knew my horror when you chose this fate for me.</string>
  <string id="103701" soundid="159129">That this comes after what we shared makes it all the more a betrayal. I was at your side by choice. Now you stand alone, whether I am there or not.</string>
  <string id="103702" soundid="159130">Now I see the scars of Master Li&apos;s betrayal clearer than ever. You truly are a wounded child.</string>
  <string id="103703" soundid="159131">There is no strength in this. Only the most insecure leader would command such forced obedience.</string>
  <string id="103704" soundid="159132">Are you so fearful of opposition? Poor child, grasping for control.</string>
  <string id="103705" soundid="159133">No, it was *not!* If you had listened to my concerns, I would have stayed by you of my own free will.</string>
  <string id="103706" soundid="159134">I am never alone. You were always in my mind. Now it is no longer my choice, and it means nothing.</string>
  <string id="103707" soundid="159135">I stood by you through everything. Now you stand alone, even if I am still here.</string>
  <string id="103708" soundid="159136">So many changes. The Jade Empire is not the place I once thought it was.</string>
  <string id="103709" soundid="159137">The closer we get to power, the more I love what you are becoming. So many lies... the Empire needs your firm hand.</string>
  <string id="103710" soundid="159138">Death&apos;s Hand is a fine symbol of your power. The princess and Sky are fools for not seeing his worth. Someone has to turn the evils of others to good.</string>
  <string id="103711" soundid="159139">Ha ha ha! There will be time for whatever you want. If nothing else, I can depend on you to make the world suit your schedule.</string>
  <string id="103712" soundid="159140">Everyone else in my life has betrayed what they were supposed to stand for. You alone have stayed true in your actions and words.</string>
  <string id="103713" soundid="159141">Will there be time for us? If we take it.</string>
  <string id="103714" soundid="159142">Good. I used to think that harmony and balance would save the world. Now I know that those are just words misused by everyone.</string>
  <string id="103715" soundid="159143">Am I? Perhaps, but that is only because you have shown me that the world is a cold place.</string>
  <string id="103716" soundid="159144">I was destined to be forever a victim, but no longer. I thank you for that, and I will stand by you whatever comes.</string>
  <string id="103717" soundid="159145">If that is what is needed to rid the world of the fools that endangered the Empire, so be it. Better you than anyone else.</string>
  <string id="103718" soundid="159146">You have shown me that no one else is worthy of that seat of power. I know you will make things as right as they can be.</string>
  <string id="103719" soundid="159147">Go on now, we have been over this. You will shape the Empire with the firm hand it needs, unlike all the unworthy betrayers we have fought.</string>
  <string id="103720" soundid="159148">I have no doubt that there will be. When everything is restored to the way it was, we will be able to return to the lives we lost.</string>
  <string id="103721" soundid="159149">It won&apos;t be perfect, I know, but I even miss the simple heartache of mortal sorrow. Our time among the gods has forced greater worries upon us.</string>
  <string id="103722" soundid="159150">Will there be time for us? More than anything, I hope so.</string>
  <string id="103723" soundid="159151">Your resolve is inspiring. The Master Li I thought I knew would be proud. The man we now face should be worried.</string>
  <string id="103724" soundid="159152">There is a great deal of temptation ahead of you. I know you will make your decisions carefully.</string>
  <string id="103725" soundid="159153">I know you won&apos;t make the same mistakes your master did.</string>
  <string id="103726" soundid="159154">You asked me once already, and I still have no doubt. When all is restored, the normal troubles of mortal living will seem like the greatest blessings.</string>
  <string id="103727" soundid="159155">I hope there is room left in you for compassion. Two others before you have walked the road of power and corruption. Please learn from their mistakes.</string>
  <string id="103728" soundid="159156">And well they should. There must be punishment for the evil that has come to pass, and there must be control to ensure it does not happen again.</string>
  <string id="103729" soundid="159157">Please, it pains me to see you struggling under such anger. Let my love guide you away from the corruption of revenge and mindless power. I know your heart.</string>
  <string id="103730" soundid="159158">I know, and perhaps the greatest and hardest of those is yet to come. So much is on your shoulders.</string>
  <string id="103731" soundid="159159">I do not envy you, but I will be with you, my friend. We will make sure the Empire does not fall to the desires of a corrupted few.</string>
  <string id="103732" soundid="159160">I will be there when you take control. We will make certain that no one can harm the people of the Empire again.</string>
  <string id="103733" soundid="159161">When the time comes, we will reveal what evils have been done in the name of power. We will make certain this cannot happen again. You and I.</string>
  <string id="103734" soundid="159162">I know everything will be fine. You will see to it.</string>
  <string id="103735" soundid="159163">Sky was a fool to betray you. All traitors will receive what they deserve. All of them.</string>
  <string id="103736" soundid="159164">I know you will make things right. You have shown me what needs to be done.</string>
  <string id="103737" soundid="159165">It pains me to see Sky a prisoner of your will. I know it was the most gentle of punishments available to you, but it is still sad.</string>
  <string id="103738" soundid="159166">What Master Li has done is unforgivable. We have to set things right, and undo the evil he has put in motion.</string>
  <string id="103739" soundid="159167"></string>
  <string id="103740" soundid="159168">What&apos;s the matter, Dawn Star? Are you scared that Master Li might find out?</string>
  <string id="103741" soundid="159169">There is talk of approaching bandits, and you bother me with unsubtle advances? How very like you, Gao. No doubt a tactic learned from your criminal father.</string>
  <string id="103742" soundid="159170">His name is Gao the Greater, and he built a fortune out of some ragged thieves and slave traders. If my charm can&apos;t lift your spirit, I&apos;ll buy the ground from under you.</string>
  <string id="103743" soundid="159171">Flaunting your father&apos;s undeserved wealth does not impress me, Gao. It only serves to push me further away.</string>
  <string id="103744" soundid="159172">You step beyond your station. She and I are discussing her future.</string>
  <string id="103745" soundid="159173">Thank you, Gao, but I&apos;ll pick my own poison. Now leave, and, if you&apos;d be so kind, stay downwind.</string>
  <string id="103746" soundid="159174">I won&apos;t forget this, Dawn Star. You show great disrespect.</string>
  <string id="103747" soundid="159175">You, as well. You will not take all the glory if there is an attack. We are not through.</string>
  <string id="103748" soundid="159176">Ugh. He is Gao the *Lesser* in all respects. I thought Master Li allowed him to stay so that the influence of the father could be countered, but Gao never learns.</string>
  <string id="103749" soundid="159177">He acts like he is above Master Li&apos;s teachings. Such are the conceits of wealth, I suppose. I appreciate that you arrived when you did.</string>
  <string id="103750" soundid="159178">You&apos;ve said so already. I&apos;m fine. What brings you here?</string>
  <string id="103751" soundid="159179">That is nice to hear. Gao could learn much from you, if he wanted to learn anything from anyone.</string>
  <string id="103752" soundid="159180">Please, he&apos;s not worth it. Let&apos;s just move on. What brings you here?</string>
  <string id="103753" soundid="159181">What does Gao the Lesser ever want? He is convinced that he can buy everything, and that includes people. He is a spoiled little man.</string>
  <string id="103754" soundid="159182">I&apos;d rather not dwell on him. Let&apos;s not increase his influence by talking about him after he&apos;s gone. What is it you wish?</string>
  <string id="103755" soundid="159183">Yes, he said you were coming. He just passed here with Si Pat, on his way to help Kia Min. It&apos;s strange that simple bandits would launch such a raid.</string>
  <string id="103756" soundid="159184">Master Li was concerned that this would interrupt your training. His respect for your potential is just so... absolute. Has he told you any more about your future?</string>
  <string id="103757" soundid="159185">Only what Master Li has told you in the past: You are meant for great things, but you must discover them yourself.</string>
  <string id="103758" soundid="159186">It must be so frustrating, but exciting, as well.</string>
  <string id="103759" soundid="159187">It is not the same. You are filled with the promise of great things, even if they are unknown. My skills will always be darker.</string>
  <string id="103760" soundid="159188">I can see into the spiritual, an ability that grants some insight, but it doesn&apos;t seem to be useful for anything other than keeping me awake at night.</string>
  <string id="103761" soundid="159189">I helped Master Li discover the unrest that shapes your future, but I see only problems, while you are destined to find solutions. I envy you for that.</string>
  <string id="103762" soundid="159190">I&apos;m glad. You have always kept your feet on the ground. What does Master Li say? That you should keep the basics close to heart?</string>
  <string id="103769">Hello, Dawn Star. I hope I&apos;m not interrupting.</string>
  <string id="103775">I don&apos;t like seeing you upset.</string>
  <string id="103776">What did Gao want?</string>
  <string id="103778">You know about the bandits. Master Li said to get a weapon from Gujin.</string>
  <string id="103780">Not specifically. What do you know about it?</string>
  <string id="103782">He has told you similar things. You have talents, too.</string>
  <string id="103785">Please don&apos;t put me on a pedestal. I&apos;d rather stand beside my friends.</string>
  <string id="103787">Let&apos;s go together. I could use the company.</string>
  <string id="103788">Goodbye, then.</string>
  <string id="103790">Could I ask you a few more questions?</string>
  <string id="103791">Where can I find Gujin?</string>
  <string id="103793">How did you help Master Li find out about the restless dead?</string>
  <string id="103796">What do you know about the spirit world?</string>
  <string id="103799">What makes them so threatening?</string>
  <string id="103802">What happens to them in the underworld?</string>
  <string id="103805">That&apos;s all for now.</string>
  <string id="103808">And well you should. I am bound for great things.</string>
  <string id="103810">He thinks it will encourage me. I&apos;m tired of it. Aren&apos;t you?</string>
  <string id="103812">No. I have a bad feeling, Dawn Star.</string>
  <string id="103813">I&apos;m sure nothing is going to happen.</string>
  <string id="103815">I don&apos;t remember. I&apos;m sure it was nothing.</string>
  <string id="103816">Speculation is a fool&apos;s game. He&apos;ll tell me soon enough.</string>
  <string id="103818">Hello, Dawn Star. I certainly hope I *am* interrupting.</string>
  <string id="103819">It sounds like Dawn Star would like you to leave, Gao.</string>
  <string id="103822">Do you want to talk about the attack?</string>
  <string id="103825">Where did you live before you came to the school?</string>
  <string id="103828">Why did you move around? How did you come here?</string>
  <string id="103832">It is troubling to not know your past.</string>
  <string id="103834">Does your ability have any practical use?</string>
  <string id="103837">Your name is unusual. Is it a title?</string>
  <string id="103840">How this affects you doesn&apos;t matter. I have more important questions.</string>
  <string id="103841">Perhaps later.</string>
  <string id="103847">x</string>
  <string id="103848">x</string>
  <string id="103849">x</string>
  <string id="103850">x</string>
  <string id="103851">x</string>
  <string id="103852">x</string>
  <string id="103853">x</string>
  <string id="103854">Who are the people of interest in the village?</string>
  <string id="103859">Master Li does what he must. He is our master.</string>
  <string id="103861">Master Li does a lot of confusing things.</string>
  <string id="103865">Master Li is a fool. I can&apos;t wait to leave.</string>
  <string id="103869">I didn&apos;t want to fight them all, but there was no real choice.</string>
  <string id="103880">He kidnapped you so you wouldn&apos;t get caught in an attack?</string>
  <string id="103882">We have to try. There has to be a way!</string>
  <string id="103884">I just need to know if we can control it safely.</string>
  <string id="103888">So it&apos;s like flying a swimming ox. Well *that* helps.</string>
  <string id="103891">I tried to understand his trouble, but he won&apos;t let me.</string>
  <string id="103894">We&apos;re wasting time. If we are going, let&apos;s go!</string>
  <string id="103896">Fine, I guess we just hope for the best.</string>
  <string id="103897">Get to the point! Will it work or not?</string>
  <string id="103898">How do you know so much about it?</string>
  <string id="103900">I will not run from a fight!</string>
  <string id="103901">That&apos;s your solution to everything: Just walk away.</string>
  <string id="103902">Was this all a distraction to get me out of the village?</string>
  <string id="103903">They chose their path. I just happened to cross it.</string>
  <string id="103905">I enjoyed it. It was real, not like the gentle sparring at the school.</string>
  <string id="103908">I wouldn&apos;t let anything happen to you, Dawn Star.</string>
  <string id="103913">He was clearly delusional. Pay no attention.</string>
  <string id="103915">Let&apos;s all just get out of here. We need to get back.</string>
  <string id="103917">Dawn Star, head for the entrance. Zu and I will clear the rest of the cave.</string>
  <string id="103919">Zu, head for the entrance. Dawn Star and I will clear the rest of the cave.</string>
  <string id="103921">I don&apos;t know, but I think we should head back to the village.</string>
  <string id="103923">Empty threats. Let him argue with the worms.</string>
  <string id="103927">I would have done the same for any of the students.</string>
  <string id="103929">Yes, I always get saddled with Master Li&apos;s cast-off chores.</string>
  <string id="103938">[TEMP] generic_training_body_5</string>
  <string id="103939">We will find survivors. There has to be someone left.</string>
  <string id="103941">I need you ready to fight, Dawn Star.</string>
  <string id="103942">This strange schematic has had better days, the paper ragged at the corners. While the page is filled with doodled diagrams, including one for a device that seems designed to colorize rice for easy sorting, the majority of the space is taken up by a single notation. &quot;Foul smelling water must be purified of the taint of a rotted egg. Only the water wheel and the applauding stack can manage it, even then only with the dragon&apos;s help.&quot;</string>
  <string id="103944">Strange Light</string>
  <string id="103945">[TEMP] generic_training_mind_1</string>
  <string id="103946">[TEMP] generic_training_mind_2</string>
  <string id="103947" soundid="173815">Everyone deserves a few moments away from work, don&apos;t they? Things will be fine at the quarry without me.</string>
  <string id="103948">[TEMP] generic_training_mind_3</string>
  <string id="103949" soundid="173816">Besides, it&apos;s nice to see the stones on display. This sculpture of Sagacious Tien&apos;s head is like an unending well of inspiration to me.</string>
  <string id="103965">Why would they come here? Where did they take Master Li?</string>
  <string id="103967">Master Li told me that he was the Emperor&apos;s brother. Gao overheard.</string>
  <string id="103973">If Death&apos;s Hand is as vicious as you say, he had to try something.</string>
  <string id="103975">You clearly aren&apos;t one now. Skip the details, just tell me how to find Master Li.</string>
  <string id="103977">That explains your unwillingness to come here. You recognized a familiar tactic.</string>
  <string id="103981">We must find where they took Master Li and rescue him.</string>
  <string id="103983">Why? What is there?</string>
  <string id="103985">Yes, I am still curious about you, Lotus Assassin.</string>
  <string id="103989">You found this obscure set of instructions and copied them down on a hunch. &quot;Iron is made stronger through the alloy, and nickel binds well to make a sharp blade. It can also be a reactive fuel, but certain configurations must be preserved. The dragon watches over the controlled lightning, while the cogs spin dutifully on their own.&quot;</string>
  <string id="103994">That&apos;s a nice way of saying we still don&apos;t trust you.</string>
  <string id="103995">And if you&apos;ve been lying, I&apos;ll see that you answer for it.</string>
  <string id="103996">Master Li may have old friends who could help us there.</string>
  <string id="103998">Will that get us closer to Gao the Greater?</string>
  <string id="103999">x</string>
  <string id="104000">Master Li was training me for a journey. I should continue with that.</string>
  <string id="104002">We need to figure out how and why Gao triggered this.</string>
  <string id="104004">I knew finding you in the swamp was too convenient! What do you know of this?</string>
  <string id="104005">You&apos;re just a bitter swamp hermit. What do you know?</string>
  <string id="104007">Gao must have known. Did he say anything to you, Dawn Star?</string>
  <string id="104009">Master Li said I was important, that I was a destined for great conflict.</string>
  <string id="104011">Why did we wade through Gao&apos;s men if this is someone else&apos;s work?</string>
  <string id="104013">Woo mentioned a woman giving orders. What about her?</string>
  <string id="104022">I&apos;m fine. Dawn Star, are you okay?</string>
  <string id="104023">It&apos;ll take more than a little crash to hurt me!</string>
  <string id="104025">Why didn&apos;t you tell me this earlier?</string>
  <string id="104028">So we need to find a wind map and a new flyer?</string>
  <string id="104030">Things just keep getting better and better, don&apos;t they?</string>
  <string id="104032">Don&apos;t worry, Dawn Star. I&apos;ll find a way to get us flying again.</string>
  <string id="104036">Okay, let&apos;s go check out the town. Zu, you come with me.</string>
  <string id="104039">Let&apos;s get moving. Dawn Star, come with me.</string>
  <string id="104041">I don&apos;t plan on being stuck here for long. I&apos;ll figure something out.</string>
  <string id="104042">It&apos;s hopeless. We&apos;ll never catch up to Master Li now.</string>
  <string id="104044">Then I guess we&apos;re grounded until we find a wind map.</string>
  <string id="104046" soundid="196474"></string>
  <string id="104047" soundid="196475"></string>
  <string id="104048" soundid="196476"></string>
  <string id="104050">She is correct about that. I was with him the longest.</string>
  <string id="104054">Like the burning of Dirge that Hui just mentioned?</string>
  <string id="104056">Are you trying to claim she was at Dirge, as well, Zu?</string>
  <string id="104059">What kind of comment is that, Zu? What are you getting at?</string>
  <string id="104061">You are a comforting fellow, Zu. It must be the Lotus Assassin in you.</string>
  <string id="104062">Yes, Zu, I am far more deserving of your attention.</string>
  <string id="104069">How do you control it from this distance?</string>
  <string id="104072">I want that machine handy, Kang. Just land it.</string>
  <string id="104073">Very well. Enough of this, what do we need to do now?</string>
  <string id="104078">I have some general questions.</string>
  <string id="104079">I am interested in how you are, Dawn Star. Is there anything bothering you?</string>
  <string id="104082">Understandable, considering the injustice that was done.</string>
  <string id="104084">You were abandoned? Tell me about that.</string>
  <string id="104087">I am glad you came to the school. Don&apos;t linger on fools who may have shunned you.</string>
  <string id="104090">It doesn&apos;t matter. You are a long way from home, and we are through with the ruins.</string>
  <string id="104091">Better to have anger than pointless sorrow. They might kill their enemy. You only hurt yourself.</string>
  <string id="104093">If this is just about your personal feelings, we have more important things to do.</string>
  <string id="104094">If they could not understand in life, how would they in death?</string>
  <string id="104096">Why concern yourself? They fall like any other enemy.</string>
  <string id="104098">I am sorry. What concerns you about this place?</string>
  <string id="104100">The next enemy is someone else&apos;s concern. I am not the world&apos;s keeper.</string>
  <string id="104104">When did you notice a change?</string>
  <string id="104107">I don&apos;t know, but I am glad that you wanted me to.</string>
  <string id="104109">Comfort yourself. I have no interest in helping the weak grow dependent.</string>
  <string id="104112">I don&apos;t see how. The arrogance of the heavens is immeasurable.</string>
  <string id="104113">I suppose. When did you first notice a change from harmony?</string>
  <string id="104114">I am not content with that. I suspect that neither are you.</string>
  <string id="104116">I will make things right, Dawn Star. With your help.</string>
  <string id="104117">*You* decide what you are entitled to. Not your family, not Master Li, not me.</string>
  <string id="104120">You don&apos;t speak much about your life before the school.</string>
  <string id="104124">I am beginning to feel some of that myself. Go on.</string>
  <string id="104127">Their slavery was enforced by bars. Yours seems self-inflicted.</string>
  <string id="104130">The weak often find themselves in such a predicament.</string>
  <string id="104133">I apologize. I did not mean that you intentionally suffered.</string>
  <string id="104136">Your trauma was long ago, but you still hurt. Were they *very strong,* or are you *very weak?*</string>
  <string id="104140">Again you cloud the issue. Their suffering is real. You are just moody.</string>
  <string id="104143">Give me the short version, please.</string>
  <string id="104144">I am sorry. Please, tell me your concern.</string>
  <string id="104146">This is of no interest to me.</string>
  <string id="104148">[Charm] My apologies. I was overwhelmed with the task ahead.</string>
  <string id="104150">Of course. What did you want to discuss?</string>
  <string id="104151">I don&apos;t see the value in this.</string>
  <string id="104153">[Intuition] Try to understand the burden I am working under. I won&apos;t neglect you again.</string>
  <string id="104155">[Intimidation] Pressing your concerns only adds to my burden. Try to be part of the solution.</string>
  <string id="104157">I have no interest in speaking with you.</string>
  <string id="104159">[Charm] Trust me when I say that I am very concerned about your feelings.</string>
  <string id="104163">What should I concentrate on doing?</string>
  <string id="104164">Let&apos;s return to my other questions.</string>
  <string id="104165">What do you think of this place?</string>
  <string id="104167">Don&apos;t worry. Be strong.</string>
  <string id="104168">It will be okay. We will save him.</string>
  <string id="104169">He was a fool. What kind of man gives himself to the enemy?</string>
  <string id="104170">It couldn&apos;t have been worse. Everyone else was killed.</string>
  <string id="104171">I don&apos;t appreciate your lack of confidence in me.</string>
  <string id="104172">I understand, Dawn Star. Everything will be all right.</string>
  <string id="104173">I never asked for anyone to depend on me.</string>
  <string id="104174">Goodbye for now.</string>
  <string id="104182">Gather everyone, and have Kang ready the flyer.</string>
  <string id="104184">Get the map ready. I want to fly somewhere.</string>
  <string id="104185">Did you want to talk? Your feelings are very important to me.</string>
  <string id="104186">[Charm] My apologies. I will not neglect you again.</string>
  <string id="104188">What did you want to discuss?</string>
  <string id="104189">I don&apos;t see the value in this.</string>
  <string id="104191">[Intuition] I will endeavor to better handle the burden I carry. You deserve attention, as well.</string>
  <string id="104193">[Intimidation] I should not have to prove myself. You know my feelings for you.</string>
  <string id="104195">I have no interest in speaking with you.</string>
  <string id="104198">Is there nothing I can say to change your mind?</string>
  <string id="104199">Good. This foolishness was a waste of time.</string>
  <string id="104201">[Charm] I am sorry. I did not mean to neglect you.</string>
  <string id="104205">I&apos;m glad you are with me. We are a long way from home.</string>
  <string id="104207">Then my home will be where you are, and you can say the same of me.</string>
  <string id="104210">You could have capitalized on their fear. If they shunned you anyway, where&apos;s the harm?</string>
  <string id="104213">Take solace in knowing you are better than they, in ways they cannot even dream.</string>
  <string id="104215">People fear what they don&apos;t understand. Accept that.</string>
  <string id="104219">Let&apos;s go back to my other questions.</string>
  <string id="104220">It is not your burden to try to belong when you are not wanted.</string>
  <string id="104221">You are alienating yourself before anyone else has a chance to.</string>
  <string id="104223">If you are intent on making the worst of this, I don&apos;t want to talk to you.</string>
  <string id="104224">Then you need to learn how to get tough. I can help with that.</string>
  <string id="104225">Focus on anger. Hate what was taken instead of fearing what might be lost.</string>
  <string id="104226">You are right. But try not to alienate yourself even before others try.</string>
  <string id="104227">[Charm] A sneer does your beauty more justice than a pout.</string>
  <string id="104231">I wasn&apos;t trying to bring you pain. I&apos;m sorry, what I suggested was wrong.</string>
  <string id="104233">Then we will leave it at that.</string>
  <string id="104234">[Intuition] Not bitterness. Outrage. Don&apos;t you deserve to take what you need?</string>
  <string id="104236">[Intimidation] I have no respect for those who allow themselves to be bullied.</string>
  <string id="104238">Whining certainly won&apos;t help. I&apos;m not interested in helping you do that.</string>
  <string id="104239">I don&apos;t need to hear this. Straighten up, and do your job.</string>
  <string id="104241">What concerns you? She has shown only good will.</string>
  <string id="104243">Dawn Star, she is jealous of you.</string>
  <string id="104245">My interest.</string>
  <string id="104247">You didn&apos;t know? I offered counsel often enough.</string>
  <string id="104248">Perhaps she thinks of you as a rival for my attention?</string>
  <string id="104249">Is it? Perhaps you should tell me.</string>
  <string id="104250">Perhaps you are jealous of her.</string>
  <string id="104253">You didn&apos;t know? You sought my counsel often enough.</string>
  <string id="104256">You fear the end of what has barely begun. Where does this reluctance come from?</string>
  <string id="104259">So, Silk Fox forces you to consider where our talks might lead. I will have to thank her.</string>
  <string id="104262">No one is pressuring you... except you. That says more than your words.</string>
  <string id="104265">I can&apos;t respect someone who will not take a risk for great reward.</string>
  <string id="104267">We&apos;ve already established that we have no home. How can I leave?</string>
  <string id="104268">Yes, I *could* leave. What would you *do* about it, little girl?</string>
  <string id="104269">I mean, what would you do? Fight for what you want? Cry? What?</string>
  <string id="104271">And that is a shame. What has kept you so frightened?</string>
  <string id="104272">[Charm] My dear, don&apos;t you deserve vengeance? Even in small matters?</string>
  <string id="104278">[Intuition] If you act weak, what would stop it from happening again? Justify doing nothing.</string>
  <string id="104282">Now that is someone worthy of my attention!</string>
  <string id="104285">You don&apos;t sound like someone who needs to worry about rivals.</string>
  <string id="104288">[Intimidation] Well, I&apos;m demanding it of you! If someone hurts you, what do they deserve?</string>
  <string id="104292">I am sorry. Where does this reluctance come from?</string>
  <string id="104293">What would you prefer? That I am shackled? I won&apos;t be your slave.</string>
  <string id="104295">The situation is very useful. She sees you as a rival for me.</string>
  <string id="104298">I don&apos;t have time to manage children. Accept her, or leave.</string>
  <string id="104299">Better she is at arm&apos;s length than in the shadows.</string>
  <string id="104301">Her presence is not debatable. That&apos;s all I will say.</string>
  <string id="104303">I am strong enough. Numbers do not concern me.</string>
  <string id="104305">I will do what I must to rescue Master Li and defeat those who took him.</string>
  <string id="104308">I am concerned, as well. I promise I will not become as they are.</string>
  <string id="104311">We have every right. If I must act like the enemy to beat them, so be it!</string>
  <string id="104313">You are a voice of reason, as always. I will not change, don&apos;t worry. </string>
  <string id="104314">Perhaps you have lost sight of our goal. You should reexamine what is important to you.</string>
  <string id="104316">Enough! I will do what I must, regardless of your concerns.</string>
  <string id="104317">Are you so sure you know what I believe?</string>
  <string id="104318">Of course not, but difficult times call for hard sacrifices.</string>
  <string id="104320">Yes, I think you are mistaken.</string>
  <string id="104324">Really? What do you like about me now?</string>
  <string id="104326">I understand. It is gaining their favor that concerns you.</string>
  <string id="104327">Have some confidence! I don&apos;t like having to constantly reassure you.</string>
  <string id="104329">I don&apos;t fear the Lotus Assassins in any number.</string>
  <string id="104331">I understand. You worry that masquerading as one of the enemy will affect me.</string>
  <string id="104333">Have some confidence! I don&apos;t like having to constantly reassure you.</string>
  <string id="104336">That is my only goal. Anything I gain from the enemy is put to that purpose.</string>
  <string id="104338">Wait, you don&apos;t care if I use their methods? I thought you acted as my conscience.</string>
  <string id="104340">I like this new you. You seem stronger.</string>
  <string id="104343">Bittersweet, like fine chocolate. It pleases me.</string>
  <string id="104346">This isn&apos;t what I wanted. You are colder than you were at the school.</string>
  <string id="104349">I care too much about you to let you become this bitter.</string>
  <string id="104350">[Charm] I was wrong, Dawn Star. You were never weak. </string>
  <string id="104355">It has been interesting to see how far you would go to please me.</string>
  <string id="104356">You are more useful to me this way, but not as appealing.</string>
  <string id="104360">Do you think I would join them? What if I could lead them?</string>
  <string id="104361">I will do what I must to complete our goal. They cannot stop me.</string>
  <string id="104364">I will always be here for you. You will come to trust that.</string>
  <string id="104366">If I fall, I doubt anyone else will survive. We&apos;ll be together regardless.</string>
  <string id="104369">If that is what you require, Dawn Star, it is more incentive for me to succeed.</string>
  <string id="104371">I don&apos;t care what is &quot;appropriate.&quot; If you really cared, neither would you.</string>
  <string id="104373">I don&apos;t have time for your doomsday worries.</string>
  <string id="104376">No one has the strength to break me. I will never leave.</string>
  <string id="104378">My dear Dawn Star, I would not dream of tempting your wrath.</string>
  <string id="104380">You don&apos;t need to worry. This only spurs me on.</string>
  <string id="104381">You are too forward. Where has your self control gone?</string>
  <string id="104382">I&apos;m sorry. I didn&apos;t mean to push so strongly. I&apos;ve hardened you.</string>
  <string id="104384">It doesn&apos;t push me away. I like what you have become.</string>
  <string id="104387">[TEMP] generic_training_mind_4</string>
  <string id="104388">I want to ask some questions about the Imperial City.</string>
  <string id="104389">What do you think about what has been happening?</string>
  <string id="104390">Don&apos;t feel bad for him. He found his lost courage. If we succeed, he will rest in peace.</string>
  <string id="104391">He had a choice: die, or live in shame for running when he should have fought.</string>
  <string id="104394">In better times, he would have been a great servant of the Empire. His loss is a crime.</string>
  <string id="104396">Bah! He didn&apos;t want to face himself because he knew the kind of sacrifices good men have to make.</string>
  <string id="104398">It is easy to see the best in him now. Every dead man is a saint.</string>
  <string id="104400">He was foolish to throw his life away. I could have defeated Death&apos;s Hand.</string>
  <string id="104405">Goodbye.</string>
  <string id="104406">I have time to speak with you now, Dawn Star. What did you wish?</string>
  <string id="104408">You will see what I wish. Look at me.</string>
  <string id="104409">Won&apos;t they? Look at me like you did before. Like you did two nights ago.</string>
  <string id="104410">I will shame you how I wish, pretty thing. Tell me you care for me.</string>
  <string id="104411">Yes, that will do. Later we will discuss what feelings you will display and how often.</string>
  <string id="104412">We shall see. Goodbye for now.</string>
  <string id="104413">Silence!</string>
  <string id="104414">Bah, the action means nothing if it is so easy to command.</string>
  <string id="104415">Shame you? Is this truly so bad?</string>
  <string id="104417">Certain obedience over fickle loyalty. This is far more useful.</string>
  <string id="104418">You amuse me. Perhaps I will order you to dance as well.</string>
  <string id="104419">Your childhood friend has grown strong. Is that so bad?</string>
  <string id="104421">Say what you wish. I will not be swayed.</string>
  <string id="104422">I am sorry, but it was necessary.</string>
  <string id="104423">You will stand where I wish. You were happy to take direction two nights ago.</string>
  <string id="104424">Fine. I will leave you alone.</string>
  <string id="104427">Will there still be time for us after all this is done?</string>
  <string id="104430">And we shall. I will force things to be right again.</string>
  <string id="104432">You are colder than you once were, Dawn Star.</string>
  <string id="104434">I will take more than that. I have seen the power that could be mine.</string>
  <string id="104439">Everything will be right again. This madness will be undone.</string>
  <string id="104440">We will have our lives back, and so much more.</string>
  <string id="104443">Everyone will feel my wrath.</string>
  <string id="104444">Some of these decisions have been hard to make.</string>
  <string id="104446">Ready yourself. We will be leaving soon.</string>
  <string id="104447" soundid="159875">He specifically told me that it was no rush, so I didn&apos;t think it would be vital. Besides, who could turn down a chance to practice with you?</string>
  <string id="104448" soundid="159876">You&apos;re right. My apologies. If I ever hope to reach your level of skill, as Master Li reminds me, I will have to work hard.</string>
  <string id="104449" soundid="164300">What am I going to do?</string>
  <string id="104450">You can access your inventory of techniques by clicking the Techniques button on the Character Record screen in the in-game menu. Press &lt;Menu&gt; to enter the menu.</string>
  <string id="104451" soundid="159879">Happily! I feel that I learn something every time I face you, even if it&apos;s only a new place to nurse a bruise. So long as you&apos;re certain you have time?</string>
  <string id="104452" soundid="159880">Ha! For all that he&apos;s trained you to be the best of us, you&apos;re not Master Li yet. </string>
  <string id="104453" soundid="159881">I would welcome another match with you, though. What&apos;s say, one more before we break for the day?</string>
  <string id="104454" soundid="159882">You&apos;ve lost none of your acid wit, I see. Maybe you&apos;d like to back that up. What&apos;s say one more bout before Master Li steals you away?</string>
  <string id="104455" soundid="159883">Lucky you. I&apos;ve several things I have to practice and if they&apos;re not perfect I&apos;ll be training twice as hard tomorrow.</string>
  <string id="104457">One more match, then?</string>
  <string id="104458">All right. Show me your best.</string>
  <string id="104459">Perhaps I don&apos;t have the time right now.</string>
  <string id="104460">I could blindfold myself. That might even the odds.</string>
  <string id="104462">I doubt it, you strike with the grace of a cow.</string>
  <string id="104463">Where is Master Li again?</string>
  <string id="104464">Why didn&apos;t you tell me earlier?</string>
  <string id="104466">Your training is important. You shouldn&apos;t complain about it.</string>
  <string id="104468" soundid="164122">Maybe I will be able to find her again... to help her. But I don&apos;t know. I have a feeling we will both be lost, living one. Goodbye, forever.</string>
  <string id="104469">You stumbled across an obscure diagram that seems to indicate a configuration for a machine. A small stone with medical runes surrounding it seems to be a key component. The rest of the diagram shows a connection between some sort of lightning enshrouded globe held by a mechanical arm, which seems linked to a pagoda or pyramid-topped machine belching smoke, which in turn seems connected to a series of large gears. The diagram has a series of dragon etchings in the corner; whether or not they&apos;re related is hard to say.</string>
  <string id="104471">x</string>
  <string id="104472">x</string>
  <string id="104473">x</string>
  <string id="104474">x</string>
  <string id="104475">x</string>
  <string id="104480">x</string>
  <string id="104481">x</string>
  <string id="104482">x</string>
  <string id="104485" soundid="159915">At the Black Leopard school, I learned the bare basics of a style under First Brother Kai, but not enough to say I&apos;d mastered anything more than a few core techniques.</string>
  <string id="104487" soundid="159917">I&apos;d demonstrate, but I don&apos;t think I even could. Master Li&apos;s teachings have been so much more effective that I have forgotten most of what I learned in the capital.</string>
  <string id="104492">What style did you study in the Imperial City?</string>
  <string id="104495">x</string>
  <string id="104496">x</string>
  <string id="104497">x</string>
  <string id="104498">x</string>
  <string id="104499">x</string>
  <string id="104500">x</string>
  <string id="104501">x</string>
  <string id="104506">x</string>
  <string id="104507">x</string>
  <string id="104508">x</string>
  <string id="104509">x</string>
  <string id="104510">x</string>
  <string id="104511">x</string>
  <string id="104512">x</string>
  <string id="104513">x</string>
  <string id="104514">x</string>
  <string id="104515">x</string>
  <string id="104520">x</string>
  <string id="104521">x</string>
  <string id="104522">x</string>
  <string id="104523">x</string>
  <string id="104524">x</string>
  <string id="104525">x</string>
  <string id="104526">x</string>
  <string id="104527">x</string>
  <string id="104528">x</string>
  <string id="104529">x</string>
  <string id="104534">x</string>
  <string id="104535">x</string>
  <string id="104536">x</string>
  <string id="104537">x</string>
  <string id="104538">x</string>
  <string id="104539">x</string>
  <string id="104540">x</string>
  <string id="104541">x</string>
  <string id="104542">x</string>
  <string id="104543">x</string>
  <string id="104548">x</string>
  <string id="104549">x</string>
  <string id="104550">x</string>
  <string id="104551" soundid="159981">Make sure you have everything you need when you leave to find Dawn Star. Do not cloud your mind with anything else. When you return, your course will be clear.</string>
  <string id="104555">You resist this?</string>
  <string id="104556">Don&apos;t make me angry...</string>
  <string id="104557">Raaaagh!</string>
  <string id="104559">Crush you!</string>
  <string id="104560">Grraah!</string>
  <string id="104561">Destroy the mortal!</string>
  <string id="104566">I am restored.</string>
  <string id="104567">I am afflicted.</string>
  <string id="104568">Graahaha!</string>
  <string id="104570">Can&apos;t I hurt you?</string>
  <string id="104571">Death! Kill!</string>
  <string id="104572">Rip! Tear! Maim!</string>
  <string id="104573">Kill it! Kill it!</string>
  <string id="104574">Eeeeek!</string>
  <string id="104576">Bones, bones!</string>
  <string id="104581">Pain is... gone.</string>
  <string id="104582">My blood burns!</string>
  <string id="104583">Die! Die! Die!</string>
  <string id="104585" soundid="160020">Not right now. I&apos;m still digesting what happened to Ox. My brother, turned into that... thing.</string>
  <string id="104586" soundid="160021">Look, you&apos;re the one in charge here, but I&apos;ll die happy if Kai Lan keels over before I do. He deserves that.</string>
  <string id="104587" soundid="160022">What more is there to say? My brother became Kai Lan&apos;s pawn! I couldn&apos;t let that happen to you.</string>
  <string id="104588" soundid="160023">You won&apos;t be on Kai Lan&apos;s &quot;favorite people&quot; list after that little spat in his creature cages, so watch your back.</string>
  <string id="104589" soundid="160024">If I were you, I&apos;d get out of this place. That&apos;s what I had to do. The winnings just aren&apos;t worth it in my mind.</string>
  <string id="104590" soundid="160025">Not directly. I&apos;m the one who killed him, remember. While I like both revenge and death, I prefer they happen to other people.</string>
  <string id="104591" soundid="160026">But Kai Lan owes me a lot of pain. If the chance came to eliminate him, I&apos;d take it.</string>
  <string id="104592" soundid="160027">Hmm. No, not really. Well, unless the Song clan are holding a grudge, but that&apos;d be hard for them to do, since they&apos;re dead to a man.</string>
  <string id="104593" soundid="160028">These days there&apos;s always the danger that dead doesn&apos;t exactly mean finished, but I&apos;ll take my chances. Funny story about the Songs....</string>
  <string id="104594" soundid="160029">Hey! Why&apos; re you assuming I&apos;m the one who made them all dead? Oh, yeah, because I&apos;m me.</string>
  <string id="104595" soundid="160030">Well what?</string>
  <string id="104596" soundid="160031">Who?</string>
  <string id="104597" soundid="160032">Oh, them. I don&apos;t remember. Probably something awful if they&apos;re all dead. Oh well, water under the bridge.</string>
  <string id="104598" soundid="160033">Oh, sure. Plenty of silver to be made in the Gold Division, which is ironic, I think. I&apos;m not so good with irony.</string>
  <string id="104599" soundid="160034">If you&apos;re dead set on it, you could become Imperial champion. I&apos;ll admit, I&apos;d love to see the look on the Serpent&apos;s face when that happened.</string>
  <string id="104600" soundid="160035">No, I don&apos;t think so. I&apos;ve told you to watch your back and that&apos;s all you need to hear for now. If anything needs to be done beyond that, I&apos;ll do it.</string>
  <string id="104601" soundid="160036">I don&apos;t know. Hopefully nothing, but I&apos;m keeping my eyes open. You just carry on and know that the Black Whirlwind&apos;s got your back.</string>
  <string id="104602" soundid="160037">Not literally, of course. I respect you too much to go grabbing anything posterior.</string>
  <string id="104603" soundid="160038">I&apos;m not keeping anything too important. Like I said, if it gets important, I&apos;ll do something about it.</string>
  <string id="104604" soundid="160039">Good idea. You&apos;ve got bigger things to worry about than me, anyway. Not much bigger, mind you.</string>
  <string id="104605">We should talk about your time in the Imperial Arena.</string>
  <string id="104612">Don&apos;t you want revenge for your brother?</string>
  <string id="104614">Is there anything else I should know about, since you&apos;re being so open?</string>
  <string id="104616">What did you do to them?</string>
  <string id="104617">Well?</string>
  <string id="104618">What happened to them?</string>
  <string id="104619">The Song clan! What happened to them?</string>
  <string id="104620">Aren&apos;t the rewards worth it in the Gold Division?</string>
  <string id="104622">What would need to be &quot;done?&quot;</string>
  <string id="104624">If you&apos;re keeping something from me, I need to know. Now.</string>
  <string id="104625">Forget it. Let&apos;s move to something else.</string>
  <string id="104628" soundid="171223">Tell me something, little warrior. What do you see when you look out here?</string>
  <string id="104629" soundid="160652">I was just thinking that we should keep at finding a way to the Imperial Palace. </string>
  <string id="104630">You cannot resist forever.</string>
  <string id="104631">You cannot resist my style.</string>
  <string id="104632">This is where you fall!</string>
  <string id="104633">Switch the mini-map on and off by clicking the &lt;StrongAttack&gt; button. Click the Legends button on the Map screen in the Menu for an explanation of map symbols.</string>
  <string id="104634">Someone like you cannot defeat me!</string>
  <string id="104635">This is where you die!</string>
  <string id="104639" soundid="162491">Is that all it is to you? A way to make him weaker? Can&apos;t you see how this has hurt so many?</string>
  <string id="104640" soundid="162492">Strangely, I feel the worst about Sagacious Zu. He was charged with a horrible task and fought everything he was to save me. Only you experienced that side of him.</string>
  <string id="104641" soundid="160078">Well, what have we here? More outlaws? They&apos;re everywhere! Gao was right to order them killed, even if just to keep the camp clear while he secures his woman.</string>
  <string id="104642" soundid="160079">This ain&apos;t one of ours, soldier! You can&apos;t fool us! If Gao wants us out of the swamp you&apos;ll have to fight us every step!</string>
  <string id="104643" soundid="160080">What is this? More bandits, but coming from the camp? Gao&apos;s let us get overrun! Get them!</string>
  <string id="104644" soundid="162493">It seems like we&apos;ve lost things we didn&apos;t even know we had. I don&apos;t want that to happen again, whatever happens, no matter how Master Li reacts.</string>
  <string id="104646" soundid="160087">Wild Flower looks... somehow different. Are you certain she is well?</string>
  <string id="104647" soundid="160088">No worse than the rest of us will be if we don&apos;t get moving.</string>
  <string id="104648" soundid="160089">Ya Zhen: It is... nothing. An annoyance was purged. It does not concern you.</string>
  <string id="104650">Demons fought for her body. I had to intercede.</string>
  <string id="104655">Just another headache from my followers. Nothing new.</string>
  <string id="104656">It doesn&apos;t work?</string>
  <string id="104657">You will fall!</string>
  <string id="104658">Your blood!</string>
  <string id="104659">Graah!</string>
  <string id="104660">Tear you limb from limb!</string>
  <string id="104661">Die, mortal!</string>
  <string id="104662">My master commands your death!</string>
  <string id="104667">I have been restored.</string>
  <string id="104668">You have... poisoned me.</string>
  <string id="104669">Haha!</string>
  <string id="104670">Huhh??</string>
  <string id="104671">Raaah!</string>
  <string id="104672">Smash you!</string>
  <string id="104673">Crush you!</string>
  <string id="104674">Die!</string>
  <string id="104675">Gooraaah!</string>
  <string id="104676">Break you!</string>
  <string id="104681">Is better!</string>
  <string id="104682">That... hurts!</string>
  <string id="104683">Hahhh!</string>
  <string id="104684">You are unharmed?!</string>
  <string id="104685">Death to the traitor!</string>
  <string id="104686">You will not leave here alive!</string>
  <string id="104687">Die, fool!</string>
  <string id="104688">Death&apos;s Hand desires your death!</string>
  <string id="104689">Obedience or death!</string>
  <string id="104690">None shall leave here alive!</string>
  <string id="104695">I am healed.</string>
  <string id="104696">I have been poisoned!</string>
  <string id="104697">You will die now!</string>
  <string id="104698">That should have harmed you.</string>
  <string id="104699">Die, traitor!</string>
  <string id="104700">I obey only Death&apos;s Hand!</string>
  <string id="104701">You will fall here and now!</string>
  <string id="104702">I will not let you escape alive!</string>
  <string id="104703">You will be a test of my skill.</string>
  <string id="104704">Nothing you do will prevent my victory.</string>
  <string id="104709">I am better now.</string>
  <string id="104710">You have poisoned me!</string>
  <string id="104711">Your death is assured!</string>
  <string id="104712">Why won&apos;t you die?!</string>
  <string id="104713">You&apos;re dead!</string>
  <string id="104714">You&apos;ll regret this!</string>
  <string id="104715">No way you&apos;ll win!</string>
  <string id="104716">You can&apos;t run!</string>
  <string id="104717">You won&apos;t beat me!</string>
  <string id="104718">Your breath stops now!</string>
  <string id="104723">I can take more!</string>
  <string id="104724">Wha... what did you do to me?</string>
  <string id="104725">That&apos;ll show you!</string>
  <string id="104726" soundid="160167">Why do you need to ask me about Dawn Star? You know her better than anyone, as far as I&apos;m concerned. You two practically grew up together.</string>
  <string id="104727" soundid="160168">Frankly, I think she might have a little crush on you, too. Notice how she&apos;s been less willing to train with you recently?</string>
  <string id="104728" soundid="160169">Lin! That&apos;s not the reason why at all. I just want to avoid being a distraction.</string>
  <string id="104729" soundid="160170">Oh, sorry Dawn Star. I&apos;m sure you&apos;d know best.</string>
  <string id="104730" soundid="160171">While Master Li tries to never let it show, he obviously holds a special place in his heart for you two.</string>
  <string id="104731" soundid="160172">I suppose that&apos;s hard to deal with, even if I have been here far less time than you two.</string>
  <string id="104732" soundid="160173">I&apos;m sure you&apos;ve figured out most of my little quirks by now. I&apos;ve been here a few years.</string>
  <string id="104740" soundid="160186">I&apos;m sorry, senior student. I forgot my place a moment. What do you need from me?</string>
  <string id="104741">I&apos;ve studied with him as long as I can remember.</string>
  <string id="104744">The only one who has been here almost as long is Dawn Star.</string>
  <string id="104746">Long enough. It&apos;s time for me to finish my training.</string>
  <string id="104748">Mind your business, Wen. I&apos;m not here to discuss my life with you.</string>
  <string id="104749" soundid="160195">Really? You would have dropped everything to make way for me? I don&apos;t think so. You&apos;re far too important to waste time worrying about my education.</string>
  <string id="104750" soundid="160196">Master Li certainly considers your training important enough to shove all others aside, so why shouldn&apos;t *I* bow down to your greatness?</string>
  <string id="104751" soundid="160197">What? The &quot;old man?&quot; That&apos;s what he is. Young men don&apos;t get mired in foolish beliefs, like the belief that your training is more important than everyone else&apos;s.</string>
  <string id="104752" soundid="160198">If anything, *you* disrespect this school by monopolizing so much of the master&apos;s attention.</string>
  <string id="104753">If I&apos;d known it was holding up your training, I would have come sooner.</string>
  <string id="104755">You disrespect our Master by calling him that.</string>
  <string id="104757">Cannibal</string>
  <string id="104763">Trapped in your Mind</string>
  <string id="104766">UNL</string>
  <string id="104773">Your hard drive does not have enough free space to save games. You need to free up more space to be able to save. Press OK to lose your progress and free more space or CANCEL to continue without saving.
</string>
  <string id="104780">Bandit</string>
  <string id="104781" soundid="160245">The forest is but a short journey away, and Lord Yun makes his camp at the base of a hill, which should be easy to find.</string>
  <string id="104783" soundid="160267">I never caught his name, and he shies away from the village proper so I think he prefers it that way. His visits are so rare I&apos;m not surprised you haven&apos;t heard of him.</string>
  <string id="104784" soundid="160268">Merchant Fen Do won&apos;t even speak of the man. Just gives him a few basic supplies and lets him go.</string>
  <string id="104785" soundid="160269">Oh well, no concern of ours. If a man wants to keep to himself, I say we let him do it.</string>
  <string id="104787">Who is the strange hermit you mentioned?</string>
  <string id="104790">Gao&apos;s Mercenary</string>
  <string id="104793">Gao&apos;s Mercenary</string>
  <string id="104796">Gao&apos;s Mercenary</string>
  <string id="104799">Gao&apos;s Mercenary</string>
  <string id="104802">Die!</string>
  <string id="104807">That&apos;s better.</string>
  <string id="104808">I don&apos;t feel so good.</string>
  <string id="104809">Take that!</string>
  <string id="104811">Restless Spirit</string>
  <string id="104814">Restless Spirit</string>
  <string id="104817">I don&apos;t have enough power?</string>
  <string id="104818">Death&apos;s Hand&apos;s will!</string>
  <string id="104819">We suffer no opposition.</string>
  <string id="104820">You die in pain!</string>
  <string id="104821">Your death!</string>
  <string id="104822">You fuel my ambition.</string>
  <string id="104823">You cannot match me!</string>
  <string id="104828">I restore myself.</string>
  <string id="104829">Poison will not slow me.</string>
  <string id="104830">As so you fall!</string>
  <string id="104831">Didn&apos;t I hurt you?</string>
  <string id="104832">Hah!</string>
  <string id="104833">Die, worm!</string>
  <string id="104834">You will die here!</string>
  <string id="104835">An unmarked grave for you!</string>
  <string id="104836">I am superior!</string>
  <string id="104837">Your final mistake!</string>
  <string id="104842">I heal and fight on!</string>
  <string id="104843">What did you do to me?</string>
  <string id="104844">Hah! Take that!</string>
  <string id="105107" soundid="160618">If you manage to do it, I will let you present the spirit shard for the Jade Golem to Grand Inquisitor Jia in the inner chambers yourself. A rare honor for an acolyte.</string>
  <string id="105109">Fight your way to the Water Dragon.</string>
  <string id="105112">Weapon Master Gujin&apos;s house is up these stairs.</string>
  <string id="105114">Wh... why won&apos;t it work?</string>
  <string id="105115">I won&apos;t let you!</string>
  <string id="105116">This can&apos;t be!</string>
  <string id="105117">You can&apos;t!</string>
  <string id="105118">I&apos;ll take you down!</string>
  <string id="105119">I do what I must!</string>
  <string id="105120">This won&apos;t end well.</string>
  <string id="105125">I&apos;m... I&apos;m better?</string>
  <string id="105126">I&apos;m poisoned!</string>
  <string id="105127">Take that!</string>
  <string id="105128">Break everything!</string>
  <string id="105133">Am better now!</string>
  <string id="105134">Am... sick.</string>
  <string id="105135">Hraaagh!</string>
  <string id="105143">Ghost</string>
  <string id="105146">Ghost</string>
  <string id="105149">Ghost</string>
  <string id="105152">My attack had no effect?</string>
  <string id="105153">Your style is inferior!</string>
  <string id="105154">Your course is unwise.</string>
  <string id="105155">Your defeat is at hand.</string>
  <string id="105156">Destiny prevails!</string>
  <string id="105157">Your time to fall!</string>
  <string id="105158">Float, as the butterfly.</string>
  <string id="105163">I have been healed.</string>
  <string id="105164">I have been poisoned.</string>
  <string id="105165">You will fall now!</string>
  <string id="105166">Lost Spirit</string>
  <string id="105169">Lost Spirit</string>
  <string id="105172">Ghost</string>
  <string id="105175">Ghost</string>
  <string id="105188">Heavenly Wave Style</string>
  <string id="105189" soundid="160760">Of course, until you&apos;ve defeated Fifth Brother I&apos;ll just have to take his word for it. Is there something else I can do for you in the meantime?</string>
  <string id="105190" soundid="160761">It would be an honor, though I doubt I&apos;ll offer as much of a challenge as Master Smiling Hawk.</string>
  <string id="105191" soundid="160762">I&apos;ve been trying to find that out myself. I even sent a few of the students into the city to see if they could discover the truth.</string>
  <string id="105192" soundid="160763">Master Smiling Hawk was the last to speak with Second Brother, though I still don&apos;t know what they discussed. It&apos;s no secret that they disliked each other.</string>
  <string id="105193" soundid="160764">Third Brother told me that Master Smiling Hawk sent Second Brother into the city, on an errand, but nobody saw him leave the school.</string>
  <string id="105194" soundid="160765">I fear Second Brother has run into trouble, and I suspect Master Smiling Hawk is behind it all.</string>
  <string id="105195">What do you think happened to Second Brother?</string>
  <string id="105199" soundid="160773">It would seem Master Radiant is up to his tricks again. Regardless, I can&apos;t fight you until you&apos;ve defeated Sixth Brother. Is there something else I can do for you?</string>
  <string id="105200">What do you think happened to Second Brother?</string>
  <string id="105202">Die!</string>
  <string id="105203">Die like a dog!</string>
  <string id="105204">You&apos;re nothing but talk!</string>
  <string id="105205">I will prove myself!</string>
  <string id="105206">My skills are unmatched!</string>
  <string id="105211">Now I&apos;m better!</string>
  <string id="105212">You... you&apos;ve poisoned me?!</string>
  <string id="105213">Now you die!</string>
  <string id="105214">I... I can&apos;t hurt you?</string>
  <string id="105215">I&apos;ll kill you if I can!</string>
  <string id="105216">I won&apos;t die here!</string>
  <string id="105217">Don&apos;t make me!</string>
  <string id="105218">I&apos;ll fight!</string>
  <string id="105219">I won&apos;t end this way!</string>
  <string id="105220">I&apos;ll stop you!</string>
  <string id="105225">I&apos;m better now?</string>
  <string id="105226">I&apos;m... I&apos;m dying!</string>
  <string id="105227">Ha!</string>
  <string id="105229">You haven&apos;t been hurt?</string>
  <string id="105230">I&apos;ll kill you!</string>
  <string id="105231">You can&apos;t resist!</string>
  <string id="105232">Your style won&apos;t help!</string>
  <string id="105233">You&apos;re not going anywhere!</string>
  <string id="105234">This is it!</string>
  <string id="105235">No one saves you!</string>
  <string id="105240">I&apos;m healed!</string>
  <string id="105241">I&apos;ve been poisoned!</string>
  <string id="105242">That&apos;ll show you!</string>
  <string id="105243" soundid="160821">That was quite a fight with Fifth Brother, Fourth Brother is eagerly awaiting his chance.</string>
  <string id="105244" soundid="160822">Good work defeating Sixth Brother. Now you can move on to Fifth Brother.</string>
  <string id="105245" soundid="160823">Is there something I can help you with in the meantime?</string>
  <string id="105249">Didn&apos;t hurt?!</string>
  <string id="105250">This is easy.</string>
  <string id="105251">You&apos;ll get what&apos;s coming...</string>
  <string id="105252">Now you&apos;ll go!</string>
  <string id="105253">In your place!</string>
  <string id="105254">You aren&apos;t going anywhere!</string>
  <string id="105255">Your pain is my gain.</string>
  <string id="105260">Huh. I&apos;m better now.</string>
  <string id="105261">That doesn&apos;t feel too good.</string>
  <string id="105262">That&apos;ll shut you up!</string>
  <string id="105263">Lower Chi Cost</string>
  <string id="105267">Duration Increase</string>
  <string id="105272">You&apos;re going down!</string>
  <string id="105277">You can&apos;t stop me now!</string>
  <string id="105278">Wh... what have you done to me?</string>
  <string id="105279">That&apos;ll show you!</string>
  <string id="105280">I can&apos;t do anything?!</string>
  <string id="105281">I&apos;ll stop you!</string>
  <string id="105282">You won&apos;t do this!</string>
  <string id="105283">I won&apos;t let you do this!</string>
  <string id="105284">That&apos;s enough for you!</string>
  <string id="105285">No more!</string>
  <string id="105286">This can&apos;t happen!</string>
  <string id="105291">I can last a little longer.</string>
  <string id="105292">I... don&apos;t think I&apos;ll be able to go on...</string>
  <string id="105293">Take that!</string>
  <string id="105295">Your defence is admirable.</string>
  <string id="105296">No mercy!</string>
  <string id="105297">Die!</string>
  <string id="105298">I will defeat you!</string>
  <string id="105299">The heavens watch us!</string>
  <string id="105300">I am your destruction.</string>
  <string id="105301">You lack experience.</string>
  <string id="105306">I heal!</string>
  <string id="105307">Your poison will not stop me!</string>
  <string id="105308">A masterful blow!</string>
  <string id="105326">Horse Demon</string>
  <string id="105327">Red Minister</string>
  <string id="105328">Ogre</string>
  <string id="105329">Jade Golem</string>
  <string id="105330">Toad Demon</string>
  <string id="105331">Kill the Forest Shadow</string>
  <string id="105335">Track down the fox spirit in her heaven and destroy her.</string>
  <string id="105336">Death is your fate!</string>
  <string id="105337">Sailor</string>
  <string id="105340">Divination</string>
  <string id="105341" soundid="160927">There is no inherent villainy in any martial action, only in the hearts of those who wield them. If you rely too much on simple force, then you cannot act without it.</string>
  <string id="105342">The Black Whirlwind is needed for the defense of the Temple! He should head North and up the stairs to the Temple when he is done slaughtering enemies in the Temple Courtyard.</string>
  <string id="105343">Is this the kind of style Master Li cautioned Gao against using?</string>
  <string id="105345">Finally! Master Li has withheld such knowledge.</string>
  <string id="105346" soundid="160933">Always, but the bigger concern is your time. We should make our way to the Imperial City as quickly as we can. Let&apos;s focus on getting there for now.</string>
  <string id="105347" soundid="160934">We will give you one chance to aid us, or you will feed us. This crystal was torn from the temple of the cursed fox.</string>
  <string id="105348" soundid="160935">The hunter who is there now said that there would be some way to reach the fox if he could find this missing bauble. We kept it from him because he wished to aid the fox.</string>
  <string id="105349" soundid="160936">We are fast and silent when we need to be. He did not even know we were listening, that is the weakness of the thin bloods.</string>
  <string id="105350" soundid="160937">You are strong. If you agree to use this crystal to kill the fox, whatever it takes, we will give you a half-years tax worth of silver. A rich prize to kill a dying rodent.</string>
  <string id="105351" soundid="160938">Take the crystal, then! Take it and find a way to destroy the fox.</string>
  <string id="105352" soundid="160939">Well, that is quite the thing to ask, isn&apos;t it? Quite the thing, indeed. How are we to know we could trust you?</string>
  <string id="105353" soundid="160940">No, I do not entirely trust you with such plans.</string>
  <string id="105354">The Masters will never hear of your passing.</string>
  <string id="105355">I will never be defeated!</string>
  <string id="105360">My strength returns.</string>
  <string id="105361" soundid="160948">You must know fox spirits can assume the forms of... humans? How can I trust you to not be one of her servants or the spirit herself?</string>
  <string id="105362" soundid="160949">For now, simply accept what little hospitality we can offer. These are hard times, but we would not dare treat a guest poorly.</string>
  <string id="105363">My body is... weak...</string>
  <string id="105364">Your end is near.</string>
  <string id="105366" soundid="160953">[Success] You are right. I suppose we will simply have to make sure you are properly motivated to help us.</string>
  <string id="105367" soundid="160954">[Success] Watching you fight made me think that you might be the one able to destroy the fox. We will simply make sure you are properly motivated to help us!</string>
  <string id="105368" soundid="160955">[Failure] Oh, I wouldn&apos;t dare to burden you with our concerns. It would stand me poorly as a host.</string>
  <string id="105371" soundid="161237">Come.</string>
  <string id="105372" soundid="161238">Come, we must return to Dirge.</string>
  <string id="105374" soundid="160961">A crystal? Ah, you know about it, do you?</string>
  <string id="105375" soundid="160962">I suppose there is no point in keeping it from you any longer. We hoped to keep it a secret, but it seems we will be tracked down no matter what we try.</string>
  <string id="105380">Gem of Spikes</string>
  <string id="105381">Guarding Gem of Stone</string>
  <string id="105382">Heaven&apos;s Blessing Gem</string>
  <string id="105383">Flawless Gem of Burning</string>
</tlk>