<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<tlk language="0">
  <string id="77738" soundid="112887">Suffice to say, those items could be from any number of sellers. I don&apos;t recall who sold them to me, but that certainly doesn&apos;t make me guilty of slave trading.</string>
  <string id="77739" soundid="112888">I can honestly say I had never met or heard of the man until he was arrested. He&apos;s obviously not wealthy enough to be one of my clients.</string>
  <string id="77740" soundid="112889">Apparently, he spends a good deal of time with the poorer folk in the city. No doubt that&apos;s why he is under suspicion.</string>
  <string id="77741" soundid="112890">Doesn&apos;t strike you as a bit odd? A scholar, with all the benefits that position entails, *choosing* to spend time with the poor people. It does seem a little... suspicious.</string>
  <string id="77742" soundid="112891">No more than you&apos;ve heard for yourself, I&apos;m sure. They are a myth, a rumor really. Nobody has ever seen them and nobody has any proof they exist.</string>
  <string id="77743" soundid="112892">And yet, still there is a belief that they exist... madmen terrorizing the poor and abducting the helpless. It all seems very... superstitious.</string>
  <string id="77744" soundid="112893">Abducting a person isn&apos;t like picking someone&apos;s pocket, you know. There would be evidence, signs of a struggle. But people will believe what they want to.</string>
  <string id="77745" soundid="112894">Ah, you&apos;ve returned and, I&apos;m sorry to say, I&apos;m still here. Is there something I can do for you?</string>
  <string id="77746">Why are you so sure I&apos;ll be at risk?</string>
  <string id="77749">I should be going. Goodbye.</string>
  <string id="77750">Tell me about yourself, Chandler Ling.</string>
  <string id="77753">Why were you arrested? What were you doing?</string>
  <string id="77756">How did you acquire those items belonging to Jitong&apos;s men?</string>
  <string id="77759">What do you know about Scholar Songtao?</string>
  <string id="77762">What can you tell me about the slave traders?</string>
  <string id="77765">No, thanks. I should be going. Goodbye.</string>
  <string id="77766" soundid="112915">Good day, miss. Are... you the new investigator I sent for?</string>
  <string id="77767" soundid="112916">Good day, sir. Are... you the new investigator I sent for?</string>
  <string id="77768" soundid="156887"></string>
  <string id="77770" soundid="162119">No, I cannot. Master Smiling Hawk told us you are no longer a member of the school, and that we are forbidden from sparring with you.</string>
  <string id="77771" soundid="112920">No, I can tell from your attire that you&apos;re not from the ministry. (sigh) This is terrible.</string>
  <string id="77772" soundid="112921">Everyone I send for disappears. There are powers at work here that are beyond my means to control.</string>
  <string id="77773" soundid="112922">Please, please just hear my cause. I promise I will not detain you long.</string>
  <string id="77774" soundid="112923">I am Prefect Jitong. It&apos;s my duty to ensure that convicted criminals in the city are sentenced appropriately. But there are... complications with my current trial.</string>
  <string id="77775" soundid="112924">I have in my custody a suspected slave trader, Chandler Ling, but one of the high ranking ministers is trying to get him released, and he wants me to convict another man.</string>
  <string id="77776" soundid="112925">The man they want to accuse, Scholar Songtao, is a friend of mine... and I&apos;m certain of his innocence. I need you to find proof so I can present it to the Minister of Justice.</string>
  <string id="77777" soundid="112926">Really? You will help me? Thank you... thank you so very much. I need to find proof that Ling is the guilty one, and by so doing, exonerate Songtao.</string>
  <string id="77778" soundid="112927">So... you&apos;ll help me? That&apos;s... wonderful. All I need really, is proof. Proof that Ling is indeed involved with the slave traders.</string>
  <string id="77779" soundid="112928">If I can&apos;t prove Ling&apos;s guilt, I&apos;ll be forced to sentence Songtao... to death. But every time I ask someone to discover the truth, they disappear, or turn up dead.</string>
  <string id="77780" soundid="112929">Our best lead is Zi Bao, the last person known to have spoken with Ling before his arrest. But Bao knows me and my men; he won&apos;t talk to us.</string>
  <string id="77785" soundid="112934">I&apos;ve know Scholar Songtao for several years. His uncle and my father were good friends. I only wish I knew why the governor wants him accused of this crime.</string>
  <string id="77787">Winnings Purse</string>
  <string id="77788" soundid="112937">If you want to know more about Songtao, you should speak with him yourself.</string>
  <string id="77789" soundid="112938">Chandler Ling is a well-respected business man and merchant here in the city. Until recently, I had no reason to suspect him of any wrongdoing.</string>
  <string id="77790" soundid="112939">When I investigated Ling&apos;s shop, I found a valuable knife that I had purposely entrusted to one of my men. A man who has since disappeared.</string>
  <string id="77791" soundid="112940">Chandler Ling had a knife belonging to a man whose body couldn&apos;t be found. That was all the evidence I required.</string>
  <string id="77792" soundid="151788">Chai Ka: The road will be divided. There is a powerful presence stirring, and her will must be obeyed.</string>
  <string id="77793" soundid="151789">Chai Ka: There will be no interference, but there will be guidance. There is... something you must see.</string>
  <string id="77794" soundid="151790">Perhaps she means the tombs near the heart of the palace?</string>
  <string id="77795" soundid="112944">I have no idea. The two men were seen together before we arrested Ling. But I have no other information about Zi Bao.</string>
  <string id="77796" soundid="112945">He spends most of his time in the Heart of the Empire Tavern, and he doesn&apos;t seem to have dealings with anyone else besides Chandler Ling.</string>
  <string id="77797" soundid="112946">I know if I went to speak with him I would get nowhere, but you could speak to him without raising suspicion.</string>
  <string id="77798" soundid="151791"></string>
  <string id="77799" soundid="112948">I wish there was something concrete I could tell you. They&apos;re like a whisper on the wind, or a shifting shadow. You think you see something, and then there&apos;s nothing.</string>
  <string id="77800">This small satchel is marked to make it identifiable as one of Gambler Daoshen&apos;s winnings purses. It contains the silver he plans to offer to the Guild in return for permission to increase the limits on his wagers.</string>
  <string id="77802" soundid="112951">Whoever is behind the slavers must have a great deal of power. To remain that... invisible is a hard thing to do.</string>
  <string id="77803" soundid="112952">Good... look for him in the Heart of the Empire Tavern, it&apos;s upstairs at the Imperial Arena. Don&apos;t scare him away... if we lose him, we lose our last connection to Ling.</string>
  <string id="77804" soundid="112953">I see... well, there really isn&apos;t anyone else. If you change your mind, please come and see me.</string>
  <string id="77805" soundid="112954">Oh, it&apos;s you again. Have you reconsidered helping me prove Songtao&apos;s innocence?</string>
  <string id="77806" soundid="112955">Hello again. I don&apos;t mean to sound impatient, but have you spoken with Zi Bao yet?</string>
  <string id="77807" soundid="112956">If you think it will help you find out what&apos;s going on, I&apos;ll gladly answer your questions. What do you want to know?</string>
  <string id="77808" soundid="112957">All right. Remember, Zi Bao is in the Heart of the Empire Tavern in the Imperial Arena. I suggest you try and speak with him if you can. Good luck.</string>
  <string id="77810" soundid="112959">There you are. The governor sent Ho Chong, one of his lapdogs, to oversee the trial. I hope you learned something, or I&apos;ll have to proceed with Songtao&apos;s sentencing.</string>
  <string id="77811" soundid="112960">He... took you there. That&apos;s incredible... that&apos;s remarkable. Well, what did you find? Have you discovered evidence that exonerates Scholar Songtao?</string>
  <string id="77812" soundid="112961">Ha! That doesn&apos;t prove a thing. Pieces of paper can be bought and sold just like anything... just like *anyone.*</string>
  <string id="77813" soundid="112962">I&apos;m afraid you&apos;re quite mistaken, Chandler Ling. This proves a great many things, including your guilt. I never suspected the slavers were so well... connected.</string>
  <string id="77814" soundid="112963">Let me see that. Hmm. Well, this certainly looks... interesting. I... ah, suppose Scholar Songtao can go free then.</string>
  <string id="77815" soundid="112964">And you, Chandler Ling, will come with me for sentencing. It will be quick and harsh, I suspect. This sort of thing will not be tolerated in the Empire.</string>
  <string id="77816" soundid="112965">Thank you... thank you for risking yourself to help me. If there is anything I can do to repay you, please ask.</string>
  <string id="77817" soundid="112966">You are too kind. I have no real way to repay you; however, I do have some items you might be interested in.</string>
  <string id="77818" soundid="123432">Good day again. You&apos;ve done a great deal to aid me. If there&apos;s anything I can do for you, just let me know. I&apos;ve got some interesting items, if you&apos;d like to see them.</string>
  <string id="77819" soundid="123433"></string>
  <string id="77820" soundid="112969">I... don&apos;t really have that much in the way of silver. I give most of it to the poor. I do, however, have several items you may find interesting.</string>
  <string id="77823" soundid="112972">It&apos;s a lie! I have never worked with the slave traders. I don&apos;t even know who the slave traders are. Please... Jitong, you must believe me.</string>
  <string id="77824" soundid="112973">If I weren&apos;t looking at it with my own eyes, I wouldn&apos;t believe it. I&apos;m sorry, Songtao, but with this evidence... there is nothing I can do to help you.</string>
  <string id="77825" soundid="112974">Are you absolutely sure this evidence is valid? Are you sure that Songtao is guilty?</string>
  <string id="77826" soundid="112975">So Chandler Ling is free to go. The governor will be pleased to hear it.</string>
  <string id="77827" soundid="112976">Songtao, you will come with me. Your sentencing will be quick and harsh. This sort of thing cannot be tolerated in the Empire.</string>
  <string id="77828" soundid="112977">I am truly sorry, Songtao. I will go to the governor and throw myself at his mercy, though I&apos;m afraid it will do little good now.</string>
  <string id="77829" soundid="112978">Well, you have certainly done me a great service, though I suspect Cao Zeng had something to do with it as well.</string>
  <string id="77830" soundid="112979">Hello there, and thanks again for all your help. Scholar Songtao and I owe you a great debt of gratitude.</string>
  <string id="77840">Who are you?</string>
  <string id="77841">What are you talking about?</string>
  <string id="77842">I don&apos;t have time for your problems.</string>
  <string id="77846">I&apos;ll do it; I can&apos;t stand to see an innocent man accused.</string>
  <string id="77848">All right... where should I start?</string>
  <string id="77855">I want to know more about Scholar Songtao.</string>
  <string id="77859">Tell me about Chandler Ling.</string>
  <string id="77862" soundid="151792">Whatever we are doing, we have to do it now!</string>
  <string id="77863" soundid="151793">This is going to be a mess, I know it is.</string>
  <string id="77864" soundid="151794"></string>
  <string id="77865">What is Zi Bao&apos;s connection to Chandler Ling?</string>
  <string id="77868" soundid="151795">It&apos;s about time!</string>
  <string id="77869">Tell me about the slave traders.</string>
  <string id="77873">I&apos;ll go find Zi Bao then.</string>
  <string id="77874">Find someone else to solve your problem!</string>
  <string id="77875">Actually, I don&apos;t think I want to help.</string>
  <string id="77876">Yes, I have. I&apos;ll help you if I can.</string>
  <string id="77877">Remind me again what the problem is.</string>
  <string id="77878">No. I must be going.</string>
  <string id="77879">No, I haven&apos;t spoken with him yet.</string>
  <string id="77880">I want to ask you some questions.</string>
  <string id="77881">I&apos;m still working on it.</string>
  <string id="77882">I spoke with Zi Bao and he took me to the slavers.</string>
  <string id="77883">Yes, I have; it&apos;s right here. Take a look for yourself.</string>
  <string id="77888">I&apos;m just glad an innocent man didn&apos;t suffer.</string>
  <string id="77890" soundid="123434">Of course. Good fortune to you.</string>
  <string id="77891">You could pay me for my effort.</string>
  <string id="77894">Actually, the evidence proves his guilt. See for yourself.</string>
  <string id="77897">I just found the evidence; it&apos;s up to you to judge.</string>
  <string id="77901" soundid="113050">So, you think you can free me? Prefect Jitong has sent many good men to their deaths trying to free me. I hope you won&apos;t get into similar trouble.</string>
  <string id="77902" soundid="113051">Well, that&apos;s what Jitong fears. I have no reason to doubt him. Besides, why else would the men not return, and their belongings suddenly appear on the market?</string>
  <string id="77903" soundid="113052">Pure coincidence. It&apos;s not proof; it&apos;s purely circumstantial. Anyone will tell you that.</string>
  <string id="77904" soundid="113053">At any rate, it seems likely that&apos;s what has happened to the men. I feel terrible for them, but I have my own problems to deal with... as you can see.</string>
  <string id="77905" soundid="113054">I understand. If there is anything that might help you find the slave traders, I will gladly tell you. Please don&apos;t give up until you&apos;ve found them.</string>
  <string id="77906" soundid="113055">I... am a scholar, though still a junior scholar by most regards. I assist the philosophers and scholars with their work.</string>
  <string id="77907" soundid="113056">It&apos;s a good life, though I can&apos;t help feeling... guilty, sometimes. The scholars and philosophers have many privileges, while so many live with so little.</string>
  <string id="77908" soundid="113057">I spend my spare time in the poor quarters, helping where I can. If I have any extra money, I use it to help the people there. It&apos;s not much, but I like to think it helps.</string>
  <string id="77909" soundid="113058">I don&apos;t know. I was just down in the poor quarters, helping a family with some repairs on their hut. I was leaving their house when the guards came for me.</string>
  <string id="77910" soundid="113059">They told me I was suspected of abducting people from the poor quarters. I told them it was ridiculous, that I only wanted to help the poor, but they didn&apos;t listen.</string>
  <string id="77911" soundid="113060">I admit I spend time in the poor quarters, but I don&apos;t try to hide it. I&apos;m there several times a week in fact, usually in plain sight of everyone.</string>
  <string id="77912" soundid="113061">Well... nothing really. I&apos;d never heard of him before this. I&apos;ve heard what Jitong said about him, but that&apos;s about it. He seems... decent enough, I suppose.</string>
  <string id="77913" soundid="113062">Nothing! I&apos;ve heard rumors in the past few months. The residents in the poor areas were getting worried, though I never knew anyone who disappeared.</string>
  <string id="77914" soundid="113063">One of the girls I helped out in the poor area said her uncle had disappeared, but I never met him. She was devastated of course, and she blamed the slavers.</string>
  <string id="77915" soundid="113064">But it was all just speculation. No one had ever seen anyone being abducted, there wasn&apos;t even evidence of struggles or violence. I don&apos;t know what else to tell you.</string>
  <string id="77916" soundid="113065">Hello again. Is there something else I can tell you that might help you find the slave traders?</string>
  <string id="77917">How do you know they are dead?</string>
  <string id="77920">I must be going. Goodbye.</string>
  <string id="77921">Tell me about yourself, Scholar Songtao.</string>
  <string id="77924">Why were you arrested? What were you doing?</string>
  <string id="77927">Tell me what you know about Chandler Ling.</string>
  <string id="77928">What do you know about the slave traders?</string>
  <string id="77931">No, I should be going.</string>
  <string id="77936">[temp string]</string>
  <string id="77943">Die, worm!</string>
  <string id="77998" soundid="140427">F... forgive me. I saw a new face and hoped there was kindness there. I was mistaken.</string>
  <string id="77999" soundid="140428">I am a criminal, I suppose. For lightening a few purses I was sentenced to work on the Wall, but I was delivered here instead.</string>
  <string id="78001">If you were strong, you could have survived.</string>
  <string id="78074" soundid="124240">Like what?</string>
  <string id="78075" soundid="124241">They come from across the Empire. Some are brought from the south, some from the poor quarters of the city. Others are those who have merely spoken ill of us.</string>
  <string id="78076" soundid="124242">Their lives before don&apos;t matter. Only their deaths concern us.</string>
  <string id="78077" soundid="124243">Death&apos;s Hand is our lord and master. He holds our souls in bondage and grants us power through it. We obey him unquestioningly. He is the will of the Emperor.</string>
  <string id="78078" soundid="124244">Inquisitor Jia is second only to Death&apos;s Hand himself. She is in charge of our work here, and she oversees our operations in the Imperial City.</string>
  <string id="78079">I need to talk to you about Gambler Daoshen.</string>
  <string id="78082">I have the five hundred silver right here.</string>
  <string id="78083">What if I told you I had won this entire purse of silver off of one roll?</string>
  <string id="78085">I didn&apos;t win that purse. It&apos;s his payment.</string>
  <string id="78087">He&apos;s obviously ignoring your limits and rules. Shut him down.</string>
  <string id="78088">I hope you mean to kill him slowly for defying your control like this.</string>
  <string id="78091">I&apos;m not here to make his payment.</string>
  <string id="78092" soundid="113519">The Guild shut me down! Didn&apos;t you pay them?</string>
  <string id="78093" soundid="113520">A misunderstanding? I cultivated my relationship with the Guild for years, and you tell me this was a *misunderstanding?*</string>
  <string id="78094" soundid="113521">Either a fool or you hold some imagined grudge against my family. Either way I am ruined!</string>
  <string id="78095" soundid="113522">You lie! I spent years securing my position here, and now some crooked dicer will move in and milk my good reputation.</string>
  <string id="78096" soundid="113523">But... you lied to them! I&apos;ve always played by the Guild rules! How will I feed my children?</string>
  <string id="78097" soundid="113524">I was a fool to ask for your help. I may as well have asked a Lotus Assassin to carry my message to the Guild.</string>
  <string id="78098" soundid="113525">At least they would have been honest about destroying my life.</string>
  <string id="78099" soundid="113526">I ran an honest game! It was hard enough earning my keep without loading the dice. Is the entertainment I provide worth nothing to you?</string>
  <string id="78100" soundid="113527">You are a monster! I asked for your help and you ruined me!</string>
  <string id="78101" soundid="113528">I can&apos;t dice here in the city. Maybe there&apos;s a corner of the Empire where the Guild&apos;s influence doesn&apos;t reach.</string>
  <string id="78102" soundid="113529">Before you say a thing, I had a visit from one of Sweet Poison Lyn&apos;s contacts.</string>
  <string id="78103" soundid="113530">Fantastic news. I can up the bets! Now you can wager ten or twenty-five silver on each roll! This is perfect, and I have you to thank!</string>
  <string id="78104" soundid="113531">I already gave you the coin to pay Lyn. I thank you for its safe delivery.</string>
  <string id="78105" soundid="113532">Thank you again for paying the fee from your own silver. Here&apos;s your repayment and a little extra for your time.</string>
  <string id="78106" soundid="113533">Go away. I want nothing more to do with petty thieves.</string>
  <string id="78107" soundid="113534">They say you&apos;re in good with the Guild. You&apos;re allowed into the back rooms where Sweet Poison Lyn runs her shop, aren&apos;t you?</string>
  <string id="78108" soundid="113535">I have a favor to ask of you, when you have a moment. My name&apos;s Gambler Daoshen, by the way. </string>
  <string id="78110" soundid="113537">I know you have a brilliant career to attend to here, but I have a favor to ask of you if you can spare a moment.</string>
  <string id="78111" soundid="113538">I was wondering if you&apos;d wander over here to test your luck. It&apos;s hard to resist the rattling call of the dice, isn&apos;t it? Gambler Daoshen&apos;s the name.</string>
  <string id="78112" soundid="113539">I run the straightest dice in the Imperial City. I wouldn&apos;t want to feed my children with tarnished silver, would I?</string>
  <string id="78113" soundid="113540">Good odds and fair play, that&apos;s how I keep them coming back.</string>
  <string id="78114" soundid="113541">You&apos;re not here to play? What did you want to talk to me for, then?</string>
  <string id="78115" soundid="113542">A simple enough game called High Low. You predict how you&apos;ll roll against my toss and double your coin if you&apos;re right.</string>
  <string id="78116" soundid="113543">You&apos;ll catch on easily enough, I&apos;m sure.</string>
  <string id="78117" soundid="113544">You should see Sweet Poison Lyn as soon as you can. I would love to be able to play for higher stakes.</string>
  <string id="78118" soundid="113545">Back to try your luck, I hope?</string>
  <string id="78119" soundid="113546">I trusted you with that silver! It took me a month of scrimping to save it up! </string>
  <string id="78120" soundid="113547">That it was, but I forgive you, if you&apos;ll go see Sweet Poison Lyn soon.</string>
  <string id="78121" soundid="113548">The only lesson I&apos;ve learned is about you. Leave me alone, thief.</string>
  <string id="78122" soundid="113549">That does it! No more dice for you, thief! I will start saving again and then we shall see!</string>
  <string id="78123" soundid="113550">I know you&apos;re allowed to go freely into the back room past Qui&apos;s office. Would you carry a message to someone in there for me?</string>
  <string id="78124" soundid="113551">I&apos;m sorry, I meant no offense.</string>
  <string id="78125" soundid="113552">There&apos;s a merchant in the back named Sweet Poison Lyn. She has connections with the Guild, the real authorities in this place.</string>
  <string id="78126" soundid="113553">I want to expand my operation, but without the Guild&apos;s approval and protection, I can only take very small bets. If I made any larger transactions, they&apos;d be quite upset.</string>
  <string id="78127" soundid="113554">I spoke to some of the lesser Guild members, and there&apos;s a set fee that must be paid to Sweet Poison Lyn.</string>
  <string id="78128" soundid="113555">It took me some time to save up the silver, but I have the fee. I just can&apos;t get back there to talk to Lyn and pay her directly. </string>
  <string id="78129" soundid="113556">If you could go in there and pay her on my behalf, I&apos;d happily repay you.</string>
  <string id="78130" soundid="113557">A richer game with higher bets, of course. I&apos;m sorry I can&apos;t offer you more, but you must admit this is a small favor.</string>
  <string id="78131" soundid="113558">My thanks. I&apos;m sure Sweet Poison Lyn knows about my interest. I&apos;ve been angling this deal for a while.</string>
  <string id="78132" soundid="113559">You should run back there now. The sooner you go, the sooner we can up the antes!</string>
  <string id="78133" soundid="113560">I understand where you&apos;re coming from, but look at it from my point of view: my game is established and comfortable. I gain nothing by refusing to repay you.</string>
  <string id="78134" soundid="113561">On the other hand, you have little to lose by running off with my silver. Trust me, I will pay you back if you do me this small favor.</string>
  <string id="78135" soundid="113562">[Success] I suppose there&apos;s some truth to that.</string>
  <string id="78136" soundid="113563">[Success] No! That&apos;s not what... oh, you&apos;re right. Why would you run off with my pittance, anyway?</string>
  <string id="78137" soundid="113564">[Success] A wager on your character, is it? Fair enough! I&apos;ll take it.</string>
  <string id="78138" soundid="113565">Here&apos;s one of my winnings purses with the silver. The marking on it will let her know it&apos;s from me. Please take it to Sweet Poison Lyn as quickly as possible.</string>
  <string id="78139" soundid="113566">[Failure] I&apos;m sorry. If my request is an imposition on your time or your purse, I will find someone else to help me.</string>
  <string id="78140" soundid="113567">A shame. If you change your mind.... Well, how about a game?</string>
  <string id="78141" soundid="113568">I&apos;d love to help you out, but you&apos;ve stripped me as bare as an orchid in a hail storm.</string>
  <string id="78142" soundid="113569">That&apos;s what I was waiting to hear. So, what&apos;ll it be? Will your roll be higher or lower than mine? </string>
  <string id="78143" soundid="113570">High it is. Let&apos;s see how sure you are. How much will you bet?</string>
  <string id="78144" soundid="113571">Aiming under my roll are you? I&apos;m happy with that if you are. How confident are you?</string>
  <string id="78145" soundid="113572">Let&apos;s see how they fall, shall we?</string>
  <string id="78146" soundid="113573">You called it right! A high roll doubles your wager.</string>
  <string id="78147" soundid="113574">Rolling low and winning large! You called it well.</string>
  <string id="78148" soundid="113575">Even! House takes the pot on an even bust, my friend.</string>
  <string id="78149" soundid="113576">Not enough spin on the wrist to best my roll, it seems. Don&apos;t worry, you&apos;ll make it back on the next round.</string>
  <string id="78150" soundid="113577">You called low but rolled high. Oh well, there&apos;s always next round!</string>
  <string id="78151" soundid="113578">Well, this is a pickled egg! That&apos;s quite the streak of luck you have there. You&apos;ve cleaned me out.</string>
  <string id="78152" soundid="113579">I&apos;ll have to call the game off for a bit until I can come up with more silver to cover my bets. Congratulations, you&apos;ve beat the house!</string>
  <string id="78153" soundid="113580">What say we try again?</string>
  <string id="78154">Not hurt?</string>
  <string id="78155" soundid="113582">Well, suit yourself. If you change your mind, I&apos;m always ready to roll.</string>
  <string id="78156" soundid="113583">The rules are easier than the lonely daughter of an outskirts farmer, my friend.</string>
  <string id="78157" soundid="113584">The rules are simpler to deduce than the motives of a desperate lad memorizing sappy poetry.</string>
  <string id="78158" soundid="113585">You make a simple prediction of &quot;High&quot; or &quot;Low.&quot; Then we roll. I throw first and you throw second. If you wagered high and roll above me, you double your wager.</string>
  <string id="78159" soundid="113586">If you wagered low and roll below me, you also win. If we roll the same, the house takes all.</string>
  <string id="78160" soundid="113587">Thanks to your help, I can take bets of ten or twenty-five silver. I expect the Guild likes the work I&apos;m doing at those rates.</string>
  <string id="78161" soundid="113588">I can take bets of one and five silver. Nothing extravagant, I know, but Gambler Daoshen plays by the rules.</string>
  <string id="78162" soundid="113589">Well, now, that goes back to the little favor I was hoping to ask of you.</string>
  <string id="78163" soundid="113590">The kind of rules you ignore only if you&apos;re tired of using your arms. I could probably find a way around them if I knew someone who could go into the back room, past Qui&apos;s office.</string>
  <string id="78164" soundid="113591">You&apos;re one of the fighters, aren&apos;t you? If you&apos;re ever allowed back there, come see me, and we&apos;ll talk.</string>
  <string id="78165" soundid="113592">I think they only let arena folk go back there. Fighters in some of the higher divisions.</string>
  <string id="78166" soundid="113593">High Low is easy to learn, and people like it. Why change?</string>
  <string id="78167" soundid="113594">Right you are. Educated as an ancient scholar, I hope?</string>
  <string id="78168" soundid="113595">Thanks again for all your help. Be seeing you around, I hope.</string>
  <string id="78169" soundid="113596">You take care of yourself, and come back soon to the best game in the city.</string>
  <string id="78170">There was a misunderstanding about the fee.</string>
  <string id="78173">I have no idea what happened.</string>
  <string id="78175">The money you gave me convinced them you were over your limit.</string>
  <string id="78176">I told them you offered to let me play outside your limit.</string>
  <string id="78177">That&apos;s not my problem. Tell someone who cares.</string>
  <string id="78180">Find some real employment and *earn* your way.</string>
  <string id="78182">Sell your children into slavery. Their master is required by law to feed them.</string>
  <string id="78190">What&apos;s the nature of the game?</string>
  <string id="78191">I&apos;m not really interested in gambling.</string>
  <string id="78192">Enough of the patter. I&apos;m here for information only.</string>
  <string id="78193">I might be able to play a round. What&apos;s the game?</string>
  <string id="78195">I&apos;m not here to play games. I should go.</string>
  <string id="78196">I&apos;ve decided to keep your silver for myself.</string>
  <string id="78197">My apologies. That was a tasteless joke.</string>
  <string id="78198">This should teach you a lesson about trusting strangers.</string>
  <string id="78199">Ask someone who cares.</string>
  <string id="78200">What&apos;s this favor you need me to do?</string>
  <string id="78201">That sounds easy enough, I&apos;d be happy to help.</string>
  <string id="78202">What message do you need me to carry?</string>
  <string id="78203">I&apos;m no one&apos;s serving girl. Don&apos;t waste my time.</string>
  <string id="78204">I&apos;m no one&apos;s messenger boy. Don&apos;t waste my time.</string>
  <string id="78205">Tell me what you wanted, just make it fast.</string>
  <string id="78207">What would it take to get their protection?</string>
  <string id="78208">I assume their approval has a price.</string>
  <string id="78211">How would I benefit from helping you?</string>
  <string id="78212">I&apos;d be happy to help. I&apos;ll go talk to her.</string>
  <string id="78214">I&apos;m not paying for you. Give me the money and I&apos;ll take it to her.</string>
  <string id="78216">[Charm] You trusted me enough to ask for my help. You can trust me with your silver.</string>
  <string id="78218">[Intimidation] You ask my help, then question my honor? I am no thief!</string>
  <string id="78220">[Intuition] You&apos;re a gambler, aren&apos;t you? Sometimes you have to take a risk to win.</string>
  <string id="78222">Fine. I&apos;ll go talk to her for you.</string>
  <string id="78223">I&apos;m not interested in helping you right now.</string>
  <string id="78224">Let&apos;s roll the dice, I&apos;d like to try my luck.</string>
  <string id="78226">I bet I&apos;ll roll higher than you. </string>
  <string id="78227">Lower. I&apos;m betting I&apos;ll be under your roll.</string>
  <string id="78228">I&apos;ll wager ten silver.</string>
  <string id="78229">I&apos;ll put twenty-five coins down on this roll.</string>
  <string id="78230">I&apos;ll wager one silver.</string>
  <string id="78231">Let&apos;s go with five silver for my wager.</string>
  <string id="78233" soundid="157151">I&apos;ve never seen anything like that! I... I&apos;m going to have to change my shirt.</string>
  <string id="78236">Let&apos;s play again.</string>
  <string id="78237">Crush you!</string>
  <string id="78238">On second thought, I don&apos;t want to bet right now.</string>
  <string id="78239">Explain the rules for me.</string>
  <string id="78243">What kind of bets do you take?</string>
  <string id="78244">What rules stop you from taking larger bets?</string>
  <string id="78246">Do you run any other games?</string>
  <string id="78247">That&apos;s all I wanted to know about the rules.</string>
  <string id="78248">That&apos;s enough for now. I should go.</string>
  <string id="78249" soundid="113676">I dropped you off at the pirate camp, you killed some pirates, I got drunk, you killed more pirates, and I took a nap! We are an unstoppable team, my friend!</string>
  <string id="78250" soundid="113677">[Success] Yes... yes! You&apos;re right. A wife... a family... I can do this! Even if it means giving up the wine!</string>
  <string id="78251" soundid="113678">[Failure] No, I&apos;m afraid it&apos;s not so simple. I&apos;d like those things: a wife, a family. But wine is everything to me. I could never give it up.</string>
  <string id="78252" soundid="113679">[Success] I... I suppose that&apos;s true. I did get you up the river when nobody else could... when nobody else dared! If I can take on the pirates, surely I can give up the wine!</string>
  <string id="78253" soundid="113680">You... you really believe I can do this, don&apos;t you? Well then, maybe I can! I took on the pirates... surely I can give up the wine!</string>
  <string id="78255">[Charm] It won&apos;t be easy, Ru. But I know you&apos;re strong enough to do this.</string>
  <string id="78259">[Intimidation] Quit making excuses! You can do this!</string>
  <string id="78261">I want to ask you some questions.</string>
  <string id="78308" soundid="113885">All this talk is just the rambling of an old woman. Put it out of your head and enjoy yourself. It may not be mine anymore, but this is still a fine teahouse.</string>
  <string id="78309" soundid="113886">I&apos;m afraid you&apos;ll have to wait your turn, dearie. Waitress Yanwan is very busy. I&apos;m sure she&apos;ll get to you in time.</string>
  <string id="78310" soundid="113887">Poor girl. Master Dutong works her too hard. If I still owned this place, she&apos;d get far more than the few coins he gives her each week. But I guess he&apos;s in charge now.</string>
  <string id="78311" soundid="113888">Oh, of course I do, dearie. It was all I ever had. No children of my own. But it&apos;s Master Dutong&apos;s teahouse now. You can&apos;t argue with an Imperial Writ, you know.</string>
  <string id="78314">Where can I get a drink?</string>
  <string id="78316">Do you miss owning the teahouse?</string>
  <string id="78374">There are a few things I better look into, first.</string>
  <string id="78379">I&apos;m still looking into this.</string>
  <string id="78383">There&apos;s got to be more to this story.</string>
  <string id="78389">I haven&apos;t spoken to him yet.</string>
  <string id="78554">Black Whirlwind</string>
  <string id="78567">Retry Mission</string>
  <string id="78568">Disengage</string>
  <string id="78675">Dialog Review</string>
  <string id="78678" soundid="140429">Some of the others were captured by pirates and sold. One merely asked why the Imperial Army reports to the Lotus Assassins now.</string>
  <string id="78680" soundid="143815">Gao killed someone? And I let him go past here without questioning him? I&apos;m an old fool!</string>
  <string id="78682">Gao has killed a student, and now Dawn Star is missing.</string>
  <string id="78684" soundid="140430">We did nothing to deserve this harsh fate. You must be able to see that.</string>
  <string id="78686" soundid="140431">Hundreds... thousands... I don&apos;t know. All that were here when I arrived are gone. There are scratches on the walls... names of wives, of daughters.</string>
  <string id="78688" soundid="140432">What did so many do to deserve such a horrible death? We can hear them scream... one by one.</string>
  <string id="78690" soundid="140433">You... you would do that?</string>
  <string id="78692">Gao has killed a student, and now Dawn Star is missing.</string>
  <string id="78693">[Main level.]</string>
  <string id="78696">[Prison level.]</string>
  <string id="78699" soundid="140434">You are a long way from the authority you need to make such promises. Don&apos;t get attached to them. There will always be more.</string>
  <string id="78702">[Near-surface mine level.]</string>
  <string id="78705">[Abandoned deep-level mine.]</string>
  <string id="78708" soundid="140435">Yes... farewell.</string>
  <string id="78711" soundid="140436">Yes, Lotus Acolyte? Is there anything I can do before my... death?</string>
  <string id="78714" soundid="140437">We are free, if only for a little while. There are sure to be other guards. Thank you for what you have done, but I&apos;m not sure where to go now.</string>
  <string id="78717" soundid="140438">The mine! The smaller one, remember? Before they stopped digging out the graves, there was light from the surface coming in.</string>
  <string id="78720" soundid="143818">I heard about student Si Pat! That&apos;s terrible news... he seemed so earnest!</string>
  <string id="78721">Slave</string>
  <string id="78724">Slave Han Ro</string>
  <string id="78727">Slave</string>
  <string id="78730">Slave</string>
  <string id="78733">Slave</string>
  <string id="78736">Slave</string>
  <string id="78739">Slave</string>
  <string id="78742">Slave</string>
  <string id="78760" soundid="124245">You will meet her in time, and when you do, pray you do not anger her.</string>
  <string id="78812" soundid="126231">I am sworn to serve you, great one. My entire purpose in the mortal realm is to help you fulfill your destiny. I will do everything in my power to aid you.</string>
  <string id="78817">I&apos;ll bury your bones for you.</string>
  <string id="78819" soundid="126232">The little girl you spoke to before is named Wild Flower. She is my anchor to your world. It is through her that I can exist here.</string>
  <string id="78826">Can I ask you some questions?</string>
  <string id="78831">I&apos;ll see if I can find him for you.</string>
  <string id="78839">You&apos;re dead. There&apos;s nothing I can do for you.</string>
  <string id="78877" soundid="189221"></string>
  <string id="78878" soundid="189222"></string>
  <string id="78879" soundid="189223"></string>
  <string id="78880" soundid="189224"></string>
  <string id="78881" soundid="189225"></string>
  <string id="78882" soundid="189226"></string>
  <string id="78883" soundid="189227"></string>
  <string id="78884" soundid="189228"></string>
  <string id="78885" soundid="189229"></string>
  <string id="78886" soundid="189230"></string>
  <string id="78887" soundid="189231"></string>
  <string id="78888" soundid="189232"></string>
  <string id="78889" soundid="189233"></string>
  <string id="78890" soundid="189234"></string>
  <string id="78927">Patron</string>
  <string id="78930">Patron</string>
  <string id="78933">Patron</string>
  <string id="78936">Patron</string>
  <string id="79140" soundid="165691">There is something chaotic enough to disrupt that. In the elevator room to come, descend to the deepest mine, to the oldest graves.</string>
  <string id="79142" soundid="157003">Good day, citizen. Some minor thing I can help you with?</string>
  <string id="79143" soundid="157004">As long as these questions aren&apos;t about anything sensitive. For instance, I would be happy to provide directions.</string>
  <string id="79144" soundid="157005">Easy enough to find. Just head as far east as you can go in this district and take the smaller path up the hill.</string>
  <string id="79145" soundid="157006">It winds a bit past the performers&apos; pagoda and leads right into the Scholars&apos; Garden.</string>
  <string id="79146" soundid="157007">The garden is just off the Golden Way, so you&apos;ll need to head there, first. One of the guards in there can take you the rest of the way, if you need.</string>
  <string id="79147" soundid="157008">You&apos;ll want to be careful in there. To get there, head to the western edge of this district. There&apos;s a footbridge that leads to the Necropolis gates.</string>
  <string id="79148" soundid="157009">Somewhat hard to miss, as it&apos;s cut right into the rock with three statues around it.</string>
  <string id="79149" soundid="157010">A pleasure. Anything else?</string>
  <string id="79150" soundid="157011">To reach the Necropolis, you need to go to the Golden Way first. Once there, you can ask another guard, if you&apos;re still lost.</string>
  <string id="79151" soundid="157012">Fair enough. What else can I do for you?</string>
  <string id="79152" soundid="157013">I&apos;m afraid not. I&apos;m on duty, and it&apos;s imperative that I remain focused on what few tasks I&apos;m still deemed capable of performing.</string>
  <string id="79153" soundid="157014">A fellow guard once paused for idle chit-chat with a woman. She went to the Lotus Assassins with a story of his inattentiveness.</string>
  <string id="79154" soundid="157015">Next thing you know, he&apos;s arrested for threatening the security of the Empire with his lax ways. I don&apos;t know what happened to him, but I don&apos;t want to share his fate.</string>
  <string id="79155" soundid="157016">Be about your business, and stay out of trouble. Pleasure to be of service.</string>
  <string id="79156" soundid="157017">It&apos;s the honorable Lotus Assassins, you see. They feel that those of us dedicated to the Imperial Army are nothing more than louts to be ordered about.</string>
  <string id="79157" soundid="157018">Any member of the army, even city guard, is expected to defer any major disturbances to them. Makes me about as useful as a lamp post.</string>
  <string id="79158" soundid="157019">Seems like the Imperial Army can&apos;t be trusted with even the simplest of tasks these days. The Lotus Assassins have made sure that we&apos;re pushed aside.</string>
  <string id="79159" soundid="157020">If you find yourself needing directions, I or any of the other guards will be happy to help. We have to do something to pass the time.</string>
  <string id="79160" soundid="157021">Lost, citizen?</string>
  <string id="79164" soundid="135865">My manners desert me. I am Lord Yun, owner of this land and charged by the Emperor himself to keep it safe.</string>
  <string id="79165" soundid="135866">You should turn back south to Tien&apos;s Landing. This is the safest part of the Great Southern Forest, and even it is polluted with these strange ghosts.</string>
  <string id="79166" soundid="135867">I suppose no one knows this land better than I. Very well, what did you need to know?</string>
  <string id="79170" soundid="157022">This area is known as the Market District. Predictably, plenty of merchants set up their shops around here, and it&apos;s usually bustling.</string>
  <string id="79171" soundid="157023">On the north side of the district is the Imperial Arena. The Heart of the Empire Tavern in the upper level is a nice place to relax.</string>
  <string id="79172" soundid="157024">What else? Oh, yes, there&apos;s the Black Leopard School up the hill on the south side. Lots of skilled warriors get their start there.</string>
  <string id="79173" soundid="157025">This district? Well, it&apos;s called the Golden Way for a variety of reasons. Certainly one of the richer areas of the city, and one of the best looking, as well.</string>
  <string id="79174" soundid="157026">This district is a major thoroughfare, with the Scholars&apos; Garden at one end and the Market District at the other.</string>
  <string id="79175" soundid="157027">There&apos;s also the Necropolis, but most people avoid that place. Who wants to spend time with the dead?</string>
  <string id="79176" soundid="157028">The Scholars&apos; Garden is a quiet place.... Quiet until a pair of the scholars break out into debate, that is.</string>
  <string id="79177" soundid="157029">Certainly a lot of... knowledge being thrown around this place. I&apos;ll let you decide for yourself how much of it is worthwhile.</string>
  <string id="79179">Pirate</string>
  <string id="79182" soundid="157034">What district are you looking for?</string>
  <string id="79183" soundid="157035">The Market District&apos;s easy enough to find. Just head to the west end of the Golden Way and then turn north and go through the large gate.</string>
  <string id="79184" soundid="157036">From here, you need to head to the Golden Way to get to the Market District. So you don&apos;t get turned around, head there and, if you&apos;re still lost, ask another guard.</string>
  <string id="79185" soundid="157037">The Golden Way is through a gate in the southeast corner of this district. Just up a broad flight of steps that lead up from a courtyard.</string>
  <string id="79186" soundid="157038">To reach the Golden Way from here, go through these gates here. They lead west right into the Golden Way.</string>
  <string id="79187" soundid="157039">To reach the Golden Way, go into the pavilion on the north side of the garden and make your way through the rooms of illumination.</string>
  <string id="79188" soundid="157040">When you reach the large wooden pavilion, exit its west side and proceed down the hill to the south.</string>
  <string id="79189">You&apos;ll only help me with minor things?</string>
  <string id="79190">I do have some questions for you.</string>
  <string id="79192">I don&apos;t need any directions.</string>
  <string id="79193">Can you tell me anything other than directions?</string>
  <string id="79196">Goodbye.</string>
  <string id="79202">No, I&apos;m fine. I should go.</string>
  <string id="79204">What can you tell me about this area of the city?</string>
  <string id="79210">Pirate</string>
  <string id="79222">I need help finding my way.</string>
  <string id="79223">How would I reach the Market District?</string>
  <string id="79232">Where would I find the Golden Way?</string>
  <string id="79234">I&apos;m looking for the Scholars&apos; Garden.</string>
  <string id="79237">Where is the Necropolis?</string>
  <string id="79239">That&apos;s all the directions I need. Thank you.</string>
  <string id="79283">Pc fights Aishi for Sen</string>
  <string id="79286">Aishi the Mournful Blade is dead, and you have collected a sizable bounty for eliminating her in front of Captain Sen.</string>
  <string id="79287">PC lets Aishi fight Sen</string>
  <string id="79290">Aishi the Mournful Blade had her revenge on Captain Sen for a crime committed long ago. She refused to just walk away, and you emerged the victor from her attack. With any luck, she has found some peace at last.</string>
  <string id="79291">Fight Aishi</string>
  <string id="79773" soundid="117948">And if that wasn&apos;t bad enough, we have the pirates to worry about, too. They&apos;ve been raiding the countryside, taking prisoners to sell into slavery.</string>
  <string id="79774" soundid="117949">The dam was built nearly twenty years ago, causing the river to rise. Now, the dam is open, and the river has fallen so low no ships can navigate it.</string>
  <string id="79775" soundid="117950">Tien&apos;s Landing cannot survive without the river, but nobody in the town dares to go into the ruins to close the dam. The ruins are haunted with the spirits of the dead!</string>
  <string id="79776" soundid="117951">It&apos;s bad luck to speak of such things! Old Wei in the town might tell you more; he&apos;s too old to care about ghosts and curses. But I have enough bad luck already.</string>
  <string id="79777" soundid="117952">A generous offer, great one, but the gate leading to the ruins is locked. If you want to close the dam, you&apos;ll have to get the key from Minister Sheng.</string>
  <string id="79778" soundid="117953">I&apos;m sure he&apos;d be glad to give you a key to the gate. Nobody else will risk going into the ruins because of the ghosts.</string>
  <string id="79779" soundid="117954">There&apos;s a road off to the right just beyond this teahouse. Keep following it up until you reach the town square. Minister Sheng is usually there.</string>
  <string id="79780" soundid="117955">I wish I could help you, great one. But I am only a humble peasant woman. All I know about pirates is to try and avoid them.</string>
  <string id="79781" soundid="117956">Maybe Sheng knows more. I&apos;m sure he&apos;d do all he could to help you get rid of the pirates threatening the town. After all, he is our Imperial Minister.</string>
  <string id="79782">Never mind. I want to ask you something else.</string>
  <string id="79784">I want to ask you something else.</string>
  <string id="79785">I want to know more about the dam.</string>
  <string id="79787">Haunted ruins? Tell me more.</string>
  <string id="79788">Maybe I can close the dam for you.</string>
  <string id="79790">How do I find Minister Sheng?</string>
  <string id="79791">I have more questions for you.</string>
  <string id="79792">I have questions about the pirates.</string>
  <string id="80185">Cannibal</string>
  <string id="80197" soundid="118623">Don&apos;t worry about that. When the Marvelous Dragonfly takes off, the earth shakes and the sky trembles! You can&apos;t miss it.</string>
  <string id="80198" soundid="118624">Your friend will see us take off, and he&apos;ll head back to town on his own.</string>
  <string id="80199">What about Ru? He&apos;s waiting to take me back.</string>
  <string id="80219">Return to the Flyer</string>
  <string id="80220">[Charm] If you help me end the troubles, everybody benefits.</string>
  <string id="80225" soundid="118680">Four students test their skills against one master.</string>
  <string id="80226" soundid="118681">Unyielding stone meets the press of time.</string>
  <string id="80227" soundid="118682"></string>
  <string id="80228" soundid="118683">These monsters crave the flesh of man.</string>
  <string id="80229" soundid="118684">The Pit of Pain: Only the quick survive its fiery embrace.</string>
  <string id="80230" soundid="118685">Only in our Empire can demons be harnessed for sport!</string>
  <string id="80231" soundid="118686"></string>
  <string id="80232" soundid="118687">Will the demon rend flesh from bone, or will a lone warrior prove stronger?</string>
  <string id="80233" soundid="118688">Flashing blades and deadly grace.</string>
  <string id="80234" soundid="118689">The Imperial Army honors us with a most unique trial.</string>
  <string id="80235" soundid="118690"></string>
  <string id="80236" soundid="118691">The Phoenix Unity is among the rarest of styles. No one person has defeated it... yet.</string>
  <string id="80237" soundid="118692">Speed, might, and magic will be needed to defeat these brothers three.</string>
  <string id="80238" soundid="118693">The Imperial Engagement begins! An ogre begins the onslaught!</string>
  <string id="80239" soundid="118694">Hapless Han enters the fray!</string>
  <string id="80240" soundid="118695">What is the greater foe? Exhaustion, or a fiend fallen from the heavens?</string>
  <string id="80241" soundid="118696">Iron Soldier makes another foray against his nemesis.</string>
  <string id="80242" soundid="118697">How long can one warrior last, battling a tide of foes?</string>
  <string id="80243" soundid="118698"></string>
  <string id="80244" soundid="118699">The Serpent returns, and the contest will be decided here and now.</string>
  <string id="80245" soundid="118700">The Black Whirlwind returns to the ring to face the Serpent. Might meets magic.</string>
  <string id="80255">Assassin Supplies</string>
  <string id="80261">Let&apos;s go back to my other questions.</string>
  <string id="80262">Prince of Sorrow</string>
  <string id="80281" soundid="124246">If there is nothing else, you should leave me alone.</string>
  <string id="80285" soundid="140439">I heard someone got away once. I don&apos;t know if they made it out of the Necropolis, but it is a chance!</string>
  <string id="80286" soundid="140440">But... there will be guards.</string>
  <string id="80287">Paused</string>
  <string id="80289" soundid="140441">Then... then we have no choice. Come... if we stay here, we die. If we fight, there is a chance.</string>
  <string id="80291" soundid="124251">Do what you like.</string>
  <string id="80299" soundid="140442">Let&apos;s... let&apos;s go!</string>
  <string id="80302" soundid="140443">Thank you. I did not expect to find a kind soul in this place.</string>
  <string id="80305" soundid="126152">Change will take you. Soon, you will be one of us!</string>
  <string id="80306">I want to ask you some questions.</string>
  <string id="80307">Where do these slaves come from?</string>
  <string id="80318" soundid="140444">Thank you. I don&apos;t think we would have a chance without you.</string>
  <string id="80319">Tell me about Death&apos;s Hand.</string>
  <string id="80320">Tell me about Inquisitor Jia.</string>
  <string id="80326">Nothing for now.</string>
  <string id="80327" soundid="140445">Thank you again for your help. We await your signal that it is safe to make our way to the mine. It is our only hope.</string>
  <string id="80329" soundid="140446">They... they are all dead. I don&apos;t know whether to thank you for release or curse you for this fate.</string>
  <string id="80331" soundid="126153">So... hungry....</string>
  <string id="80334" soundid="126154">What? Who are you?</string>
  <string id="80339" soundid="140447">I can&apos;t get out of here soon enough. This is nothing but a nightmare. You&apos;re demons, all of you!</string>
  <string id="80340">Red Minister</string>
  <string id="80346">Toad Demon</string>
  <string id="80350">Tea House</string>
  <string id="80352">Lever</string>
  <string id="80353">Chimney</string>
  <string id="80354">Conductor</string>
  <string id="80355">Button</string>
  <string id="80356">Fuel Hopper</string>
  <string id="80358">Button</string>
  <string id="80359">Water wheel</string>
  <string id="80360">Machine</string>
  <string id="80491" soundid="118949">Get up, you lot. I&apos;ll be embarrassed for myself, thank you. Save your false modesty for my father&apos;s court.</string>
  <string id="80497" soundid="143819">Gao killed someone? Maybe he took Dawn Star as well!</string>
  <string id="80498" soundid="118956">Come, one more bout before our master steals you away.</string>
  <string id="80501">I am rarely beaten, friend.</string>
  <string id="80502" soundid="118960">I&apos;m sure the others agree that my tastes are balanced. The Minister, however, is easily engaged by sympathetic pleas, as are Scholars Zou and Gu.</string>
  <string id="80503" soundid="118961">I find their appreciation of such fawning to be distasteful, but that is one of the arguments they prefer.</string>
  <string id="80504" soundid="118962">I don&apos;t dislike him. I find some of his points to be worth discussing, but Sir Roderick is... a bit disruptive for the garden.</string>
  <string id="80505" soundid="118963">He may bring attention that we do not want. It would be best to peacefully encourage him to be on his way.</string>
  <string id="80506" soundid="118964">The debate was a terrible defeat. If you won&apos;t face the Outlander in combat, what victory can we claim?</string>
  <string id="80508">Why do you dislike the Outlander?</string>
  <string id="80510" soundid="118968">I... I haven&apos;t given it much thought. I pictured myself as balanced, but some of the others are very specific in their tastes.</string>
  <string id="80511" soundid="118969">Actually, you can sway Scholars Cai and Gu by mocking your opponent. I don&apos;t care for it, but they seem to respond quite vigorously.</string>
  <string id="80512" soundid="118970">He is coarser than the thinkers I am used to, but on the whole I am not as upset by him as others appear to be.</string>
  <string id="80513" soundid="118971">He seems bent on disruptive behavior. He should be encouraged to take that elsewhere.</string>
  <string id="80514" soundid="118972">It is unfortunate that you could not defeat the Outlander in the debate. What recourse do we have now?</string>
  <string id="80516">Do you share the Minister&apos;s dislike of the Outlander?</string>
  <string id="80518" soundid="118979">I don&apos;t care where he came from. Anything to get him on his way.</string>
  <string id="80519" soundid="118980">Your failure in the debate was abysmal. What will you do to recover your honor?</string>
  <string id="80521">Do you share the Minister&apos;s disdain for the Outlander?</string>
  <string id="80523" soundid="118985">Scholars Zou and Cai are easy to predict. Dismissing a weak argument gets their attention immediately and will spur them one way or another.</string>
  <string id="80524" soundid="118986">He doesn&apos;t seem that interested in gathering any. He is clearly used to imposing his opinion, regardless of the recipients&apos; desire to have it.</string>
  <string id="80525" soundid="118987">His points are debatable, but his presentation is not compatible with the garden.</string>
  <string id="80526" soundid="118988">This was a troubling affair. Is there nothing we can do now about this Outlander?</string>
  <string id="80528">The Outlander has very few supporters.</string>
  <string id="80530" soundid="118993">I will take my leave. Remember, however, that while I may have succumbed to your fists, my mind bested yours in no uncertain terms.</string>
  <string id="80533" soundid="151796">Trust her voice. We need a path through Master Li&apos;s corruption.</string>
  <string id="80675" soundid="119144">The Minister is not the best at... applied intelligence. Many of the scholars are theoretically smart.</string>
  <string id="80676" soundid="119145">The Minister had me insult thirty-four people. The best answer before yours was a smart slap in the face.</string>
  <string id="80677" soundid="119146">I am supposed to be the servant of an educated man. Destiny is a trickster that does not share the joke.</string>
  <string id="80678" soundid="119147">I like this Outlander. His foolishness is not disguised behind education.</string>
  <string id="80679" soundid="119148">The Minister is not the most aware of what he says.</string>
  <string id="80680" soundid="119149">Such a string of improprieties. Spirits have tricked his mouth into mocking him.</string>
  <string id="80681" soundid="119150">He may not know he is the center of a joke, but that does not decrease my enjoyment.</string>
  <string id="80682" soundid="119151">Your actions must have brought too much sense to the world. The Minister seems to be charged with returning balance.</string>
  <string id="80683" soundid="119152">A shame you had to send the Outlander on his way. I welcome anything that shakes up these bookworms.</string>
  <string id="80684" soundid="119153">I almost wish the Outlander had won. Everyone is back to thinking about how important they are.</string>
  <string id="80685">**TEMP** Daze turns to confusion (target attacks enemies)</string>
  <string id="80686">**TEMP** Adds 5 second daze effect to punch 4. Chi charge casts a confusion beam.</string>
  <string id="80687">**Temp** triples daze duration</string>
  <string id="80688">**TEMP** Power becomes area effect (5 meters)</string>
  <string id="80689" soundid="119179">You are strange indeed, but what you say is true. The Heavenly Lily could never abide such a situation.</string>
  <string id="80690" soundid="119180">I would bite my own tongue before ever allowing that... &quot;man&quot; to touch me.</string>
  <string id="80691" soundid="119181">You still underestimate his power. But one way or another, we must stop him.</string>
  <string id="80692" soundid="119182">I&apos;m sorry, I&apos;ve ruined the mood. We should continue our talk another time. First, we must expose Death&apos;s Hand, reveal his treachery and manipulation. </string>
  <string id="80693" soundid="119183">Generosity is a part of my character from time to time as well. It is more than most men will show for you.</string>
  <string id="80694" soundid="119184">The Imperial Palace holds many treasures... although Death&apos;s Hand carted many off, to what end I do not know.</string>
  <string id="80695" soundid="119185">Well, perhaps it would be best if we restricted this relationship to business. There is a limit to my patience and I will end this before I reach that limit.</string>
  <string id="80696" soundid="119186">I thank you for your courtesy. One always likes to hear when one&apos;s gifts are appreciated.</string>
  <string id="80697" soundid="119187">Can I not simply want to give you something? Does my noble birth not give me the same right as any other to... to show favor?</string>
  <string id="80698" soundid="119188">You rebuff my attempt at friendship? I am a daughter of the Emperor himself. It would be wise of you not to draw my ire. Civility is prized in the Imperial City.</string>
  <string id="80699" soundid="119189">But I understand the strains and pressures that you have been under. I am willing to forgive your impertinence this once.</string>
  <string id="80700" soundid="119190">After the... disappearance of my uncle, Sun Kin the Hand of Heaven, the Imperial Order of the Lotus Monks was directionless.</string>
  <string id="80701" soundid="119191">Instead of taking on that role himself, my father gave it to an advisor: Death&apos;s Hand. I was only a baby at the time.</string>
  <string id="80702" soundid="119192">He did not have enough time. The burden of state is heavy and he is not a well man. Death&apos;s Hand takes advantage of this.</string>
  <string id="80703" soundid="119193">Regardless, the Lotus Monks were placed in the care of Death&apos;s Hand, a duty reserved for royalty. It was almost as if my father took Death&apos;s Hand into our family! My family!</string>
  <string id="80704" soundid="119194">We have been caretakers of the Empire for generations. We have created a bastion of culture in an otherwise uncivilized world. Death&apos;s Hand threatens all of this.</string>
  <string id="80705" soundid="119195">It is my duty to see that the natural order is preserved.</string>
  <string id="80706" soundid="119196">About... about me? But... why?</string>
  <string id="80707" soundid="119197">I mean, there&apos;s so much I&apos;ve told you already, I really don&apos;t think that we need any more information to complete our mission.</string>
  <string id="80708" soundid="119198">Oh... well, I suppose I could answer a few  questions.</string>
  <string id="80709" soundid="119199">Although I&apos;m sure more than enough has been said about me by the peasants or others. I am quite used to defending myself from all quarters.</string>
  <string id="80710" soundid="119200">Am I really that way? Perhaps I appear to be, but only because I have no other way to fight what is happening. I care deeply about the traditions of this land.</string>
  <string id="80711" soundid="119201">It pains me to go against what I try to protect. What other choice do I have? I hope the people speak of other things... how I try to make things right.</string>
  <string id="80712" soundid="119202">You presume a great deal. Can you really have seen this in such a short time?</string>
  <string id="80713" soundid="119203">Those are qualities I would like to say I have, but I am not certain that I do. I have little time for listening when I seem to be fighting the very system of which I am a part.</string>
  <string id="80714" soundid="119204">You... well, you might. I don&apos;t know what the future will bring for us.</string>
  <string id="80715" soundid="119205">Do you think yourself worthy of reminding me of what is important? To keep me humble? My father will take a dim view of that.</string>
  <string id="80716" soundid="119206">My father, the Emperor, is the heart and soul of this Empire. He is the one who can restore your master to you. You must respect him.</string>
  <string id="80717" soundid="119207">He should be of great concern to you, if only because he is of concern to me.</string>
  <string id="80718" soundid="119208">Ha! Your ambition knows no bounds, but the Empire is no stranger to your kind. We have dealt with many like you.</string>
  <string id="80719" soundid="119209">Of course, it appears that we have also nearly fallen to one. I will stand with you against Death&apos;s Hand, but remember our purpose. I will see my father restored.</string>
  <string id="80720" soundid="119210">I think we&apos;ve talked enough for now. I have enjoyed this. Perhaps we can continue later.</string>
  <string id="80721" soundid="119211">That is not true. Without the support of the people, an Emperor... or Empress... has nothing. My father has forgotten this in the spell Death&apos;s Hand has woven.</string>
  <string id="80722" soundid="119212">So the burden is left for me to bear. I don&apos;t know if I can overcome all that fate will put in my way.</string>
  <string id="80723" soundid="119213">Ha! Strong words, indeed! I never pictured myself as a harsh ruler, but I certainly try to maintain the virtue of justice. Is that how I present myself to you?</string>
  <string id="80724" soundid="119214">I do know what I want, but getting it is something else. Sometimes, I think you know what I mean, and others... I don&apos;t know myself.</string>
  <string id="80725" soundid="119215">Wait... this is further than I thought this conversation would go. This is not proper... I will not allow it. You presume too much.</string>
  <string id="80726" soundid="119216">I think we have had quite enough amusement for now. Perhaps... perhaps we will continue this a little later. I have enjoyed our little... talk.</string>
  <string id="80727" soundid="119217">You are very unlike the women of the court I grew up with. I have long tried to separate myself from them.</string>
  <string id="80728" soundid="119218">First you stab at me with your words, then twist them around to seek my heart. You are very adept.</string>
  <string id="80729" soundid="119219">So, why dress this revelation in so many previous compliments? If this is your true opinion, I don&apos;t see a need to continue this.</string>
  <string id="80730" soundid="119220">How very superficial, yet... flattering... coming from you.</string>
  <string id="80731" soundid="119221">I suppose peasants tend to focus on certain things, given their short and brutish lives. Something to imagine, some perfection to seek...</string>
  <string id="80732" soundid="119222">And do you agree with them?</string>
  <string id="80733" soundid="119223">Useful. And that is all? If that is the extent of what you want from me, why disguise your intent with your previous words? You are very confusing.</string>
  <string id="80734" soundid="119224">I think it would be best to confine our talks to the task at hand. If you require something, I will help, but this game of yours is too distracting.</string>
  <string id="80735" soundid="119225">That is... not what I was expecting you to say. You are very unlike the women of the court I grew up with. I have long tried to separate myself from them.</string>
  <string id="80736" soundid="119226">As you can tell from my unconventional choice of traveling... companions. I think we are very similar, you and I. You are... interesting.</string>
  <string id="80737" soundid="119227">We will continue this another time. I find myself at a loss for words. Very few people have had such an effect. Yes, you are... interesting.</string>
  <string id="80738" soundid="119228">I have never seen myself as particularly generous, but it would not be so bad to be remembered in that way. The gratitude of the peasants is important to any ruler.</string>
  <string id="80739" soundid="119229">They, even unknowingly, have the power to see the Empire rise or fall. The love of the people is powerful.</string>
  <string id="80740" soundid="119230">I hope, however, that I am not just seen as a giver of charity. Anyone can throw money at the downtrodden. I try to accomplish more than that.</string>
  <string id="80741" soundid="119231">Harsh times demand harsh actions. This is a time of trial for my family and the Empire. One I shall not fail!</string>
  <string id="80742" soundid="119232">I hope they do not only speak of my harshness, despite my position above them. We all want people to speak well of us.</string>
  <string id="80743" soundid="119233">I was at least trying to be civil, but you persist in treating me this way. Very well. Other than the goals we share, there shall be nothing between us.</string>
  <string id="80744" soundid="119234">Now, if there is anything you wish to ask regarding those goals, I shall speak. Otherwise, let&apos;s just get on with it.</string>
  <string id="80745" soundid="119235">I mean, if you were a man, I could understand how there might be some interest but... never mind. Is this about the mission?</string>
  <string id="80746" soundid="119236">I don&apos;t know. I have made... inquiries, but no one had seen or heard of him before he rose to power. He was like a Lotus Assassin even then... hiding in the shadows.</string>
  <string id="80747" soundid="119237">I don&apos;t know. My father said he and my other uncle, Sun Li, were lost in the battle to end the Long Drought, but I can find no record of who or what they fought.</string>
  <string id="80748" soundid="119238">And don&apos;t start your foolishness that your master is the Glorious Strategist. You have no proof of that. He remains a dead man, and possibly a traitor.</string>
  <string id="80749" soundid="119239">Sometimes he refers to them in very unflattering terms. My father may refuse to speak of it for the good of the Empire.</string>
  <string id="80750" soundid="119240">I need your help and will aid you in return, but I don&apos;t need to hear your insults. You will see when all of this is done.</string>
  <string id="80751" soundid="119241">My father will be restored, Death&apos;s Hand will be punished, and you will take your master back to whatever mud hole you crawled from.</string>
  <string id="80752" soundid="119242">I think we are through talking. Onward with business. I will trouble you with nothing else from now on.</string>
  <string id="80772">Commoner</string>
  <string id="80782" soundid="126487">I&apos;m trapped here in this cave. It&apos;s so cold and dark... I just want to get outside. But this puddle&apos;s blocking me in, and there&apos;s no way across.</string>
  <string id="80784" soundid="126488">Thank you! Thank you so much! I just need to get across this puddle, but I can&apos;t touch the water because... because of how I died.</string>
  <string id="80798" soundid="126233">She is... special. Without her, I could not bridge the gap between your realm and my own. With her as my host, I can manifest myself here.</string>
  <string id="80799" soundid="126234">I have done nothing to her. She has helped give me form, and in return, I protect her.</string>
  <string id="80800" soundid="126235">No, she has no command of magic. She is my anchor in this world.</string>
  <string id="80801">Feel death&apos;s icy breath!</string>
  <string id="80802" soundid="126237">She is an anchor binding me to the mortal realm. I could not exist in your realm without her. I protect Wild Flower from danger, and she allows me to fulfill my duties.</string>
  <string id="80803" soundid="126238">We are separate, but in many ways we are also one. I would explain it better if I could, but as I said, it is difficult to understand.</string>
  <string id="80804" soundid="126239">I do not know. The will of heaven is kept from me. I know only what I am supposed to do.</string>
  <string id="80805" soundid="126240">I knew I was to guard the amulet and the gem. And I was to wait for their rightful owner. Now I know I must help you fulfill your destiny... whatever that may be.</string>
  <string id="80806" soundid="126241">To exist here, I needed an anchor. That is where Wild Flower has helped me. With the ability to influence and manipulate the material realm, I could carry out my task.
</string>
  <string id="80807" soundid="126242">But even with Wild Flower anchoring me to this world, I failed in my mission. Treachery took the amulet from me; now we must recover it to fulfill your destiny.</string>
  <string id="80808" soundid="126243">She... was already here. It was of benefit to both of us that she serve as my host. The will of the heavens dictate, and no mortal or demon can resist them.</string>
  <string id="80809" soundid="126244">I have given you the gem and fulfilled part of my mission, but the Lotus Assassins took the amulet from me. You will need them both to fulfill your destiny.</string>
  <string id="80810" soundid="126245">I was able to kill them all... all but the leader. While I was fighting his followers, he seized the amulet and fled. I could not follow.</string>
  <string id="80811" soundid="126246">My duty bound me here. I had to stay and wait for you. But now that you are here, I am free to leave this place and go with you to reclaim the amulet.</string>
  <string id="80812" soundid="126247">No. He has fled beyond my reach. But I am confident you will find him and reclaim the amulet. It was destined for you, not him.</string>
  <string id="80813" soundid="126248">I cannot follow you in the normal sense. I exist here, within Wild Flower, and can only manifest for short periods. She will accompany you, and through her, so will I.</string>
  <string id="80814">By the honor of my family!</string>
  <string id="80815">I must inflict pain.</string>
  <string id="80816">I tried to tell you, I am not a Lotus Assassin!</string>
  <string id="80817">My name is none of your business!</string>
  <string id="80820">I don&apos;t need another servant.</string>
  <string id="80821">Why shouldn&apos;t I just kill you, monster?</string>
  <string id="80823">I am honored to have you as my companion, Chai Ka.</string>
  <string id="80824">You better make yourself useful.</string>
  <string id="80825">Who was that little girl?</string>
  <string id="80826">So what happens now?</string>
  <string id="80828">What have you done to her, demon?!</string>
  <string id="80830">Is she a sorceress?</string>
  <string id="80832">I don&apos;t understand.</string>
  <string id="80833">I&apos;ll re-educate you.</string>
  <string id="80835">So what is my destiny?</string>
  <string id="80839">How did Wild Flower know to come here?</string>
  <string id="80840" soundid="177520">Most believe Sun Li fell at Dirge... a lie spread by the Emperor. A handful of us knew that he lived, and we also learned the terrible price of his rebellion.</string>
  <string id="80844">Do you know where the thief went?</string>
  <string id="80845">If you&apos;re coming with me, let&apos;s go.</string>
  <string id="80846">My art brings you low.</string>
  <string id="80853">It sounds too dangerous. Forget it.</string>
  <string id="80880">Immolated</string>
  <string id="80881">Commoner</string>
  <string id="80884">Commoner</string>
  <string id="80887">Commoner</string>
  <string id="80894">Drunk</string>
  <string id="80895" soundid="160244">Our men are no match for the ghosts in the forest. Perhaps you are.</string>
  <string id="80896">I appreciated your gift.</string>
  <string id="80898">Then why take the risk?</string>
  <string id="80902">I thank you for the gift and the risk you took giving it.</string>
  <string id="80906">It is a noble&apos;s duty to face hardship. It is the burden you must bear.</string>
  <string id="80908">The power of royalty is the power to command. And your father will not live forever.</string>
  <string id="80912">We cannot allow such a travesty to happen.</string>
  <string id="80915">Your flower would only wither under such harsh conditions.</string>
  <string id="80920">It doesn&apos;t really matter, since I will kill Death&apos;s Hand soon enough.</string>
  <string id="80922">Where did you find it, anyway?</string>
  <string id="80924">Your favor means nothing to me. You are useful so long as you help me.</string>
  <string id="80926">I question your motives. I do not trust you yet.</string>
  <string id="80928">Trinkets from spoiled princesses are useless to me.</string>
  <string id="80931">That annoys you, I can see. Tell me about it.</string>
  <string id="80933">Why didn&apos;t your father take the role for himself?</string>
  <string id="80937">That is your duty, but what about who you are? Tell me about yourself.</string>
  <string id="80939">The princess and her duties interest me less than the woman behind them.</string>
  <string id="80941">What do they say? That she is a hellion? She flies in the face of tradition?</string>
  <string id="80943">I&apos;m sure they say the princess has the authority to command, yet the wisdom to listen to advice.</string>
  <string id="80945">Don&apos;t worry. I&apos;ll keep you grounded.</string>
  <string id="80947">I&apos;ll be wherever you wish me to be.</string>
  <string id="80948">Your father is far from my mind right now.</string>
  <string id="80950">You misunderstand. He is far from my mind because I am enjoying your company.</string>
  <string id="80951">If need be, your father will fall to me.</string>
  <string id="80954">You don&apos;t need to care what other people think.</string>
  <string id="80957">No doubt they say the princess brooks no challenge and tolerates no incompetence.</string>
  <string id="80958">You are a strong woman who knows how to get what she wants.</string>
  <string id="80962">As cold as ice... and as flawless.</string>
  <string id="80964">You&apos;re much too harsh a person. It&apos;s unappealing.</string>
  <string id="80966">I&apos;m sure they cannot stop talking about the beauty of this princess.</string>
  <string id="80969">I think you are very beautiful.</string>
  <string id="80970">I think you will be very useful to me.</string>
  <string id="80974">What do they say? That she would do anything for those in need?</string>
  <string id="80977">I&apos;ll wager that they say she has an iron will and a heart of ice.</string>
  <string id="80979">You&apos;re right... you aren&apos;t that interesting.</string>
  <string id="80981">Are men the only ones with interests? Tell me about yourself.</string>
  <string id="80982">Typical of the elite. All that matters is how important *you* are.</string>
  <string id="80983">Who was Death&apos;s Hand before?</string>
  <string id="80985">What happened to Sun Kin?</string>
  <string id="80989">Then your father is weak and will get what he deserves.</string>
  <string id="80993">Leave me alone, damnable spirit!</string>
  <string id="80999">Tremor</string>
  <string id="81000">Dragon&apos;s Wrath</string>
  <string id="81001">Shrieking Fury</string>
  <string id="81002">Mirage</string>
  <string id="81003" soundid="183650">[Master Li sealed the doors behind you. You must uncover the mysteries of this cave before you may return to the school.]</string>
  <string id="81004" soundid="183651"></string>
  <string id="81019" soundid="160018">I wish you&apos;d let me cut the head off the Serpent, but I can respect you wanting to take care of things yourself.</string>
  <string id="81020">Consume Spirit</string>
  <string id="81021">Cloudburst</string>
  <string id="81022">Firestorm</string>
  <string id="81023">Reverse Tides</string>
  <string id="81024">Radiant Aura</string>
  <string id="81025">Spirit&apos;s Calling</string>
  <string id="81033" soundid="126467">You have... you have given us a chance. Please, let us out!</string>
  <string id="81036">Lotus Wizard</string>
  <string id="81039">Merchant</string>
  <string id="81052">I&apos;ve changed my mind. I&apos;ll just leave you here.</string>
  <string id="81152">Is there something troubling you? Your feelings are important to me.</string>
  <string id="81153">Is there anything you wanted to discuss before I get moving? Anything personal?</string>
  <string id="84177" soundid="122680"></string>
  <string id="84178" soundid="122681">*ahem* Your parentage is below average, and your ancestry is of questionable worth.</string>
  <string id="84179" soundid="122682">You dress yourself in the manner of a common laborer.</string>
  <string id="84180" soundid="122683">Nobody is paying any attention.</string>
  <string id="84181" soundid="122684">Keep trying. Just as I instructed!</string>
  <string id="84182" soundid="122685">Your physique seems exceptional. Clearly you are a peasant; a noble could afford sloth.</string>
  <string id="84183" soundid="122686">Your breath is like the wind of an ox. Your last meal was of suspect quality.</string>
  <string id="84184" soundid="122687">Your beliefs are superficial, and your culture is substandard.</string>
  <string id="84185" soundid="122688">You are right to demand an explanation. Forgive my servant. I instructed him to find someone not distracted by mere insults. Someone who would command respect.</string>
  <string id="84186" soundid="122689">Your demand for justification of his arguments was admirable. You are exactly what we need.</string>
  <string id="84187" soundid="122690">An Outlander strolled into the city several days ago and now sits, like a cormorant, taking what he wants from the river of our hospitality.</string>
  <string id="84188" soundid="122691">So far, he has escaped the notice of any higher officials. Perhaps he was mistaken for an actor in a troupe, but that will not last.</string>
  <string id="84189" soundid="122692">If he is reported, the Lotus Assassins will take notice. They&apos;ll want to know if he was harbored or his offense was encouraged. Guilt by association is enough for them.</string>
  <string id="84190" soundid="122693">He claims he crossed the Glass Sea, which would mean he is from the Mysterious East. I&apos;ve heard reports of minor trade with that region, but only on a small scale.</string>
  <string id="84191" soundid="122694">Please, my intent is noble. An Outlander arrived several days ago, and now we cannot get him to leave. He is consuming copious amounts of our food and wine.</string>
  <string id="84192" soundid="122695">Hold! You must forgive my servant. He was acting for me. I asked him to find someone not distracted by mere insults. Someone who would command respect.</string>
  <string id="84193" soundid="122696">Just a moment! You are Raging Dragon from the arena, are you not? Now I am *certain* we have the right person.</string>
  <string id="84194" soundid="122697">Wait! You are Silver Phoenix from the arena, are you not? Now I *know* you are perfect for the job I have in mind.</string>
  <string id="84195" soundid="122698">Are you... you are! You are Tiger Lifts the Mountain from the arena. Yes, you will be perfect!</string>
  <string id="84196" soundid="122699">I must say, your refusal to stand for it was admirable. I think you are exactly what we need.</string>
  <string id="84197" soundid="122700">I am ill-equipped to see my own faults, but I, like my fellow scholars, am adept at exploiting the weaknesses of others.</string>
  <string id="84198" soundid="122701">Scholars Heng and Zou are easily swayed with simple facts. Cite such details and they are certain to change their opinion either for or against.</string>
  <string id="84199" soundid="122702">It is not so much the subject but the tactic that triggers reaction. Each judge will respond only to argument styles they favor.</string>
  <string id="84200" soundid="122703">If a judge likes fact, use it once and he will join your side. Use it again and he will switch back, just to further debate. Other arguments may not interest him at all.</string>
  <string id="84201" soundid="122704"></string>
  <string id="84202" soundid="122705"></string>
  <string id="84203" soundid="122706">(snicker)</string>
  <string id="84204" soundid="122707">Do you disagree? I have never seen such a cunning linguist.</string>
  <string id="84205" soundid="122708">Ha!</string>
  <string id="84206" soundid="122709">It is money well spent; compensation because my own diction came up short.</string>
  <string id="84207" soundid="122710">Baaahahaha!</string>
  <string id="84208" soundid="122711">[Failure] Your argument is compelling, but your failure to defeat the Outlander in the debate makes me reluctant. </string>
  <string id="84209" soundid="122712">Here, a few more coins, but there will be no more. If attention is brought to this now, you will suffer as much as the rest of us.</string>
  <string id="84210" soundid="122713">Our business is concluded. Thank you once again. Now, goodbye.</string>
  <string id="84211" soundid="122714">I did not expect this from someone who performed so well in the debate. Clearly the Outlander&apos;s boorish nature has rubbed off on you.</string>
  <string id="84212" soundid="122715">Your service is appreciated. If only there were more like you in the Empire.</string>
  <string id="84213" soundid="122716">Yes, we were glad to have you, despite the half-victory.</string>
  <string id="84214" soundid="122717">Quiet rumblings, of course. We are clearly the more proficient fighters. Please, accept this token amount of silver for your service.</string>
  <string id="84215" soundid="122718"></string>
  <string id="84216" soundid="122719">If my ministry had more members we could have put up a stiffer resistance.</string>
  <string id="84217" soundid="122720">(snort) Heh.</string>
  <string id="84218" soundid="122721">It is shameful how our members shrank from the Outlander&apos;s chilling arguments.</string>
  <string id="84219" soundid="122722">Heh.</string>
  <string id="84220" soundid="122723">Rarely have I been so envious of someone&apos;s oral skills. Your skillful tongue had the crowd gushing praise.</string>
  <string id="84221" soundid="122724">Pft. Heehee.</string>
  <string id="84222" soundid="122725">I was prepared to help, but I left my part out because I knew you would handle everything.</string>
  <string id="84223" soundid="122726">Oh, hehe.</string>
  <string id="84224" soundid="122727">If Sir Roderick pushes his way back into my garden, he&apos;ll find such a cold reception that he&apos;ll never come again.</string>
  <string id="84225" soundid="122728">[snicker] Aiya.</string>
  <string id="84226" soundid="122729">Someday I&apos;ll invite you to my wife&apos;s tavern by the stone river marker. The best carn dock teas in the city.</string>
  <string id="84227" soundid="122730">Uh, heh. Hmm.</string>
  <string id="84228" soundid="122731">A well defined rebuttal is a beautiful thing. I polled the other scholars and they agree.</string>
  <string id="84229" soundid="122732">Pfft! Ha!</string>
  <string id="84230" soundid="122733"></string>
  <string id="84231" soundid="122734">It has been a great honor having your assistance. The elite of the Scholars&apos; Garden are in your debt.</string>
  <string id="84232" soundid="122735">Your defense of our way of life was masterful. An excellent example of the craft of debating.</string>
  <string id="84233" soundid="122736">Many of our debates are decided by form over content. I suppose that is why the subtleties of being a scholar are lost on so many.</string>
  <string id="84234" soundid="122737">Perhaps I will organize a series of debates in your honor. I just have to find a way of doing so without mentioning the Outlander.</string>
  <string id="84235" soundid="122738"></string>
  <string id="84236" soundid="122739">I must confess, when you lost the debate, it only increased my desire to see the Outlander defeated in battle.</string>
  <string id="84237" soundid="122740">It is difficult to defeat a well-entrenched enemy on two fronts. I had hopes you would do better.</string>
  <string id="84238" soundid="122741">Many of the Scholars were cheering you. Anger over the debate certainly inspired their... baser instincts.</string>
  <string id="84239" soundid="122742">I may have heard one or two voices against you during your fight. Perhaps they thought winning the fight only secured the Outlander&apos;s view of us as savages.</string>
  <string id="84245">What are you doing? Why attempt to insult me?</string>
  <string id="84246">I asked for an explanation. Justify yourself or I will take offense.</string>
  <string id="84247">There is no point to your insults. Defend your claims, or cease this instant!</string>
  <string id="84249">Explain yourself.</string>
  <string id="84252">Where did this man come from?</string>
  <string id="84254">If you were behind this, then I owe *you* a beating!</string>
  <string id="84256">That&apos;s it. I will put an end to your pointless heckling!</string>
  <string id="84258">I am warning you. I demand respect!</string>
  <string id="84259">What is going on here? Answer me!</string>
  <string id="84286">Big Tian</string>
  <string id="84292">Guard</string>
  <string id="84298" soundid="122849">[Success] Very well, but I will hear no more of this from now on. You risk becoming as much a problem as the man you coarsely defeated.</string>
  <string id="84299" soundid="122850">[Failure] I... am sorry, but as skillful as you are, I feel my offer was fair. </string>
  <string id="84300" soundid="122851"></string>
  <string id="84301" soundid="122852"></string>
  <string id="84302" soundid="122853"></string>
  <string id="84303" soundid="122854"></string>
  <string id="84304" soundid="122855">The Outlander manhandled every defense we erected, but you beat him off wonderfully.</string>
  <string id="84313">Zeng Sai</string>
  <string id="84319">Thug</string>
  <string id="84322">Ogre</string>
  <string id="84327">You must enter a name.</string>
  <string id="84337" soundid="122902">&quot;The storms of misfortune always pass, and the rains of sorrow bring forth a field of opportunity.&quot; Words to live by, I say.</string>
  <string id="84339" soundid="122904">You&apos;re not the only one. All over town people keep saying to me, &quot;Lishun, why are you so happy? Can&apos;t you see how bad things are?&quot; But it&apos;s just a matter of perspective.</string>
  <string id="84340" soundid="122905">Things will get better. They always do. It&apos;s like my father used to say: The greater the problem, the greater the solution. I&apos;m sure it will all work out.</string>
  <string id="84341" soundid="122906">You came to the right place, then. I won&apos;t give you the doom and gloom others will. Sure, we&apos;ve got problems, but Tien&apos;s Landing is still the best village in the district!</string>
  <string id="84342" soundid="122907">Now, now. &quot;Drunk&quot; is such a harsh word. Perhaps he ingests more wine than most of us, but can you blame him?</string>
  <string id="84343" soundid="122908">This region is known for its remarkable wines; they say a single drop is like the sweet tears of a goddess. It&apos;s a wonder we don&apos;t all drink as much as he does.</string>
  <string id="84344" soundid="122909">Denial? Preposterous. Sure, half the people have moved away, and those who stayed have mostly given up hope. And the entire town is running out of food and silver.</string>
  <string id="84345" soundid="122910">But does my optimism mean I&apos;m in denial? Of course not! I mean, none of the buildings are on fire, right? See? Something good, just like that. Right off the top of my head.</string>
  <string id="84346" soundid="122911">I admit that some see our Imperial Minister Sheng as... well... not entirely competent or capable of dealing with our problems. But somehow things will work out. They always do.</string>
  <string id="84347" soundid="122912">Of course, of course. I will gladly converse on any number of topics. It&apos;s a fine way to pass the time on such a beautiful day!</string>
  <string id="84348" soundid="122913">Before he was Emperor, before there even was an Empire, Sagacious Tien was a young man fond of wandering the countryside. One day he stopped, weary from his travels.</string>
  <string id="84349" soundid="122914">He lay down to rest beneath the shade of a cool tree and had a marvelous dream of a shining empire. This dream drove him to create the Jade Empire as we know it.</string>
  <string id="84350" soundid="122915">Yes, but there *used* to be. Many centuries ago. All evidence of it may be gone now, but just knowing it was here once is all the proof I need.</string>
  <string id="84351" soundid="122916">Other villages try to claim the Emperor had his dream while crossing their lands, but I know the truth. Tien&apos;s Landing--my home town--is the birthplace of the Empire.</string>
  <string id="84352" soundid="122917">Most of the merchants, and our glorious Minister Sheng, gather in the town square, the highest point in the village. Just follow any path that leads up until you reach it.</string>
  <string id="84354">I want to talk about something else.</string>
  <string id="84357">But there is no castle.</string>
  <string id="84362">Glad to see you&apos;re keeping your spirits up.</string>
  <string id="84364">You mean he&apos;s a drunk.</string>
  <string id="84366">I think you&apos;re in denial.</string>
  <string id="84369">He seemed like a pathetic drunk to me.</string>
  <string id="84374" soundid="123248">The artifact is supposed to be in the room at the end of the tomb. Once you&apos;re there, I&apos;ll catch up with you.</string>
  <string id="84375" soundid="123249">There are still ghosts. I can&apos;t get the artifact unless the ghosts are gone.</string>
  <string id="84376" soundid="123250">All right. I&apos;ll wait here until you&apos;ve cleared them all. Good luck.</string>
  <string id="84377" soundid="123251">I... see. Well, please don&apos;t be too long. I need to get that artifact back to Purveyor Shouji soon.</string>
  <string id="84378" soundid="123252">That&apos;s it. I&apos;ve got it. Now let&apos;s get out of here before... what&apos;s that? Did you hear that?</string>
  <string id="84379" soundid="123253">Getting out of here is going to be harder than getting in, I think.</string>
  <string id="84380" soundid="123254">I&apos;m glad you&apos;re looking forward to this. I&apos;m just going to hide in here until it&apos;s all over.</string>
  <string id="84381" soundid="123255">That doesn&apos;t sound like nothing.</string>
  <string id="84382" soundid="123256">I can&apos;t believe we made it out of there alive. You&apos;re an amazing fighter.</string>
  <string id="84383" soundid="123257">I wonder why Purveyor Shouji wants this bowl so badly. It looks so... ordinary, except for maybe this writing.</string>
  <string id="84384" soundid="123258">It doesn&apos;t make any sense. &quot;Conductor, cog, and a bit of iron. Don&apos;t play with the tiger.&quot; Whatever that means.</string>
  <string id="84385" soundid="123259">Huh. Well I&apos;m glad it was useful to you.</string>
  <string id="84386" soundid="123260">I can&apos;t imagine how it could be interesting, but I&apos;m glad you think so.</string>
  <string id="84387" soundid="123261">I... I told you before that I have nothing of value to give you. You can have everything in the tomb.</string>
  <string id="84388" soundid="123262">Thank you again for helping me. Purveyor Shouji is waiting, so I should be going. Goodbye.</string>
  <string id="84389" soundid="123263">What? No! Purveyor Shouji would sell my mom to the slave traders if I give it to you. I have to go now; Shouji is waiting.</string>
  <string id="84390" soundid="123264">Hello again. Purveyor Shouji was so happy to see the artifact that he released me and my mom from our debts. Thank you again for all your help.</string>
  <string id="84391" soundid="123265">Thanks again for all your help. My mom and I are very grateful for all you&apos;ve done.</string>
  <string id="84392" soundid="151797">Trust what you see. Voices can come from anywhere.</string>
  <string id="84393" soundid="151798">She will coerce and belittle. Trust your desire.</string>
  <string id="84394" soundid="123268">I... don&apos;t have anything to give you. My mom and I are very poor, or we wouldn&apos;t be working for Purveyor Shouji.</string>
  <string id="84395" soundid="123269">I overheard Shouji say the artifact was in an old emperor&apos;s tomb. I bet there&apos;s a lot of stuff in there you could take... once I get us inside.</string>
  <string id="84396" soundid="123270">I don&apos;t care about anything but the artifact. Anything else is yours.</string>
  <string id="84397" soundid="123271">I... see. Well, goodbye then.</string>
  <string id="84399">That&apos;s not enough. Forget it.</string>
  <string id="84400">That sounds like a fair deal. Okay, I&apos;ll help you.</string>
  <string id="84401" soundid="151799">Ya Zhen: She is strong here... but I don&apos;t think she means to interfere. Something about... guidance. You will know more inside.</string>
  <string id="84402">I&apos;ve decided to help you after all.</string>
  <string id="84403">Why was that man bothering you before?</string>
  <string id="84406">Stay here until I&apos;ve cleared the ghosts.</string>
  <string id="84408">Don&apos;t worry. I&apos;ll get rid of the ghosts in no time.</string>
  <string id="84409">I&apos;m not worried. I&apos;ve fought tougher things than ghosts.</string>
  <string id="84411">Sorry, I must have got turned around.</string>
  <string id="84412">I must go, but I&apos;ll return shortly.</string>
  <string id="84413">I have to go.</string>
  <string id="84414">Sounds like trouble.</string>
  <string id="84415">A chance for more fighting, if I&apos;m lucky!</string>
  <string id="84416">It&apos;s probably nothing.</string>
  <string id="84419">That might be a configuration I&apos;m looking for.</string>
  <string id="84421">Hmm, interesting.</string>
  <string id="84423">Well, you&apos;ve got your artifact. What do I get?</string>
  <string id="84424">All right. Get going then.</string>
  <string id="84425">Give me the artifact.</string>
  <string id="84427" soundid="151800">Ya Zhen: Urgh... it may not matter who walks through the door. I sense a great power within, and her will cannot be ignored.</string>
  <string id="84428">I&apos;ll go there immediately.</string>
  <string id="84429">I can do it, but it&apos;ll cost you.</string>
  <string id="84449">Boathouse Door</string>
  <string id="84467">Fine. Here&apos;s the evidence. Songtao is guilty after all.</string>
  <string id="84468">Yes, Songtao is obviously guilty.</string>
  <string id="84470">Yes, I want silver and goods!</string>
  <string id="84471">Of course. I don&apos;t work for free!</string>
  <string id="84472" soundid="123435">Is there anything else I can do for you today, my friend?</string>
  <string id="84473">Yes, show me what you&apos;ve got for sale.</string>
  <string id="84474">No thanks. I must be going.</string>
  <string id="84475">Show me your items again.</string>
  <string id="84486" soundid="135868">This region is known as the Great Southern Forest, as I said. The forest stretches for miles to the north, east, and west of here.</string>
  <string id="84487" soundid="135869">This specific area is known as the Pilgrim&apos;s Path. These hills house several small shrines, and a large temple lies at the top of the path that begins with these stairs.</string>
  <string id="84488" soundid="135870">As it stands, this is the only part of the forest that&apos;s even vaguely passable. Coming from the Imperial City, I had no choice but to take a flyer to Tien&apos;s Landing.</string>
  <string id="84490">Gao&apos;s Mercenary</string>
  <string id="84493" soundid="135871">Things have worsened in the past few months, which is roughly the time since the trees of the forest started to look sickly.</string>
  <string id="84494" soundid="135872">Before I flew here from the Imperial City, I heard rumors of more and more ghosts in the outer provinces, but I foolishly thought them exaggeration.</string>
  <string id="84495" soundid="135873">The forest is polluted with ghosts of all types, and they are only growing in number. As you must know, ghosts can only be dispersed, never destroyed completely.</string>
  <string id="84496" soundid="135874">Of the vast expanse of this forest, this area--the Pilgrim&apos;s Path, as it&apos;s called--is the safest.</string>
  <string id="84497" soundid="135875">I hoped that coming here might help me learn why the forest is as it is, but that seems a lost cause.</string>
  <string id="84498" soundid="135876">If things don&apos;t improve soon, I shall have to abandon this camp and fly back to the Imperial City a failure. That would be unfortunate.</string>
  <string id="84541">Local Thug</string>
  <string id="84551" soundid="123520">Hold on a sec. We got company.</string>
  <string id="84552" soundid="123521">You&apos;re a little too interested in our business, friend. Looks like we gotta teach you to back off when Ai Ling&apos;s boys are working.</string>
  <string id="84553" soundid="123522">Yes, you&apos;re right, of course. I suppose I can&apos;t fault Lan for being worried about me. I&apos;ve taken some serious beatings lately.</string>
  <string id="84554" soundid="123523">Sorry, sorry. Forgive me, honorable stranger. I&apos;m not normally so... well, I&apos;m a bit of a wreck right now. I&apos;ve taken some pretty bad beatings these past few days.</string>
  <string id="84555" soundid="123524">She&apos;s obviously crazy. I&apos;ve done nothing to her. We haven&apos;t even spoken in years! If I go to her hideout to talk to her, I&apos;m afraid I&apos;ll never come out.</string>
  <string id="84556" soundid="123525">At least the beatings on the street are out in public. They won&apos;t kill me in front of witnesses. Well, not on purpose, anyway.</string>
  <string id="84557" soundid="123526">No. Lan&apos;s very emotional; I didn&apos;t want her to get upset. At first, I didn&apos;t tell her anything at all. But I couldn&apos;t hide my bruises forever, so I told her about the beatings.</string>
  <string id="84558" soundid="123527">But even then, I didn&apos;t mention Ai Ling. It&apos;s bad enough what&apos;s happening to me. I was afraid if Lan became more involved, Ai Ling might hurt her, too.</string>
  <string id="84559" soundid="123528">I&apos;m being completely honest, I swear! I... I know how this looks. You must think I&apos;ve done something to deserve this. But I have no idea why Ai Ling is after me!</string>
  <string id="84560" soundid="123529">I... I understand. You must have more important things to do than help out a simple baker with his problems. But I have nowhere else to turn.</string>
  <string id="84561" soundid="123530">Please, if you get a chance, go speak with Ai Ling in the boathouse. See if you can get her to leave me alone. Lan and I just want to live our lives in peace.</string>
  <string id="84562">I don&apos;t have time for this.</string>
  <string id="84565">Lan figured you couldn&apos;t handle things on your own.</string>
  <string id="84568">Dawn Star</string>
  <string id="84569">Actually, Lan sent me to help you.</string>
  <string id="84570">She&apos;s just worried about you.</string>
  <string id="84573">So why did those thugs attack you?</string>
  <string id="84575">Have you told any of this to Lan?</string>
  <string id="84577">I get the feeling you&apos;re not telling me something.</string>
  <string id="84626">Never mind. Goodbye.</string>
  <string id="84627" soundid="129033">Now look what you&apos;ve made me do! I&apos;ve collapsed the way out! When I catch you, woman, you will be sorry!</string>
  <string id="84628" soundid="129034">It&apos;s always someone else&apos;s fault, isn&apos;t it, Gao! This is your mess! I didn&apos;t make you kidnap me!</string>
  <string id="84650" soundid="129037">Your friend is doing a good job of frustrating Gao into carelessness. That will work in your favor. But it also means we have to follow them by a different route.</string>
  <string id="84666" soundid="129038">Be careful, that means fresh enemies for us. These caves harbor strange creatures.</string>
  <string id="84764">So you do know each other!</string>
  <string id="84823" soundid="137215">Well, this is certainly foreboding. You really have to work to get this level of menace into a building.</string>
  <string id="84854" soundid="129069">Yes, I&apos;m Spear Catches Leaf, Lord Yun&apos;s lead hunter. I learned a ritual from Lord Yun&apos;s father, and I had hoped to use it to ask the aid of the Forest Shadow.</string>
  <string id="84855" soundid="182898">He is corrupting its nature. Fortunately, you now see that, as a Spirit Monk, essence gems will serve you without it. The amulet is a pathway, not a source of power.</string>
  <string id="84857" soundid="129072">Cannibals? Humans twisted inside by consuming others&apos; flesh? Why would you ask that?</string>
  <string id="84858" soundid="129073">It&apos;s all the more pressing that you try to reach her, then! Cannibals? What could cause men to warp so? I&apos;d almost rather not know.</string>
  <string id="84860" soundid="129074">It is true that spirits can grow fickle. Some become vindictive, punishing men for imagined crimes. The Forest Shadow, though, has been constant for centuries.</string>
  <string id="84873" soundid="129076">Not that I can think of, but I haven&apos;t yet visited the Pilgrim&apos;s Rest. Could they have incurred her wrath? Perhaps you should ask them.</string>
  <string id="84877" soundid="132990">[Spirits go mad if denied passage to the underworld. They are strong, but you can fight them. You can&apos;t kill the dead, but in defeat they are disrupted and can&apos;t reform for a time.]</string>
  <string id="84879">Debating Ground</string>
  <string id="84880" soundid="129081">I&apos;ve set the fires, and the furnaces are ready, but one of the key crystals is missing. Without it, we can&apos;t even see what these furnaces are supposed to do.</string>
  <string id="84899" soundid="129083">I examined the area when I realized that the crystal was gone, and I stumbled across some strange tracks that lead in the direction of the inn.</string>
  <string id="84909" soundid="129085">I don&apos;t know. They looked like bare human feet, but the tracks were closely spaced and bore a strange gait. As if a child made them... A deformed child.</string>
  <string id="84947" soundid="124451">But the fact is, Bei promised to marry me long before that seamstress batted her brazen little eyes at him.</string>
  <string id="84948" soundid="124452">He didn&apos;t even have the decency to tell me himself. Even now he&apos;d rather get beaten up every day than face me... or he sends someone in his place, like you.</string>
  <string id="84949" soundid="124453">I get it. I&apos;m just a thug, right? But Bei promised to marry me, whether he admits it or not. And now he won&apos;t even come here and face me himself. That should tell you something.</string>
  <string id="84950" soundid="124454">I hope things work out for Bei and Lan. After everything I put them through, they deserve it. I don&apos;t know what came over me.</string>
  <string id="84951" soundid="124455">She said there was something I need to know, Bei. What&apos;s going on? What is she talking about?</string>
  <string id="84952" soundid="124456">I was crying, so you took my hand and said, &quot;I think you&apos;re pretty, Ai Ling. And someday, when we&apos;re grown up, I&apos;ll marry you.&quot;</string>
  <string id="84953" soundid="124457">It meant something to me, Bei! You were the only boy who didn&apos;t tease me, the only one I liked. You promised to marry me, and you&apos;re going to keep that promise!</string>
  <string id="84954" soundid="124458">It&apos;s okay, Ai Ling. I hope... I hope things work out for you.</string>
  <string id="84955" soundid="124459">Come on, Bei. Let&apos;s go.</string>
  <string id="84956" soundid="124460">If I had more, I would gladly give it to you. But my family isn&apos;t rich; this dowry is all I have. Please, take it with my thanks.</string>
  <string id="84957" soundid="124461">You can&apos;t be serious. Ai Ling would kill her!</string>
  <string id="84966" soundid="129088">Make your way there. I will stay behind to tend the furnaces. If you need more information, supplies, or even training, you know where to find me.</string>
  <string id="84984" soundid="129090">It&apos;s good to see you again. Is there anything I can do for you?</string>
  <string id="84985" soundid="129091">Greetings, my friend. Have you had any luck finding the crystal?</string>
  <string id="84986">That&apos;s because he&apos;s afraid of you.</string>
  <string id="84987">You can&apos;t force him to marry you.</string>
  <string id="84988">I guess he&apos;s getting what he deserves.</string>
  <string id="84989">I think you&apos;re lying about Bei proposing.</string>
  <string id="84991">Seems like you&apos;re being unreasonable, Ai Ling.</string>
  <string id="84993">Glad to be of service.</string>
  <string id="84997" soundid="196171"></string>
  <string id="84998">That&apos;s it? I was hoping for more.</string>
  <string id="85010" soundid="129092">You have it? Excellent! I should return and report this to Lord Yun. He will want to hear this news.</string>
  <string id="85012" soundid="129094">I am a hunter, not a warrior. My gifts lie in moving swiftly, silently, and alone. The news must be brought to Lord Yun and it is my duty to bring it.</string>
  <string id="85015" soundid="129097">The crystal fits into the central pedestal atop these steps, unlocking the lens arms in the lower furnaces so they can direct light to the remaining furnaces. </string>
  <string id="85017">Was that a key you put in my pack?</string>
  <string id="85037" soundid="129103">Hey! I&apos;m not some cheap bottle of wine to be passed around! Damn it, even wine shouldn&apos;t be passed, in my opinion.</string>
  <string id="85038" soundid="129104">Lord Yun paid you very well to safeguard his men, and now you&apos;re being paid to safeguard his new agent. Surely you don&apos;t mean to go back on your word?</string>
  <string id="85039" soundid="129105">My word isn&apos;t worth a damn thing. That said, I&apos;m still reeling from actually losing to anyone short of an army.</string>
  <string id="85040">Fine, hand it over.</string>
  <string id="85059" soundid="129106">My only rules are; don&apos;t touch my axes, don&apos;t touch my wine, and don&apos;t get between me and my enemies. If you can live with that, we&apos;ll get along just fine.</string>
  <string id="85060" soundid="129107">Well, you and me and Little Miss Magenta here. Maybe she can distract our foes, flash a little leg.</string>
  <string id="85061" soundid="129108">Would you like to see the damage these legs can inflict firsthand?</string>
  <string id="85062" soundid="129109">Well... you, me, and the fellow with the dark hands and dark looks.</string>
  <string id="85063" soundid="129110">I already tire of this fool. Keep him away from me if you want him to stay alive.</string>
  <string id="85064" soundid="129111">Well... you, me, and the pretty boy. You must be wealthy to have your own eunuch.</string>
  <string id="85065" soundid="129112">Ha! You&apos;re going to fit right in.  You must like to dice, correct?</string>
  <string id="85066" soundid="129113">Sure! Can&apos;t say as I&apos;m very good at it, I can never remember the rules....</string>
  <string id="85067" soundid="129114">Well... you, me, and the kid. I hope she&apos;s well trained.</string>
  <string id="85068" soundid="129115">You smell funny.</string>
  <string id="85069" soundid="129116">Whoa... almost didn&apos;t see the little guy. Is he with you, too?</string>
  <string id="85070" soundid="129117">Yep, just you and me, bashing aside anything that gets in our way.</string>
  <string id="85071" soundid="129118">Be safe. The spirits willing, I will reach Lord Yun&apos;s camp quickly. If you need more supplies or training, that is where I will be.</string>
  <string id="85072" soundid="129119">Let&apos;s go find something and make its day a lot worse.</string>
  <string id="85073" soundid="129120">Hey, careful, now. I&apos;m being paid to look after you, and not doing that would break the code.</string>
  <string id="85074" soundid="129121">To be fair, I don&apos;t remember what the code says, but I&apos;m standing by it, so you&apos;re stuck with me.</string>
  <string id="85075" soundid="129122">You got it. But you can&apos;t actually *use* my axes. Just so we&apos;re clear, I&apos;m the only one who touches the axes.</string>
  <string id="85076" soundid="129123">Right. If I&apos;m lucky, something will try to jump me on the way there. Though I bet you&apos;ve ruined the fun by clearing a path for me already. Maybe I&apos;ll take the long way.</string>
  <string id="85077" soundid="129124">Have a look and tell me what you need. I&apos;m collecting the silver to honor the men we lost to these accursed ghosts.</string>
  <string id="85078" soundid="129125">I have a small stock of supplies, and I can also train you to be more precise and focused in battle. My name is well earned, some tell me.</string>
  <string id="85082">Door</string>
  <string id="85084">Thug</string>
  <string id="85087" soundid="124073">They took it pretty hard. Even after all the beatings I gave them over the years, they still aren&apos;t used to losing to a girl. Maybe the humiliation will be good for them.</string>
  <string id="85088" soundid="124074">You&apos;d think after all the beatings I gave them over the years they&apos;d be used to losing, but they&apos;re still taking it pretty hard. Maybe the humiliation will be good for them.</string>
  <string id="85089" soundid="124075">I know what you&apos;re thinking. Why would Bei want to marry someone like me?</string>
  <string id="85090" soundid="124076">No, I bet he didn&apos;t. Wouldn&apos;t want to go around telling people how he left me high and dry, would he?</string>
  <string id="85091" soundid="124077">I may not be a delicate little flower like Lan, but I don&apos;t want to run this gang forever. Someday I want a husband. Maybe a little house. Kids, too.</string>
  <string id="85093">He promised to marry you?</string>
  <string id="85094">I don&apos;t believe you.</string>
  <string id="85096">Bei never said anything about this.</string>
  <string id="85100" soundid="129131">The Great Southern Forest is vast, but we&apos;re within a day&apos;s journey of Tien&apos;s Landing. If you&apos;re weary, however, the Pilgrim&apos;s Rest Inn lies at the top of this hill.</string>
  <string id="85105" soundid="129136">Lord Yun&apos;s family has maintained it for centuries, although Lord Yun seems to care little for it. It is as if he is embarrased by it somehow.</string>
  <string id="85108" soundid="129139">To tell the truth, I really can&apos;t say why he is the way he is. Might be something to do with the Forest Shadow. You could always ask him.</string>
  <string id="85109" soundid="129140">We hunters think differently of the two Ways: the Open Palm and the Closed Fist. A hunter&apos;s life must be one of balance if one wishes to excel.</string>
  <string id="85119" soundid="129150">To kill without purpose is evil. But if you hunt to feed and clothe your family, you act with intent. The hunter uses discord to achieve harmony; all is in balance.</string>
  <string id="85125" soundid="129156">Balance is itself a choice. For a hunter it is vital. We must be in harmony with nature if we wish to stalk our prey, yet rely on discord to make the kill.</string>
  <string id="85127" soundid="129158">What else did you need?</string>
  <string id="85128" soundid="129159">Lord Yun is satisfied with what you have done. I can only hope the forest will recover.</string>
  <string id="85129" soundid="129160">Thank you again for all you have done.</string>
  <string id="85130" soundid="129161">Step safely. The ghosts grow more aggressive by the hour.</string>
  <string id="85131" soundid="137217">I suppose an emperor deserves a tomb like this if anyone does, but I&apos;d prefer a simple memorial.</string>
  <string id="85132" soundid="182899">Perhaps, but Sun Hai did not have your amulet. Fortunately, you now see that, as a Spirit Monk, essence gems will serve you without it. It is a pathway, not a source of power.</string>
  <string id="85133" soundid="137219">This neglect is infuriating. This is the center of the Empire, yet they let it rot from the inside out.</string>
  <string id="85134" soundid="137220">Is this even... possible?</string>
  <string id="85135" soundid="137221">Don&apos;t underestimate him. Your master is just toying with you.</string>
  <string id="85142">How would she feel about cannibals?</string>
  <string id="85143">The Pilgrim&apos;s Rest was full of them. I have eliminated some, but there are more.</string>
  <string id="85145">You&apos;d rather not know.</string>
  <string id="85146">Couldn&apos;t this all be her fault?</string>
  <string id="85148">Would there be a reason she would attack someone from the inn?</string>
  <string id="85149">That&apos;s all I need to know about the attack.</string>
  <string id="85151">This&apos;ll be the end!</string>
  <string id="85154">The Treasury</string>
  <string id="85155">Dirge Fountain</string>
  <string id="85156">I have the crystal here.</string>
  <string id="85157">If you had thought to go ask at the inn, you&apos;d already have your crystal.</string>
  <string id="85158">Do you have any idea where the crystal might be?</string>
  <string id="85159">You&apos;ve made yourself useful setting up the furnaces.</string>
  <string id="85160">Diseased</string>
  <string id="85161">What was strange about them?</string>
  <string id="85162">Some sort of animal took the crystal?</string>
  <string id="85165">Drain the Chi of the target.</string>
  <string id="85166">I met a man from the inn on my way up here.</string>
  <string id="85170">I have the missing crystal here.</string>
  <string id="85172">It&apos;s safest if you get out of here, I agree.</string>
  <string id="85173">You&apos;re running like a coward?</string>
  <string id="85176">What needs to be done for this ritual?</string>
  <string id="85182">That&apos;s all I need to know, I&apos;ll see what can be done.</string>
  <string id="85184">I&apos;m sure I can find a use for him.</string>
  <string id="85185">So long as he does what he&apos;s told, he could prove useful.</string>
  <string id="85186">He&apos;s a buffoon. Take him with you.</string>
  <string id="85189">Stick with me and you&apos;ll see more than that.</string>
  <string id="85203">Forget it. I honestly have no need of your services.</string>
  <string id="85205">Come with me now. I could use your axes.</string>
  <string id="85207">Make your way to Tien&apos;s Landing, and look for my other followers.</string>
  <string id="85210">What supplies and training do you have available?</string>
</tlk>