<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<tlk language="0">
  <string id="109166" soundid="166381">Well... everywhere but here, it seems. Woe is to Minister Sheng that the only place available was this filthy dock house.</string>
  <string id="109167" soundid="166382">You were not alone in that assumption! It seems it was recently procured and has not been &quot;modified&quot; for Ministry use yet.</string>
  <string id="109168" soundid="166383">At least there&apos;s no drunken sailors attempting to set fire to this building. At least, not yet.</string>
  <string id="109169" soundid="166384">Minister Sheng does not whine! He simply points out the absurdity of his existence.</string>
  <string id="109170" soundid="166385">Remember that the Ministry of Harmony controls executions and taxations. I shudder to think which landed them ownership of this &quot;fine&quot; establishment. Ah well.</string>
  <string id="109171">I thought this was supposed to be the Ministry Hostel?</string>
  <string id="109173">I would have thought you&apos;d be used to this kind of place after Tien&apos;s Landing.</string>
  <string id="109175">You&apos;re still whining. Some things never change.</string>
  <string id="109178" soundid="166393">If your lies are true, then Shen, that murdering monster, would have buried him here. All my family is here. But... I don&apos;t know these names! I don&apos;t know my baby&apos;s name!</string>
  <string id="109180" soundid="166395">Alas, fate had a crueler path in mind for me. Let that be a lesson for you; always read the fine print, or you may end up with more than you bargained for!</string>
  <string id="109181" soundid="166396">As to why I became a bun master... well, it&apos;s a hard, thankless job that keeps me very, very busy. Very busy.</string>
  <string id="109182" soundid="166397">No... you have saved my life. You deserve to hear the terrible, awful truth. As I said, there were other problems.</string>
  <string id="109183" soundid="166398">No! My wife has only *happened* to one man... me! Besides, I wasn&apos;t the source of all of our problems.</string>
  <string id="109184" soundid="166399">There&apos;s really not much more to tell I&apos;m afraid.</string>
  <string id="109185" soundid="166400">Never. Though no one can accuse me of not trying.</string>
  <string id="109186">I guess you really owed him after that.</string>
  <string id="109187">Yes, there&apos;s always a catch isn&apos;t there?</string>
  <string id="109191">What other problems did you have?</string>
  <string id="109192">Don&apos;t worry Hou, it happens to lots of men.</string>
  <string id="109195">So... you never had a child?</string>
  <string id="109197">You&apos;re a wild man, Hou!</string>
  <string id="109198">Ready the flyer. I want to go somewhere.</string>
  <string id="109199">What did you do?</string>
  <string id="109200">Whole months? That&apos;s impressive.</string>
  <string id="109201" soundid="166420">You have our thanks. Those with the hunger had to die.</string>
  <string id="109202" soundid="166421">We are the victims of this place. Not all, but some. Others have slipped away.</string>
  <string id="109203" soundid="166422">We would not attack you, living one. You are a savior.</string>
  <string id="109204" soundid="166423">We stay here only because we have nowhere else to go. We thought the Mother&apos;s calls were silencing the voice we yearn to hear, but we were wrong.</string>
  <string id="109205" soundid="166424">Yes! That is her name.</string>
  <string id="109206" soundid="166425">You cannot destroy the dead, only disperse us for some time.</string>
  <string id="109207" soundid="166426">Without the Water Dragon, we have nowhere to go, but there is still something....</string>
  <string id="109208" soundid="166427">Yes! Something we can do! Take this as a token of our thanks. Farewell, peace-bringer.</string>
  <string id="109209">This is where you fall!</string>
  <string id="109213">Why are you spirits here?</string>
  <string id="109214">Who are you?</string>
  <string id="109216">If you think to attack me, I&apos;ll disperse you like the others.</string>
  <string id="109218">The Water Dragon! You wanted her to guide you to the underworld.</string>
  <string id="109220">That&apos;s pathetic. I should destroy you before you go mad.</string>
  <string id="109227" soundid="166446"></string>
  <string id="109228" soundid="166447"></string>
  <string id="109229" soundid="166448"></string>
  <string id="109230" soundid="166449"></string>
  <string id="109233" soundid="166452"></string>
  <string id="109234" soundid="166453"></string>
  <string id="109235" soundid="166454"></string>
  <string id="109236" soundid="166455"></string>
  <string id="109237" soundid="166456">I still can&apos;t believe it&apos;s that easy to become a Lotus Assassin. If I had known sooner I would have joined their ranks as soon as possible.</string>
  <string id="109238" soundid="166457">It would be brutal work, with little reward, and there&apos;s a good chance I&apos;d die a hideous, painful death, but it couldn&apos;t *all* be better than married life... could it?</string>
  <string id="109239" soundid="166458"></string>
  <string id="109240" soundid="166459">Asking the same question over and over and expecting a different answer... that is the definition of a pestering and overbearing wife.</string>
  <string id="109241" soundid="166460">Please try to stop reminding me of my missing missus, it is a memory too painful to bear.</string>
  <string id="109254" soundid="166473">I stayed on the outskirts. I saw him at a distance a couple of times, but had no reason to look past the beard for a man twenty years dead. I had... other interests.</string>
  <string id="109255" soundid="166474">It doesn&apos;t matter. I know enough about the Glorious Strategist to say he would not have made these mistakes. And I know... far too much about the Lotus Assassins.</string>
  <string id="109256">Wouldn&apos;t you recognize him? You must have seen him when visiting the village.</string>
  <string id="109260">Destroy all remaining ships!</string>
  <string id="109261">Water Dragon Spirit</string>
  <string id="109278">Find the Slave Breaker</string>
  <string id="109279">Find the slave breaker and rescue Fuyao.</string>
  <string id="109280">Yifong&apos;s daughter, Fuyao has been captured by pirates. She is powerless to deal with these brutal men. Find Fuyao and rescue her from the pirates.</string>
  <string id="109282">The Slaves are Free</string>
  <string id="109285">You have freed Yifong and Fuyao from the pirates and the slave traders.</string>
  <string id="109286">Fuyao has Killed Lordling Lun</string>
  <string id="109289">You convinced Fuyao to kill Lordling Lun to gain her freedom. She is free, as is her mother Yifong, but she has been changed by the murder.</string>
  <string id="109290">Lordling Lun Purchased the Slaves</string>
  <string id="109293">Lordling Lun paid you well for Yifong and Fuyao.</string>
  <string id="109295">You Lost Zi Bao</string>
  <string id="109298">With Zi Bao gone, there is no way to find the slave traders. Songtao will likely be convicted of the crime, whether he is guilty or not.</string>
  <string id="109305" soundid="166534"></string>
  <string id="109306" soundid="166535"></string>
  <string id="109308" soundid="192898">You&apos;d think a seven year old might be an easy target, but I soon learned just where to cut a man to make a him squeal like a pig. Ahh... those were the days.</string>
  <string id="109309">Turtle Eggs</string>
  <string id="109340">Goodbye.</string>
  <string id="109341">Goodbye.</string>
  <string id="109342">Damn! I need more wine!</string>
  <string id="109343">Blood and axes!</string>
  <string id="109344">Death to everyone!</string>
  <string id="109345">Cower before me!</string>
  <string id="109346">Die!</string>
  <string id="109347">Arrgh!</string>
  <string id="109348">I will taste blood!</string>
  <string id="109349">Have a taste of my steel!</string>
  <string id="109350">Kiss my axe goodbye!</string>
  <string id="109351">You will die!</string>
  <string id="109352">I&apos;ll destroy you all!</string>
  <string id="109353">Ahh! That&apos;s better.</string>
  <string id="109354">You... Treacherous... Pig!</string>
  <string id="109355">Ha! No one can withstand the Black Whirlwind!</string>
  <string id="109356">Ha! You can&apos;t hurt me!</string>
  <string id="109357">Let&apos;s get moving!</string>
  <string id="109358">The blood on my axes is getting dry, as is my throat!</string>
  <string id="109359">(snoring, loudly, then waking up... general grumbling with no actual words)</string>
  <string id="109360">I need wine!</string>
  <string id="109361">Blacksmith Fong</string>
  <string id="109362">Merchant Cheung</string>
  <string id="109364">Tien&apos;s Landing</string>
  <string id="109365">Captain Ing</string>
  <string id="109366">Minister Sheng</string>
  <string id="109367">Ben and Miao</string>
  <string id="109368">Ministry Hostel</string>
  <string id="109370">What kind of things have you seen?</string>
  <string id="109372">Why haven&apos;t you mentioned this before?</string>
  <string id="109375">Have you seen anything that can be of help?</string>
  <string id="109377">That could be... disconcerting.</string>
  <string id="109378">Stay with the living. It&apos;s almost as if you prefer the company of the dead.</string>
  <string id="109380">It wouldn&apos;t surprise me. It is almost as old as the Empire itself.</string>
  <string id="109381">I&apos;m not interested in the past. Keep focused on our task.</string>
  <string id="109384" soundid="166697">[You place the once-missing crystal into the pedestal. The crystal clicks into place, and the pedestal begins to move.]</string>
  <string id="109385" soundid="166698">Hello there, stranger!</string>
  <string id="109386" soundid="166699">The last time I was talking to the town&apos;s illustrious leader, he mentioned a young hero who had &quot;closed the dam on behalf of the mighty Minister Sheng.&quot; Good work!</string>
  <string id="109387" soundid="166700">I haven&apos;t spotted you around Tien&apos;s Landing before. You&apos;ve come at a bad time, what with the dam being open and all.</string>
  <string id="109388" soundid="166701">Regardless, it&apos;s good to meet you! I&apos;m Darting Lynx, the acrobat. Unfortunately, I&apos;m not putting any shows on in Tien&apos;s Landing, if that&apos;s why you&apos;re here.</string>
  <string id="109389" soundid="166702">You know, feats of balance and precision, delicate routines to shock and amaze. Whatever brings some silver, really.</string>
  <string id="109390" soundid="166703">Let me tell you, it raises a few eyebrows at first. That&apos;s why I tell people I&apos;m an acrobat up front these days.</string>
  <string id="109391" soundid="166704">Oh, I&apos;m not really one to ask. Minister Sheng in the town square is the one you want to talk to. I&apos;m not from Tien&apos;s Landing.</string>
  <string id="109392" soundid="166705">I travel around the countryside putting on acts and sometimes teaching people a few tricks. Hey, now that I think of it, you&apos;re a warrior, right?</string>
  <string id="109393" soundid="166706">I may not be putting on any shows here, but I could teach you a few techniques to improve your balance and speed if you&apos;re interested.</string>
  <string id="109394" soundid="166707">Hello again! What&apos;s on your mind this fine day?</string>
  <string id="109395" soundid="166708">It&apos;s not much of a story, really. It&apos;s just a stage name I picked up when I first started practicing acrobatics.</string>
  <string id="109396" soundid="166709">I was quite young, and my master felt I was a little too fast for my own good. &quot;You dart like a lynx,&quot; he would say, &quot;but you balance like a drunken frog!&quot;</string>
  <string id="109397" soundid="166710">He taught me to slow my movements and really focus on what I was doing, but his nickname for me stuck.</string>
  <string id="109398" soundid="166711">With the dam closed, things seem to have really improved around here. Have you noticed that the people have remembered how to smile?</string>
  <string id="109399" soundid="166712">I&apos;m not sure what else I can tell you. I don&apos;t know this town all that well.</string>
  <string id="109400" soundid="166713">As I said, I&apos;m not really from here, so there&apos;s not much I can tell you. You could try talking to Minister Sheng, though. He always knows what&apos;s going on.</string>
  <string id="109401" soundid="166714">I get the sense that he doesn&apos;t *do* much about it, but he&apos;s at least aware.</string>
  <string id="109402" soundid="166715">I&apos;d be happy to! I&apos;ll be leaving Tien&apos;s Landing someday soon, and silver always helps the trip go smoother.</string>
  <string id="109403" soundid="166716">Let&apos;s see what I can teach you.</string>
  <string id="109404" soundid="166717">All the best to you!</string>
  <string id="109408">What kind of shows would you normally put on?</string>
  <string id="109410">That&apos;s an interesting name you have.</string>
  <string id="109412">Could you answer some questions for me?</string>
  <string id="109415">How did you come by the name Darting Lynx?</string>
  <string id="109418">Can I talk to you about Tien&apos;s Landing?</string>
  <string id="109421">Show me what you can teach and what you have for sale.</string>
  <string id="109423">I should go.</string>
  <string id="109424" soundid="166737">At least you&apos;ll be easy to teach. I don&apos;t know if you&apos;ve ever tried to teach a man balance, but it&apos;s no simple task.</string>
  <string id="109425" soundid="166738">You&apos;d think *we&apos;d* be the ones having a hard time. I swear, if men had breasts they wouldn&apos;t be able to walk straight, let alone hold a handstand.</string>
  <string id="109426" soundid="166739">You, of all people, must be able to sympathize. Nothing we can&apos;t overcome. Let&apos;s see what I can teach you.</string>
  <string id="109429">Support Only</string>
  <string id="109430">Favorite Support Style</string>
  <string id="109435" soundid="166748">Do we really have time to be wandering the countryside? We must return to the palace as quickly as we are able.</string>
  <string id="109436" soundid="166749">I think we should return to the palace soon.</string>
  <string id="109439">Lost Spirit</string>
  <string id="109442">Lost Spirit</string>
  <string id="109445">Lost Spirit</string>
  <string id="109448">Lost Spirit</string>
  <string id="109451">Lost Spirit</string>
  <string id="109454">Tactic: </string>
  <string id="109457" soundid="166770">I can&apos;t believe I&apos;m going to say this... but shouldn&apos;t we be heading back to the palace? I don&apos;t like it any more than you, but it seems that&apos;s where we need to be.</string>
  <string id="109458" soundid="166771">[This once-sturdy wall seems weakened by its years under the water. It is still too strong to destroy by hand, however.]</string>
  <string id="109471" soundid="166784"></string>
  <string id="109472" soundid="187876">What was the most difficult? Hmm... reloads. Piecing those golems back together isn&apos;t easy, to say nothing of getting the blood out of your robes. We had a disappearing dye that helped, but it just doesn&apos;t hit the wall right, you know?</string>
  <string id="109473" soundid="187877">We all got along well enough. I had no trouble with anyone. We&apos;re not friends, mind you. I mean, it was just business. You have to be a professional no matter how much Sky bugs you. Did I just say that?</string>
  <string id="109474" soundid="187878">My favorite player model? Radiant Jen Zi. She just looks interesting, you know? Plucky. Of course, some smartass would ruin it by changing her name during testing. I guess they used up all the good ones in the actual game. Creamy Nougat? What the hell is that?</string>
  <string id="109475" soundid="187879">Sometimes... the competition got on my nerves, you know? I mean, here I am, clearly a badass loner with a dangerous past, and what happens? I&apos;ll tell you. Someone discovers Drunken style and spends the rest of the game with that chucklehead Ho throwing booze at his head. Pfft!</string>
  <string id="109476" soundid="187880">I&apos;m classically trained, you know, and not just in the martial arts. Yeah, I&apos;ve got a few projects lined up. Arthouse stuff, so I don&apos;t get typecast in the loner enforcer role. But check me out in Loner Enforcer 9: the Bloodening. The best of the series. I don&apos;t want to leave my fans behind.</string>
  <string id="109477" soundid="187881">I think we&apos;re done here. Shut that camera off.</string>
  <string id="109482" soundid="187885">I see Jade Empire really as an extension of my previous film work. Dangerous Loner 2: Alone and Dangerous? Water&apos;s Edge: Beach Razor Nightmare? Come on, that was a classic coming of age story. Oh, and Cats. Near the end of the run when it was more real.</string>
  <string id="109483" soundid="187886">I was set to be the bad guy in a kids&apos; movie about a dog that rides a champion racehorse. Airbiscuit, I think it was. But the guy that plays Zhong the Ox Carrier told me BioWare was auditioning, and, eh, I decided to take the pay cut to broaden my horizons.</string>
  <string id="109486">Lessons of the Forge</string>
  <string id="109487">Health +2

Smiling Mountain&apos;s training sessions in Two Rivers can teach valuable lessons. Standing one&apos;s ground against increasing numbers of students helps young warriors learn to pace themselves and last longer in battles. As metals are carefully folded to make them stronger still, so are those students who have learned the lessons of the forge.</string>
  <string id="109491">My style is perfect!</string>
  <string id="109492">Evade</string>
  <string id="109493">Attack Your Target</string>
  <string id="109494">Attack Other Opponents</string>
  <string id="109495">Support</string>
  <string id="109496">Attack</string>
  <string id="109497">Defend Themselves</string>
  <string id="109498" soundid="166815">[The igniter is lit, and you have placed a supply of dragon powder in the priming pan. The rockets should be ready to go.]</string>
  <string id="109499" soundid="166816">[You trigger the igniter.]</string>
  <string id="109500" soundid="166817">[The igniter itself is lit, but the pan at the front of the assembly needs a supply of the highly flammable dragon powder to prime the fuses.]</string>
  <string id="109501" soundid="166818">[This device seems designed to fire three dragon powder fueled rockets at an old wall across the clearing.]</string>
  <string id="109502" soundid="166819">[Fireworks of this size, if engineered correctly, should create an explosion big enough to destroy the wall.]</string>
  <string id="109503" soundid="166820">[You step away from the igniter.]</string>
  <string id="109504" soundid="166821">[The rockets have already fired.]</string>
  <string id="109506">[Fire the rockets.]</string>
  <string id="109507">[Examine the setup.]</string>
  <string id="109509">[Place the dragon powder in the tray.]</string>
  <string id="109511">[Leave the igniter.]</string>
  <string id="109590">Horse</string>
  <string id="109593">Rooster</string>
  <string id="109596">Crane</string>
  <string id="109599">Crane</string>
  <string id="109603">Ghost</string>
  <string id="109605">Teahouse</string>
  <string id="109607" soundid="167023">You! Is it not enough you destroyed all the humans here, now you wish to attack us as well? Foolish human.</string>
  <string id="109608" soundid="167679">Uss? We are here because there are so many spirits here... where the dead are... sso are we.</string>
  <string id="109610">[TEMP] generic_training_mind_5</string>
  <string id="109611">[TEMP] generic_training_spirit_1</string>
  <string id="109612">[TEMP] generic_training_spirit_2</string>
  <string id="109613">[TEMP] generic_training_spirit_3</string>
  <string id="109614">[TEMP] generic_training_spirit_4</string>
  <string id="109615">[TEMP] generic_training_spirit_5</string>
  <string id="109616">[TEMP] generic_training_health_1</string>
  <string id="109617">[TEMP] generic_training_health_2</string>
  <string id="109618">[TEMP] generic_training_health_3</string>
  <string id="109619">[TEMP] generic_training_health_4</string>
  <string id="109620">[TEMP] generic_training_health_5</string>
  <string id="109621">[TEMP] generic_training_focus_1</string>
  <string id="109622">[TEMP] generic_training_focus_2</string>
  <string id="109623">[TEMP] generic_training_focus_3</string>
  <string id="109624">[TEMP] generic_training_focus_4</string>
  <string id="109625">[TEMP] generic_training_focus_5</string>
  <string id="109626">[TEMP] generic_training_chi_1</string>
  <string id="109627">[TEMP] generic_training_chi_2</string>
  <string id="109628">[TEMP] generic_training_chi_3</string>
  <string id="109629">[TEMP] generic_training_chi_4</string>
  <string id="109630">[TEMP] generic_training_chi_5</string>
  <string id="109631">[TEMP] generic_training_charm_I</string>
  <string id="109632">[TEMP] generic_training_charm_II</string>
  <string id="109633">[TEMP] generic_training_charm_III</string>
  <string id="109634">[TEMP] generic_training_intuition_I</string>
  <string id="109635">[TEMP] generic_training_intuition_II</string>
  <string id="109636">[TEMP] generic_training_intuition_III</string>
  <string id="109637">[TEMP] generic_training_intimidation_I</string>
  <string id="109638">[TEMP] generic_training_intimidation_II</string>
  <string id="109639">[TEMP] generic_training_intimidation_III</string>
  <string id="109640" soundid="167056">Whats have we here? Masters said there would be others?</string>
  <string id="109641" soundid="167057">What are you doing here humans? All the others are gone... dead... spirits only now.</string>
  <string id="109642">[TEMP] generic_style_quicksilver</string>
  <string id="109643">[TEMP] generic_style_tempest</string>
  <string id="109644" soundid="167060">If you are here to kills us, then you are going to be very sorry you came.</string>
  <string id="109648" soundid="167724">My... Master.</string>
  <string id="109649">[TEMP] DESC generic_training_body_1</string>
  <string id="109650">[TEMP] DESC generic_training_body_2</string>
  <string id="109651">[TEMP] DESC generic_training_body_3</string>
  <string id="109652">[TEMP] DESC generic_training_body_4</string>
  <string id="109653" soundid="167069">What is going on here? What are you two doing? What are these... humans doing here?</string>
  <string id="109654" soundid="167070">Masters! We were justs... um... trying... to... ah... trying to helps the, ah....</string>
  <string id="109655" soundid="167071">Do not play with these things.... destroy them! Do not fail me, you miserable worms, or you will pay dearly.</string>
  <string id="109656" soundid="167072">Yes masters!</string>
  <string id="109657" soundid="167073">Now kill them! And be quick about it. Report to me in the tower when you&apos;re finished with them.</string>
  <string id="109658" soundid="167074">Now see what you haves done... the masters is angry with us.</string>
  <string id="109659" soundid="167075">We can&apos;t have the masters angry with us.</string>
  <string id="109661">[TEMP] DESC generic_training_body_5</string>
  <string id="109662">What are you doing here?</string>
  <string id="109663">That&apos;s none of your business, rat!</string>
  <string id="109664">[TEMP] DESC generic_training_mind_1</string>
  <string id="109665">I&apos;m here to kill you, it would seem.</string>
  <string id="109667">[TEMP] DESC generic_training_mind_2</string>
  <string id="109668">Ghost</string>
  <string id="109669">[TEMP] DESC generic_training_mind_3</string>
  <string id="109670">[TEMP] DESC generic_training_mind_4</string>
  <string id="109671">[TEMP] DESC generic_training_mind_5</string>
  <string id="109672">[TEMP] DESC generic_training_spirit_1</string>
  <string id="109673">[TEMP] DESC generic_training_spirit_2</string>
  <string id="109674">[TEMP] DESC generic_training_spirit_3</string>
  <string id="109675">[TEMP] DESC generic_training_spirit_4</string>
  <string id="109676">[TEMP] DESC generic_training_spirit_5</string>
  <string id="109683">Lost Spirit</string>
  <string id="109706">I have healed.</string>
  <string id="109707">I... I&apos;ve been poisoned!</string>
  <string id="109708">Take that!</string>
  <string id="109709">The Long Drought</string>
  <string id="109710">You blocked my attack!</string>
  <string id="109711">Fight!</string>
  <string id="109712">This is it!</string>
  <string id="109713">Now we see!</string>
  <string id="109717" soundid="167350">The arena has a new champion, have you heard?</string>
  <string id="109718" soundid="167351">Raging Dragon, isn&apos;t it?</string>
  <string id="109719" soundid="167352">Yes! Silver Phoenix is the best!</string>
  <string id="109720" soundid="167353">Who hasn&apos;t? Everyone&apos;s talking about Tiger Lifts the Mountain.</string>
  <string id="109721" soundid="167354">He&apos;s my favorite.</string>
  <string id="109722" soundid="167355">She deserves the title of Imperial Champion!</string>
  <string id="109723" soundid="168393">I&apos;m not sure we have the time. There are too many important matters at stake. We need to make progress before I will feel comfortable spending more time on idle chatter.</string>
  <string id="109724" soundid="168394"></string>
  <string id="109726" soundid="168396">Thank the heavens you came down here! They&apos;re animals!</string>
  <string id="109727" soundid="167360">No more Judge Fang, the rumors say.</string>
  <string id="109728" soundid="167361">They also say a tattooed man was asking questions about the good Judge. Interesting.</string>
  <string id="109729" soundid="167362">According to the rumors, it would be best if men in powerful positions avoided men wearing yellow sashes.</string>
  <string id="109730" soundid="167363">Indeed. It seems having a fellow in robes asking about you can be bad for your... career.</string>
  <string id="109731" soundid="167364">Yes. I know I&apos;ll be doing my best to avoid the attentions of any large, broad shouldered fellows for the next little while.</string>
  <string id="109732" soundid="167365">Caught the attention of one too many ladies, it seems. Women in blue can be bad for one&apos;s... career, it seems.</string>
  <string id="109733" soundid="167366">Given his stance on marriage, the old dog should have known better than to attract the attentions of a woman in red.</string>
  <string id="109734" soundid="167367">He should have stuck to Breezes. The attentions of a certain warrior woman in purple can be hard on one&apos;s... career, apparently.</string>
  <string id="109735" soundid="168397">Do you have a moment?</string>
  <string id="109736" soundid="167369">What&apos;s happening in the Necropolis?</string>
  <string id="109737" soundid="167370">I don&apos;t care! Just keep your head down and don&apos;t cause any trouble.</string>
  <string id="109738" soundid="168398">I&apos;ll just go. I don&apos;t want any trouble.</string>
  <string id="109739" soundid="167372">The... problem in the Scholars&apos; Garden has packed his things and left, I hear.</string>
  <string id="109740" soundid="167373">Yes, and it was that well muscled fellow with the tattoos who encouraged the buffoon to leave.</string>
  <string id="109741" soundid="167374">Who cares about him! Now, the fellow in the blue vest who sent him packing... Mmmm.</string>
  <string id="109742" soundid="167375">It was that exotic looking fellow in the robes. I wonder if he&apos;s a noble? Or single?</string>
  <string id="109743" soundid="167376">More important, did you see the man who bested the buffoon? Shoulders broad enough to hold up the sky.</string>
  <string id="109744" soundid="167377">Yes, it was some woman in blue that encouraged him to leave. Quite the beauty, I&apos;m told.</string>
  <string id="109745" soundid="167378">Yes. If I had more time, I&apos;d send a man to see if that girl in red would like to join my house as a servant. Most impressive.</string>
  <string id="109746" soundid="167379">I wouldn&apos;t have expected that woman in plum to have success where all the scholars failed.</string>
  <string id="109747" soundid="168399">Could I ask you something?</string>
  <string id="109748" soundid="167381">Did you catch that performance in the Golden Way?</string>
  <string id="109749" soundid="167382">Brilliant!</string>
  <string id="109750" soundid="167383">It was passable, I suppose.</string>
  <string id="109751" soundid="167384">Sadly, yes. I&apos;d have been happier if I&apos;d kept studying my books.</string>
  <string id="109752" soundid="167385">The Lady&apos;s makeup was far too realistic. Hardly looked like a man in costume at all!</string>
  <string id="109753" soundid="167386">Wasn&apos;t the Lady gorgeous? You simply don&apos;t find actors able to pull off a noblewoman so well.</string>
  <string id="109754" soundid="168400">Yes, hello?</string>
  <string id="109755" soundid="168401">Oh, senior student! I wanted to thank you for your help earlier. I wasn&apos;t sure anyone would come down to our little circle of houses when the bandits attacked.</string>
  <string id="109756" soundid="168402">It&apos;s out of the way, so I&apos;d almost given up hope.</string>
  <string id="109757" soundid="168403">And I was glad to see you... though, er... there&apos;s the small matter of my chest.</string>
  <string id="109758" soundid="167391">I hear another division has been reassigned out of the south.</string>
  <string id="109759" soundid="167392">There have been some problems down there, I hear.</string>
  <string id="109760" soundid="167393">It&apos;s like the Assassins don&apos;t care what happens, and the army does nothing without their nod.</string>
  <string id="109761" soundid="168404">That they did, that they did. Though, there&apos;s one other thing. A small matter really, but I appear to be missing my chest.</string>
  <string id="109762" soundid="168405">I am no warrior! I&apos;m certainly glad you arrived. There&apos;s just one thing. When I returned, I appeared to be missing one chest.</string>
  <string id="109763">Change Tactics</string>
  <string id="109764">[TEMP] DESC generic_training_health_1</string>
  <string id="109765">[TEMP] DESC generic_training_health_2</string>
  <string id="109766">[TEMP] DESC generic_training_health_3</string>
  <string id="109773">Dirge Fountain</string>
  <string id="109774">Gate to Inner Courtyard</string>
  <string id="109778">Rat Demon</string>
  <string id="109788" soundid="167438">Why not you and your friend there? Incentive enough for any man to perform superhuman feats of stamina.</string>
  <string id="109789" soundid="167439">I suddenly feel like I need a bath.</string>
  <string id="109790" soundid="167440">He&apos;s so desperate, it&apos;s almost charming. Almost.</string>
  <string id="109791" soundid="167441">You travel with such lovely companions, Lustful Lao would not risk your displeasure. You had questions to ask, I will endeavor to answer.</string>
  <string id="109792" soundid="167442">That depends on your... preferences, doesn&apos;t it, little peach? Still, I would not risk your displeasure when we are so close to just the opposite.</string>
  <string id="109793" soundid="167443">Ask the questions you truly had for Lustful Lao, and he will find you your answers, yes indeed.</string>
  <string id="109794">That depends on who the two people in the rickshaw are.</string>
  <string id="109810">Dawn Star</string>
  <string id="109814">Lotus Assassin</string>
  <string id="109817">Grand Inquisitor Jia</string>
  <string id="109820">Death&apos;s Hand</string>
  <string id="109823">Lotus Assassin</string>
  <string id="109828">Scholar</string>
  <string id="109831">Scholar</string>
  <string id="109834">Button Mappings</string>
  <string id="109835">Guard</string>
  <string id="109839" soundid="168114"></string>
  <string id="109840" soundid="168115">We need to get back to the others. Be careful, there&apos;s no telling what the shifting of the fortress stirred up among all these graves.</string>
  <string id="109841" soundid="168116">We have to get out of the Necropolis so we can deal with this information. Be careful, the ground has shifted. There&apos;s no telling what has been disturbed.</string>
  <string id="109842" soundid="168117">We need to get back to the others so we can deal with what we know now. Careful out here, there&apos;s no telling what the collapsing fortress has stirred up.</string>
  <string id="109843" soundid="168118">We must get out of here. Be careful, so much ground has shifted under these graves, there&apos;s no telling what we woke up.</string>
  <string id="109844" soundid="168119">Ah, good, we&apos;re back in the open. Let&apos;s get going. The shifting ground has probably shaken up a few new spirits to fight.</string>
  <string id="109845" soundid="168120">Ya Zhen: Another walk through the graves, but be wary, the ground has shifted. Yes, I sense a number of spirits have been disturbed.</string>
  <string id="109847" soundid="168122">A lowly acolyte walks away? You should have died beside your master preventing the escape of whoever did this! Unless you had a role in it! Destroy them to be sure!</string>
  <string id="109848">Tomb of Ji Xin</string>
  <string id="109852">You can&apos;t beat me!</string>
  <string id="109853">This is your final fight.</string>
  <string id="109858">I heal myself and go on.</string>
  <string id="109859">That... that was a dirty trick.</string>
  <string id="109860">Now you&apos;re feeling pain!</string>
  <string id="109861">That doesn&apos;t work...</string>
  <string id="109862">You will feel pain!</string>
  <string id="109863">Your last breath!</string>
  <string id="109864">No one gets away!</string>
  <string id="109865">Fight dirty!</string>
  <string id="109866">You can&apos;t beat me!</string>
  <string id="109867">This is your final fight.</string>
  <string id="109872">I heal myself and go on.</string>
  <string id="109873">That... that was a dirty trick.</string>
  <string id="109874">Now you&apos;re feeling pain!</string>
  <string id="109875">That doesn&apos;t work...</string>
  <string id="109876">You will feel pain!</string>
  <string id="109877">Your last breath!</string>
  <string id="109878">No one gets away!</string>
  <string id="109879">Fight dirty!</string>
  <string id="109880">You can&apos;t beat me!</string>
  <string id="109881">This is your final fight.</string>
  <string id="109886">I heal myself and go on.</string>
  <string id="109887">That... that was a dirty trick.</string>
  <string id="109888">Now you&apos;re feeling pain!</string>
  <string id="109889">That doesn&apos;t work...</string>
  <string id="109890">You will feel pain!</string>
  <string id="109891">Your last breath!</string>
  <string id="109892">No one gets away!</string>
  <string id="109893">Fight dirty!</string>
  <string id="109894">You can&apos;t beat me!</string>
  <string id="109895">This is your final fight.</string>
  <string id="109900">I heal myself and go on.</string>
  <string id="109901">That... that was a dirty trick.</string>
  <string id="109902">Now you&apos;re feeling pain!</string>
  <string id="109904">That should have harmed you.</string>
  <string id="109905">Die, traitor!</string>
  <string id="109906">I obey only Death&apos;s Hand!</string>
  <string id="109907">You will fall here and now!</string>
  <string id="109908">I will not let you escape alive!</string>
  <string id="109909">You will be a test of my skill.</string>
  <string id="109910">Nothing you do will prevent my victory.</string>
  <string id="109915">I am better now.</string>
  <string id="109916">You have poisoned me!</string>
  <string id="109917">Your death is assured!</string>
  <string id="109918">That should have harmed you.</string>
  <string id="109919">Die, traitor!</string>
  <string id="109920">I obey only Death&apos;s Hand!</string>
  <string id="109921">You will fall here and now!</string>
  <string id="109922">I will not let you escape alive!</string>
  <string id="109923">You will be a test of my skill.</string>
  <string id="109924">Nothing you do will prevent my victory.</string>
  <string id="109929">I am better now.</string>
  <string id="109930">You have poisoned me!</string>
  <string id="109931">Your death is assured!</string>
  <string id="109932">That should have harmed you.</string>
  <string id="109933">Die, traitor!</string>
  <string id="109934">I obey only Death&apos;s Hand!</string>
  <string id="109935">You will fall here and now!</string>
  <string id="109936">I will not let you escape alive!</string>
  <string id="109937">You will be a test of my skill.</string>
  <string id="109938">Nothing you do will prevent my victory.</string>
  <string id="109946">I am better now.</string>
  <string id="109947">You have poisoned me!</string>
  <string id="109950">Your death is assured!</string>
  <string id="109951">It doesn&apos;t work?</string>
  <string id="109954">You will fall!</string>
  <string id="109955">Your blood will paint these walls!</string>
  <string id="109956">Graah!</string>
  <string id="109957">Tear you limb from limb!</string>
  <string id="109958">Die, mortal!</string>
  <string id="109959">My master commands your death!</string>
  <string id="109964">I have been restored.</string>
  <string id="109965">You have... poisoned me.</string>
  <string id="109966">Haha!</string>
  <string id="109967">It doesn&apos;t work?</string>
  <string id="109968">You will fall!</string>
  <string id="109969">Your blood will paint these walls!</string>
  <string id="109970">Graah!</string>
  <string id="109971">Tear you limb from limb!</string>
  <string id="109972">Die, mortal!</string>
  <string id="109973">My master commands your death!</string>
  <string id="109978">I have been restored.</string>
  <string id="109979">You have... poisoned me.</string>
  <string id="109980">Haha!</string>
  <string id="109981">It doesn&apos;t work?</string>
  <string id="109982">You will fall!</string>
  <string id="109983">Your blood will paint these walls!</string>
  <string id="109984">Graah!</string>
  <string id="109985">Tear you limb from limb!</string>
  <string id="109986">Die, mortal!</string>
  <string id="110001">My master commands your death!</string>
  <string id="110007">A fortress under siege.</string>
  <string id="110008">


Following rumors of trouble in a mysterious fortress temple high in the mountains, you believe you may have found the source. Despite tales of dark rituals and horrible creatures in the temple, you grab your long sword, brush up on the secrets of Dire Flame, and prepare for battle.</string>
  <string id="110009" soundid="167661">You are the reason we are here.... The suffering of these pitiful humans has drawn us here. If you do not enjoy our presence, then blame only yourself!</string>
  <string id="110010" soundid="167662">Pain, suffering, hate... these things draw us. When the spirits are angry, when they die in a place like this... we are inevitably drawn to them.</string>
  <string id="110011" soundid="167663">I&apos;m glad you&apos;ve come. We need more like you. Suffering may draw us here, but we require more death... more pain... more suffering, if we wish to stay.</string>
  <string id="110012" soundid="167664">Just like this pathetic one... Cheung, I believe he was called. He suffered a great deal, and he has given us much for his sufferings.</string>
  <string id="110013" soundid="167665">I will gladly make certain that *your* final moments will at least give us something in return as well!</string>
  <string id="110014" soundid="167666">Let me destroy it, master! I will make sure it suffers greatly.</string>
  <string id="110015" soundid="167667">Ha, ha, ha! Good... I prefer it when they die angry!</string>
  <string id="110017">I didn&apos;t ask you to come here.</string>
  <string id="110018">Why does suffering draw you here?</string>
  <string id="110020">I don&apos;t care why you&apos;re here, I&apos;m going to kill you!</string>
  <string id="110024">I can&apos;t allow you to remain here!</string>
  <string id="110025">You are the ones who will be destroyed!</string>
  <string id="110026">Enough talk! Fight or leave!</string>
  <string id="110027">[TEMP] DESC generic_training_health_4</string>
  <string id="110028">[TEMP] DESC generic_training_health_5</string>
  <string id="110029">[TEMP] DESC generic_training_focus_1</string>
  <string id="110030">[TEMP] DESC generic_training_focus_2</string>
  <string id="110031">[TEMP] DESC generic_training_focus_3</string>
  <string id="110032">[TEMP] DESC generic_training_focus_4</string>
  <string id="110033">[TEMP] DESC generic_training_focus_5</string>
  <string id="110034">[TEMP] DESC generic_training_chi_1</string>
  <string id="110035">[TEMP] DESC generic_training_chi_2</string>
  <string id="110036">[TEMP] DESC generic_training_chi_3</string>
  <string id="110037">[TEMP] DESC generic_training_chi_4</string>
  <string id="110038">[TEMP] DESC generic_training_chi_5</string>
  <string id="110039">[TEMP] DESC generic_training_charm_I</string>
  <string id="110040">[TEMP] DESC generic_training_charm_II</string>
  <string id="110041">[TEMP] DESC generic_training_charm_III</string>
  <string id="110042">[TEMP] DESC generic_training_intuition_I</string>
  <string id="110043">[TEMP] DESC generic_training_intuition_II</string>
  <string id="110044">[TEMP] DESC generic_training_intuition_III</string>
  <string id="110045">[TEMP] DESC generic_training_intimidation_I</string>
  <string id="110046">[TEMP] DESC generic_training_intimidation_II</string>
  <string id="110047">[TEMP] DESC generic_training_intimidation_III</string>
  <string id="110048">[TEMP] DESC generic_style_quicksilver</string>
  <string id="110049">Magic Style
Resonance: Stronger When Wielded by a Follower of the Way of the Closed Fist
Drains Chi
This style&apos;s Power Attack can initiate a Harmonic Combo that produces a Focus power-up.

Warriors proficient in Tempest have the winds at their beck and call. Fighters who have faced this style and survived tell tales of blasts of gale-force winds and of powerful whirlwinds that effortlessly sent them flying away from the Tempest master himself. Many practitioners of Tempest face entire gangs without ever taking a wound, as the mighty winds at their command keep their foes at bay. Warriors with the chill of the wind in their hearts find Tempest far easier to command, so it is a favored style of the Way of the Closed Fist.</string>
  <string id="110052">Guard</string>
  <string id="110053" soundid="167877">You don&apos;t need to know. All that matters is the glory of the Empire.</string>
  <string id="110054" soundid="167878">But we need to ask questions to honor what was done. What if this hero wasn&apos;t finished?</string>
  <string id="110116">Gate to the Imperial Arena</string>
  <string id="110117">Ghost</string>
  <string id="110120">Ghost</string>
  <string id="110123" soundid="167869">Everything has gone as it should.</string>
  <string id="110125" soundid="167871">You surprise me yet again. I&apos;m a better teacher than I thought.</string>
  <string id="110127" soundid="167879">This is your lesson for today. To be happy in your station, you don&apos;t need to know.</string>
  <string id="110128" soundid="167880">We don&apos;t need to know.</string>
  <string id="110129" soundid="167881">Very good. Return to your place.</string>
  <string id="110130" soundid="167882">Now, who has delivered the Empire from war and pestilence?</string>
  <string id="110131" soundid="167883">The hero and The Glorious Strategist.</string>
  <string id="110132" soundid="167884">Who showed us how to sacrifice for the greater good, so we are free to live in peace?</string>
  <string id="110133" soundid="167885">The hero and The Glorious Strategist.</string>
  <string id="110134" soundid="167886">Who has ensured that the Empire will endure forever?</string>
  <string id="110135" soundid="167887">The hero and The Glorious Strategist.</string>
  <string id="110136" soundid="167888">[Triumphant laugh.]</string>
  <string id="110151" soundid="167903">This Inquisitor will be more interested in you than he&apos;ll let on. I&apos;m not even sure if you needed to talk to Dongow to catch his attention.</string>
  <string id="110152" soundid="167904">Sorry! I forget myself sometimes. It&apos;s just... well, let&apos;s not be late for that little meeting at the flyer.</string>
  <string id="110153" soundid="167905">That is the wisest thing you could have said. Especially... well, the Inquisitors are not dealt with lightly. Let&apos;s get back to the flyer as soon as we can.</string>
  <string id="110154" soundid="190714">[TEMP] Root node for DS.</string>
  <string id="110155">A compliment without even a hint of flirting, Sky?</string>
  <string id="110157">Just watch my back. I don&apos;t trust this Inquisitor.</string>
  <string id="110159">GO!</string>
  <string id="110161">Whatever. Just stay behind me and keep quiet.</string>
  <string id="110164">Kang is not a warrior and would not be helpful in close personal combat. He prefers to help you with the Marvelous Dragonfly where he&apos;ll be most useful.</string>
  <string id="110165">Imperial Captain</string>
  <string id="110168">Imperial Guard</string>
  <string id="110171">Lost Spirit</string>
  <string id="110173" soundid="167927">He has had no experience battling spirits, and he fears that he just may lose... he is driven by greed, but controlled by fear.</string>
  <string id="110174" soundid="167928">I am the only thing keeping him in check. If I fail to defeat him, there will be nothing standing in his way. For now, his fear of my powers as a spirit keep him at bay.</string>
  <string id="110182" soundid="167939">[Success] [Shendao falls silent, obviously afraid. He shrinks away from you.]</string>
  <string id="110183">[Intimidation] You grumbling old windbag. Shut your mouth and keep it closed.</string>
  <string id="110184">Noble</string>
  <string id="110187">Noble</string>
  <string id="110191">Silk Fox, the woman in black who keeps appearing as you travel around Tien&apos;s Landing, informed you that a man named Lord Yun has a wind map that covers the skies to the Imperial City.</string>
  <string id="110193">Spirit Font</string>
  <string id="110195">Ru</string>
  <string id="110200">The Emperor</string>
  <string id="110203">I&apos;m just here to play. Find someone else to do this favor.</string>
  <string id="110204">I&apos;m done with you. I&apos;m leaving.</string>
  <string id="110206">Lotus Assassin</string>
  <string id="110209">Lotus Assassin</string>
  <string id="110212">Lotus Assassin</string>
  <string id="110215">Lotus Assassin</string>
  <string id="110218">Lotus Assassin</string>
  <string id="110221">Lost Spirit</string>
  <string id="110224">Bull Demon</string>
  <string id="110225" soundid="167998">Give me 300 silver to cover my expenses. If you can eat all three dishes in a row and stay on your feet, I&apos;ll give you back your money, and you&apos;ll leave none the poorer, but well fed!</string>
  <string id="110226" soundid="167999">If you don&apos;t mind, I think I&apos;ll get back to my food before it gets cold. I hate to waste any of it. Come back later and try again when you&apos;re feeling better.</string>
  <string id="110228" soundid="168001">Suit yourself, I&apos;ll be here if you change your mind.</string>
  <string id="110230">I&apos;m not interested right now. Good bye.</string>
  <string id="110232">To the ruins</string>
  <string id="110233">The Marvelous Dragonfly</string>
  <string id="110234">Yes, here&apos;s your 300 silver.</string>
  <string id="110235">No thanks, I think I&apos;ll pass.</string>
  <string id="110236">I just want to try the last dish.</string>
  <string id="110239">Lost Spirit</string>
  <string id="110242">That mercenary is your man. He&apos;s Yukong in disguise.</string>
  <string id="110243">Lost Spirit</string>
  <string id="110246">Mummy</string>
  <string id="110249">Lost Spirit</string>
  <string id="110252">Lost Spirit</string>
  <string id="110255">Lost Spirit</string>
  <string id="110258">Lost Spirit</string>
  <string id="110261">Lost Spirit</string>
  <string id="110264">Lost Spirit</string>
  <string id="110267">Lost Spirit</string>
  <string id="110270">Lost Spirit</string>
  <string id="110273">Lost Spirit</string>
  <string id="110276">Mummy</string>
  <string id="110279">Mummy</string>
  <string id="110282">Darting Lynx</string>
  <string id="110284">Commoner</string>
  <string id="110287">Discard changes?</string>
  <string id="110288">Discard</string>
  <string id="110289">Lotus Elite Wizard</string>
  <string id="110292">Lotus Elite</string>
  <string id="110295" soundid="168071">I was thinking about a story my father once told me. He was a scoundrel, but he could spin a fine yarn when he wasn&apos;t robbing caravans.</string>
  <string id="110296">More!</string>
  <string id="110299">Commoner</string>
  <string id="110302">Commoner</string>
  <string id="110305">Noble</string>
  <string id="110308">Noble</string>
  <string id="110315">I have been restored.</string>
  <string id="110316">You have... poisoned me.</string>
  <string id="110317">Haha!</string>
  <string id="110318">It doesn&apos;t work?</string>
  <string id="110319">You will fall!</string>
  <string id="110320">Your blood will paint these walls!</string>
  <string id="110321">Graah!</string>
  <string id="110322">Tear you limb from limb!</string>
  <string id="110323">Die, mortal!</string>
  <string id="110324">My master commands your death!</string>
  <string id="110329">I have been restored.</string>
  <string id="110330">You have... poisoned me.</string>
  <string id="110331">Haha!</string>
  <string id="110336" soundid="168301">[Failure] I don&apos;t think that would be wise. Someone as powerful as her would not be interested in someone like me.</string>
  <string id="110337" soundid="168302">What do you... oh! I&apos;m sorry. I didn&apos;t mean to jump. Just a little nervous is all.</string>
  <string id="110338" soundid="168303">Oh, you&apos;re one of Master Li&apos;s students, right? Yes, I&apos;ve heard about you. Quite skilled, they say. Well, don&apos;t mind me.</string>
  <string id="110339" soundid="168304">Looking at your purse, I&apos;m not sure you have enough to help me, student.</string>
  <string id="110340" soundid="168305">Well, of course I do. That&apos;s precisely what I&apos;m trying to figure out, isn&apos;t it?</string>
  <string id="110341" soundid="168306">You&apos;re right! There must be something I can do. I don&apos;t know what yet, but it will come to me!</string>
  <string id="110342" soundid="168307">You were right to encourage him, but couldn&apos;t we have done something ourselves?</string>
  <string id="110343" soundid="168308">Is that what you think I&apos;m doing? You insult me, student! I *will* find a way to make this silver back.</string>
  <string id="110344" soundid="168309">Was that really necessary? He didn&apos;t bother you for silver.</string>
  <string id="110345" soundid="168310">That&apos;s a hard sort of encouragement, but I see what you mean.</string>
  <string id="110346" soundid="168311">I suppose we all have to look out for ourselves, but remember that there&apos;s always time for others, too.</string>
  <string id="110347" soundid="168312">I didn&apos;t really think he was whining, but... it certainly ended the conversation.</string>
  <string id="110348" soundid="168313">With all due respect, student, now isn&apos;t really the time. I&apos;m quite preoccupied. Someone from around town can help you, I&apos;m sure.</string>
  <string id="110349" soundid="168314">I have to figure out how to deal with this little debt I have to Gao the Greater.</string>
  <string id="110350" soundid="168315">Well, have a good day. I shall try to do the same.</string>
  <string id="110351" soundid="168316">What? Oh, you. I&apos;m busy trying to think of what I will do to earn the money for Gao&apos;s men.</string>
  <string id="110352" soundid="168317">Surely you have something far more important to do than talk to me.</string>
  <string id="110353" soundid="168318">Not enough. Just not enough.</string>
  <string id="110354" soundid="168319">What am I going to do?</string>
  <string id="110355" soundid="168320">Oh dear.</string>
  <string id="110356" soundid="168321">Oh, I wouldn&apos;t think to presume. The town doesn&apos;t owe me anything, and neither do the students of your fine school.</string>
  <string id="110357" soundid="168322">I&apos;m afraid I wouldn&apos;t have much to say. You should ask one of the locals, I think.</string>
  <string id="110358" soundid="168323">Me? No.</string>
  <string id="110359" soundid="168324">I&apos;m not from Two Rivers, though I do occasionally come into town to do some business.</string>
  <string id="110360" soundid="168325">Today has not been an overly good day for me. I was hoping to make a little more silver than I did selling my wares.</string>
  <string id="110361" soundid="168326">Oh, it is very tough luck. You don&apos;t know the half of it.</string>
  <string id="110362" soundid="168327">I owe a small amount of silver to a man who works for a... gentleman named Gao the Greater. He&apos;s quite insistent that I pay, but I&apos;m falling a bit short.</string>
  <string id="110363" soundid="168328">It is no more than the price of a small pig, but Gao the Greater takes his debts very seriously.</string>
  <string id="110364" soundid="168329">Gao the Lesser? Oh, no, I know that he attends the school, but this doesn&apos;t involve him. There&apos;s nothing he could do either way.</string>
  <string id="110365" soundid="168330">Gao the Greater is not known for his generosity. I.... No, I&apos;ll figure a way out of this myself.</string>
  <string id="110366" soundid="168331">Quite the day, quite the day. What can I do for you?</string>
  <string id="110367" soundid="168332">Give me silver? Just hand it over? I don&apos;t know.</string>
  <string id="110368" soundid="168333">That seems close to begging, and the spirits of my ancestors would be shamed if they thought I was doing that.</string>
  <string id="110369" soundid="168334">[Success] Is that so? All right then, I&apos;ll take the silver... but I *will* pay you back!</string>
  <string id="110370" soundid="168335">[Success] I meant no offense, good student. My apologies! I accept your generous gift.</string>
  <string id="110371" soundid="168336">[Success] You&apos;re right! I hadn&apos;t looked at it that way.</string>
  <string id="110372" soundid="168337">I&apos;ll take just enough to pay back what I owe. Many, many thanks!</string>
  <string id="110373" soundid="168338">That will make his life a lot easier. Gao&apos;s father is not a good man to have angry at you, from what I hear.</string>
  <string id="110374" soundid="168339">Farewell, student! I&apos;m off to deal with my debt so I can get back to my farm in peace!</string>
  <string id="110375" soundid="168340">[Failure] I understand where you&apos;re coming from, but I really can&apos;t risk shaming my family name. There are things a man must do alone.</string>
  <string id="110376" soundid="168341">I&apos;m going to head back to my farm. I&apos;m close enough to paying back my debt that I don&apos;t think it will be a problem much longer.</string>
  <string id="110377" soundid="168342">At least you tried. I&apos;m sure he&apos;ll be fine. From the sounds of it, he isn&apos;t too far from paying Gao&apos;s father back his silver.</string>
  <string id="110378" soundid="168343">Thank you for listening to my troubles, student! That alone helped. Take care!</string>
  <string id="110379" soundid="168344">It is a matter of family pride, you understand.</string>
  <string id="110381">Why are you nervous? Anything I can do to help?</string>
  <string id="110386">If you won&apos;t take it, I won&apos;t force you to.</string>
  <string id="110387">I&apos;ll be back when I gather the twenty silver you owe.</string>
  <string id="110388">You need to help yourself out of this situation with Gao the Greater.</string>
  <string id="110389">All you&apos;re doing is standing around. If you want to help yourself, act!</string>
  <string id="110391">It sounds like you&apos;re looking for a sympathy handout. Pathetic.</string>
  <string id="110393">I just wanted to encourage him. He needed it.</string>
  <string id="110394">He has to learn to help himself. Complaining solves nothing.</string>
  <string id="110395">It put an end to his whining, didn&apos;t it?</string>
  <string id="110396">Could I ask you some questions?</string>
  <string id="110398">I&apos;ll leave you alone.</string>
  <string id="110401">Do you have a moment to talk?</string>
  <string id="110403">I don&apos;t know you, are you from Two Rivers?</string>
  <string id="110406">Is that why you&apos;re nervous? I could lend you some silver.</string>
  <string id="110407">Why do you need money badly?</string>
  <string id="110408">Sounds like tough luck to me.</string>
  <string id="110411">I could talk to his son about this for you.</string>
  <string id="110413">What will happen if you don&apos;t pay the twenty silver?</string>
  <string id="110414">If you can&apos;t repay your debts, you&apos;ll have to live with the consequences.</string>
  <string id="110415">The price of a small pig, you said? Let me give you the twenty silver.</string>
  <string id="110417">[Charm] I&apos;m sure you&apos;ll find some way to repay me eventually.</string>
  <string id="110419">[Intimidation] You shame us both by calling this meaningless charity!</string>
  <string id="110421">[Intuition] Your ancestors will be more upset if you can&apos;t repay that debt.</string>
  <string id="110424" soundid="168389">Time to pay back your debt, farmer. Let&apos;s see if your life is worth a few silvers, ha!</string>
  <string id="110425" soundid="168390">You told me I should *do* something, student. Well, my new friends have given me an easy way to pay Gao the Greater back!</string>
  <string id="110428" soundid="168406">You... would have? Oh my. Well, I hate to bring it up, especially now, but there&apos;s the small matter of my chest.</string>
  <string id="110429" soundid="168407">Which is to say, its contents were not there. The bandits had taken almost everything I had, but I know it was still there when... well, when you arrived.</string>
  <string id="110430" soundid="168408">It was rather full of silver. A life&apos;s savings, you know. Would you happen to know what happened?</string>
  <string id="110431" soundid="168409">Such generosity!</string>
  <string id="110432" soundid="168410">Oh my. Well, that&apos;s all right. You couldn&apos;t have known.</string>
  <string id="110433" soundid="168411">Oh, no, no! I would never make a demand. In fact, I was just wondering if you had found it.</string>
  <string id="110434" soundid="168412">[Success] You saw... nothing. I understand.</string>
  <string id="110435" soundid="168413">[Failure] You may be considered the best student at this school--everyone knows that--but you can&apos;t lie to my face!</string>
  <string id="110436" soundid="168414">Out of respect for your master, I&apos;ll forget you tried.</string>
  <string id="110437" soundid="168415">I was thinking that while the silver is mine, you deserve a reward for all your good work. What say you to half of the silver that was in that chest?</string>
  <string id="110438" soundid="168416">There are days when I&apos;m more proud than usual to be your friend, you know that?</string>
  <string id="110439" soundid="168417">Thank you so much. I will never forget this.</string>
  <string id="110440" soundid="168418">The whole village is talking about you, and it&apos;s richly deserved. Good day to you!</string>
  <string id="110441" soundid="168419">But... but that silver was mine! What gives you the right to take it? You&apos;re no better than those bandits!</string>
  <string id="110442" soundid="168420">Maybe I couldn&apos;t protect it, but I could at least earn it honestly!</string>
  <string id="110443" soundid="168421">You&apos;re no better than those bandits! You saved my life, but that doesn&apos;t justify your thuggery!</string>
  <string id="110444" soundid="168422">I had always thought your Master strove to teach you students values. It seems I was wrong!</string>
  <string id="110446">I was glad to help.</string>
  <string id="110448">Those bandits learned a lesson in humility.</string>
  <string id="110450">You should have fought for your home. You were cowering when I went down there.</string>
  <string id="110452">If I&apos;d had longer, I would have made them suffer more.</string>
  <string id="110455">That silver was yours? I&apos;m so sorry! Here, have it back.</string>
  <string id="110457">I want to repay you, but I appear to have spent some of it.</string>
  <string id="110459">I saved your life, and you demand your money back?</string>
  <string id="110461">[Intimidation] I saw no chest. Don&apos;t come to me with these lies.</string>
  <string id="110465">I won&apos;t take any of your savings. You need it more than I.</string>
  <string id="110468">I appreciate that. Here, have half your silver back.</string>
  <string id="110469">No. I&apos;m keeping it all.</string>
  <string id="110470">If you cannot protect what is yours, then it is not truly yours.</string>
  <string id="110472">If you value silver more than your life, you are a fool.</string>
  <string id="110474">I don&apos;t need a reason. Get out of my sight, you worm.</string>
  <string id="110475" soundid="168453">What, oh... I didn&apos;t see you there. This magnificent sculpture takes all of my attention, I&apos;m afraid. Is there something I can help you with?</string>
  <string id="110476" soundid="168454">My name is Tong Wei. I am a Master Excavator from the Valley of the Sprightly Stones. I am here to oversee the installation of this fine specimen of rock.</string>
  <string id="110477" soundid="168455">This is one of the finest specimens to come from the Valley of the Sprightly Stones in some time. That is why Sagacious Tien himself is carved upon it.</string>
  <string id="110478" soundid="168456">I apologize. I sometimes get excited when speaking about one of our grandest treasures. The valley is truly remarkable.</string>
  <string id="110479" soundid="168457">No one knows exactly. There are theories of course. Some say it is divine, and others say it is simply a trick of nature. But the debates truly don&apos;t matter.</string>
  <string id="110480" soundid="168458">The stones are remarkable, regardless of the reasons for their sprightly behavior. I count myself honored to be able to work so closely with these wonderful stones.</string>
  <string id="110481" soundid="168459">Of course, looking upon this sculpture, it is easy to see why some believe that the divine had a hand in their making.</string>
  <string id="110482" soundid="168460">Ah, the Valley of the Sprightly Stones. It is truly a marvel. Discovered many centuries ago by explorers who saw the floating stones from some way off.</string>
  <string id="110483" soundid="168461">Eventually, people came from around the Empire to marvel at the strange occurrence. It wasn&apos;t until Emperor Yu Baosi that the stones were used to build.</string>
  <string id="110484" soundid="168462">The grandest achievement is the Imperial Palace itself, which floats above the city like a grand heaven. Of course, it uses additional magic to keep it aloft.</string>
  <string id="110485" soundid="168463">Oh, yes... I have much to do myself. Good fortune to you.</string>
  <string id="110486" soundid="168464">Ah, good to see you again. Have you come back to enjoy this magnificent piece of workmanship? Or do you simply wish to talk?</string>
  <string id="110487">Who are you?</string>
  <string id="110488">You don&apos;t look like one of the scholars.</string>
  <string id="110490">What so magnificent about this sculpture?</string>
  <string id="110492">What makes the stones so... sprightly?</string>
  <string id="110495">Tell me more about the valley where these stones come from.</string>
  <string id="110498">I need to be going now.</string>
  <string id="110500">Die like a coward!</string>
  <string id="110501">Suffer forever!</string>
  <string id="110502">Taste death!</string>
  <string id="110503">You are weak!</string>
  <string id="110504">I see your death!</string>
  <string id="110509">Healing.</string>
  <string id="110510">I will not succumb.</string>
  <string id="110511">That is the way!</string>
  <string id="110513">If she&apos;s an ancient ally of yours, I&apos;m sure she&apos;ll want to help, if I can find her.</string>
  <string id="110515" soundid="168500">Of course, if you survive this final dish, I will gladly reimburse all your silver. I may even have a few treasures that I could part with.</string>
  <string id="110516" soundid="168501">If you&apos;ll excuse me, I must go in search of new ingredients, for it seems you have eaten everything I have. Good fortune to you.</string>
  <string id="110517" soundid="168502">[You retrieve Chai Jin&apos;s purse and a glowing gem from his corpse]</string>
  <string id="110518" soundid="168503">[You leave]</string>
  <string id="110519">Jin&apos;s Exotic Weapon&apos;s</string>
  <string id="110521">Here&apos;s another 300 silver. Let me try it!</string>
  <string id="110524">[Loot the body]</string>
  <string id="110525">[Leave]</string>
  <string id="110528">Horse Demon</string>
  <string id="110533">Lotus Assassin</string>
  <string id="110536">Imperial Guard</string>
  <string id="110539">Imperial Guard</string>
  <string id="110542">Rat Demon</string>
  <string id="110545">Ghost</string>
  <string id="110548">Mask Spirit</string>
  <string id="110552">Villager</string>
  <string id="110555">Villager</string>
  <string id="110558">Fox Spirit</string>
  <string id="110567">Tong Wei</string>
  <string id="110570">Phoenix Assassin</string>
  <string id="110573">Phoenix Assassin</string>
  <string id="110576">Phoenix Assassin</string>
  <string id="110594" soundid="168595">Behind you!</string>
  <string id="110598">Commoner</string>
  <string id="110601">Commoner</string>
  <string id="110604">Peasant</string>
  <string id="110607">Peasant</string>
  <string id="110610">Don&apos;t Save</string>
  <string id="110611">Peasant</string>
  <string id="110614">Peasant</string>
  <string id="110619">Jade Empire Bestiary: Vol. 4</string>
  <string id="110623">Save</string>
  <string id="110624">Commoner</string>
  <string id="110627">Commoner</string>
  <string id="110630">Peasant</string>
  <string id="110633">Peasant</string>
  <string id="110636">You can&apos;t resist!</string>
  <string id="110637">You&apos;re going down!</string>
  <string id="110642">My body is... better now!</string>
  <string id="110643">Wh... what have you done to me?</string>
  <string id="110644">That&apos;ll show you!</string>
  <string id="110645">I can&apos;t do anything?!</string>
  <string id="110646">I&apos;ll stop you!</string>
  <string id="110647">You won&apos;t do this!</string>
  <string id="110648">I won&apos;t let you do this!</string>
  <string id="110649">That&apos;s enough for you!</string>
  <string id="110650">No more!</string>
  <string id="110651">This can&apos;t happen!</string>
  <string id="110656">I can take more!</string>
  <string id="110657">I&apos;m... poisoned!</string>
  <string id="110658">Take that!</string>
  <string id="110659">You are unharmed?!</string>
  <string id="110660">You will fall now.</string>
  <string id="110661">You cannot resist us.</string>
  <string id="110662">The Emperor&apos;s will be done.</string>
  <string id="110663">All traitors die!</string>
  <string id="110664">Your death will be painful.</string>
  <string id="110665">We cannot be defeated.</string>
  <string id="110670">I heal and I can continue.</string>
  <string id="110671">You have poisoned me.</string>
  <string id="110672">Your death comes.</string>
  <string id="110673">That didn&apos;t work...</string>
  <string id="110674">You&apos;re dead now!</string>
  <string id="110675">You won&apos;t resist me for long!</string>
  <string id="110676">Your chi is weak!</string>
  <string id="110677">I will not be defeated!</string>
  <string id="110678">The dance of battle...</string>
  <string id="110679">My style is superior!</string>
  <string id="110684">I&apos;m better...</string>
  <string id="110685">You fight dirty!</string>
  <string id="110686">Take that!</string>
  <string id="110687">That didn&apos;t work...</string>
  <string id="110688">You&apos;re dead now!</string>
  <string id="110689">You won&apos;t resist me for long!</string>
  <string id="110690">Your chi is weak!</string>
  <string id="110691">I will not be defeated!</string>
  <string id="110692">The dance of battle...</string>
  <string id="110693">My style is superior!</string>
  <string id="110698">I&apos;m better...</string>
  <string id="110699">You fight dirty!</string>
  <string id="110700">Take that!</string>
  <string id="110701">That didn&apos;t work...</string>
  <string id="110702">You&apos;re dead now!</string>
  <string id="110703">You won&apos;t resist me for long!</string>
  <string id="110704">Your chi is weak!</string>
  <string id="110705">I will not be defeated!</string>
  <string id="110706">The dance of battle...</string>
  <string id="110707">My style is superior!</string>
  <string id="110712">I&apos;m better...</string>
  <string id="110713">You fight dirty!</string>
  <string id="110714">Take that!</string>
  <string id="110715">That didn&apos;t work...</string>
  <string id="110716">You&apos;re dead now!</string>
  <string id="110717">You won&apos;t resist me for long!</string>
  <string id="110718">Your chi is weak!</string>
  <string id="110719">I will not be defeated!</string>
  <string id="110720">The dance of battle...</string>
  <string id="110721">My style is superior!</string>
  <string id="110726">I&apos;m better...</string>
  <string id="110727">You fight dirty!</string>
  <string id="110728">Take that!</string>
  <string id="110729">No effect?!</string>
  <string id="110730">Fighting is life.</string>
  <string id="110731">This ends in death.</string>
  <string id="110732">Crush you!</string>
  <string id="110733">No one beats me!</string>
  <string id="110734">This&apos;ll be fun!</string>
  <string id="110735">I&apos;ll beat you!</string>
  <string id="110740">Healed! I won&apos;t stop!</string>
  <string id="110741">I&apos;m... weakened...</string>
  <string id="110742">That should end it!</string>
  <string id="110743">No effect?!</string>
  <string id="110744">Fighting is life.</string>
  <string id="110745">This ends in death.</string>
  <string id="110746">Crush you!</string>
  <string id="110747">No one beats me!</string>
  <string id="110748">This&apos;ll be fun!</string>
  <string id="110749">I&apos;ll beat you!</string>
  <string id="110754">Healed! I won&apos;t stop!</string>
  <string id="110755">I&apos;m... weakened...</string>
  <string id="110756">That should end it!</string>
  <string id="110757">No effect?!</string>
  <string id="110758">Fighting is life.</string>
  <string id="110759">This ends in death.</string>
  <string id="110760">Crush you!</string>
  <string id="110761">No one beats me!</string>
  <string id="110762">This&apos;ll be fun!</string>
  <string id="110763">I&apos;ll beat you!</string>
  <string id="110768">Healed! I won&apos;t stop!</string>
  <string id="110769">I&apos;m... weakened...</string>
  <string id="110770">That should end it!</string>
  <string id="110771">Why can&apos;t I hurt you?</string>
  <string id="110772">I&apos;ll beat you!</string>
  <string id="110773">I&apos;ll prove myself!</string>
  <string id="110774">You won&apos;t be difficult!</string>
  <string id="110775">Everyone sees me!</string>
  <string id="110776">No way you&apos;ll win!</string>
  <string id="110777">My style will beat you!</string>
  <string id="110782">I... I can go on! I&apos;m healed!</string>
  <string id="110783">You poisoned me!</string>
  <string id="110784">Haah!</string>
  <string id="110785">So that didn&apos;t work, did it?</string>
  <string id="110786">You&apos;re going down!</string>
  <string id="110787">Nothing you can do!</string>
  <string id="110788">This will end quickly.</string>
  <string id="110789">Don&apos;t try to resist!</string>
  <string id="110790">This fight ends now!</string>
  <string id="110791">Down you go!</string>
  <string id="110796">I&apos;m healed!</string>
  <string id="110797">Gah! You poisoned me!</string>
  <string id="110798">That had to hurt!</string>
  <string id="110799">I WILL hurt you!</string>
  <string id="110800">I burn brightly!</string>
  <string id="110801">You&apos;ll burn!</string>
  <string id="110802">Maggot!</string>
  <string id="110803">Death comes!</string>
  <string id="110804">You&apos;ll never have my head!</string>
  <string id="110805">You&apos;ll scream soon!</string>
  <string id="110810">I have healed.</string>
  <string id="110811">You think poison will stop me?</string>
  <string id="110812">Scream while you burn!</string>
  <string id="110813">You&apos;re tough!</string>
  <string id="110814">I&apos;ll beat you!</string>
  <string id="110815">You won&apos;t escape me!</string>
  <string id="110816">Time to die!</string>
  <string id="110817">Just die quietly!</string>
  <string id="110818">This is what you deserve!</string>
  <string id="110819">I&apos;m stronger than you!</string>
  <string id="110824">I&apos;ve healed.</string>
  <string id="110825">How could you... poison me?</string>
  <string id="110826">I told you!</string>
  <string id="110827" soundid="168862">Jizu draws strength from all others. They serve Jizu!</string>
  <string id="110828" soundid="168863">You can not hurt Jizu! He king of all in this place!</string>
  <string id="110829">You weren&apos;t hurt?</string>
  <string id="110830">You&apos;re nothing!</string>
  <string id="110831">Die!</string>
  <string id="110832">Die like a dog!</string>
  <string id="110833">You&apos;re nothing but talk!</string>
  <string id="110834">I will prove myself!</string>
  <string id="110835">My skills are unmatched!</string>
  <string id="110840">Now I&apos;m better!</string>
  <string id="110841">You... you&apos;ve poisoned me?!</string>
  <string id="110842">Now you die!</string>
  <string id="110857">Hidden bonus: Book set complete!</string>
  <string id="110858" soundid="178552">Are you certain? This doesn&apos;t seem right.</string>
  <string id="110859" soundid="178553">Is that really necessary? I know our task is important, but I question this.</string>
  <string id="110860" soundid="178554">I don&apos;t think this is really that necessary, is it?</string>
  <string id="110861" soundid="178555">Whatever. As long as I get to wet my axes.</string>
  <string id="110862">L</string>
  <string id="110863">R</string>
  <string id="110864" soundid="178556">Is this really necessary?</string>
  <string id="110865" soundid="178557">This isn&apos;t fun. You shouldn&apos;t be such a bully.</string>
  <string id="110866" soundid="178558">Ah, why pass off a good fight?</string>
  <string id="110867" soundid="178559">Yes, give the task to someone that really wants it.</string>
  <string id="110868" soundid="178560">People get what they deserve. Or they should.</string>
  <string id="110869" soundid="178561">This place is full of nothing but cold killers. They are all the same.</string>
  <string id="110870" soundid="178562">A cold attitude, but a man has to eat, I suppose.</string>
  <string id="110871" soundid="178563">What&apos;s one death? Spit in a bucket.</string>
  <string id="110872" soundid="178564">It is sad that he could talk like that. This place colors your thinking.</string>
  <string id="110873" soundid="178565">I would be sad. People here don&apos;t seem to feel much at all.</string>
  <string id="110874">Just kill them all. Our cause is more important than them.</string>
  <string id="110884" soundid="168919">Finally! Someone stronger than these cowed peasants. This town disgusts me. I am Scholar Six Heavens, and I need someone who possesses great strength and skill.</string>
  <string id="110887" soundid="168922">Have you managed to retrieve the bridge from the Zither of Discord? It is somewhere in the Great Southern Forest. Just follow the north gate, near the center of town.</string>
  <string id="110889" soundid="168924">You&apos;re back? I wait to hear of your success.</string>
  <string id="110890" soundid="168925">Do you? Impressive. Give it here.</string>
  <string id="110891" soundid="168926">This will show those stuffy scholars in the Imperial City that I am serious. People will talk for centuries about this discovery! *My* discovery.</string>
  <string id="110892" soundid="168927">You... what? You met the ghost of the greatest thinker in the Empire and dispersed it? Give me the bridge, then, and take your fool&apos;s reward.</string>
  <string id="110894" soundid="168929">Did he? And you killed him to... protect me?</string>
  <string id="110895" soundid="168930">So it seems. Maybe I misjudged the Way of the Closed Fist. Had you followed its tenets perfectly, I would be dead now.</string>
  <string id="110897" soundid="168932">Here is your reward. I will return to my quarters for some solitude and...reflection. You have my thanks.</string>
  <string id="110898" soundid="168933">The rashness of your actions reveal how little you understand about the Way of the Closed Fist. Regardless, here is the silver I promised you.</string>
  <string id="110900" soundid="168935">Here is the silver I promised you. I should be able to return to the Imperial City in triumph after I spend a few more months here, in seclusion, studying the instrument.</string>
  <string id="110901" soundid="168936">Do not bother me with your minor successess. Completing half a task is completing nothing at all. I need *both* components of the Zither of Discord.</string>
  <string id="110904" soundid="168939">Yes, as I thought. These are the original strings, and the case seems untouched by age. Perfect.</string>
  <string id="110905" soundid="168940">The bridge is missing, as I thought it would be. Since you have proven capable so far, I&apos;d like you to acquire one more part.</string>
  <string id="110907" soundid="168942">Bladed Thesis penned his last work in contemplation of the Great Southern Forest. That is why the pieces are all here around Tien&apos;s Landing. </string>
  <string id="110909" soundid="168944">If we can recover the last part of this zither, the bridge that would lift the strings off the case, then I will double the silver I was going to give you.</string>
  <string id="110910" soundid="168945">You don&apos;t *think* you have time? What sort of answer is that? You do, or you do not.</string>
  <string id="110911" soundid="168946">Good. In his last work, Bladed Thesis wrote of the &quot;final test,&quot; and it taking place where &quot;wood met water and rock.&quot;</string>
  <string id="110914" soundid="168949">Here. This is the silver for your efforts. I will retire to my quarters in this town and study what I have so far.</string>
  <string id="110915" soundid="168950">It is a shame you lacked the drive to see this through.</string>
  <string id="110916" soundid="168951">As I said, I believe it&apos;s in the Great Southern Forest at the spot where Bladed Thesis penned his last work. A place where &quot;wood met water and rock.&quot;</string>
  <string id="110917" soundid="168952">The work talks of a test for followers of his philosophies. I suspect the reward is the final piece to his famous Zither of Discord.</string>
  <string id="110918" soundid="168953">Yes, that&apos;s it! Now I suspect this final test is magical in nature. You should go there and attempt it, as long as you are confident in your understanding of the Way.</string>
  <string id="110919">To Imperial City</string>
  <string id="110920" soundid="168955">From studying the full text, it seems that it would be near a river in the Great Southern Forest. There must be some structure that allowed him to stay there for some time.</string>
  <string id="110923" soundid="168958">I expect the test to measure your conviction to the ideals of the Way of the Closed Fist. Bladed Thesis would not let his instrument fall into anyone else&apos;s hands.</string>
  <string id="110925">Focus Shrine</string>
  <string id="110926" soundid="168961">The strings should be in the army&apos;s outpost tower to the west of Tien&apos;s Landing, just outside the gates to the old ruins. The case rests in Gao the Greater&apos;s pirate lair.</string>
  <string id="110928" soundid="168963">How you reach the pirates&apos; lair is your problem. Perhaps you already know a way, or Minister Sheng may have some insight.</string>
  <string id="110929" soundid="168964">As I said, it was an instrument that belonged to Bladed Thesis, the scholar who first advanced the Way of the Closed Fist as a philosophy.</string>
  <string id="110930" soundid="168965">It is said that he played this instrument before writing some of his greatest works, as if the instrument particularly inspired him.</string>
  <string id="110932" soundid="168967">The basic premise of Bladed Thesis&apos; writings was that one could live life according to a philosophy of strength. If one is too weak to help oneself, one deserves no help.</string>
  <string id="110933" soundid="168968">Some mistook him as encouraging immoral acts or &quot;evil,&quot; but his true argument was that life was a test which could only be passed through struggle.</string>
  <string id="110935" soundid="168970">Evil men act without reason. Followers of the Way act with the intention of encouraging others to become stronger. The action may be the same but the intent differs.</string>
  <string id="110938" soundid="168973">Played from a seated position, the entire instrument is a soundboard with strings that run across its length. Beneath skilled hands, it offers the sound of heaven itself.</string>
  <string id="110940" soundid="168975">The Zither of Discord is as unique as it is ancient, however. It has five strings instead of seven, and each is fashioned from unbreakable silk.</string>
  <string id="110941" soundid="168976">Go to the forest and see if you can find the place I described.</string>
  <string id="110942" soundid="168977">Remember, I need both the case and the strings of the Zither of Discord. Bring them here when you find them.</string>
  <string id="110943" soundid="168978">If you change your mind. I&apos;ll be here.</string>
  <string id="110944" soundid="168979">No! What...?</string>
  <string id="110945" soundid="168980">Mostly, though, I need someone like you, who walks the Way of the Closed Fist. Aid me, and I will see that you are rewarded most generously.</string>
  <string id="110947" soundid="168982">What I do not need, however, is someone who walks the Way of the Open Palm. I can read in every movement that you would protect the weak and coddle the poor.</string>
  <string id="110948" soundid="168983">They must protect themselves! You see? Your every action, and each word, tells me that you are not the person I need.</string>
  <string id="110949" soundid="168984">That is exactly the case. You are not worthy to help me in my task. I need someone who understands that discord, friction, and trial are the true sources of strength.</string>
  <string id="110950" soundid="168985">Amusing. You encourage me to solve my own problems. That is exactly the attitude I need to aid me in my project. If you make your actions match your words, I will reconsider.</string>
  <string id="110951" soundid="168986">If I can see by your actions that you understand the Way of the Closed Fist, I promise to make it worth your while. Otherwise, I will not waste any more time with you.</string>
  <string id="110953" soundid="168988">You? Again?</string>
  <string id="110954" soundid="168989">My offer still stands, if you are interested. I need your help to recover an artifact, and I have silver enough to justify your aid.</string>
  <string id="110955" soundid="168990">I seek the Zither of Discord, an artifact that belonged to Bladed Thesis, the sage who first advanced the Way of the Closed Fist as a philosophy.</string>
  <string id="110958" soundid="168993">The Imperial Army found the strings not too long ago and will soon send them to the Imperial Museum where they&apos;ll rot and be forgotten. I will make far better use of them.</string>
  <string id="110960" soundid="168995">Currently, I believe the army has stored the strings in the outpost tower just outside of Tien&apos;s Landing to the west. It&apos;s near the gates to the old town ruins.</string>
  <string id="110961" soundid="168996">A merchant lord named Gao the Greater recently acquired the case but knows nothing of its import. Up the river lies a pirate stronghold, where Gao was recently seen.</string>
  <string id="110963" soundid="168998">You will have to find a way there if you hope to acquire the case. Perhaps Minister Sheng could suggest a way to reach these pirates. He might even be grateful for your aid.</string>
  <string id="110964" soundid="168999">Bladed Thesis was a genius, and I am a strong adherent of his writings. I also believe there is more to the zither than meets the eye, if it were only to be reassembled.</string>
  <string id="110966" soundid="169001">No. I will not waste time on pleasantries or mindless questions about this muddy cluster of hovels. I need aid, not friends.</string>
  <string id="110967" soundid="169002">I see that you have found an understanding of the Way of the Closed Fist. I still need a skilled warrior&apos;s aid.</string>
  <string id="110968" soundid="169003">I have no time for those who do not understand strength. Return when your actions tell me that you follow the Way of the Closed Fist and perhaps I will consider you.</string>
  <string id="110972">Someone must protect the weak. What&apos;s so wrong about that?</string>
  <string id="110974">You&apos;re saying you need help, but not mine?</string>
  <string id="110976">I don&apos;t need this. Solve your own problem.</string>
  <string id="110980">I&apos;m interested. What do you need done?</string>
  <string id="110982">What&apos;s so important about this instrument?</string>
  <string id="110983">Where would I find the strings?</string>
  <string id="110986">Where would I find the case?</string>
  <string id="110989">Why do you need these items?</string>
  <string id="110991">Could I ask you some other questions before I go?</string>
  <string id="110992">I&apos;ll start looking for them now.</string>
  <string id="110993">How about answering a few questions for me instead?</string>
  <string id="110995">Ghost</string>
  <string id="110997">I have the bridge here. It&apos;s all yours.</string>
  <string id="110999">I have the bridge, but I had to defeat the spirit of Bladed Thesis.</string>
  <string id="111001">You should know that Bladed Thesis planned to kill you.</string>
  <string id="111002">Sometimes you have to protect the weak.</string>
  <string id="111004">Ghost</string>
  <string id="111005">No, I just killed him for fun. But I thought you should know.</string>
  <string id="111007">Here. It&apos;s yours.</string>
  <string id="111009">I&apos;ve found one of the components you were looking for.</string>
  <string id="111011">I found both of the components you were looking for.</string>
  <string id="111012">Ghost</string>
  <string id="111014">What do you need me to do?</string>
  <string id="111019">I don&apos;t think I have time.</string>
  <string id="111020">I&apos;ll do it.</string>
  <string id="111023">I&apos;ll have to pass. Good luck.</string>
  <string id="111025">Forget it. I&apos;m done helping you.</string>
  <string id="111026">It&apos;s time for you to find someone else to help you.</string>
  <string id="111028">Can we go over where you think the instrument&apos;s bridge is, again?</string>
  <string id="111030">There&apos;s a wooden gazebo overlooking a river in the forest.</string>
  <string id="111032">Where is this spot?</string>
  <string id="111035">What was the &quot;test&quot; you mentioned?</string>
  <string id="111038">That&apos;s all I needed to know about finding the bridge.</string>
  <string id="111039">Where should I look for the components?</string>
  <string id="111042">Can I ask you more details about this Zither of Discord?</string>
  <string id="111045">Tell me more about the Way of the Closed Fist.</string>
  <string id="111048">How is that different from our concept of evil?</string>
  <string id="111051">What exactly is a zither?</string>
  <string id="111054">Goodbye.</string>
  <string id="111081">Take this!</string>
  <string id="111082">My style is perfect!</string>
  <string id="111087">I have healed.</string>
  <string id="111088">I... I&apos;ve been poisoned!</string>
</tlk>