<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<tlk language="0">
  <string id="22771">Afraid</string>
  <string id="22772">Sorry, Bin. I&apos;m letting Miao have her revenge.</string>
  <string id="22774">Howling Haulun</string>
  <string id="22777">Do as Bin says, Yushan. Bury these bones.</string>
  <string id="22783" soundid="125467">Wait! This man is just a poor peasant. Show some compassion. At least hear what he has to say!</string>
  <string id="22784">Fleeing</string>
  <string id="22785">Old Mother Kwan</string>
  <string id="22850" soundid="135860">This forest is full of ghosts, and they grow bolder by the day. They have never appeared in this campsite before, but now I find you under attack here.</string>
  <string id="22879" soundid="141785">You have no right to talk, vermin.</string>
  <string id="22880" soundid="141786">And here is one more to kill for Gao. What fun.</string>
  <string id="22882">Slaver</string>
  <string id="22883" soundid="26319">You are an orphan, but you were not abandoned. You were rescued from the temple of Dirge, in the Land of Howling Spirits. You were orphaned by violent action.</string>
  <string id="22884">Thank you for the bout.</string>
  <string id="22886">Sagacious Zu</string>
  <string id="22887" soundid="26323">I take responsibility for it. You see, I used to be more than a humble teacher. To learn of yourself, you must learn more of me. I was once leader of the Imperial Army.</string>
  <string id="22888">Each bruise is a mark of your failure to learn our Master&apos;s teachings.</string>
  <string id="22890">Such things happen.</string>
  <string id="22891">Enjoy it. It won&apos;t happen again.</string>
  <string id="22894" soundid="26330">I am sorry, but I wanted your development unspoiled by expectation, and with the events of late... well, there have been many factors acting upon you.</string>
  <string id="22898" soundid="131758"></string>
  <string id="22899" soundid="68527">I almost forgot! The director asked me to give you this. He was very pleased with how you worked the new revisions into the play so naturally.</string>
  <string id="22904" soundid="26340">I will tell you more, but first, we have an uninvited visitor.</string>
  <string id="22905" soundid="26341"></string>
  <string id="22906" soundid="26342"></string>
  <string id="22907" soundid="26343"></string>
  <string id="22908" soundid="26344">Gao never could keep his ears to himself, especially when angry. So predictable. He&apos;s heard as much as I wanted him to. Perhaps it will give him a little perspective.</string>
  <string id="22909" soundid="26345">He should respect even the most humble person, because who knows what lies within? That includes you and me both.</string>
  <string id="22913" soundid="26349">I withdrew my support, and tried to rally your people against the siege I had helped plan. A doomed effort. Many died on both sides. Sun Kin, another brother, also fell.</string>
  <string id="22914" soundid="26350">Your people were killed. I am haunted by it, and now the world may join me. The assassin on the beach was a Lotus Assassin, a minion of Death&apos;s Hand. More will come.</string>
  <string id="22915" soundid="26351">Most in the Empire know nothing of the Land of Howling Spirits. I found its people to be honorable, but I can&apos;t tell you more than that. There was no time to learn more.</string>
  <string id="22917" soundid="26353">You were meant for something important, but because of my actions it was denied you. Stories about ghosts... the assassin on the beach. You are tied to this.</string>
  <string id="22920" soundid="26356">The Spirit Cave will make things as clear as they can be. Only you are meant to understand what is within. You will see the corruption of the spirit realm for yourself.</string>
  <string id="22924" soundid="26360">No, but few places truly are. This has been a lot to comprehend, so take your time. There are instructions inside, and something that belongs to you. An amulet.</string>
  <string id="22925" soundid="26361">When you emerge you will know more about yourself and your destiny than I can explain. And you will better know your enemy.</string>
  <string id="22927" soundid="26363"></string>
  <string id="22928" soundid="26364"></string>
  <string id="22929" soundid="26365">It was partly the strange skills of Dawn Star that showed me to the corruption, and partly something that belongs to you. You&apos;ll understand when you enter.</string>
  <string id="22930" soundid="26366">Er, well, it is thought that spirits naturally try to find their way to the underworld, but if their lives or deaths were painful, they return to what was familiar.</string>
  <string id="22931" soundid="26367">The school has seen its share of tragedy in the past. Something of yours has allowed me to keep the students protected, but the dead will be everywhere soon enough.</string>
  <string id="22932" soundid="26368">You must enter and see for yourself.</string>
  <string id="22933" soundid="26369">Good. Focus on that. It will... keep your head clear. I know you are up to this task. There are instructions inside, and something that belongs to you. An amulet.</string>
  <string id="22934" soundid="26370">He is the right hand of the Emperor, and rules the Lotus Assassins in place of Prince Sun Kin who was killed at Dirge, a death he may have orchestrated.</string>
  <string id="22935" soundid="26371">He shows no hesitation, and gave no thought to the lives of those we faced. His influence poisons the Emperor. I have no doubt he is utterly evil.</string>
  <string id="22936" soundid="156563">I know you. You are servants of the Water Dragon, who once ruled Dirge. But your mistress has no power here now.</string>
  <string id="22937" soundid="26373">There were three: Emperor Sun Hai; Prince Sun Kin the Hand of Heaven; and myself, Sun Li the Glorious Strategist. Age decided our place in the order of things.</string>
  <string id="22938" soundid="26374">Sun Hai was the eldest and therefore emperor. I was next and was head of the army. Sun Kin was the youngest and leader of the monastic order.</string>
  <string id="22939" soundid="156157"></string>
  <string id="22940" soundid="26376">Your people were guardians, but we did not have a clear idea of what. It is tied to your destiny. I will explain if you want me to move on.</string>
  <string id="22941" soundid="26377">I&apos;ve hid it well, along with my shame. He seized your homeland during the Long Drought. It was an aggressive change in the Empire that would soon bring Death&apos;s Hand to power.</string>
  <string id="22946" soundid="26382"></string>
  <string id="22947" soundid="26383"></string>
  <string id="22948" soundid="26384">What are you doing out here? You are supposed to be meditating on the amulet and what you have learned for at least another day!</string>
  <string id="22949" soundid="26385">A vision? Ah... of course you did. A natural reaction to the great amount of information I have placed before you. It may have something to do with your amulet.</string>
  <string id="22950" soundid="26386">Er... tell me, did you learn anything about the destiny that stretches before you? Or what has led you this far?</string>
  <string id="22951" soundid="26387">A spirit released you? That explains your strange exit. This is a very sudden development I did not foresee. Perhaps it has something to do with your amulet.</string>
  <string id="22955" soundid="26391"></string>
  <string id="22956" soundid="26392">Master Li! There&apos;s still no sign of her.</string>
  <string id="22957" soundid="26393">What? What is it, Woo? I&apos;m sorry, my mind was elsewhere.</string>
  <string id="22958" soundid="26394">Dawn Star, as I told you, Master. She went missing after Gao&apos;s men were discovered in the school. The state of her room suggests some sort of fight took place.</string>
  <string id="22959" soundid="26395">I see. She is not there?</string>
  <string id="22960" soundid="26396">No, Master Li. There is no sign of her.</string>
  <string id="22961" soundid="26397">I see. This may prove useful. Thank you, Jing Woo. You may go.</string>
  <string id="22962" soundid="26398"></string>
  <string id="22963" soundid="26399">Your appearance put Gao&apos;s disgrace out of my mind, but it would seem that your... early exit from the caves has come at just the right time.</string>
  <string id="22964" soundid="26400">I doubt she has come to harm. She is a strong woman, as you know. That doesn&apos;t mean you shouldn&apos;t search for her. It will be a good measure of your ability.</string>
  <string id="22965" soundid="26401">I didn&apos;t mean to appear callous. I&apos;m sure Dawn Star is fine. What I meant was that this will serve as a final measure of your abilities.</string>
  <string id="22966" soundid="26402">What better way to show mastery over your abilities than to turn them towards helping your fellow student?</string>
  <string id="22967" soundid="26403">Seek her out. I doubt she is in the school, and someone would have seen her if she was in the village. You might want to try the surrounding marshland. </string>
  <string id="22968" soundid="26404">That is good. Time is very important. Here, take some silver. I asked Fen Do and the others to stock essence gems in preparation for this day. Hopefully, they have done so.</string>
  <string id="22969" soundid="26405">Questions must wait. Time is critical. Take some silver. I asked Fen Do and the others to stock essence gems in preparation for this day. Hopefully, they have done so.</string>
  <string id="22972" soundid="26408">Dawn Star needs you. Gao will not simply hide in the village. Leave quickly, but take your time searching the marshes. All will be clear when you return.</string>
  <string id="23000" soundid="155550">I think I&apos;m better now. The Other is down... far down. I can&apos;t really tell where he is anymore. I know I&apos;ll stay with you no matter what.</string>
  <string id="23007">Sorcerer</string>
  <string id="23011">Summoned Ghost</string>
  <string id="23012">How would I know that? You tell me nothing!</string>
  <string id="23016" soundid="144493">You are a fool. You would act as the Empire&apos;s conscience, but you flock to the garish displays of Death&apos;s Hand, oblivious to the truth.</string>
  <string id="23017" soundid="144494">You lay claim to a powerful lineage. Indeed, you seem to have correctly named your enemy, despite the more obvious target of Death&apos;s Hand.</string>
  <string id="23018">I am listening. What is the next step?</string>
  <string id="23019" soundid="131759">You there. Sky. I see you skulking around like a ghost. Where have you been?</string>
  <string id="23024">Master! You&apos;ve never said anything about this!</string>
  <string id="23032">Why hide that you are the Emperor&apos;s brother?</string>
  <string id="23035">Can you tell me anything about my people?</string>
  <string id="23037">Let&apos;s move on. Tell me what this has to do with my destiny.</string>
  <string id="23038" soundid="155552">Kill...</string>
  <string id="23039" soundid="155797">Death...</string>
  <string id="23044">Is it safe?</string>
  <string id="23046" soundid="155554">Feed...</string>
  <string id="23049">Why is it part of the school?</string>
  <string id="23050">But how did it get here? How do you know what is inside?</string>
  <string id="23053">It still seems odd to me.</string>
  <string id="23055">Who is this &quot;Death&apos;s Hand?&quot;</string>
  <string id="23061">What do you mean that the world may join you?</string>
  <string id="23062">How many brothers are in the Emperor&apos;s family?</string>
  <string id="23063">I&apos;m not sure I believe you are the Emperor&apos;s brother.</string>
  <string id="23064" soundid="145340">I couldn&apos;t say. It was awfully large and looked heavy, but I was watching from a ways away. We didn&apos;t want to get close to that murderer.</string>
  <string id="23067">Why would I believe that? It&apos;s too incredible.</string>
  <string id="23070">Recessed Hatch</string>
  <string id="23071" soundid="109204">Don&apos;t let the novices bother you. They can be a bit annoying until they learn to respect you properly.</string>
  <string id="23074">I had a vision. It was very sudden. </string>
  <string id="23076">She said I was the last Spirit Monk. What does that mean?</string>
  <string id="23077">I didn&apos;t need that long. A spirit released me.</string>
  <string id="23090">Dawn Star is missing? Where would she go?</string>
  <string id="23092">What did you mean when you said this will be useful?</string>
  <string id="23095">I will start right away.</string>
  <string id="23096">I have more questions about what I have seen.</string>
  <string id="23099">I need information about this journey I&apos;m supposed to go on.</string>
  <string id="23131">Strange Spirit</string>
  <string id="23132" soundid="109205">If you want to learn how to fight, speak with First Brother. If you want to *see* great fighting, watch Third Brother.</string>
  <string id="23133" soundid="151642">Good. Let&apos;s head to the practice ring so Master Radiant can observe the fight from his room.</string>
  <string id="23134">Yes, let&apos;s begin.</string>
  <string id="23135">I&apos;m ready if you are.</string>
  <string id="23143" soundid="109213">Finally, Master Radiant is out of the way. Now Master Smiling Hawk can make our school strong again.</string>
  <string id="23145" soundid="109214">Master Smiling Hawk said you aren&apos;t a member of the school anymore. I&apos;m not allowed to fight with you.</string>
  <string id="23146" soundid="109215"></string>
  <string id="23147" soundid="154590">Thank you so much. I was at my wit&apos;s end. You&apos;ve done me a great service today.</string>
  <string id="23149" soundid="154591">Come Zhong, let&apos;s go home.</string>
  <string id="23151" soundid="109218">That&apos;s fine with me. The more I fight you, the closer I come to figuring out your technique.</string>
  <string id="23152" soundid="109219">You again. I&apos;ll fight you again if you want, but maybe you should try Fifth Brother next... if you haven&apos;t already. It&apos;s up to you.</string>
  <string id="23153" soundid="109220">Hello again. Come to regain your pride? Don&apos;t worry, I&apos;ve beaten most of the students here. I&apos;ll give you another chance, if you like.</string>
  <string id="23154" soundid="109221">Are you interested in fighting, or did you just come here to talk?</string>
  <string id="23155">I&apos;m always ready to fight!</string>
  <string id="23157" soundid="109223">So you&apos;re the one who was challenging our novices earlier. That might impress Master Radiant, but it won&apos;t get you noticed by Master Smiling Hawk.</string>
  <string id="23158" soundid="109224">I&apos;m Sixth Brother Gaoshan. If you think you can defeat a disciple of Master Smiling Hawk, challenge *me*. I assure you, I&apos;m much tougher than the novices.</string>
  <string id="23168" soundid="109225">All right, follow me.</string>
  <string id="23173" soundid="151646">You will be well rewarded... if you succeed. Go now... Third Brother has agreed to withdraw from his fight with you. You can deal directly with First Brother.</string>
  <string id="23177" soundid="51567">Master Li keeps talking about restless dead, but there&apos;s nothing like that around here.</string>
  <string id="23178" soundid="51568">Gao refuses to practice with the rest of us. He thinks he&apos;s too good for us.</string>
  <string id="23180" soundid="109232">Ha! So you&apos;d rather talk than fight. It&apos;s students like you that are giving the Black Leopard School a bad name.</string>
  <string id="23188" soundid="154592">Zhong coming. Zhong go home now.</string>
  <string id="23190">I&apos;d like to spar with you.</string>
  <string id="23191" soundid="144609">At the center of it all is the Emperor&apos;s Tomb. A monstrosity, I tell you. Completely unnecessary, but the Emperor&apos;s word is law. And they never even finished the thing.</string>
  <string id="23194">Cold Quing</string>
  <string id="23202">So there is no way I can get rid of you?</string>
  <string id="23206">I have you!</string>
  <string id="23207">My style won&apos;t serve here.</string>
  <string id="23211">Thug</string>
  <string id="23213">Cry for your life.</string>
  <string id="23214" soundid="27146">You have attracted a very odd minion in that girl, Wild Flower. I sense great conflict in that one. Tread lightly.</string>
  <string id="23215" soundid="27147">Sagacious Zu, could that be actual concern in your voice?</string>
  <string id="23216" soundid="27148">It would be a great inconvenience if we were all suddenly slaughtered. Now, what do you need of me?</string>
  <string id="23222" soundid="31129">Have I become such a thorn in the Serpent&apos;s side? How do you know this?</string>
  <string id="23223" soundid="126581">I&apos;ve come to finish what you started.</string>
  <string id="23224" soundid="107306">You got something to say, you say it to Ai Ling. She&apos;s in charge here.</string>
  <string id="23225">Guard</string>
  <string id="23229" soundid="145341">We hid out of sight as Gao went toward the gate out of town.</string>
  <string id="23231">&lt;CUSTOM0&gt; Silver</string>
  <string id="23232" soundid="191420"></string>
  <string id="23245">I got some red silk grass from Old Ming and need to return to Fen Do so he can produce the medicinal wraps.</string>
  <string id="23253">Kia Ming from the school asked me to get her some medicinal wraps from the merchant Fen Do in the village. I got some red silk grass from Old Ming and need to bring it to Fen Do so he can produce the wraps.</string>
  <string id="23267" soundid="156834">Ah, are you the student I am waiting for? I can&apos;t delay any longer. I cannot miss the window of opportunity for a summoning.</string>
  <string id="23274" soundid="156835">As I was saying, golems are playthings, devoid of cunning. The latest stockpile stands idle, waiting for a Jade Golem to make them useful. A waste.</string>
  <string id="23275" soundid="156836">I will show Grand Inquisitor Jia that tapping the spirit realm for servants is more efficient. Witness as I effortlessly summon an able minion from the void.</string>
  <string id="23276" soundid="156837">There are hardly any preparations needed, acolyte. They *want* to serve. They tell me so. Golems want nothing.</string>
  <string id="23281">Swamp Cave</string>
  <string id="23283">Jade Golem</string>
  <string id="23300" soundid="45783">Ours... mine. All mine. Alive, dead... no matter. All mine.</string>
  <string id="23336">To the school</string>
  <string id="23337" soundid="145342">Possibly, but we were too far away to say for sure. If you really want to know, go catch that fiend! He was headed for the gate out of town.</string>
  <string id="23338" soundid="127127">It is not important. Suffice to say that I prefer this little village to the temptations of a greater city. Enough about me. What else can I do for you?</string>
  <string id="23341" soundid="145343">Gao was in a rush, but you might be able to catch him still.</string>
  <string id="23343" soundid="31131">The feeling is mutual, though I think you deserve more than just thanks.</string>
  <string id="23344" soundid="31132">I suspect they are constantly adjusting odds through their control of the bets, but at least we can keep the combat honorable in the ring.</string>
  <string id="23345">Pirate</string>
  <string id="23346" soundid="31134">The whetstone must give of itself to hone the blade. For a second I thought I&apos;d detected a glimpse of altruism in this place.</string>
  <string id="23347" soundid="31135">I have long promised that I would train anyone who defeats me. My skills with the sword are imperfect but there are things I can teach you that no other could.</string>
  <string id="23423">Dawn Star</string>
  <string id="23503">Good Play, Satire</string>
  <string id="23504" soundid="70294"></string>
  <string id="23505" soundid="70295"></string>
  <string id="23506" soundid="70296">I can take you no farther. Be wary in this place. Pirates everywhere.</string>
  <string id="23507" soundid="109254">Master Radiant is a great leader, but he never comes out of his room anymore. Master Smiling Hawk, on the other hand... well, I shouldn&apos;t say anything about that.</string>
  <string id="23509">Rat Demon</string>
  <string id="23510">Crowd Member</string>
  <string id="23513" soundid="70300">Not I! Remember, this barge is our only way out of here. Someone has to guard it, or else the pirates could cut us off.</string>
  <string id="23516">Very well.</string>
  <string id="23523" soundid="27464">One of the slaves is loose!</string>
  <string id="23524" soundid="27465">Thief! Die!</string>
  <string id="23525" soundid="27466">You&apos;re in for it now!</string>
  <string id="23526" soundid="27467">You&apos;re going down!</string>
  <string id="23527" soundid="27468">You&apos;re a pretty lass, but I&apos;ll kill you anyway!</string>
  <string id="23617" soundid="27558">You&apos;re a handsome fella, but I&apos;ll kill you anyway!</string>
  <string id="23618" soundid="27559">I&apos;ll throw you in the slave pens, I will!</string>
  <string id="23619" soundid="27560">You shouldn&apos;t have come here!</string>
  <string id="23620" soundid="27561">Now you pay!</string>
  <string id="23621" soundid="27562">Scum! Do you know who we work for?</string>
  <string id="23622" soundid="27563">Master Gao will reward me for your head! Even the Lotus Assassins will be jealous!</string>
  <string id="23637">Search the Ruins</string>
  <string id="23638">

Wherein a Master foretells of doom,
A rival challenges for station, 
And the past haunts the present.

Your training nears its completion in the idyllic setting of Two Rivers. Master Li promises that soon you will know more about how you came here and where your future will lead. All the while, strange tales begin to spread of ghosts that will not rest and shadowy assassins who heed no law.</string>
  <string id="23639">Find the amulet lost in the ruins west of Tien&apos;s Landing. Be careful; there may be hidden dangers in the newly uncovered town.</string>
  <string id="23644">Hui told a story of a wounded monk who fled the destruction of Dirge with another piece of the amulet Master Li gave you. The monk died in old Tien&apos;s Landing, and his possessions were lost there when the village flooded. Now that the waters have receded, you should be able to recover the amulet piece and add it to the piece you now wear.</string>
  <string id="23647" soundid="164814">Something tells me it will be a long time before Min fully recovers.</string>
  <string id="23648" soundid="164815">It was good of you to help her. Min is the best of the newer students.</string>
  <string id="23649" soundid="142481"></string>
  <string id="23650">Where is Gao? He has taken my friend.</string>
  <string id="23653" soundid="112011"></string>
  <string id="23654" soundid="112012">Thank you, my lady. I have my daughter back, and we are free. If I had any type of reward to give you, it would be yours.</string>
  <string id="23655" soundid="112013">This... this is madness! Stop this at once! Put that knife down!</string>
  <string id="23656" soundid="112014">I... I don&apos;t want to be a slave. I have to be strong.</string>
  <string id="23657" soundid="112015"></string>
  <string id="23658" soundid="112016"></string>
  <string id="23659" soundid="112017">No! Fuyao, what have you done!</string>
  <string id="23668">Bend like the willow: switch styles with the directional pad to quickly adjust your tactics.</string>
  <string id="23669">Speak With Master Li</string>
  <string id="23673">According to Jing Woo, there is no real rush, but Master Li wishes to speak with you in his house when you are ready.</string>
  <string id="23677">Find Dawn Star</string>
  <string id="23678">Master Li asked you to find Dawn Star, a childhood friend and fellow student. She should be in her garden on the way toward town.</string>
  <string id="23679">Master Li was about to tell you something important, but word of a student injured by bandits interrupted your conversation. With no other town near, it seems likely Two Rivers is their destination.</string>
  <string id="23684" soundid="112018">I... I killed him. I stabbed him with the knife. He... he didn&apos;t even fight back.</string>
  <string id="23685" soundid="112019">Even if it&apos;s true, did she have learn it like this?</string>
  <string id="23686" soundid="112020">That&apos;s not true! How dare you preach such a philosophy to my daughter?</string>
  <string id="23687" soundid="112021">How dare you say that to my child! She&apos;s not a murderer!</string>
  <string id="23688" soundid="112022">I think... I think I liked it when I felt the knife go in. Like people have to listen to me now. It made me feel... good.</string>
  <string id="23689" soundid="112023">No, Fuyao! Don&apos;t say such horrible things!</string>
  <string id="23690" soundid="112024">I... I guess you speak the truth. These are dark times, and no one can afford innocence any more. I suppose... I suppose we should be grateful.</string>
  <string id="23699" soundid="179083">Eternally Mistepping Hou! Where have you been! Do you have any idea how long I have waited for you to come back from your &quot;errand!&quot;</string>
  <string id="23700" soundid="179084">&quot;I&apos;ll only be gone for a minute.&quot; That&apos;s what you said. Now I find you&apos;ve been gallivanting across the Empire with... some band of misfits. And women!</string>
  <string id="23701" soundid="179085">It&apos;s like my sister said about you: &quot;That man&apos;s going to run off on you,&quot; she said! &quot;He&apos;ll be unfaithful at the drop of a bun, and you know how often he does that!&quot;</string>
  <string id="23702" soundid="179086">You left me with how many orders? Too many, and only your worthless cousin to help. The man doesn&apos;t know a bun from road apple. A hard lesson, but I taught him.</string>
  <string id="23703" soundid="179087">Wait... why do you smell like wine? You&apos;ve been teaching Drunken Master again. You promised to give that up. Weaving may avoid blows but it&apos;s no good for cooking.</string>
  <string id="23705">Lotus Assassin</string>
  <string id="23709">Student Zheng</string>
  <string id="23716">Load Most Recent</string>
  <string id="23717" soundid="179088">Remember the six batches of buns we had to throw away? They tasted the same, but no one wanted your twisted creations. Bendy buns make people uncomfortable.</string>
  <string id="23718" soundid="179089">I should know. I have to hear the comments while you are off doing who knows what at the ends of the Empire. Just who are those people I saw you with?</string>
  <string id="23719" soundid="179090">A bunch of fighters, drunks, slumming nobles, and charlatan mystics. You always find the worst sort of rabble to bring home. Well, not this time.</string>
  <string id="23720" soundid="179091">Why do you keep running around like this? You are not lord of the arena anymore. You are Hou, bun master and husband. Is that not enough?</string>
  <string id="23721" soundid="179092">I should have known you wouldn&apos;t be happy with a simple life, but you know you would be dead if you kept up your old ways. I saved you, and this is the thanks I get.</string>
  <string id="23725" soundid="109255">I can&apos;t really think of anything else to tell you. If you want to know more, ask First Brother Kai.</string>
  <string id="23726" soundid="188144">The other furnaces have colored crystals in them, presumably to alter the light. Lord Yun&apos;s father called this &quot;the ritual of seasons.&quot;</string>
  <string id="23727">But how can one choose both the Open Palm and Closed Fist?</string>
  <string id="23728" soundid="188146">&quot;A forest,&quot; he said, &quot;cares about only two seasons. The cooler air of winter and the blistering heat of summer are the only things it notices.&quot;</string>
  <string id="23729" soundid="188147">It&apos;s attached to some sort of lens that I believe is designed to focus light from the furnaces. If you get the ritual right, it is supposed to reveal the Forest Shadow.</string>
  <string id="23731" soundid="66195">You are one of Master Li&apos;s students! You... you are the one who killed my son, Gao!</string>
  <string id="23732" soundid="188149">&quot;Winter skies are crisp and blue, while the fields of spring are green. Summer&apos;s heat is burning red, while in autumn, yellow leaves are seen.&quot;</string>
  <string id="23783" soundid="71939">He dares to use my own weapons against me? Stop that fool before he does any more damage!</string>
  <string id="23786" soundid="71940">She dares to use my own weapons against me? Stop that fool before she does any more damage!</string>
  <string id="23787" soundid="71941"></string>
  <string id="23789" soundid="27730">Get away from my ship!</string>
  <string id="23790" soundid="27731">This is a restricted area, slave!</string>
  <string id="23791">Sagacious Zu</string>
  <string id="23805" soundid="27751">Use the brands! Hit him with the hot brands!</string>
  <string id="23810" soundid="152323">The pirates are just one more affliction that plagues this troubled town, and yet another headache for poor Minister Sheng.</string>
  <string id="23811" soundid="152324">They raid the surrounding countryside, swooping down with their flyers to capture slaves. Do you know how bad it looks when someone under my jurisdiction is captured by slavers?</string>
  <string id="23812" soundid="152325">Fortunately, they haven&apos;t attacked the town itself yet. Gao, the man I hear is running them, knows that would draw too much attention.</string>
  <string id="23813" soundid="152326">The drunks clogging up the streets aren&apos;t pirates. They&apos;re only traveling merchants, sailors who were trapped here when the dam was opened.</string>
  <string id="23814" soundid="152327">Minister Sheng finds them to be an annoyance, but not a concern worth worrying about. If the dam is closed they will simply disappear. Not like Gao and his pirates.</string>
  <string id="23815" soundid="152328">Yes, I believe that was his name. Gao. An unsavory character by all accounts. There are even rumors he is connected to that infamous crime syndicate known as the Guild.</string>
  <string id="23816" soundid="152329">The pirates have been operating in this area for many years, or so I was told. However, things became much more serious when Gao took over.</string>
  <string id="23838" soundid="27800">You dare disturb me in my grief? I said, no interruptions! You will pay for... wait. You are not one of my servants. I know you.</string>
  <string id="23839" soundid="165645">That is the way of things here. Take care of yourself first. Risks bear penalties as well as rewards.</string>
  <string id="23840">Why didn&apos;t you help me fight Shin&apos;s Attendants?</string>
  <string id="23841" soundid="191421"></string>
  <string id="23843" soundid="43931">It will be a simple matter. Five judges, six topics. I&apos;ll pose my argument about why your foolish land stumbles like a child, and you try to answer.</string>
  <string id="23844" soundid="43932">The judges will raise their arms to indicate whom they favor. Arms up for you, arms down for me. After six topics, if you have a majority, you are the winner.</string>
  <string id="23845" soundid="43933">By the Queen&apos;s corset, if you get them all on your side at any time, I&apos;ll declare the match over. Now, shall we proceed?</string>
  <string id="23847" soundid="43935">I will pull no punches, and I expect no mercy on your part. Let us see which of us is truly superior.</string>
  <string id="23848" soundid="27794">You have gone quite far enough. I am Inquisitor Lim, an elite of the Lotus Assassins.</string>
  <string id="23851" soundid="66276">I simply fill a need the best way I can. What is the crime in that? Now, if you&apos;re looking for a little extra coin, I really need some help.</string>
  <string id="23852" soundid="66277">Someone who knows how to keep their mouth shut and recognizes a good deal. Someone who likes silver... lots of silver. Does this sound like you?</string>
  <string id="23854" soundid="110013">You do not face Emperor Sun Li. You face the whole of the Imperial Army. All of it. Not lone Assassins or a single brigade, but the whole of the army, golems and all!</string>
  <string id="23855">Map to D-pad</string>
  <string id="23856" soundid="165563">It&apos;s funny what things you can learn if you just ask at the right time, like when you have a knife to someone&apos;s throat.</string>
  <string id="23857" soundid="66217">The door at the top of this stair is locked through a fairly ingenious mechanism. Gao&apos;s engineer, Kang the Mad, designed it for security.</string>
  <string id="23858" soundid="66218">Kang the Mad is a crafty fellow. The door requires two to unlock it. Up high there is a platform with the release lever.</string>
  <string id="23859" soundid="66219">The door must be operated while that lever is held forward. There used to be a sentry up there who handled that kind of thing, but he had an... accident.</string>
  <string id="23860" soundid="66220">Once the door is open, we can go our separate ways. I have my goals, and I&apos;m sure you have yours. Since we both have much to do, why don&apos;t I go unlock the door now?</string>
  <string id="23861">One of the people hit hardest by the opening of the dam is Captain Ing. The river is too low and fast for his ship, so he is trapped in Tien&apos;s Landing with no way to earn his livelihood, and his men are becoming mutinous. If you close the dam, he will reward you with silver, although he has little to spare.</string>
  <string id="23862">Trapped</string>
  <string id="23871">Lost Spirit</string>
  <string id="24039" soundid="152330">The pirates started using flyers and gathering slaves at an enormous rate. I imagine things are very unpleasant over at their camp... not that I&apos;m willing to go take a look!</string>
  <string id="24040" soundid="152331">Are you accusing Minister Sheng of neglecting this problem? It&apos;s not that easy. One can&apos;t simply point and say &quot;the pirates are over there&quot;! Well, actually one can.</string>
  <string id="24041" soundid="152332">But the only approach is by river, and no sane bargeman would be willing to risk such a journey. Sane people don&apos;t go looking for the pirates, they avoid them.</string>
  <string id="24043" soundid="152333">I suppose Ru the Boatswain is mad enough to take you, if he&apos;s drunk. Hmmm... yes. Ru is surely the only one who would make the trip. And then the pirates would kill you.</string>
  <string id="24044" soundid="152334">Oh, yes! Let&apos;s! Nothing would please Minister Sheng more.</string>
  <string id="24045">I&apos;ve heard there are pirates around.</string>
  <string id="24046">What can you tell me about these pirates?</string>
  <string id="24047">What do you know about pirates in the area?</string>
  <string id="24049" soundid="66198">Damn you and that school! My Gao was never good enough for Master Li; you were always his prize pupil. And now my son is....</string>
  <string id="24050" soundid="66199">Gao may be gone, but I will avenge him! I know the styles your broken old master taught you, and I know how to beat them! I promise your death will be both slow and painful!</string>
  <string id="24051" soundid="66200"></string>
  <string id="24053" soundid="128706">A reasonable punishment. Gao has some things right.</string>
  <string id="24058" soundid="109403">Good job with those ruffians! Those bandits weren&apos;t gentle with this town. I&apos;m going to help out with some of the repairs.</string>
  <string id="24059">Black Leopard Training Results</string>
  <string id="24060">Student</string>
  <string id="24068" soundid="28026">Are you sure she isn&apos;t off by herself somewhere? She&apos;s always been so moody. I&apos;m sorry, but I haven&apos;t heard or seen anything odd.</string>
  <string id="24069" soundid="28027">Everyone&apos;s here except Gao, and he has no place here any more. He seemed to be in a hurry as he was packing,though.</string>
  <string id="24070" soundid="28028">As I said, I did hear Gao muttering threats under his breath after he was removed from the school, but surely that&apos;s nothing.</string>
  <string id="24071" soundid="28029">I have no idea. If her garden or room is disturbed as Jing Woo said, maybe she chased the person who did it. I don&apos;t know why she didn&apos;t call an alarm, though.</string>
  <string id="24072" soundid="28030">The gate at the center of the village is the only way out. Sometimes boats pass by, but this isn&apos;t the season for them.</string>
  <string id="24073" soundid="28031">If you wish. What do you want to ask about?</string>
  <string id="24074" soundid="28032">Why would you ask me? Everyone knows I don&apos;t get along with her.</string>
  <string id="24075" soundid="28033">She&apos;s too moody to talk to. Always looking past you, as if there&apos;s something more interesting happening behind you.</string>
  <string id="24076" soundid="28034">You certainly don&apos;t seem to have any trouble getting along with her. And you, of all people, should know to look for her at her garden by the school gate.</string>
  <string id="24077" soundid="28035">I suppose she will be at her garden by the school gate. You could look for her there.</string>
  <string id="24078" soundid="28036">As I said, I&apos;m not really the person to ask, but she is probably near her garden by the school gate.</string>
  <string id="24079" soundid="28037">You think I will talk about them behind their backs? I will, but I don&apos;t want people to think of me as the local gossip, even if I am just that.</string>
  <string id="24080" soundid="28038">Of note? There is only one student &quot;of note,&quot; and that would be you. Everyone else, even Dawn Star, is just a background for you and your supposed destiny.</string>
  <string id="24081" soundid="28039">Not that you don&apos;t deserve the attention. I&apos;d be flirting with you non-stop if you weren&apos;t so focused on whatever it is Master Li has in store for you.</string>
  <string id="24082" soundid="28040">All of us get a little envious of that. Even Gao gets pushed aside, and he doesn&apos;t like being anything less than the center of attention.</string>
  <string id="24083" soundid="28041">I&apos;m sure you know that your implied status causes jealous remarks. I have muttered a few, but I don&apos;t mean you harm.</string>
  <string id="24084" soundid="28042">The one you should be careful of is Gao, but I&apos;m not telling you anything you don&apos;t already know.</string>
  <string id="24085" soundid="28043">You know him as well as I do. A rich man&apos;s son. He&apos;s attractive, I suppose, but arrogance follows him like a cloud of locusts.</string>
  <string id="24086" soundid="28044">I hear his father is the same way. Gao the Greater and Gao the Lesser; not a family I would want to be a part of.</string>
  <string id="24087" soundid="160181">You and Dawn Star have both had a lifetime of training under Master Li. He is stern with you, but you sure can see that he&apos;s proud as well.</string>
  <string id="24089" soundid="28047">I&apos;m sorry. I shouldn&apos;t be like that. Dawn Star is a fine person. She just... sees things that I can&apos;t.</string>
  <string id="24090" soundid="28048">I know there are ghosts and spirits, but why should she be able to &quot;sense&quot; them when I can&apos;t? What makes her special?</string>
  <string id="24092" soundid="28050">I&apos;ve already said enough. You can talk to her about what she sees.</string>
  <string id="24093" soundid="28051">Maybe that&apos;s why you two get along so well. Maybe her &quot;sense&quot; for ghosts and the like meshes well with the great destiny Master Li sees for you?</string>
  <string id="24094" soundid="28052">As I said, you&apos;ve known her forever and you&apos;re very close. Her &quot;sense&quot; for ghosts and the like obviously meshes well with whatever destiny Master Li sees for you.</string>
  <string id="24095" soundid="28053">You know what is said. Master Li believes you are special but won&apos;t say why. It makes you... interesting.</string>
  <string id="24096" soundid="28054">Some of the others don&apos;t find it as intriguing as I do. Some even consider it an attack on their worth.</string>
  <string id="24097" soundid="28055">Gao, obviously. You know he doesn&apos;t like you. He never has. And when Master Li tells him to model himself after you, that just makes it worse.</string>
  <string id="24098" soundid="28056">Master Li never stops talking about you. You are special, or so we are repeatedly told. It can get annoying. Then again, some find it outright threatening.</string>
  <string id="24099" soundid="28057">Quite a bit, as I said. Master Li considers you special, and that causes rivalries. I doubt there&apos;s much you can do about it.</string>
  <string id="24100" soundid="28058">Master Li took me in when no one else would. He is a firm master but a kind man deep inside.</string>
  <string id="24101" soundid="28059">I imagine that he walked. If you want anything more than that you&apos;ll have to ask someone who was here at the time. That was twenty years ago.</string>
  <string id="24102" soundid="28060">I really don&apos;t know or care. It may as well have been Sagacious Tien, the first Emperor. That was before I was born.</string>
  <string id="24103" soundid="28061">The Emperor&apos;s brother? I thought both of his brothers died twenty years ago. Master Li says a lot of odd things. You probably just misheard him.</string>
  <string id="24104" soundid="28062">Yes, you said that already. It&apos;s not getting any more believable.</string>
  <string id="24105" soundid="28063">Other than what Dawn Star &quot;senses,&quot; all I have is stories, but they&apos;re becoming more and more common.</string>
  <string id="24109" soundid="28067">We could, if you wish, but it&apos;s much more fun to talk about others. Oh, I&apos;m kidding. Of course we can talk a bit.</string>
  <string id="24110" soundid="28068">I wasn&apos;t the delicate flower my family had hoped for. They believed school would calm my spirit.</string>
  <string id="24111" soundid="28069">But Master Li has shown me how to focus myself. I have learned many skills while here, and not many of them require that I be &quot;delicate.&quot;</string>
  <string id="24112" soundid="28070">When I am done? I... haven&apos;t really thought about it. I won&apos;t go home; there&apos;s no place for me there.</string>
  <string id="24113" soundid="28071">If I can stomach the books, I could become a scholar. Perhaps I will go to the Imperial City. I should see it at least once in my life.</string>
  <string id="24115" soundid="28073">Again? I had no idea you were so interested. You usually spend far more time with that Dawn Star than you do talking with me.</string>
  <string id="24116" soundid="28074">Stay well. After all, how could we learn without our most senior student to guide us.</string>
  <string id="24118" soundid="28076">Perhaps I will see you later. Perhaps not.</string>
  <string id="24119" soundid="28077">Goodbye. I hope you find Dawn Star. She was always... nice.</string>
  <string id="24139">How did Master Li come here?</string>
  <string id="24140">Who was master before Master Li?</string>
  <string id="24141">Master Li told me he was the Emperor&apos;s brother.</string>
  <string id="24142">Tell me what you&apos;ve been hearing about ghosts.</string>
  <string id="24146">I don&apos;t think we&apos;ve ever talked about you, Lin.</string>
  <string id="24147">How did you come here? Why?</string>
  <string id="24149">What will you do when you are done training here?</string>
  <string id="24152">Goodbye for now.</string>
  <string id="24159" soundid="142072">You should show proper respect. Ming is an honored man in this village.</string>
  <string id="24160" soundid="142073">Wait, is that how it goes? Damn, I must be getting old if I&apos;m mixing my sayings like that. Bah, forget it.</string>
  <string id="24161">I want to ask about Dawn Star&apos;s disappearance.</string>
  <string id="24162">Are any other students missing?</string>
  <string id="24163">Have you any clue where Dawn Star would go?</string>
  <string id="24164">How many paths out of the village are there?</string>
  <string id="24165">Let&apos;s go back to my other questions.</string>
  <string id="24166">Have you seen Dawn Star?</string>
  <string id="24169">You know everyone around here. Is there any news?</string>
  <string id="24170">Who are the students of note?</string>
  <string id="24174">Tell me about Gao.</string>
  <string id="24176">Tell me about Dawn Star.</string>
  <string id="24177" soundid="160183">She also came here very young, didn&apos;t she? The two of you are generally considered the most advanced students here.</string>
  <string id="24178">What are you getting at?</string>
  <string id="24181">What have you heard about me?</string>
  <string id="24183">Who should I be concerned about?</string>
  <string id="24184">What do you think of Master Li?</string>
  <string id="24251">Confused</string>
  <string id="24277" soundid="49290">Ah... well, that is a delicate issue. The recruiter is not so easy to find. I&apos;m sorry, but I can&apos;t tell you much more than that.</string>
  <string id="24281">Novice Shen</string>
  <string id="24300">Ing Trapped for Good</string>
  <string id="24303" soundid="62622"></string>
  <string id="24304" soundid="62623"></string>
  <string id="24307">Transformation Style
Removes negative effects (such as slow or paralysis)
Drains Chi 

Powerful warriors can gain the power to take the form of the fearsome horse demon. This transformation grants the horse demon&apos;s legendary ferocity, as well as its mastery of the element of fire and its immunity to the effects of Support styles. Faced with the immolating brutality of the horse demon, weak-willed foes cower in fear, helpless against the raging flames. 
</string>
  <string id="24308" soundid="107887">I replaced the dust inductor. The Marvelous Dragonfly will cross the sky at your whim... for a short way.</string>
  <string id="24345" soundid="136177">She will tell you more. You must go speak with her as quickly as you can.</string>
  <string id="24393">Divine Void</string>
  <string id="24401">Elephant Demon</string>
  <string id="24404" soundid="146879"></string>
  <string id="24405">Viper</string>
  <string id="24413">Support Style 
Does direct damage in Chi Strike mode
This style&apos;s Area Attack can initiate a Harmonic Combo that produces a Focus power-up.

The forms and strikes of Storm Dragon enable the master to call upon the power of lightning to damage an opponent. While this style&apos;s attacks don&apos;t cause any direct damage, its motions summon forth electricity to course through its victim, doing small but constant damage over time. Storm Dragon will rarely win a fight on its own, but combined with other styles it can easily change the tide of a difficult battle.</string>
  <string id="24414">Sky</string>
  <string id="24419">Kang the Mad</string>
  <string id="24422" soundid="136181">Trip me? Make me crawl like a dog? This&apos;ll teach &apos;em a lesson they won&apos;t forget! Come on... stupid rope! Come on... Make them sorry they ever... huh?</string>
  <string id="24424">Hunter</string>
  <string id="24425" soundid="136182">Too bad about the kid, though. You know, back in my day we weren&apos;t stupid enough to fall for a trick like that.</string>
  <string id="24429">Use the Fight Style keys to switch fighting styles. Each style has its own powers and effects.</string>
  <string id="24431">Use the Left and Right triggers to switch among targets in combat. You can target enemies and objects in the area.</string>
  <string id="24433">Hold down the B button and move the left thumbstick to evade attacks in combat.</string>
  <string id="24434" soundid="109368">Now, I think it&apos;s time to leave town. Good luck in all you do. It&apos;s been a pleasure.</string>
  <string id="24439" soundid="28410">Hello there! I&apos;m Han, though the fans and, well, everyone else call me Hapless Han.</string>
  <string id="24440" soundid="28411">See, I look on the bright side of things, even if my losses make people call me &quot;hapless.&quot; Are numbers really that important? In my mind, it&apos;s trying your best that counts.</string>
  <string id="24441" soundid="28412">Take us: How could I have beaten the future champion of the arena? But I did help you get there, in a way! Since you&apos;ve honored me with a visit, what can I do for the champion?</string>
  <string id="24442" soundid="28413">Losing to you was an honor, and the bruises look like they&apos;ll heal up just fine. So, what&apos;s on your mind?</string>
  <string id="24445" soundid="28416">I know we haven&apos;t had a chance to speak before this, but let me congratulate you on the Silver Division championship.</string>
  <string id="24446" soundid="28417">I know we haven&apos;t met outside the ring, but let me be one of the first to congratulate you on the Bronze Division championship.</string>
  <string id="24448" soundid="28419">You know what I&apos;m talking about, I&apos;m sure. Things aren&apos;t exactly glamorous here in the qualifying round, are they? Now, what can I do for you?</string>
  <string id="24449" soundid="28420">You know, looking at you, I&apos;d say you could hold your own in the arena. Are you thinking of signing up, or was there something else you need?</string>
  <string id="24450" soundid="28421">Champion! This will be a mark of pride in your family for generations! I feel bad for your friend, though; Raging Ox was a good man.</string>
  <string id="24458" soundid="28429">You&apos;re back, and it is a lovely day for a chat, but if you&apos;re this interested in Hapless Han, why not join the arena yourself? You&apos;re clearly trained for combat.</string>
  <string id="24460" soundid="28431">It will be a pleasure to see a new fighter in the ring! If you want my advice, I&apos;d say to apply hot before cold to keep the swelling down.</string>
  <string id="24461">Return to Three Peaks Monastery and tell the Abbot of your success.</string>
  <string id="24462" soundid="28433">Boy! That sure was something! I wouldn&apos;t have wanted to be me out there, except that I was.... But I learned so much from facing you!</string>
  <string id="24463" soundid="28434">Next time I should try some of that fancy stuff you do! I&apos;m not exactly sure how you did it, though.</string>
  <string id="24464" soundid="28435">I watched your last match!</string>
  <string id="24465" soundid="28436">You&apos;re just getting started, but you&apos;re on the right track. I bet you&apos;ll be facing me someday soon!</string>
  <string id="24467" soundid="28438">That was quite the fight out there. </string>
  <string id="24468" soundid="28439">Congratulations on becoming champion of Silver Division. Soldier will not be happy with losing to you, but... he&apos;s been unhappy a long time, I think.</string>
  <string id="24469" soundid="28440">You&apos;re really climbing the ranks! We&apos;ll be meeting soon enough.</string>
  <string id="24470" soundid="28441">Things are a lot more difficult in the Bronze Round, are they not? I&apos;ve fought everyone who&apos;s made it that far, I should know.</string>
  <string id="24471" soundid="28442">I bet Soldier&apos;s got his eye on you. He&apos;ll be nervous about how quickly you&apos;re advancing. Keep him off balance.</string>
  <string id="24472" soundid="28443">Just a word of warning: The stakes are high where you&apos;re fighting. Be careful both in and out of the ring.</string>
  <string id="24473" soundid="118165">Be well.</string>
  <string id="24474" soundid="59533">You must have some sense of the spiritual trials of this place, since you have progressed far enough to face me next.</string>
  <string id="24475" soundid="105594">This fight will not happen! This fighter is not worthy of facing a true Imperial Champion!</string>
  <string id="24476" soundid="59535">We understand that we will face you next. We look forward to seeing how the drops of history fall.</string>
  <string id="24477" soundid="59536">A fighter poised on the cusp of entering the Bronze Division. Only Hapless Han stands in the way.</string>
  <string id="24478" soundid="59537">Khana&apos;s next opponent, if the rumors are true.</string>
  <string id="24479" soundid="59538">One close enough to reach out and snatch the Silver Division from Soldier. How fascinating.</string>
  <string id="24480">Orphans Avenged</string>
  <string id="24482" soundid="59539">Either you are extremely brave or very foolish to face the Ravager. Either way, we wish you luck.</string>
  <string id="24483">Liver Demon</string>
  <string id="24486">Stabber Yuxi</string>
  <string id="24491">Chai Ka</string>
  <string id="24496" soundid="59540">The unmasker! You have solved the mystery of the Ravager, and now we wait to see what fate has in store for the Serpent.</string>
  <string id="24505">Gao&apos;s Mercenary</string>
  <string id="24537" soundid="127129">It has been several years since I arrived in Two Rivers. I was surprised to find a teacher of Master Li&apos;s ability so far out on the borderlands. It was a fortuitous accident.</string>
  <string id="24546">[TEMP] Hello, I am a custom LoadMessage. Isn&apos;t that awesome!</string>
  <string id="24549">Phoenix Assassin</string>
  <string id="24550" soundid="31829">I&apos;m sorry? You would speak with the Sung brothers? We have no time for simple gawkers.</string>
  <string id="24551" soundid="31830">Why not bother someone like Hapless Han? He&apos;s always willing to waste time with the spectators.</string>
  <string id="24552" soundid="31831">Cast the stones, brother. The six triangles of portent indicated that new competition would advance our goals.</string>
  <string id="24553" soundid="31832">Did they really? Surprising.</string>
  <string id="24554" soundid="31833">Well, then. It seems my brother, and the fates, would encourage you to participate in the arena. You should speak with Qui the Promoter. Until you prove yourself, leave us be.</string>
  <string id="24555" soundid="31834">While my brother Sui may consider you an object of portentous fascination, I do not waste time on spectators.</string>
  <string id="24556" soundid="32829">The Emperor&apos;s tomb is ablaze, and the Lotus Assassins are looking for the person who caused it.</string>
  <string id="24562">Phoenix Assassin</string>
  <string id="24568">Phoenix Assassin</string>
  <string id="24576">Phoenix Assassin</string>
  <string id="24593" soundid="70023">If you&apos;d like more information about the Black Leopard School, speak with First Brother Kai.</string>
  <string id="24596" soundid="160770">I have no idea, though he was very vocal in condeming Master Smiling Hawk. Perhaps he grew tired of all the bickering here and decided to leave.</string>
  <string id="24599" soundid="160771">I know if I was a follower of Master Radiant I would likely get very bored, very quickly. Maybe he just decided to go to a new school, somewhere more peaceful.</string>
  <string id="24601" soundid="28572">Greetings. I am Crimson Khana, known in the Prosperous East for my swordsmanship. I came here to test my abilities but have found my will and purity of spirit tested as well.</string>
  <string id="24606" soundid="105595">The Ravager will not waste time with one so new to the ring! One must face the test of time to even *challenge* the Imperial Champion!</string>
  <string id="24609" soundid="28580">You will start to see the truth of this &quot;contest&quot; as you make your way through the Bronze round. Let your conscience guide you; that is all the advice I can offer.</string>
  <string id="24610" soundid="28581">You are just starting your career here. You will see what I&apos;m talking about soon enough, I&apos;m sure. You do not have the stance of a novice about you.</string>
  <string id="24611" soundid="28582">Forgive me. I should not speak so to a spectator. If you have questions, you should speak with Qui the Promoter.</string>
  <string id="24614" soundid="105596"></string>
  <string id="24615" soundid="31227">Others say the arena recruits for the Lotus Assassins, and it is a theory worth considering. Does my blade somehow aid these Assassins that threaten my homeland? I pray not.</string>
  <string id="24618" soundid="158314">No! Leave Zhong alone, or Zhong get angry and smash things.</string>
  <string id="24619">I demeaned the whole contest. The insult he percieved will unsettle him in combat.</string>
  <string id="24620" soundid="28591">You were drawn here because you have the eyes of a warrior. You see the wave break and the eagle soar. Speak with Qui the Promoter if you wish to compete here.</string>
  <string id="24622" soundid="28593">Your name is on the roster, yet your blade has yet to sing! My master would always say: &quot;Speak with your actions, not words!&quot; Of course, there is more to life than conflict...</string>
  <string id="24624" soundid="188151">There are some old tomes in the temple itself, in a stand near the right wall. You might be able to learn more by poring through them.</string>
  <string id="24625" soundid="28596">Well done. You learn very quickly. One thing bothers me about your moves, though. Throughout the fight I felt as if there was some opening in your defense.</string>
  <string id="24626" soundid="28597"></string>
  <string id="24627" soundid="28598">That beast barely knows why it fights; your purpose fills each strike in a way it could never understand.</string>
  <string id="24628" soundid="28599">Han lacks the competitive drive to progress beyond his current position, but he is skillful enough. Be honored by your victory.</string>
  <string id="24631" soundid="28602">Watching you fight is akin to reading fine poetry. I&apos;m sure you will meet Han in the ring soon enough.</string>
  <string id="24632" soundid="28603">Our blades are drawn to each other as a lodestone sings to steel. They will cross before long, I think.</string>
  <string id="24633" soundid="70026">First Brother Kai is a great leader. Without him, this school would not survive long.</string>
  <string id="24635" soundid="28606">Remember that there is dishonor only in not learning from your loss.</string>
  <string id="24636" soundid="28607">We met and I proved the stronger. There is no shame in this for you. In fact, I would welcome the chance to test myself against you once more.</string>
  <string id="24637" soundid="28608">Do not let this discourage you. You are simply learning the ways of this place. The Imperial Arena is not like the smaller contests in the villages.</string>
  <string id="24638" soundid="28609">Just remember to focus. The qualifying round is stocked with amateurs who know little of true combat.</string>
  <string id="24639" soundid="28610">Your opponents in the Bronze Division are more determined and more skilled than those you faced before. Remember your defense.</string>
  <string id="24641" soundid="188152">All right. Summer and winter seem to be the key. Black Whirlwind will stay behind to offer whatever help he can. If anyone can control him, it&apos;s you.</string>
  <string id="24642" soundid="28613">As the hunter does not waste words on the animals, so will I not spend my breath on you.</string>
  <string id="24643" soundid="28614">I greet you, one warrior to another.</string>
  <string id="24644">I need to know more about the ritual before you leave.</string>
  <string id="24645" soundid="28616">The Assassins recruit from this arena but I would steer clear of them. Their recruiters approached Iron Soldier so perhaps they look only to those at his level.</string>
  <string id="24649" soundid="151536">I recall your earliest lessons. You fell from a thousand feet during the Walk of Death--which alone was odd enough at your age, but you made short work of the Walk of Maiming and the Walk of Intense Discomfort--and tore your head clean off.  I comforted you--well, your head--saying that you could just walk it off, because, you know, the cut was *clean,* and then you would punch a mountain. In space!</string>
  <string id="24653" soundid="151540">I&apos;m a little busy right now. I&apos;ve got a bowl of wine that needs drinking, so why don&apos;t you just find someone else to bother?</string>
  <string id="24654" soundid="151541">[Failure] I know the value of my life... and that&apos;s not nearly enough.</string>
  <string id="24655">Can I ask you some questions before you go?</string>
  <string id="24656" soundid="151543">You&apos;re wasting my time. I wouldn&apos;t give you the time of day for that small amount of silver.</string>
  <string id="24657" soundid="151544">The conversation around here is starting to bother me... I think I&apos;ll take my wine somewhere else.</string>
  <string id="24659" soundid="28630">He is the real power behind Qui, Lucky Cho, and all the rest. He bends the fighters to his will but I will not be his puppet. The Serpent will *never* guide my sword.</string>
  <string id="24661" soundid="45853">Fair enough, though I hope you will attempt to mind your tone in the future.</string>
  <string id="24662" soundid="28633">Kai Lan&apos;s thugs are but a portion of the larger Guild, fixing fights and adjusting the odds in their favor. There are rumors of extortion and worse but it&apos;s best not to speak of it.</string>
  <string id="24664" soundid="28635">Dishonor exists everywhere. The Guild exists in an uneasy truce with the officials, and a steady stream of bribes aids the relationship, from what I hear.</string>
  <string id="24665" soundid="45854">No time spent in study of the ancient ways is lost.</string>
  <string id="24666" soundid="28637">Good. It is a sensitive subject, particularly in this place.</string>
  <string id="24667" soundid="28638">Your eyes tell me that you have already seen much in the way of battle. Ask what you will; I welcome another worthy challenger among the ranks.</string>
  <string id="24668" soundid="28639">With its three divisions, this is the Empire&apos;s largest tournament. Some, like me, come for the challenge; others, like Raging Ox, come for the coin.</string>
  <string id="24670" soundid="28641">Qui the Promoter points the way in this place. Be warned, though; he does not always see the path before he sets you upon it.</string>
  <string id="24671" soundid="28642">Smaller tournaments are simply practice. This is the only arena that truly matters. Don&apos;t worry, though. The early rounds are still filled with graceless rabble.</string>
  <string id="24672" soundid="28643">Of course. What do you need?</string>
  <string id="24673" soundid="28644">There are countless hopefuls, but only a few who are worth really watching. In time, you may find that others are asking about you, as well.</string>
  <string id="24674" soundid="28645">At this point in your career, the higher ranking fighters will tell you about themselves. Still, you must see a thing from many angles to truly know it.</string>
  <string id="24675" soundid="28646">I can tell you about myself, of course, and I know Hapless Han relatively well. I could also tell you something of the beasts they have here.</string>
  <string id="24676" soundid="28647">I am from Phoenix Gate, the largest city in the Prosperous East. There I developed my own techniques of weapon combat. I have vowed to teach them to anyone who can best me.</string>
  <string id="24678" soundid="28649">Han&apos;s... intriguing. While his skill is small, he shows no envy and learns from every encounter. I wonder if he stays in the qualifiers so he can face *every* new fighter.</string>
  <string id="24680" soundid="28651">A number of different creatures are used here to add to the spectacle. Ogres are commonplace, but more recently some sort of sub-human creature has been appearing in the ring.</string>
  <string id="24681" soundid="28652">I&apos;ve heard rumors, though, that the arena organizers are planning on bringing demons into the ring, somehow. I suppose we&apos;ll see in time if there&apos;s any truth to that.</string>
  <string id="24682" soundid="28653">Of course. What did you want to know?</string>
  <string id="24683" soundid="28654">I have not been here as long as some of the others, but I will answer as well as I can. Do you want to know about this area, the Scholars&apos; Garden, or the city in general?</string>
  <string id="24684" soundid="28655">As I&apos;m sure you know, this is the capital of the Jade Empire. The city itself is built around the Emperor&apos;s Gate, the massive passage into the Emperor&apos;s lands through the Wall.</string>
  <string id="24685" soundid="28656">Around the Heart of the Empire Tavern is the Market District, bustling with open markets and hawkers. It&apos;s vibrant, full of life, and even louder than a battlefield.</string>
  <string id="24686" soundid="28657">They&apos;re learned men and worthy of respect but they can teach me little of the sword. The garden lies across the waterway, past the nobles&apos; houses, and is open day and night.</string>
  <string id="24687" soundid="28658">What would you discuss?</string>
  <string id="24688" soundid="28659">Mind, spirit, and body must all be tested. You can *achieve* peace in a garden, but you *earn* it on the battlefield. Goals reached without trial are not so easily kept.</string>
  <string id="24689" soundid="28660">Many philosophies agree with me, many do not. The ensuing debates are no less a field of battle than this one. Not all battles are fought with weapons.</string>
  <string id="24690" soundid="105597">Good people, I do this for you! Would you have an unproven whelp as your champion? As the Empire&apos;s champion?</string>
  <string id="24691" soundid="28662">I wish you all the best when we step into the ring. Tell Qui whenever you are ready.</string>
  <string id="24692" soundid="151545">I might be able to take you there. You&apos;ll have to pay me now, and I&apos;m not promising you won&apos;t get killed once we get there.</string>
  <string id="24693" soundid="151546">It&apos;s your life, friend. No refunds either. Follow me.</string>
  <string id="24694" soundid="28665">May your battles bring you peace.</string>
  <string id="24700" soundid="151549"></string>
  <string id="24701" soundid="151550"></string>
  <string id="24708">Do you know anything about recruiters for the Lotus Assassins?</string>
  <string id="24714">Everyone has a price, Zi Bao. I&apos;ll pay you 2,000 silver.</string>
  <string id="24715">Lotus Assassin Wizard</string>
  <string id="24716">Spirit Realm</string>
  <string id="24719">Lucky Cho mentioned the Guild. I need to know your thoughts on them. </string>
  <string id="24720">What can you tell me about the Serpent?</string>
  <string id="24723">What role does the Guild play?</string>
  <string id="24726">Why does the Empire put up with the Guild?</string>
  <string id="24727">Let&apos;s talk about something else.</string>
  <string id="24728">Can I ask you a few questions about the arena?</string>
  <string id="24729">How is this arena structured?</string>
  <string id="24731">That&apos;s fine. Let&apos;s go.</string>
  <string id="24732">How do I start fighting?</string>
  <string id="24733">[Intimidation] Take me to the slavers or I&apos;ll break your neck!</string>
  <string id="24734">Will my record at other tournaments affect my standings here?</string>
  <string id="24735">Can you teach me to fight as you did?</string>
  <string id="24736">Let&apos;s go back to my other questions.</string>
  <string id="24737">I have some questions about the fighters here in the arena.</string>
  <string id="24740">I&apos;d like to hear about you, Khana.</string>
  <string id="24742">[Follow Zi Bao]</string>
  <string id="24743">Tell me about Hapless Han.</string>
  <string id="24745">[Let him go]</string>
  <string id="24746">What can you tell me about the beasts?</string>
  <string id="24748" soundid="151568">Bao, you know better than to summon me without a good reason. I hate this accursed, beast-reeking place.</string>
  <string id="24749">Let&apos;s go back to my other questions.</string>
  <string id="24750">Let&apos;s talk about the Imperial City.</string>
  <string id="24751">Just tell me about the city in general.</string>
  <string id="24753">I want to hear about the area around here.</string>
  <string id="24754" soundid="151570">Sure... what do you want to know?</string>
  <string id="24755">Tell me about the Scholars&apos; Garden.</string>
  <string id="24756">Can I ask you some questions?</string>
  <string id="24757">Let&apos;s talk about something else.</string>
  <string id="24758">You clearly dislike this place. Why not just leave?</string>
  <string id="24759">That makes a certain kind of sense.</string>
  <string id="24760">Do you think about such boring drivel all the time? Pathetic!</string>
  <string id="24761" soundid="105598"></string>
  <string id="24762">That&apos;s all I want to ask you for now.</string>
  <string id="24763" soundid="28734">You look a shade better than the usual cowardly dogs we get through here. Just a shade, though.</string>
  <string id="24764" soundid="33285">So... you have an interest in the Lotus Assassins. Very few people risk our attention by seeking us out in public.</string>
  <string id="24765" soundid="33286">I find your bold nature refreshing, but we under Death&apos;s Hand recruit only the very best. All others are cast down before us.</string>
  <string id="24768">You have successfully completed this quest by killing the Lotus Assassin and bringing news of his death back to the Abbot.</string>
  <string id="24770" soundid="28741">If you think defeating Khana impresses me, you&apos;re wrong.</string>
  <string id="24771" soundid="28742">You ground the Hapless one beneath your feet, like everyone else does, huh? Han&apos;s pathetic for wasting time on the hopefuls, if you ask me.</string>
  <string id="24772" soundid="28743">If I waste time talking to you, it&apos;s because I can respect that you&apos;re prepared to lose terribly in the arena.</string>
  <string id="24773" soundid="177256">It feels odd to have lived with an image of the Empire for so long and to lose it so quickly. I miss... I miss Two Rivers. I miss Jing Woo, Old Ming, Gujin....</string>
  <string id="24774" soundid="131869">You&apos;ve done well. With Fang out of the picture, we can assign his post to somebody less difficult. Somebody pliable and easy to control. Somebody like Sheng.</string>
  <string id="24775" soundid="131870">Sheng has no backbone; no will of his own. Things will go much more smoothly for the Lotus Assassins with a puppet like him running the Ministry of Harmony.</string>
  <string id="24777" soundid="177257">I remember lessons in the school, and you making some joke that had Smiling Mountain snickering under his breath even as he scolded us for not paying attention.</string>
  <string id="24780" soundid="60155">I&apos;m just a little girl, and I&apos;m a spirit. I have nothing I can give you. But this is such a small thing for you, and it means so much to me. Please, won&apos;t you help me?</string>
  <string id="24782" soundid="177258">What do you remember about those days?</string>
  <string id="24783" soundid="177259">I keep all our fallen friends in mind. With all the spirits I see, it would be hard not to. I see the walls between this world and the next as very thin.</string>
  <string id="24784" soundid="28755">Yeah, I saw your name on the rosters. I see a lot of names on the rosters; half of &apos;em run home to their mother before their first fight.</string>
  <string id="24785" soundid="28756">So don&apos;t get all chummy with me. I haven&apos;t the time for fawning adoration from the novices.</string>
  <string id="24786">I have his resignation right here.</string>
  <string id="24787">I blackmailed him into it.</string>
  <string id="24788" soundid="28759">Looks like you&apos;re still walking after that last match. Too bad.</string>
  <string id="24789" soundid="28760">I should probably say something encouraging since this was your first win ever, but frankly, I don&apos;t care.</string>
  <string id="24790" soundid="28761">You ground the Hapless one beneath your feet, like everyone else does, huh? Han&apos;s pathetic for wasting time on the hopefuls, if you ask me.</string>
  <string id="24791" soundid="28762">If you think defeating Khana impresses me, you&apos;re wrong.</string>
  <string id="24793" soundid="28764">Surprising. Most of the time you qualifiers hurt yourselves more than your opponent.</string>
  <string id="24794" soundid="28765">I&apos;m sure Khana will fix that once you challenge her for the division championship.</string>
  <string id="24795" soundid="28766">You just watch yourself. Qui will be sending you to see me if you keep that up, and I&apos;ll break you in two.</string>
  <string id="24796" soundid="28767">A big Gold Division win for you?</string>
  <string id="24797" soundid="28768">Can&apos;t really hold your own, can you?</string>
  <string id="24798" soundid="28769">How did you even make it this far? Dumb luck, or was everyone else having a bad day? Feel free to try again if you think you can handle it.</string>
  <string id="24799" soundid="28770">This is the part where the hopefuls usually give up and go home. When you can&apos;t even win your first challenge, it&apos;s time to go back to the farm.</string>
  <string id="24800" soundid="28771">If you&apos;re stalled behind one of the hopefuls, you&apos;ll never go anywhere.</string>
  <string id="24801" soundid="28772">The Bronze Division&apos;s not for green stalks like yourself. Go toughen up for a few years in the Imperial Army and then come back.</string>
  <string id="24802" soundid="28773">You&apos;re just another bug trying to reach my level, and it&apos;s clearly not going to happen.</string>
  <string id="24803" soundid="28774">You shouldn&apos;t give up. Just keep flinging yourself at the Gold Division, it should be entertaining.</string>
  <string id="24805" soundid="28776">What do you want now?</string>
  <string id="24806" soundid="28777">Those Lotus scum wouldn&apos;t know a fair fight if it were praying in their family temple. </string>
  <string id="24807" soundid="28778">There is, however, a vulture around here who picks off the young fighters once they become the Silver Division champion. Tried to recruit me, even.</string>
  <string id="24809">Guard</string>
  <string id="24810" soundid="70027">Hello, my name is Fourth Brother Yu, and you must be the new prodigy. First Brother told us to watch out for you. He said that you&apos;re very talented. </string>
  <string id="24812" soundid="45855">Time with you, however, seems as if consumed by the Devourers of Moments that figured so prominently in the writings of Peng the Unpunctual.</string>
  <string id="24813" soundid="70028">Since you&apos;ve defeated Fifth Brother, perhaps you&apos;d let me decide just how talented you are. Care for a match?</string>
  <string id="24815" soundid="145677">A good name, is it not? Drives fear into the commoners. Yes, that miscreant will be turned in soon enough, and pity the &quot;Scourge&quot; that shows up in my city!</string>
  <string id="24819">Guard</string>
  <string id="24820" soundid="70029">Let&apos;s go then.</string>
  <string id="24824">Dirge Fountain Seal</string>
  <string id="24825">x</string>
  <string id="24836" soundid="175160">Your move, old goat.</string>
  <string id="24846" soundid="33318">You&apos;ve already spoken with my counterpart in the arena, but his priorities are different than mine. Tell me, why have you sought us out?</string>
  <string id="24849" soundid="33321">I have been waiting for you to return. My sources tell me the problem of Minister Sheng and his report to Judge Fang is... no longer a problem.</string>
  <string id="24850" soundid="108283">This is getting too crowded. I doubt there&apos;ll be enough enemies to go around.</string>
  <string id="24852" soundid="108284">Shut up, you oaf, this is important.</string>
  <string id="24853" soundid="28824">I look forward to ending your career in the next match.</string>
  <string id="24854" soundid="28825">Why are you wasting time with me, anyway? Shouldn&apos;t you be taunting your next victim?</string>
  <string id="24855" soundid="33322">I must applaud your efforts. Judge Fang is outraged... it will be months before he agrees to meet with Minister Sheng again.</string>
  <string id="24856" soundid="28827">Good, go bother someone else.</string>
  <string id="24857" soundid="33323">I do not approve of your methods, however. Killing Fang was hardly a subtle way to handle things.</string>
  <string id="24859" soundid="33324">So I ask you, why have you sought us out? Why shouldn&apos;t I just kill you where you stand?</string>
  <string id="24860" soundid="33325">We are not a club you simply petition for admittance. In fact, I find it hard to believe anyone could be so audacious as to look me in the face and make such a brash statement.</string>
  <string id="24862" soundid="127130">I have studied the martial arts all my life, and serve your master as I am able. He is devoted to your training, and needs someone to assist the other students.</string>
  <string id="24863" soundid="126499">This town was once a worthless boil on the back-end of the Empire. It was doomed and dying, a pit of despair. Then Minister Sheng arrived, and all was well.</string>
  <string id="24864" soundid="126500">The dam was closed and prosperity reigned. Surely Sheng will be rewarded with a new posting back at the Imperial City.</string>
  <string id="24867" soundid="33327">You dare to threaten a Lotus Assassin? The bravery of such a reckless act is impressive, though I wonder about the intelligence behind your words.</string>
  <string id="24870">I need help finding a recruiter for the Lotus Assassins.</string>
  <string id="24882" soundid="33330">Your words are true, though you would be wise not to speak them so openly. The Lotus Assassins, and we Inquisitors in particular, prefer to work from the shadows.</string>
  <string id="24920">Are you always this belligerent?</string>
  <string id="24921" soundid="108285">I thought we should talk before... well, this could be very dangerous.</string>
  <string id="24922" soundid="108286">Both of us, I wonder?</string>
  <string id="24923" soundid="108287">You cheapen the importance of this, Princess. He could die in there.</string>
  <string id="24924">I&apos;ll talk to you later, Soldier.</string>
  <string id="24925" soundid="28896">The brothers Sung greet our fellow combatant warmly. I am Sung Bo, and this is my little brother Bu and my older brother Sui.</string>
  <string id="24926" soundid="32830">I wouldn&apos;t want to be the one responsible for destroying the Emperor&apos;s tomb.</string>
  <string id="24927" soundid="32831">The Outlander in the Scholars&apos; Garden is very loud. Perhaps he thinks we&apos;ll understand him better if he shouts.</string>
  <string id="24928" soundid="32832">That Outlander talks like a wounded duck. I&apos;ve never heard such strange sounding words before. </string>
  <string id="24929" soundid="32833">My uncle saw a ghost while traveling in the south. I don&apos;t think I&apos;ll be traveling that way anytime soon.</string>
  <string id="24930" soundid="32834">Those Lotus Assassins make me nervous. They just look so... unnatural.</string>
  <string id="24931" soundid="32835">I&apos;ve heard rumors of a young hero making quite a stir in Tien&apos;s Landing.</string>
  <string id="24932" soundid="32836">I haven&apos;t seen any ghosts wandering in the city. And I hope I never do!</string>
  <string id="24933" soundid="32837">Smoke and flames coming from the Necropolis... bad tidings indeed.</string>
  <string id="24934" soundid="32838">First ghosts, now this. The Necropolis is just not a safe place at all.</string>
  <string id="24936" soundid="28907">We will admit that our first loss to you worried us, but to have faced the future Imperial Champion and lost is an appropriate path for any to walk.</string>
  <string id="24937" soundid="28908">What may we do for the champion?</string>
  <string id="24942" soundid="106849">This general sounds far more honorable than Soldier. Just defeat Soldier fairly, I say.</string>
  <string id="24943" soundid="106850">In a choice between the Iron Soldier and the Stone General, I&apos;d take on the entire battalion.</string>
  <string id="24946" soundid="28917">How very strange that your name appears on the rosters, but your body has yet to appear in the ring.</string>
  <string id="24947" soundid="28918">This is indeed reminiscent of the reign of the Blood Dynasty&apos;s third emperor, notorious for having no policies, opinions, or even motion in the later years of his rule. </string>
  <string id="24948" soundid="28919">The brothers Sung fight as one, and yet you fight as if you were three!</string>
  <string id="24949" soundid="28920">While the match invited the toothless donkey of unhappiness to our stable, we still praise your skills.</string>
  <string id="24950" soundid="28921">Look who stands before us, brothers!</string>
  <string id="24951" soundid="28922">A new warrior, flush with first victory. How very quaint!</string>
  <string id="24952" soundid="28923">You are the unstoppable force that left poor Han a cluttered pile of optimistic wreckage at the side of the arena.</string>
  <string id="24953" soundid="28924">The newest champion of the Bronze Division. We shall have to keep an eye on you. Very few climb so far so quickly.</string>
  <string id="24954" soundid="28925">The one who stands just below us in the rankings: our new Silver Division champion.</string>
  <string id="24955" soundid="28926">A recent winner from the qualifying round. How quaint.</string>
  <string id="24956" soundid="28927">The new fighter who is so quickly closing on Crimson Khana&apos;s position.</string>
  <string id="24957" soundid="28928">Why, it&apos;s the reason for Soldier&apos;s increased surliness. Congratulations on managing the impossible!</string>
  <string id="24958" soundid="28929">One who needs no introduction, I&apos;m sure. We watch most avidly to see how the little drama between you and Kai Lan turns out.</string>
  <string id="24959" soundid="28930">Disappointment itself approaches us.</string>
  <string id="24960" soundid="28931">Consider yourself draped in the starry shawl of fortune, for in your loss you have avoided facing your doom.</string>
  <string id="24961" soundid="28932">I&apos;m uncertain what advice to give you this early in your career. I would suggest that you try to hit them more than they hit you.</string>
  <string id="24962" soundid="28933">Do not worry yourself, though! No one really cares about the fights at your level, so who will remember your shame?</string>
  <string id="24963" soundid="28934">If such weak competition overwhelmed you, you might want to reconsider your career path.</string>
  <string id="24964" soundid="28935">The silver round is not for the faint of heart. Consider your inner balance before you enter the ring again.</string>
  <string id="24965" soundid="28936">There is no shame in defeat at this level. Even we cannot defeat the Ravager.</string>
  <string id="24966" soundid="28937">Bah! Be gone! The brothers Sung will waste no words on a boorish competitor.</string>
  <string id="24967" soundid="28938">You would speak again with the Sung brothers? How fascinating that we have earned so much of your attention.</string>
  <string id="24968" soundid="28939">They know better than to bother the brothers Sung! Still, one of their recruiters keeps an eye on the standings here. </string>
  <string id="24969" soundid="28940">Indeed, many young fighters on the cusp of the Gold Division have walked away in pursuit of... another ideal.</string>
  <string id="24970" soundid="32839">It&apos;s finally safe to go back to the Scholars&apos; Garden now that the Outlander has been dealt with.</string>
  <string id="24971" soundid="28942">Your expansive friend returns on a dark fall of the cards, I&apos;m afraid. His story, like all stories where brothers fall out, is not lightly told.</string>
  <string id="24972" soundid="28943">The Black Whirlwind and Raging Ox had a confrontation. No really knows what happened, but suffice it to say Ox remained here.</string>
  <string id="24973" soundid="28944">Raging Ox continued to rise through the ranks to become champion, while your friend left his brother, and the arena, behind.</string>
  <string id="24974" soundid="45858">I don&apos;t think anyone would have expected the champion to lose. It may have been just an exhibition fight, but you still gave it your all.</string>
  <string id="24975" soundid="28946">No one knows where Raging Ox has gone. He spent some time as champion, but then Kai Lan informed us that Ox had retired and was leaving the arena.</string>
  <string id="24976" soundid="28947">It&apos;s a shame. Everyone enjoyed his jovial personality, and he was a fair sight more pleasant than the Ravager.</string>
  <string id="24977">Support Style
Does direct damage in Chi Strike mode
This style&apos;s Power Attack can initiate a Harmonic Combo that produces a Health power-up.

Fighters skilled in Heavenly Wave learn techniques that can slow their opponents to a crawl. While this Support style does no damage on its own, a master can manipulate the chi in the area around opponents, rendering them sluggish and easily defeated. Even the most lightning-fast of foes can be slowed to a turtle&apos;s pace with the skillful application of Heavenly Wave. </string>
  <string id="24978" soundid="28949">Has there not already been a reaction of sorts? Kai Lan likely wants nothing more than his ex-star fighter to leave this place. Of course, that means he wants the same of you.</string>
  <string id="24979" soundid="28950">The Black Whirlwind was never one to follow rules, and Kai Lan is one who demands that his rules be followed.</string>
  <string id="24981" soundid="28952">Good! I don&apos;t like even listening to this kind of thing.</string>
  <string id="24982" soundid="28953">We can tell you to be careful whom you ask about such things. Secrets kept in the open are the most sensitive.</string>
  <string id="24983" soundid="28954">The serpent who dwells in the shadows of this place. Like an air spirit, he is everywhere and yet invisible to the eye.</string>
  <string id="24984" soundid="28955">Brother Sui puts it well. Kai Lan the Serpent is the Guild&apos;s will in this place, powerful enough that only the brave or foolish discuss him at any length.</string>
  <string id="24985" soundid="32840">That Outlander thought he was better than all of us. I doubt he&apos;ll be so arrogant in the future.</string>
  <string id="24986" soundid="28957">Besides running the most expansive betting operation in the Empire? I speculate that they do much more than that, but we have been smart enough not to find out.</string>
  <string id="24987" soundid="28958">We question things in the arena, though. For example, why are we allowed to fight as one body when the rules suggest such a thing should be illegal?</string>
  <string id="24988" soundid="28959">I agree! I don&apos;t want them around any more, they scare me.</string>
  <string id="24989" soundid="32841">That Outlander finally got his due. Hopefully, he&apos;s learned to be more tolerant.</string>
  <string id="24990" soundid="28961">A wise choice; the Guild always prefers that people not speak of them. What do you need to know?</string>
  <string id="24991">Crane</string>
  <string id="24996">To Two Rivers</string>
  <string id="24997" soundid="32842">It&apos;s about time somebody dealt with that annoying Outlander.</string>
  <string id="24998" soundid="28969">You have earned the right to ask about your peers.</string>
  <string id="24999" soundid="28970">Would you like to know about Soldier, or our current champion, the Ravager?</string>
  <string id="25000" soundid="32843">Please, don&apos;t hurt me. I never said anything against the Lotus Assassins, honestly.</string>
  <string id="25001" soundid="32844">I see the Lotus Assassins have gotten to you, too. I mean... not that there&apos;s anything wrong with that.</string>
  <string id="25002" soundid="32845">I&apos;ve never said an unkind word about the Lotus Assassins. Not one. Ever.</string>
  <string id="25003" soundid="32846">Didn&apos;t I see you talking with the Lotus Assassins earlier? Or was it that other strange looking... ah, er... never mind.</string>
  <string id="25004" soundid="28975">There is something unnatural about that one.</string>
  <string id="25005" soundid="28976">He smells bad, too, like he&apos;s sick all the time or something.</string>
  <string id="25006" soundid="28977">Of course. What did you want to know?</string>
  <string id="25007" soundid="28978">We should not discuss the city, Brother, while we are within its bounds. </string>
  <string id="25008" soundid="28979">Do the stars show the dragons in ascension again? Then we should not speak of the city for now. The very topic is risky.</string>
  <string id="25009" soundid="32847">I have seen many Arena Champions come and go, and I can honestly say, that you&apos;re one of them.</string>
  <string id="25010" soundid="32848">I knew you would win your championship fight when I first saw you. The heavens favor you greatly.</string>
  <string id="25011" soundid="32849">I only wish I had seen you defeat the Ravager with my own eyes. I didn&apos;t think anyone could beat him.</string>
  <string id="25012" soundid="28983">How dare you mock our family unity?</string>
  <string id="25013" soundid="28984">Indeed. We deal with enough ignorance of the ancient ways and customs of the Empire; we do not need additional abuse.</string>
  <string id="25014" soundid="32850">Aren&apos;t you the new Arena Champion? What good fortune to actually meet you in person!</string>
  <string id="25015" soundid="32851">You should be careful now that you&apos;ve done well in the arena. You might draw unwanted attention.</string>
  <string id="25016" soundid="32852">I lost plenty of silver betting against you. Next time, my money&apos;s on you.</string>
  <string id="25017" soundid="32853">You&apos;ve done well so far in the arena, but I&apos;m not sure you&apos;re a match for the Ravager.</string>
  <string id="25018" soundid="32854">I&apos;ve heard about your exploits in the arena. Very impressive for a first-timer.</string>
  <string id="25020" soundid="32855">I&apos;ve seen what happens to some of the arena fighters. It isn&apos;t pretty.</string>
  <string id="25026" soundid="106851">Iron Soldier&apos;s offer is too lucrative to be strictly honorable. He&apos;s appealing to your greed, so there&apos;s obviously more to this story.</string>
  <string id="25032">Do you know anything about recruiters for the Lotus Assassins?</string>
  <string id="25035">I need to know about the Black Whirlwind and Kai Lan.</string>
  <string id="25036">Why did the Black Whirlwind leave the arena?</string>
  <string id="25038">Where can I find the Black Whirlwind&apos;s brother?</string>
  <string id="25040">How do you think Kai Lan will react to the Black Whirlwind&apos;s return?</string>
  <string id="25042">Let&apos;s talk about something else.</string>
  <string id="25043">What can you tell me about the Guild?</string>
  <string id="25044">Who is Kai Lan?</string>
  <string id="25046" soundid="32856">My grandfather fought in the arena... once.</string>
  <string id="25047">What does the Guild do here, exactly?</string>
  <string id="25049" soundid="32857">You look tough, but I&apos;m not sure if you have what it takes to win in the arena.</string>
  <string id="25050">Why doesn&apos;t the Empire just stop the Guild?</string>
  <string id="25051">I want to ask about something else.</string>
  <string id="25052" soundid="127133">I can arrange for a little sparring. Are there any special conditions you would like to introduce? I know you prefer a challenge.</string>
  <string id="25054" soundid="31892">Minister Sheng has very little to say. There is a rumor that the Great Dam is broken. We are doomed. No goods can enter the town. No fish can be taken from the river.</string>
  <string id="25055" soundid="31893">Perhaps I did not do enough. May I confide something in you?</string>
  <string id="25056" soundid="31894">I am not nearly as capable as I let on. It is even possible that my banishment here was not entirely because of the jealousy of others.</string>
  <string id="25057" soundid="31895">It may have been due to my numerous failings in the Imperial City. But I am sure you don&apos;t want to listen to the ramblings of a tired, broken man.</string>
  <string id="25058" soundid="31896">What can I do for you?</string>
  <string id="25059" soundid="31897">Very well then, Minister Sheng shall carry the burden of his misery alone. What can I do for you?</string>
  <string id="25060" soundid="31898">Not at all! I may even mention you in my report.</string>
  <string id="25061">Can we talk about some of the fighters around here?</string>
  <string id="25062" soundid="32858">So you&apos;re the new fighter in town. Good luck, you&apos;ll need it.</string>
  <string id="25064" soundid="32859">That Outlander in the Scholars&apos; Garden has a terrible weapon, the likes of which I&apos;ve never seen before.</string>
  <string id="25065" soundid="32860">Apparently the Outlander is causing some problems in the Scholars&apos; Garden.</string>
  <string id="25067">What&apos;s the story with Soldier?</string>
  <string id="25070">Tell me about the Ravager, then.</string>
  <string id="25073">Let&apos;s go back to my other questions.</string>
  <string id="25074">Let&apos;s talk about the city in general.</string>
  <string id="25082">I&apos;m growing tired of having three conversations. Even if you can&apos;t fight alone, you should be able to talk alone.</string>
  <string id="25086">That&apos;s all I need from you three for now.</string>
  <string id="25120">Pirate</string>
  <string id="25141" soundid="29153">How&apos;d I know you&apos;d be deadly in a fight? You&apos;ll have to accept my apologies for dragging you into that, but I can&apos;t afford to be stopped. Not now.</string>
  <string id="25186">How did you end up here?</string>
  <string id="25187">Your plan didn&apos;t work out too well.</string>
  <string id="25189">Player Backed Out of the Play</string>
  <string id="25190">Apple</string>
  <string id="25243">I didn&apos;t want to kill him. He left me no choice.</string>
  <string id="25244">Gao brought his fate on himself.</string>
  <string id="25246">I enjoyed killing your son... now I&apos;m going to kill you!</string>
  <string id="25254" soundid="150747">What? Oh... you... you&apos;re the one with the flyer aren&apos;t you? Forgive my impertinence, but do you own that flyer perhaps?</string>
  <string id="25255" soundid="150748">No, you&apos;re right. I don&apos;t mean to offend, but if you would allow me, I would like to make it my business.</string>
  <string id="25259" soundid="150749">I am Hin Goo, a mechanic and a businessman. I supply upgrades to people fortunate enough to have flyers.</string>
  <string id="25261" soundid="71818">Spirit? I&apos;m not dead, you idiot! If I were, would I be this upset about losing my house? Or breathing, for that matter?</string>
  <string id="25262" soundid="71819">So, that&apos;s how this goes, is it? Who is paying you? My son? Shen? First, my son catches me sleeping and convinces everyone I&apos;d died, then he gets the damn gravedigger to bury me!</string>
  <string id="25263" soundid="71820">With all the real ghosts coming up out of their graves, no one wants to get close enough to find out the truth. That young bastard has stolen my life! Well, what&apos;s left of it.</string>
  <string id="25264" soundid="71821">With no place to go, and everyone running in fear from the &quot;ghost,&quot; where else could I go? I built this house from the ground up, and I&apos;m not about to let him take it from me!</string>
  <string id="25265" soundid="71822">They sent the quick one, didn&apos;t they?</string>
  <string id="25266" soundid="71823">No, I&apos;m not dead, you idiot!</string>
  <string id="25267" soundid="71824">My son just used that as an excuse to take everything!</string>
  <string id="25268" soundid="71825">Why do you think? Money, the house, my business that I spent 20 years making....</string>
  <string id="25270" soundid="165564">Still don&apos;t trust my intentions? Have a little faith that sometimes fate provides answers when they&apos;re needed most. Either way, we need to deal with that door.</string>
  <string id="25272">This seems awfully convenient.</string>
  <string id="25303">Thousand Cuts</string>
  <string id="25331" soundid="45785">The water kept rising. And rising. And then we died. But the quarry is still ours, even when we&apos;re dead! And now you&apos;ll join us!</string>
  <string id="25384" soundid="70032">As you wish. If you&apos;d like to try a match later, come and see me.</string>
  <string id="25386">Pirate</string>
  <string id="25387" soundid="70033">Good to see you again. What can I do for you?</string>
  <string id="25389" soundid="70034">You&apos;re one of the best students I&apos;ve ever fought. You&apos;re ready to try your skill against Third Brother. He&apos;ll offer you a much greater challenge.</string>
  <string id="25391">Captain</string>
  <string id="25392" soundid="70035">You have some very impressive moves. With practice, you&apos;ll get even better. Would you like to try another fight?</string>
  <string id="25394" soundid="151651">Do you realize how much trouble you&apos;ve caused me? I&apos;ll be doing paperwork on that fight of yours well into next week.</string>
  <string id="25396">Slave</string>
  <string id="25397" soundid="151652">For so long, it appeared you&apos;d be one of the easy ones. Then that whole bandit attack happened, and I haven&apos;t rested since.</string>
  <string id="25399" soundid="151653">You mortals have no concept of what we celestial bureaucrats have to put up with. Is it really that difficult to stop and, I don&apos;t know... *think* before brandishing your weapons?</string>
  <string id="25401">Slave</string>
  <string id="25404" soundid="70040">I&apos;m not really surprised that you defeated Smiling Hawk. Your skills are absolutely amazing.</string>
  <string id="25406">Slave</string>
  <string id="25407" soundid="70041">With Smiling Hawk out of the way, we can finally get back the respect our school has lost over the past few years.</string>
  <string id="25409" soundid="154743">Maybe we should investigate Fang in the arena first. We might be able to stop him from getting that report without hurting Sheng... or anyone else.</string>
  <string id="25411">Yeung Yifong</string>
  <string id="25416">Pirate</string>
  <string id="25417">Yes, let&apos;s fight!</string>
  <string id="25419" soundid="151654">(Sigh) You have no idea what I&apos;m talking about, do you? I am Zin Bu, the Magic Abacus. I was assigned to record, tabulate, and itemize the destruction that you cause.</string>
  <string id="25421">Kang the Mad</string>
  <string id="25422" soundid="151655">No easy task, I might add, especially since you embarked on this wild quest to find your master.</string>
  <string id="25424" soundid="151656">Our calculations keep the universe in balance. Without us, chaos... anarchy... utter ruination.</string>
  <string id="25427">I need to go. Goodbye.</string>
  <string id="25429" soundid="151657">Ha! Again you show your ignorance. Do you have any idea of the chaos that would be unleashed if we suddenly stopped calculating? It&apos;s ridiculous!</string>
  <string id="25431">Gao the Greater</string>
  <string id="25432" soundid="151658">Look at your associate, Black Whirlwind. What a nightmare. A whole department can&apos;t keep up with his antics!</string>
  <string id="25434">Tseng</string>
  <string id="25436">Grand Inquisitor Jia</string>
  <string id="25446">Slave Breaker</string>
  <string id="25451">Wild Flower</string>
  <string id="25461">Xianshi</string>
  <string id="25466">Pirate Cheung</string>
  <string id="25471" soundid="29789">Now you are in for it! Those guards see you!</string>
  <string id="25472" soundid="29790">Use this! Good for the head breaking!</string>
  <string id="25473" soundid="197955"></string>
  <string id="25476">I closed the dam. The Lotus Assassins removed the amulet.</string>
  <string id="25477" soundid="166499">[You have placed the powder in the pan.]</string>
  <string id="25482" soundid="29800">Hey, ha ha! Much kicking and such. It really gets the blood flowing. And explosions... lots of blood flowing from those, too.</string>
  <string id="25483" soundid="29801">Now, we should leave here! We can make it as far as that nearby town, Tien&apos;s Landing. I know the winds between here and there. Mostly. I mostly know the winds. It will be fine.</string>
  <string id="25484" soundid="29802">Ha ha! Everybody on board! The Marvelous Dragonfly is about to take flight!</string>
  <string id="25490" soundid="29808">This is good, too!  Ooh! That&apos;s going to hurt!</string>
  <string id="25491" soundid="29809">You handled the guards well, with your punching and the kicking. I was going to make more of an explody thing, but the kicking worked well, too.</string>
  <string id="25493" soundid="29811">Not so. You may have adequate feet for the kicking, but your eyes are not so good at judging. I only work for Gao because he forces me to.</string>
  <string id="25494" soundid="29812">I make all sorts of things and, yes, many are designed to expend energy, ah, quickly. But my greatest prize does not explode. Much. Something I have kept for myself.</string>
  <string id="25496" soundid="29814">I am Kang the Mad. I make things explode, and I make things fly, and I am very good at both. The things I fly tend to survive. The things I explode... not so much.</string>
  <string id="25497" soundid="29815">My greatest invention is in the launch room upstairs. Light and fast, she has weapons and capacity no other flyer does. The Marvelous Dragonfly!</string>
  <string id="25506" soundid="29824">What else can I do? Er, actually, not all that much. I mean, I can bolt any two things together and maybe a forest burns down, but flight is where I shine.</string>
  <string id="25507" soundid="29825">You don&apos;t need it now, but soon you&apos;ll wonder how you ever did without. I was the same, long ago. &quot;Flyers don&apos;t need weapons,&quot; I thought. I tried to keep them pure.</string>
  <string id="25509" soundid="110005">My best guess would be guards willing to die for their master. You shouldn&apos;t have too much trouble helping them reach that goal.</string>
  <string id="25511" soundid="29829">You are sure to profit from this partnership. In fact, I&apos;ve never accidentally exploded anyone traveling *with* me, so that alone is a benefit of my presence.</string>
  <string id="25512" soundid="29830">Of course, of course, take what you will, but if you will, er, want the Dragonfly, you&apos;ll need me. She&apos;s a delicate creation, in need of constant maintenance.</string>
  <string id="25513" soundid="29831">Anyway, you go ahead, and once all the kicking is done, I&apos;ll come along, and we&apos;ll see what&apos;s what! For now, let me think! We&apos;ll need explosives... that explode.</string>
  <string id="25515">Who are you?</string>
  <string id="25517">I do what I want and take what I want.</string>
  <string id="25519">There was nothing there. I&apos;m tracking the Lotus Assassins elsewhere.</string>
  <string id="25520">You can maintain concentration longer, allowing you to stay in Focus mode for a greater length of time</string>
  <string id="25521" soundid="197960"></string>
  <string id="25522" soundid="197961"></string>
  <string id="25529">Okay, let&apos;s get out of here.</string>
  <string id="25530">I&apos;m not ready to leave yet.</string>
  <string id="25534">You work for Gao!</string>
  <string id="25536">You make things explode?</string>
  <string id="25541">You built Gao a special flyer?</string>
  <string id="25551">What else can you do?</string>
  <string id="25553">I have no need of your toys.</string>
  <string id="25556">You recover more quickly from exiting Focus mode.</string>
  <string id="25557">I agree. I will see what I can do.</string>
  <string id="25558">Silk Fox</string>
  <string id="25581">Imperial Soldier</string>
  <string id="25586">Imperial Soldier</string>
  <string id="25591">Bin</string>
  <string id="25597">Commoner</string>
  <string id="25598" soundid="36721">I was tasked with protection of the amulet and the gems that are a part of it. But to do that, I had to enter the mortal realm, where they were.</string>
  <string id="25600" soundid="36723">Two treasures were entrusted to me: an amulet and a gem. Both are items of great power, but I do not know what they do. I only know they are meant for you.</string>
  <string id="25601" soundid="36724">They came only a few days ago, looking for the amulet and the gem I protected. There were many of them... too many. They attacked me all at once.</string>
  <string id="25603" soundid="36726">And know this before you die: I will hunt down every Lotus Assassin in the Empire until I get back the amulet your master stole!</string>
  <string id="25605">Thug</string>
  <string id="25607" soundid="36730">No! I will not listen to your lies! I will not be fooled again!</string>
  <string id="25608" soundid="36731">His followers fought me by the dozen, a distraction while he stole the amulet and fled. But you challenge me alone... and you are winning. Who are you?</string>
  <string id="25611" soundid="36734">I am Chai Ka the Heavenly Gate Guardian. In the language of your realm, I am called a demon. My mind is uneasy here, and there are many things I cannot remember.</string>
  <string id="25612" soundid="36735">But I know my fate is bound to yours. Your path will surely lead you to the amulet that was stolen from me. I will be glad to see it in your hands, where it belongs.</string>
  <string id="25613">Bandit</string>
  <string id="25614" soundid="36737">I will try to answer what I can. There is much I cannot say. I am here to fulfill the destiny that has been placed before me.</string>
  <string id="25615">I want to ask you some questions.</string>
  <string id="25621">Miao</string>
  <string id="25622">Tell me about the items you were guarding.</string>
  <string id="25623">You said Lotus Assassins stole the amulet?</string>
  <string id="25627">Amulet? Gem? What are you talking about?</string>
  <string id="25629">I am not your enemy. Stop this fighting, and we can talk.</string>
  <string id="25632">I am &lt;FullName&gt;.</string>
  <string id="25634">You better tell me what&apos;s going on here!</string>
  <string id="25646">Student Wen</string>
  <string id="25647">Blocked:  &lt;CUSTOM0&gt;</string>
  <string id="25648">Blocked</string>
  <string id="25649">Blocked</string>
  <string id="25650" soundid="30219">I&apos;ve never seen anyone dare to say so much against the royal family and live to walk away. The distress you caused her handlers was a wonder to behold.</string>
  <string id="25651" soundid="30220">Here, friend. Take this, with my compliments. I&apos;ve never seen such a thing.</string>
  <string id="25653">Ru</string>
  <string id="25658">Kindly Yushan</string>
  <string id="25705" soundid="107248"></string>
  <string id="25706">Rat Demon</string>
  <string id="25713" soundid="57435">Only those with business in the fields should leave the village, preferably with proper escort.</string>
  <string id="25732">I do not serve the Lotus Assassins!</string>
  <string id="25738">Workshop</string>
  <string id="25783">Bai the Outcrier</string>
  <string id="25793">Commoner</string>
  <string id="25805">Commoner</string>
  <string id="25809" soundid="62097">Hello again. I suppose it would be too much to hope you are here to buy some buns.</string>
  <string id="25987" soundid="161235">I sense my former student refuses to rest easy. The time for subtlety is past.</string>
  <string id="26006">Large Damage Increase</string>
  <string id="26018" soundid="139490">Hey! Leave our novices alone. If you want to fight, you can fight me!</string>
  <string id="26020" soundid="139491">Peace, Third Brother. That is no way to treat a guest.</string>
  <string id="26023" soundid="110294">You again. Why are you still pestering me? Don&apos;t you have something better to do?</string>
  <string id="26025" soundid="139492">Good. You&apos;ll need to speak with each of the brothers and ask them to fight with you. I&apos;m sure they&apos;ll be more than eager to oblige.</string>
  <string id="26028" soundid="139493">It is... complicated. If you prove yourself, I&apos;m sure that Master Radiant will be more than happy to explain it to you.</string>
  <string id="26030" soundid="139494">It is not just his fighting skills that make him dangerous. Master Smiling Hawk&apos;s need for power consumes him. He cannot be trusted.</string>
  <string id="26033" soundid="110295">Out, out, out! The dining hall is a mess, and I doubt you&apos;re here to help me clean!</string>
  <string id="26045" soundid="139495">For now, be careful and focus on defeating the brothers. Start with Sixth Brother and ask him to fight with you. I&apos;m sure he&apos;ll be eager.</string>
  <string id="26048" soundid="139496">Once you&apos;ve defeated all of the brothers, come and see me. Good luck.</string>
  <string id="26050" soundid="70120">Hello again. What can I do for you today?</string>
  <string id="26053" soundid="139497">I see. Well, if you change your mind, come back and see me. In the meantime, I should get back to the students. Goodbye and good luck.</string>
  <string id="26055" soundid="139498">Ah, welcome back. Have you changed your mind about joining our school? Say the word, and I&apos;ll ask our masters.</string>
  <string id="26058" soundid="139499">You still haven&apos;t defeated any of the brothers yet.</string>
  <string id="26060" soundid="139500">Certainly. What would you like to know?</string>
  <string id="26065" soundid="139501">Third Brother Renshan is probably the most gifted fighter I&apos;ve ever seen. None here at the school, except the masters, are his equal.</string>
  <string id="26068" soundid="139502">Unfortunately, Third Brother is a terrible leader and poor teacher. Much like Master Smiling Hawk, he cares nothing for the other students or the school.</string>
  <string id="26070" soundid="139503">Third Brother has gained his rank on shear skill, but I doubt he will climb higher. It takes more than martial skill to be a master.</string>
  <string id="26088" soundid="70135">For surely the Emperor must have been surveying the cold plains he had just conquered in the name of enlightenment. </string>
  <string id="26090" soundid="70136">The Horselords are said to ingest copious amounts of an extremely sugary, creamy form of tea. I understand it keeps their strength up. Barbarous.</string>
  <string id="26093" soundid="70137">The Emperor sends word of his return. The Horselords are unconquered? But our forces were undefeatable!</string>
  <string id="26095" soundid="70138">My lady, you have my deepest thanks for bringing this news to us! I shall inform the court immediately!</string>
  <string id="26113">Celestial Canvas</string>
  <string id="26115">Pearl Tears of the Dragon</string>
  <string id="26118">Deng Zhi&apos;s Corrupted Gem</string>
  <string id="26120">Standard of the Lost Regiment</string>
  <string id="26138">Sagacious Zu</string>
  <string id="26245">Novice Bo</string>
  <string id="26253" soundid="70221"></string>
  <string id="26255" soundid="70222">This report says that the Emperor stood at the edge of their lands and saw the brightest of shooting stars trace a path across the night sky.</string>
  <string id="26263" soundid="105599">SILENCE!</string>
  <string id="26264" soundid="105600">You have spoken, and I have heard. Your will be done! I give you...THE RAVAGER!</string>
  <string id="26265" soundid="30670">I have concerns about their order, but I will not voice them here. Not in the city where even the shadows have ears.</string>
  <string id="26286">Buy from Store</string>
  <string id="26290" soundid="127134">Very well. I&apos;ll choose someone who is competent in one-on-one combat. This is only a practice bout, so fight until your opponent is knocked out. Get ready.</string>
  <string id="26292" soundid="127136">Interesting. I have a number of students who would benefit from being on either side of such a bout. Perhaps as many as four.</string>
  <string id="26293" soundid="127137">A duo to test their cooperation. Some of the younger students will think you are easy prey in such a situation. Show them the truth.</string>
  <string id="26294" soundid="127138">Remember, this is only a practice match. It will continue until you or your opponents are rendered unconscious.</string>
  <string id="26295" soundid="127139">A trio. Very well. This will be a valuable experience for all involved.</string>
  <string id="26296" soundid="127140">Facing a foursome means that you will have to remain aware of the fighting environment the whole time. Be ready.</string>
  <string id="26297" soundid="127141">Yes, I suppose your fight against the bandits made you want to brush up on this technique. I can arrange for as many as four students to fight you.</string>
  <string id="26298" soundid="127142">Yes, I imagine Gao&apos;s actions have taught you the need to be ready for the unexpected. I can provide as many as four students to spar with you.</string>
  <string id="26299" soundid="127143">I am sorry, but Master Li does not permit such techniques to be flaunted at the school. There is danger in wielding such power if you are not ready.</string>
  <string id="26300" soundid="127144">He does not demonstrate those skills very often. There are paths of the Way that hold great temptation if one is not careful. I can clarify this, but I cannot offer the fight you wish.</string>
  <string id="26302" soundid="127146">You have seen the arrogance of others. Gao is well along the Way of the Closed Fist. I can clarify this, but I cannot offer the fight you wish.</string>
  <string id="26303" soundid="127147">No. Everyone is concerned about Dawn Star. Such distraction could lead to mistakes in the ring, and I don&apos;t want any accidents.</string>
  <string id="26304" soundid="127148">Good luck finding Dawn Star. Stay on the path of honor.</string>
  <string id="26305" soundid="127149">Goodbye. I am here if you need anything.</string>
  <string id="26307" soundid="127150">I heard how you faced those bandits in the village. Many people are impressed, but I expected no less. Your skill is a match for any rough bandit.</string>
  <string id="26308" soundid="127151">Is there anything you need? Perhaps a training session with some of the students? It would do them good.</string>
  <string id="26310" soundid="160017">Even though you let *me* cut the head off of Kai Lan the Serpent, you&apos;re still the arena champion.</string>
  <string id="26345" soundid="127153"></string>
  <string id="26346" soundid="127154">What can I do for you? I am here to serve and train.</string>
  <string id="26347" soundid="127155">Hmm, a surprising outcome, but it is the rush of the stream that smoothes the pebble. You must work to maintain focus.</string>
  <string id="26348" soundid="127156"></string>
  <string id="26350">Can I ask you some things about the school?</string>
  <string id="26351">Tell me about the philosophies you mention.</string>
  <string id="26353">Tell me about the Way of the Open Palm.</string>
  <string id="26355">Give me examples.</string>
  <string id="26356">You met the ghosts of two children at the orphanage in the ruins. They died in the flood because the orphan master, Kindly Yushan, abandoned them. They want your help.</string>
  <string id="26358">Sometimes conflict cannot be avoided.</string>
  <string id="26361">Tell me about the Way of the Closed Fist.</string>
  <string id="26363">So what is it, if it is not &quot;evil?&quot;</string>
  <string id="26368">Exit to desktop.</string>
  <string id="26409">Sure. Let&apos;s fight.</string>
  <string id="26415" soundid="151659">You, for instance, Black Whirlwind. You&apos;re a nightmare. A whole department can&apos;t keep up with your antics.</string>
  <string id="26416" soundid="151660">But imagine if they failed to record his various... deeds. We would never be able to determine his eventual position on the Great Wheel.</string>
  <string id="26417" soundid="151661">You can&apos;t just guess at it! You must have records. Itemized records, in triplicate, signed by the Overseer of Carnal Destruction and Disorder herself!</string>
  <string id="26418">Tell me about the Black Leopard School.</string>
  <string id="26427">I want to ask you some questions.</string>
  <string id="26428">Tell me about the Lotus Assassins.</string>
  <string id="26429">What were they searching for?</string>
  <string id="26430">Do you know anything about these ruins?</string>
  <string id="26433">I need to go. Goodbye.</string>
  <string id="26437" soundid="162042">I heard you got rid of Lan for me. With her out of the picture, it&apos;s only a matter of time until Bei gives in and we get married!</string>
  <string id="26438" soundid="151662">You don&apos;t know the half of it. You remember that little engagement with Gao the Lesser? Three thousand and forty pages! I lost three assistants on that report alone!</string>
  <string id="26439" soundid="151663">Ah ha! The very reason I&apos;m here, and not back in the Celestial Bureaucracy tabulating your most recent exploits. Apparently my skills are inadequate to keep up with you!</string>
  <string id="26440" soundid="151664">Time? What do you know of time? You just make the messes. *I* have to document them... or I did at least. Apparently my inability to keep up with you has cost me.</string>
  <string id="26441" soundid="151665">I&apos;m being relegated to a much lower role, in trade and commerce. My only consolation is that I will no longer have to track your exploits.</string>
  <string id="26442" soundid="109261">Well, the school is the best of its kind in all the Empire. I consider myself very fortunate to be a student here.</string>
  <string id="26443" soundid="109262">That&apos;s not to say that we don&apos;t have our problems. Having two masters is a bit... unusual, and it seems to slow the progress of the school.</string>
  <string id="26444" soundid="151666">And you&apos;re going to help me. Instead of trying to find you a buyer or supplier wherever you go, I&apos;m going to provide that service directly.</string>
  <string id="26445">Arena Tavern</string>
  <string id="26446">Tell me about the Black Leopard School.</string>
  <string id="26449" soundid="139504">I can&apos;t get into the details of how that came about. However, I can tell you that it was not intended to be that way.</string>
  <string id="26453">Keep your tongue in check, Dawn Star, or you&apos;re next!</string>
  <string id="26490" soundid="151667">I need you to buy from me and sell to me, if you wish. I already have a supplier, a friend of mine from the Untimely Deaths department, who was also demoted recently.</string>
  <string id="26492" soundid="146880">You&apos;re no ghost. Hell, you&apos;re barely human! No one has ever withstood the axes of the Black Whirlwind before!</string>
  <string id="26495" soundid="109272">The school has strong leadership, but we currently suffer from having too many leaders. Two masters is one too many.</string>
  <string id="26497" soundid="109273">I don&apos;t mind Master Radiant, but he is too detached... and too passive. Master Smiling Hawk could regain our respect, if Master Radiant would let him.</string>
  <string id="26498" soundid="109274">I really shouldn&apos;t say any more than I already have. If you are still curious, you can speak to First Brother Kai.</string>
  <string id="26499" soundid="160776">How should I know? He&apos;s probably licking Master Radiant&apos;s sandals... he was always such a devoted follower of that... man.</string>
  <string id="26501" soundid="146881">Congratulations on winning the Bronze Division. But... ah... I... ah....</string>
  <string id="26503">As you wish. Leave, peasant, and never return!</string>
  <string id="26505">Lustful Lao</string>
  <string id="26507" soundid="109276">Of course. Please return if you wish to spar. Good day.</string>
  <string id="26511" soundid="109277">The Black Leopard School is the most prestigious school in the Empire. We accept only the best students.</string>
  <string id="26512" soundid="109278">If the novices would spend more time studying and less time fighting, perhaps they would actually learn something.</string>
  <string id="26513" soundid="109279">I admire First Brother&apos;s ability to teach. He certainly has a way with the students.</string>
  <string id="26514" soundid="109280">If you need more information about the Black Leopard School, please refer your questions to First Brother Kai.</string>
  <string id="26515" soundid="151668">Actually... I need you to buy from me, and occasionally sell any items you no longer need.</string>
  <string id="26517" soundid="151669">By getting rid of the other suppliers and buyers, I can save time and be more efficient. Perhaps then I can regain some of the honor I lost through this demotion.</string>
  <string id="26518" soundid="151670">In any case, I&apos;ll be joining with you, in a sense, to offer you items for sale and to purchase anything extra you acquire. It&apos;s a fair deal, I believe.</string>
  <string id="26520" soundid="139505">A school should only have one master. The... rivalry between our masters is hurting the school and the students.</string>
  <string id="26525">Guard</string>
  <string id="26526" soundid="139506">Of course, neither master wishes to step down. It is a problem that needs to be solved if this school is going to survive.</string>
  <string id="26527" soundid="109288">It is good to have only one master again. Now, the school can focus on its future and move ahead.</string>
  <string id="26529">I don&apos;t believe you. Time to die!</string>
  <string id="26530">Fine. Answer my questions and I&apos;ll let you live.</string>
  <string id="26531">He served our enemy. He deserves only death!</string>
  <string id="26539" soundid="139507">Officially, I follow both. I am First Brother and it is my duty to assist both masters in any way I can.</string>
  <string id="26542" soundid="145344">Be on your guard if you truly mean to pursue him. Gao&apos;s mad with rage, as this poor lad learned too late.</string>
  <string id="26545">What was in the sack?</string>
  <string id="26547" soundid="139508">That being said, I was taught by Master Radiant, and I go to him for advice or learning in a given area.</string>
  <string id="26548">Could it have been a person?</string>
  <string id="26549">If he went toward the gate, maybe I can still catch him.</string>
  <string id="26551" soundid="145352">I would. I would give anything to see her saved, but my techniques are much more advanced than any normal &apos;doctor&apos; could comprehend.</string>
  <string id="26552" soundid="145353">I must do the operation myself or find a savant of such skill that I would feel safe giving them control.</string>
  <string id="26553" soundid="145354">A doctor? Of such skill? Who is it? What is his name? Where did you find such a person?</string>
  <string id="26554" soundid="145355">A doctor... and a woman? Amazing! You think she can help? Please, then, bring her to me! Let me speak with her!</string>
  <string id="26555" soundid="145356">Thank you, stranger! Thank you! Bring her to me and she may be able to help me with the operation.</string>
  <string id="26556" soundid="145357">Please stranger, even if you will not bring this doctor to me, you can still help! If you look, you might find the pristine liver I require!</string>
  <string id="26557" soundid="145358">Yes... yes! It looks like it has been preserved well enough! Although... it seems... a little dark. It feels... odd. But no matter! It is good enough!</string>
  <string id="26558" soundid="145359">Now I must begin quickly. Her life energy is fading fast.</string>
  <string id="26559" soundid="195245"></string>
  <string id="26560" soundid="145361">It looks like the operation has worked. She should be safe now. Her breathing has slowed and her heart rate is returning to normal levels.</string>
  <string id="26561" soundid="145362">It will be some time before she can stand on her own again, but I am certain she will make it. Not here, though... not in this place of death.</string>
  <string id="26562" soundid="145363">No... no! Something is wrong! Quick, come here and help me!</string>
  <string id="26563" soundid="145821">That is your cause. I understand, but you are a fool to fight our inevitable rule. Your Master will learn this, and so shall you.</string>
  <string id="26564" soundid="145365">No! No! It&apos;s not working! The liver functions, but it... it&apos;s just not working!</string>
  <string id="26565" soundid="145366"></string>
</tlk>