<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<tlk language="0">
  <string id="29146" soundid="150705">Keep an eye out for a strange looking man in priestly robes.</string>
  <string id="29147">Then you did kill him!</string>
  <string id="29148">Defeat Jing Woo!</string>
  <string id="29150">There is a problem with your husband&apos;s spirit.</string>
  <string id="29151">And I&apos;m here to carry out his curse!</string>
  <string id="29163" soundid="144348">Come to think of it, these reports of bandits might be just the thing to revitalize the local economy.</string>
  <string id="29169">Martial Style
This style can complete a Harmonic Combo. 

Practitioners of Iron Palm throw their entire body into each blow, mixing open-handed strikes with powerful, driving assaults. A low stance ensures that each blow directs momentum from the user&apos;s entire body to hit with the force of a sledgehammer. This mixture of power, balance, and brute strength demolishes individual opponents as easily as it scatters groups.</string>
  <string id="29177">Sentry Statue</string>
  <string id="29183" soundid="144349">Besides, the bandits didn&apos;t do as much to bring people to the store as I hoped, so maybe stability is underrated.</string>
  <string id="29186" soundid="144350">Happily. We don&apos;t need to waste time on my gripes when there&apos;s silver to be spent.</string>
  <string id="29187" soundid="144351">What can I do for you?</string>
  <string id="29193">You should find somewhere safe. There&apos;s already scouts here.</string>
  <string id="29204" soundid="49067">Many a bottle of wine finished, many a trip on the river. More bottles than trips, to be honest. Not much more to tell. I&apos;m just a simple man with simple needs.</string>
  <string id="29206">Falcon</string>
  <string id="29207">Monkey</string>
  <string id="29208">Demon</string>
  <string id="29209">While not the fastest or strongest of warriors, the balanced character is the most versatile. The balanced character excels at adapting to exploit her enemies&apos; weaknesses.</string>
  <string id="29210">Radiant Jen Zi</string>
  <string id="29211">Why are these demons attacking this place?</string>
  <string id="29213">I will go speak with the Forest Shadow.</string>
  <string id="29215">Enter Portal</string>
  <string id="29216">Soldier</string>
  <string id="29219" soundid="132502">Of course. I may be able to shed some light on the forest for you. I know this area very well, as I often meditate here upon my purpose and philosophy before a hunt.</string>
  <string id="29220" soundid="132503">By all reports, it will be well enough soon. We have you to thank for that.</string>
  <string id="29221">What can you tell me about the temple where we met?</string>
  <string id="29223" soundid="132506">To unlock the furnaces, you must place the crystal in the temple&apos;s central pedestal. Beyond that, you will have to inspect the old records I saw inside the temple.</string>
  <string id="29224" soundid="189937">This place is... strange. The Guardian says not to worry, but... I hear things here. I don&apos;t know what they are.</string>
  <string id="29226" soundid="132509">When I searched the area, I found those strange tracks that lead towards the inn. That is where I would begin my search.</string>
  <string id="29227">Demon</string>
  <string id="29229">Where should I look for the missing crystal?</string>
  <string id="29231">Ancient Horse Demon</string>
  <string id="29239" soundid="80424">When will more come?</string>
  <string id="29243" soundid="142119">Ha! You&apos;re so desperate for silver that you&apos;re threatening old men? That&apos;s pitiful. Here, if you&apos;re so hard off, take a few silvers.</string>
  <string id="29244" soundid="80425">The forest is closed. None will come, except from Tien&apos;s Landing, and that path is closing.</string>
  <string id="29247" soundid="132538">If I must die, then you must finish what you have started! Destroy that beast before she poisons all these lands!</string>
  <string id="29250" soundid="181947">Now... we must go to the throne room. Sun Li will be waiting.</string>
  <string id="29251" soundid="132542">We are free of the curse of the Forest Shadow, all of us! This is a time for celebration!</string>
  <string id="29257" soundid="80426">The green one will starve us with her trees!</string>
  <string id="29288" soundid="132578">I have to wedge the casks of dragon powder under the bridge. The Lotus Assassins are sure to come up that pass any minute. Keep them from this end of the bridge.</string>
  <string id="29290" soundid="138197">Yes. I don&apos;t know how, but....</string>
  <string id="29291" soundid="138198">Not this, I don&apos;t want to be one of them!</string>
  <string id="29292" soundid="138199">They...ungh...they&apos;re capturing people, changing some and eating the rest. By the spirits, you have to help me!</string>
  <string id="29293" soundid="138200">Please, I beg of you!</string>
  <string id="29294" soundid="132584">Er, Kang, old friend, I&apos;d like to borrow a few of your marvelously explosive casks. I have something special in mind for any Assassins who breach our lines.</string>
  <string id="29295" soundid="132585">What? Yes, yes, whatever you want. I have enough on my mind.</string>
  <string id="29296" soundid="132586">Are you sure I shouldn&apos;t just charge the main gate? They would not be expecting that.</string>
  <string id="29297" soundid="132587">My fill? I have been *sated* from wine and battle, but never filled.</string>
  <string id="29298" soundid="132588">Chai Ka: We will stand to the last. That is the duty of a Guardian.</string>
  <string id="29299" soundid="132589">It looks like we won&apos;t have long to wait. Kang better keep his mind on his task at the bridge, or this will be a short last stand.</string>
  <string id="29300" soundid="132590">Ya Zhen: I don&apos;t like these odds, but death is not as final for me as it is for you, so what do I care?</string>
  <string id="29301" soundid="132591">Ha! So we shall! Blood will flow like wine, and then wine will flow like blood! That is *my* Great Wheel of Life.</string>
  <string id="29302" soundid="138201">There&apos;s no way to stop... I don&apos;t want to turn.... Kill me!</string>
  <string id="29303" soundid="138202">Thank you.</string>
  <string id="29304" soundid="138203">I can&apos;t... No! Argh!</string>
  <string id="29305" soundid="138204">You&apos;re worse than.... Argh!</string>
  <string id="29306" soundid="132596">But what about the rest of us? Why just send them? Why are we sitting here holding our... Ohhh, I get it. They&apos;re coming here, too, aren&apos;t they?</string>
  <string id="29307" soundid="132597">Wh... who? The Lotus Assassins? But they&apos;d have to fly to get past the wall, and the winds are too strong.</string>
  <string id="29308" soundid="132598">Hundreds may die in crashes, but a few will get through. Do you really think Death&apos;s Hand minds such losses?</string>
  <string id="29310">If you&apos;re too weak to resist them, you deserve whatever happens.</string>
  <string id="29312">I will hold the area around the temple. Everyone else just stay out of my way.</string>
  <string id="29313">How do I help you?</string>
  <string id="29314">I don&apos;t have the time to waste on you.</string>
  <string id="29316">[Kill him.]</string>
  <string id="29317">I won&apos;t kill you, not like this.</string>
  <string id="29318">I&apos;d rather watch you suffer.</string>
  <string id="29320">[You have no silver. Leave it as it is.]</string>
  <string id="29321">[Leave it as it is.]</string>
  <string id="29323">Rat Demon</string>
  <string id="29324">They will be here soon enough. You will have your fill of battle.</string>
  <string id="29327" soundid="138447"></string>
  <string id="29329" soundid="138227">[A statue of a lion stands behind an altar. It is marked as a training aid designed by a previous master of the school. There is a crystal sphere in the lion&apos;s paw.]</string>
  <string id="29330">We&apos;ll destroy any who oppose us!</string>
  <string id="29332" soundid="138228">[The altar is less ornate than the statue, and lacks a sense of permanence. Something activates as you approach. The sphere in the lion&apos;s paw begins to glow with a blue light.]</string>
  <string id="29333" soundid="138229">[The sphere grows dim.]</string>
  <string id="29334" soundid="138230">[The sphere changes color, taking on an orange hue.]</string>
  <string id="29335" soundid="138231">[The sphere grows dim.]</string>
  <string id="29336" soundid="138232">[Nothing happens.]</string>
  <string id="29337" soundid="138233">[The sphere changes color, becoming purple.]</string>
  <string id="29340">If small groups could land anywhere, we should spread out.</string>
  <string id="29341" soundid="138234">[The sphere grows dim.]</string>
  <string id="29342">Flyer Equipment

A temporary shield that absorbs and inflicts a moderate amount of damage. The Chi cost for Radiant Aura is moderate.</string>
  <string id="29343">Flyer Equipment

This weapon does a large amount of damage over time. The Chi cost for Firestorm is high.</string>
  <string id="29344">Flyer Equipment

These magical projectiles have the uncanny ability to track enemy ships. Each missile uses a very small amount of Chi.</string>
  <string id="29345" soundid="80427">There is still food in the undercaves. We will be fine.</string>
  <string id="29346">Flyer Equipment

This weapon produces a powerful shockwave that does moderate damage to all nearby enemy ships. The Chi cost for Tremor is moderate.</string>
  <string id="29347">Flyer Equipment

This powerful weapon releases a blast that will destroy all nearby enemy ships. The Chi cost for Dragon&apos;s Wrath is extremely high.</string>
  <string id="29348">Flyer Equipment

For a short time your flyer is invisible to your enemies. Enemies and their weapons pass through you. The Chi cost for Mirage is moderate.</string>
  <string id="29349">Flyer Equipment

A devastating attack that drains Health from your enemies and transfers it to you. The Chi cost for Consume Spirit is high.</string>
  <string id="29350" soundid="80428">Do not bother me unless you wish to grace my table.</string>
  <string id="29351">Flyer Equipment

This weapon will do a moderate amount of damage over time. The Chi cost for Cloudburst is small.</string>
  <string id="29352">Flyer Equipment

This will cause all of your enemies to slow down time for a brief period. The Chi cost for Reverse Tides is moderate.</string>
  <string id="29356" soundid="138450">For this battle, Sung Bo enters alone! His speed is unmatched!</string>
  <string id="29357" soundid="138451">The towering strength of Sung Bu crashes upon the ring!</string>
  <string id="29358" soundid="132646">That racket is distracting me from the cries of my enemies. Sky better have a good reason for ringing that bell.</string>
  <string id="29359" soundid="132647">Hahaha! Come to my axes! All of you!</string>
  <string id="29360" soundid="138452">The master of mysticism is the last to enter this epic confrontation.</string>
  <string id="29363" soundid="80429">Eat! This food will make you healthy and fat.</string>
  <string id="29366">Teahouse Rowdy</string>
  <string id="29370" soundid="136183">Well, you came to the right place. That&apos;s just about all we&apos;ve got here now: airships! Not like back in my day.</string>
  <string id="29371" soundid="136184">I got nothing against the kid, but dropping the cannon is the easiest way to wipe out everyone on the pier. Tough break for the kid, but much easier for you.</string>
  <string id="29407" soundid="132694">I can&apos;t believe Sheng is head of the Ministry of Harmony! What&apos;s the world coming to?</string>
  <string id="29408" soundid="132695">Poor Sheng. I almost feel bad for him. Almost.</string>
  <string id="29409" soundid="132696">Minister Sheng hasn&apos;t slept in two days. I guess he doesn&apos;t trust us.</string>
  <string id="29410" soundid="132697">Judge Fang hired us to keep an eye on the Ministers coming in to make their reports.</string>
  <string id="29411" soundid="132698">Sheng&apos;s pretty protective of that honor gift. Must have cost him a fortune.</string>
  <string id="29414" soundid="169596">Sounds like fun to me. Might piss the Inquisitor off, though.</string>
  <string id="29415" soundid="169597">There&apos;s no need! Maybe Sheng can suggest a solution that would work better for the Inquisitor.</string>
  <string id="29416" soundid="132703"></string>
  <string id="29417" soundid="132704">Minister Sheng hasn&apos;t slept in two days. He would like nothing more than to leave this honor gift in the care of a trusted associate while he gets some much needed rest.</string>
  <string id="29418" soundid="132705">Unfortunately, I don&apos;t know if you are the most reliable individual. You removed the pirates who troubled Tien&apos;s Landing, but you never closed the Great Dam for me.</string>
  <string id="29419" soundid="132706">[Success] Well, Minister Sheng believes in second chances... I only hope Judge Fang does, too. Very well, I&apos;ll give you the honor of guarding my treasure.</string>
  <string id="29420" soundid="132707">[Success] Minister Sheng is very tired... and Judge Fang is difficult to deal with even at the best of times. Very well, I will give you the honor of guarding my treasure!</string>
  <string id="29421" soundid="132708">[Failure] Your offer is tempting, but I must decline. I have too much at stake. Minister Sheng will keep watch over the honor gift himself.</string>
  <string id="29422" soundid="132709">Please, Minister Sheng is in no mood to speak. I have heard Judge Fang has resigned, but now I live in terror at the thought of who his replacement might be.</string>
  <string id="29424" soundid="35950">I don&apos;t know what&apos;s going on over in the Necropolis, and I don&apos;t want to know.</string>
  <string id="29425" soundid="100711">I say, stick to traditional soldiers. Sagacious Tien needed no machines to build the Empire!</string>
  <string id="29426" soundid="100712">While you were fighting, Soldier asked to talk with you privately in the creature cages before your next fight.</string>
  <string id="29427" soundid="100713">He is arrogant, but equally obstinatious. He made it clear that he would not step into the ring until you spoke with him.</string>
  <string id="29428" soundid="100714">Soldier is a worthy opponent. I hope you understand how many warriors have tried to extrapolate him from the Silver Division championship. Be proud.</string>
  <string id="29429" soundid="100715">From here, your battles will be even harder. A test, if you will, to see if you stand a chance against the Ravager.</string>
  <string id="29430" soundid="100716">Impress the crowd and you will have your chance against the Ravager himself. I can promise you that.</string>
  <string id="29431" soundid="100717">Surely this was enough! I know the crowd loved that show, but there&apos;s no way I can offer you extra just because of that. All your fights are impressive!</string>
  <string id="29432" soundid="100718">[Success] You drive a hard bargain. Here, something extra for your troubles. I can&apos;t argue that the crowds love your battles.</string>
  <string id="29433" soundid="100719">[Success] Come to think of it, he wouldn&apos;t even have asked as nicely. Take this, and consider it a gift to celebrate your rapid rise.</string>
  <string id="29434" soundid="100720">[Failure] I know you feel like a rising star, but your rewards are fixed. You&apos;ll find that the Gold Division battles sate your purse&apos;s hunger.</string>
  <string id="29435" soundid="100721">Now that that&apos;s settled, what else can I do for you?</string>
  <string id="29436" soundid="100722">Legends say that the Phoenix Unity style was banned from tournaments because it was unbeatable, but I&apos;ve never put much stock in legends.</string>
  <string id="29437" soundid="100723">Three opponents at once, all of them exceptionally skilled. I thought no one could impasse them, but you have!</string>
  <string id="29438" soundid="104828">Soldier seems desperate to speak with you.</string>
  <string id="29439" soundid="100725">Defeating their combinated might has impressed the crowd immensely.</string>
  <string id="29440" soundid="100726">You pull in the egregious crowds, it&apos;s true, but I can&apos;t just break the rules and give you extra silver!</string>
  <string id="29441" soundid="100727">[Success] The crowds do call for your fights above all others. I suppose that&apos;s worth something.</string>
  <string id="29442" soundid="100728">[Failure] For one thousand years the best fighters in the Empire have graced this place.</string>
  <string id="29443" soundid="100729">[Success] This is an unusual situation, is it not? I suppose that since the rules are so bent as to be unrecognizable, you may as well have this extra purse.</string>
  <string id="29444" soundid="100730">[Failure] I am still accountable for my prizes. The winnings at this level are more than generous enough.</string>
  <string id="29445" soundid="139523">A good idea. Third Brother is a tough opponent. It&apos;s best to be fully prepared before you meet him in the ring.</string>
  <string id="29454" soundid="100731">Now that that&apos;s settled, what else can I do for you?</string>
  <string id="29455" soundid="100732">You have just emerged the victor from a multitudinous concretion of raw fighting talent! Amazing.</string>
  <string id="29456" soundid="100733">The crowd loves you, and you have proven yourself enough in my eyes. No other fighter stands a chance against the Ravager.</string>
  <string id="29457" soundid="100734">But you must think of your safety. The Ravager strikes with such power that even the wards of this arena may not be enough to save you.</string>
  <string id="29458" soundid="103026">I do not believe in outdated prohabitations. As you may see, this style is not &quot;fair&quot; for single combat, but it is a fair test of a master warrior&apos;s abilities.</string>
  <string id="29459" soundid="103027">You will be a man alone against a rushing wave of opponents, great and small.</string>
  <string id="29460" soundid="100737">This has all gone horribly wrong! I have had a dead, retired ex-fighter in a mask for a champion all this time!</string>
  <string id="29461" soundid="100738">Do you know how many rules and regulations that breaks? It&apos;s a mockery of the entire arena, and Kai Lan and his thugs are to blame!</string>
  <string id="29462" soundid="108697">Are you going to take that from her?</string>
  <string id="29463" soundid="100740">But you... you can stop him. I need you to see this through to the end. I need that man stopped before he destroys a thousand years of tradification!</string>
  <string id="29464" soundid="100741">I know it&apos;s anti-climactic, but you did earn it. Congratulations, champion.</string>
  <string id="29466" soundid="100743">Would we have expected anything less, though?</string>
  <string id="29467" soundid="103028">You will be one woman against a rushing tide of foes.</string>
  <string id="29468" soundid="103029">You must stand against them all, and when you do, your right to challenge the Ravager will be indisputable.</string>
  <string id="29469" soundid="103030">Time to take you down a peg.</string>
  <string id="29471" soundid="103032">I think it&apos;s going to be a fun challenge. You might even survive if you pace yourself.</string>
  <string id="29472" soundid="103033">The concept is simple enough.</string>
  <string id="29473" soundid="103034">If you can defeat your foe with exceptious alacricity, then you have a moment to collect yourself. If you tarry, then you will be swamped.</string>
  <string id="29474" soundid="103035">You will be facing all the champions you have dealt with already, and more.</string>
  <string id="29475" soundid="100752"></string>
  <string id="29476" soundid="100753">Han&apos;s tougher than he emulates, isn&apos;t he? When you&apos;re ready to try him again, I&apos;m sure he&apos;ll be happy to help.</string>
  <string id="29477" soundid="100754">There&apos;s no reason you should have lost that fight. I&apos;ll set it up again when you&apos;re ready.</string>
  <string id="29478" soundid="100755">I thought you would be able to tackle that beast. Perhaps I expected the impossible.</string>
  <string id="29479" soundid="100756">Possible or not, it was expected. Kai Lan is most displeased with your fighter&apos;s inabilities.</string>
  <string id="29480" soundid="100757">If you had let me tell our rising star here what they&apos;d be facing, things would have gone differently!</string>
  <string id="29481" soundid="100758">The Serpent feels that this one has abilities far greater than your bronze trash. The fight *was* possible, foreknowledge or not.</string>
  <string id="29482" soundid="100759">Is that so? One loss was not enough to teach you about humility?</string>
  <string id="29483" soundid="100760">You have failed to defeat your foe. Were things done in the ancient ways, you would be dead.</string>
  <string id="29485" soundid="100761">Were that the case, I would ensure that you did not live out the night. That would be most unprofitable for us both.</string>
  <string id="29486" soundid="100762">I suggest that you face this demon again. We will make it part of the schedule. You win, you move on. You lose, you don&apos;t.</string>
  <string id="29487" soundid="100763">Good. When you are ready, speak with Qui. I&apos;m sure he&apos;ll be happy to send you into battle.</string>
  <string id="29488" soundid="100764">Then your career stops here, in the easily tarnished and casually discarded Bronze Division. If you are comfortable with that, simply stop asking for fights.</string>
  <string id="29489" soundid="100765">When you come to your senses, talk to Qui.</string>
  <string id="29490" soundid="100766">Khana&apos;s blade is deadly, is it not? When you wish to challenge her for the Bronze Division championship, simply tell me. I will give you another attempt.</string>
  <string id="29491" soundid="100767">Expect things to be much harder here than they were in the qualifiers. No amateurs to face this time.</string>
  <string id="29492" soundid="139525">That was quite a match. I&apos;ve never seen Third Brother Renshan fight that well, and yet you still beat him.</string>
  <string id="29493" soundid="100768">He proved the stronger this time, but I believe you will dislodge Soldier in time.</string>
  <string id="29494" soundid="100769">Simply ask when you&apos;re ready to try that match again. The fans seem to really take to you, win or lose.</string>
  <string id="29495" soundid="100770">Maybe there is something to the Sung brothers&apos; magicism. They certainly managed to defeat you. If you want to face them again, I&apos;m sure it would be a welcome challenge.</string>
  <string id="29496" soundid="100771">There are no easy tasks before you in the Gold Division. When you are ready, I&apos;ll prepare that match again.</string>
  <string id="29497" soundid="100772">Your loss aside, that was an amazing match. The crowd&apos;s clamoring for more, and they want you front and center! We&apos;ll try it again, when you&apos;re ready.</string>
  <string id="29498" soundid="100773">A loss is a loss, but it&apos;s nothing we can&apos;t get past. We&apos;ll tell them it was all for show.</string>
  <string id="29506" soundid="100777">Many, many people try to break into the Bronze Division and fail miserably. You should be proud of yourself.</string>
  <string id="29507" soundid="100778">Crimson Khana is the champion of this round. You&apos;ll have to face her eventually. Be ready when you do.</string>
  <string id="29508" soundid="100779">The Bronze Division champion approaches. I hope you&apos;re ready for the challenge awaiting you in the Silver Division.</string>
  <string id="29509" soundid="100780">Remember, Soldier&apos;s the champion at this level. He&apos;ll be watching you.</string>
  <string id="29510" soundid="100781">The newest Silver champion has arrived. You are truly in the inner workings of the arena now, my friend. </string>
  <string id="29511" soundid="100782">Listen, I have been thinking. If you&apos;d like to know more about how things truly work, I&apos;d be happy to explain some of the details of the Guild. </string>
  <string id="29512" soundid="100783">Regardless, I would be careful. Some Lotus Assassins have been asking about you. They may try to recruit you.</string>
  <string id="29513" soundid="154009">No doubt many of his years have been worse than death. Once you are truly indoctrinated, you will know the hunger to serve that such loyalty brings.</string>
  <string id="29514" soundid="100785">Enough words of wisdom from me. You can take care of yourself, I&apos;m sure.</string>
  <string id="29517" soundid="100788">You know the Ravager is next. If you&apos;re ready, well....</string>
  <string id="29518" soundid="35951">My friend said she heard fighting by the Emperor&apos;s Tomb earlier. I fear there will be trouble.</string>
  <string id="29519" soundid="100789">Champion, it has been an honor to adjudicate and facilitate your rise to the top.</string>
  <string id="29520" soundid="100790">Should anyone appear to challenge you, I will let you know, but until then rest yourself. You&apos;ve earned it!</string>
  <string id="29521" soundid="108304">[Failure] You mean, so weak is your resolve. Bah, I tire of this game of veiled intent. We blush like children for your amusement.</string>
  <string id="29523" soundid="100793">All the heavens smile upon us when the champion returns to our arena. In this moment, all is as it should be.</string>
  <string id="29524" soundid="100794">What can this humble promoter do for the greatest fighter in the Empire?</string>
  <string id="29525" soundid="100795">I want to hear that you&apos;re ready for your next fight.</string>
  <string id="29526" soundid="100796">What do you need?</string>
  <string id="29527" soundid="100797"></string>
  <string id="29528" soundid="100798">Are you ready to get started?</string>
  <string id="29529" soundid="104829">Get over here, Silver champion. We have something to discuss.</string>
  <string id="29532">Shen has told you that the corpse of the Elder Tanner Fong has risen from its grave and wandered off, returning to his home. His son, who inherited the home, is none too pleased. He wants a refund or the corpse gone, and Shen doesn&apos;t like refunds.</string>
  <string id="29533">The Tanners Fong</string>
  <string id="29534" soundid="134674">I have left you without my guidance for far too long, Abbot Song. But I could not speak with you; my strength was consumed contacting the last of the order.</string>
  <string id="29535" soundid="134675">You are the last. There is no one else that can do what you are destined to do. I had to conserve and prepare. I did not know the exact day you would cross to this realm.</string>
  <string id="29536" soundid="100806">Excellent. Follow me and we&apos;ll get you ready for your next match.</string>
  <string id="29537" soundid="35952">Now that the Outlander has been defeated, the Scholars&apos; Garden is one again a place of peace.</string>
  <string id="29538" soundid="100807">If that&apos;s the decision you want to make, it&apos;s your profanation. You just let me know when you&apos;ve changed your mind.</string>
  <string id="29539" soundid="100808">For your first match, we&apos;ll start you off against a mighty ogre. I&apos;ll be watching your style closely to see how you fare. Impress me and I&apos;ll take you to the top.</string>
  <string id="29540" soundid="100809">Even our great champions start out against the ogre. Take Raging Ox, who danced around the beast singing drunkenly to earn the crowd&apos;s favor, or the Ravager, who defeated him in a single blow.</string>
  <string id="29541" soundid="100810">You didn&apos;t want to hear my quick lesson on how the arena works last time we talked. Changed your mind at all?</string>
  <string id="29542" soundid="35953">We are not as backwards as the Outlander thinks. Surely he knows that now.</string>
  <string id="29543" soundid="100811">I&apos;ve already explained how things work around here. Do you need me to go over it again?</string>
  <string id="29544" soundid="100812">I should take a moment and explain the system we use here.</string>
  <string id="29545" soundid="100813">I like to keep things simple and organized. Any other way, and things get more convultated than the Celestial Court on the Emperor&apos;s birthday.</string>
  <string id="29546" soundid="100814">When you&apos;re ready for your match, ask me about it, and I&apos;ll give you a quick summary of your opponent. I&apos;ll be setting up your matches, of course.</string>
  <string id="29547" soundid="154010">His name is not spoken to the acolytes. You must understand that to oppose Death&apos;s Hand is to lose all connection to your masters. Even if you live, you do not exist.</string>
  <string id="29548" soundid="35954">Perhaps the Outlander will treat new cultures differently now that he&apos;s had a taste of humility.</string>
  <string id="29549" soundid="100816">Various enchantments woven in this place keep the fights from being deadly, but they&apos;re no less real. You&apos;ll feel the pain if you don&apos;t keep your defense up.</string>
  <string id="29550" soundid="35955">Ah, at last. Peace and tranquility have returned to the Scholars&apos; Garden.</string>
  <string id="29551">Perhaps we should change the subject.</string>
  <string id="29552">Sounds like you&apos;re trying to compensate for something. Did your father dress you as a boy when you were little?</string>
  <string id="29553" soundid="100819">That&apos;s the spirit, dive right in with both feet first! It&apos;s not that difficult a system, and you seem bright enough to figure it out.</string>
  <string id="29554" soundid="100820">Since you held your own against the ogre brute last time, I&apos;m going to try something exciting for the crowd.</string>
  <string id="29555" soundid="100821">I&apos;ve got four boys from some school west of the city who&apos;ve been bothering me for some tougher matches. I&apos;m giving you all of them at once.</string>
  <string id="29557" soundid="100822">It&apos;ll wow the crowd and teach them a lesson at the same time. Remember to watch your sides and back.</string>
  <string id="29558" soundid="100823">The crowd&apos;s starting to catch on to you, have you noticed? People like you, and now I&apos;m going to make sure they pay attention.</string>
  <string id="29559" soundid="100824">I&apos;m going to have a roughly hewn statue hauled into the ring. I want you to discomtructulate it. Destroy the statue quickly enough, and I&apos;ll give you a shot at Hapless Han.</string>
  <string id="29561" soundid="100826">I think you&apos;re ready to face Hapless Han. Show me you&apos;re ready for the big time, and I&apos;ll make sure you don&apos;t have to dance with the children anymore.</string>
  <string id="29562" soundid="100827">Now that you have qualified for the Bronze Division, your challenges will be more difficult, but you&apos;ll earn greater rewards.</string>
  <string id="29563" soundid="100828">I want the very abacuses of heaven to rattle with the name Raging Dragon, so I&apos;ve prepared something memorable.</string>
  <string id="29564" soundid="100829">The stars themselves need to hear of Silver Phoenix if you&apos;re to make it in this division, so I&apos;ve prepared a match to remember.</string>
  <string id="29565" soundid="100830">I want people to remember Tiger Lifts the Mountain, so I&apos;ve crafted a suitably memorable challenge for your introduction to the division.</string>
  <string id="29566" soundid="100831">The guards rounded up a group of sub-human... things around the Great Southern Forest. Were going to release them into the ring in groups for you.</string>
  <string id="29568" soundid="100833">Next you&apos;re going to step into what we call the Pit of Pain. It&apos;s not the most original name, I&apos;ll admit, but that&apos;s five hundred years of tradition for you.</string>
  <string id="29569" soundid="35956">Those Lotus Assassins are the... ah, best group of people ever. The best. Bye now.</string>
  <string id="29570" soundid="35957">Please, I don&apos;t know anything. Just let me be.</string>
  <string id="29571">Exactly how many long, lonely nights with only a sword as company would it take to understand your philosophy?</string>
  <string id="29572" soundid="100835">As you know, the demon awaits you. You&apos;ll have to face him to proceed.</string>
  <string id="29573" soundid="100836">Ah, yes... your next fight. There&apos;s... been a bit of a change in plans. Not that it will affect you too much, of course. It&apos;s all part of the traditions of the arena, you see.</string>
  <string id="29574" soundid="100837">I have word that you&apos;re going to be facing a fighter specially chosen from the Guild, you see. As soon as you&apos;re ready, you&apos;ll be facing him instead of a normal match.</string>
  <string id="29575" soundid="100838">I was originally thinking that you&apos;d done well enough to face Crimson Khana for the Bronze Division championship. Things change when the Guild is involved, though.</string>
  <string id="29576" soundid="100839">The Guild&apos;s the organization that controls the betting here. That&apos;s not all, though; Kai Lan the Serpent has a lot of influence here, as well.</string>
  <string id="29577" soundid="35958">I have nothing against the Lotus Assassins. If the Emperor likes them, then so do I.</string>
  <string id="29578" soundid="35959">Hey, didn&apos;t I see you speaking with the Lotus Assass--um, never mind.</string>
  <string id="29579" soundid="35960">I can&apos;t believe that the Ravager was actually Raging Ox. That&apos;s just so strange.</string>
  <string id="29580" soundid="35961">I do not approve of the fighting, but it *is* exciting to meet an arena champion in person.</string>
  <string id="29581" soundid="35962">When he grows up, my son wants to be the arena champion, just like you.</string>
  <string id="29582" soundid="35963">My husband won a great deal of silver betting on you in the arena championship!</string>
  <string id="29583" soundid="100840">I have to bow to certain pressures. I don&apos;t like it that much, but smart men don&apos;t voice that opinion too loudly. Not around here....</string>
  <string id="29584">Town of Two Rivers</string>
  <string id="29586">[Charm] This is my chance to make it up to you.</string>
  <string id="29588">[Intuition] You can&apos;t meet Fang without getting some sleep.</string>
  <string id="29591">Where can I find Fang again?</string>
  <string id="29592">Any suggestions how I can get rid of Fang?</string>
  <string id="29594" soundid="132720">That should give us all some time to think.</string>
  <string id="29598" soundid="132724">She&apos;s dangerous like these ghosts. We&apos;re all afraid of her.</string>
  <string id="29601" soundid="80430">See the keeper if you wish to talk.</string>
  <string id="29603" soundid="132730">The tales say this man once stormed an entire fortress alone, naked, and screaming his defiance into the night.</string>
  <string id="29604" soundid="132731">Ha! Scared the tar out of those border guards! But they botched the story; I was naked, screaming, *and* I was dead drunk. </string>
  <string id="29605" soundid="132732">Wouldn&apos;t you like to know, missy! Let&apos;s just say it&apos;s the only part that matters!</string>
  <string id="29606" soundid="132733">Pretty much the part you&apos;d expect. Makes &apos;em curl up in shame, if you take my meaning.</string>
  <string id="29608" soundid="132735">We didn&apos;t exactly fight to the death, did we? Besides, I&apos;m not nearly drunk enough to be at the top of my game. There&apos;s nothing to drink in this blasted forest.</string>
  <string id="29609">Minister Sheng&apos;s Sword</string>
  <string id="29610" soundid="136089">If we did, would I be here?</string>
  <string id="29612">Find the Outlander</string>
  <string id="29617">Which part of your naked, drunk, and screaming attack works best?</string>
  <string id="29621">You didn&apos;t seem all that skilled to me.</string>
  <string id="29622">This long sword is the prized weapon of Minister Sheng, the local representative of the Ministry of Harmony. Known for its careful balance between speed and power, the long sword is a favored weapon among those who desire a deadly blade without the ponderous weight of an axe. The swirling motions of the Long Sword style make it great at dispatching groups of enemies and discouraging your foe&apos;s allies from getting too close. </string>
  <string id="29623">Bandit Swamp</string>
  <string id="29625" soundid="145406">His money and valuables are meaningless to me. His work, however... that I will take myself.</string>
  <string id="29630" soundid="39151">The dam is closed, and the pirates are gone! Thanks to you, we can start rebuilding our lives.</string>
  <string id="29632" soundid="139526">It certainly didn&apos;t look easy from where I was standing, but nevertheless, you did beat him.</string>
  <string id="29634" soundid="139527">I suspected something was amiss. But you overcame it, and you still won.</string>
  <string id="29643" soundid="34740">Now is not a good time to speak with me. You may try my brother, Bo.</string>
  <string id="29644" soundid="34741">If you wish to speak to one of us, Bo will be the most amenable.</string>
  <string id="29645" soundid="34742">I shouldn&apos;t talk too much. Talk to Brother Bo instead.</string>
  <string id="29646" soundid="34743">You&apos;re nice, but I think you should talk to Bo, not me.</string>
  <string id="29647" soundid="34744">If you want to talk, Brother Bo is better at it than I am.</string>
  <string id="29725" soundid="139528">Master Radiant was sure you would prevail, he asked me to bring you to him once you defeated Third Brother. You won&apos;t have to test yourself against me after all.</string>
  <string id="29727" soundid="139529">Come, let&apos;s go see him. He is anxious to speak with you.</string>
  <string id="29762" soundid="34859">Excuse me... out of my way. I&apos;ve got to get these buns to the Scholars&apos; Garden quick, quick. Now move.</string>
  <string id="29764" soundid="34861">I&apos;m very sorry. Please accept my heartfelt apologies. My husband has the manners of a strutting cock sometimes.</string>
  <string id="29765" soundid="34862">Hmm. I seem to recall you rather enjoyed my, ah... strutting at one time, old woman. </string>
  <string id="29766" soundid="34863">Shush now. You&apos;ll offend the gods of decency. This poor traveler&apos;s likely to think the Imperial City is full of indecent folk and offensive talk.</string>
  <string id="29767" soundid="34864">Now then, after all the trouble we&apos;ve caused you, is there anything we can help you with? We&apos;ve got fresh buns. Just made them myself.</string>
  <string id="29768" soundid="34865">Bah! Talk, talk, talk... that&apos;s all people want to do. I don&apos;t get paid to talk... I sell buns, that&apos;s what I do.</string>
  <string id="29769" soundid="34866">My yapping... rrgh. You&apos;re fortunate my wife is here, or I&apos;d show you a thing or two!</string>
  <string id="29770" soundid="34867">Don&apos;t bother, husband. This ruffian isn&apos;t worth your time and effort. Let&apos;s be on our way. We have more important things to tend to.</string>
  <string id="29771" soundid="35077">I have nothing more to say to you. Good day.</string>
  <string id="29777">Do you mind if I ask you two some questions?</string>
  <string id="29778">Who are you two? What are you doing here?</string>
  <string id="29779">What can you tell me about the Imperial City?</string>
  <string id="29780">Tell me what you know about Death&apos;s Hand.</string>
  <string id="29781">I am searching for Master Li. Have you heard of him?</string>
  <string id="29782">I need some answers, but I don&apos;t need all this banter.</string>
  <string id="29783">I&apos;d buy a bun if I could cram it down your yapping maw!</string>
  <string id="29786" soundid="100844">No, I can&apos;t actually. The Serpent, who is the Guild&apos;s chief agent in this place, has specifically requested you.</string>
  <string id="29787" soundid="100845">I&apos;m certain it will be a small thing. Best to just finish it now.</string>
  <string id="29788" soundid="100846">A noble and ultimately meaningless sediment, my friend. Regardless of what you wish, I have to give in to certain pressures, and you will go no further than this match if your pride is so offended.</string>
  <string id="29790" soundid="100848">I&apos;m sorry. Until you speak with Lucky Cho, as he requested, I&apos;m permanently reluctant to send you into the ring.</string>
  <string id="29791" soundid="100849">Until the Guild stepped in, I was ready to give you an attempt at the Bronze Division for your last match. Now it&apos;s time.</string>
  <string id="29792" soundid="100850">Are you ready to face Crimson Khana, the finest sword this august arena has seen in five genritations?</string>
  <string id="29793" soundid="100851">Now that you are champion of the Bronze Division, the Silver Division awaits. It seems that, indirectly, the Serpent has decided to keep your career interesting.</string>
  <string id="29794" soundid="100852">A demon has been added to the regular roster since your earlier victory, and since you&apos;ve shown aptitude, I&apos;m letting you face him first.</string>
  <string id="29795" soundid="100853">This is indeed an honor, though it will not be easy. Are you ready to defeat this horror?</string>
  <string id="29796" soundid="100854">I&apos;m afraid that until you talk with the Serpent, I can&apos;t let you go out there and face anyone. He was... quite incessant. Go talk to him first.</string>
  <string id="29797" soundid="35964">Doing well in the arena can draw unwanted attention.</string>
  <string id="29798" soundid="100855">This next fight should be fairly simple for you. I once more want to send you up against four opponents. The crowd loves those fights.</string>
  <string id="29799" soundid="100856">These are tougher than the students you faced before, but should pose no problem.</string>
  <string id="29803" soundid="100860">We&apos;ve had a request from the Imperial Army. They want one of our best to help them test out a small group of war machines known as golems.</string>
  <string id="29804" soundid="100861">I&apos;ve decided to put you up against them. I want you to prove that our folks are superior to any &quot;thing&quot; the army could devise.</string>
  <string id="29805" soundid="100862">Are you ready to show them what you&apos;ve got?</string>
  <string id="29806" soundid="100863">One of the reasons you&apos;re become such a crowd favorite is because you&apos;re willing to fight in the more extravagatastic battles. I want to really drive that point home.</string>
  <string id="29807" soundid="100864">Your going to participate in a timed fight. I&apos;ve rounded up a lot of the hopefuls, and I need you to eliminate ten of them in three minutes. It won&apos;t be easy, but if anyone can do it, you can.</string>
  <string id="29808" soundid="100865">Show me you can handle this, and I&apos;ll give you a shot at Soldier and the Silver Division championship. Are you ready to show them what you&apos;ve got?</string>
  <string id="29809" soundid="100866">I rushed out notification of this match, and we&apos;ve had the outcriers shouting themselves hoarse. I hear many nobles will even be in attendance.</string>
  <string id="29810" soundid="100867">It&apos;s rare that the Silver Division rests balanced against a single victory on the scales of combat, you know!</string>
  <string id="29811" soundid="35965">You have certainly done better in the arena than I would have guessed. Good luck in your future fights.</string>
  <string id="29812">Pirate</string>
  <string id="29813" soundid="139530">There you are. Master Radiant has gone, and I am left to lead this school on my own. I&apos;ll miss him very much, but at least we are rid of Smiling Hawk.</string>
  <string id="29815" soundid="139531">I wanted to thank you for all you&apos;ve done, but I also wanted to show you some items that belonged to Master Smiling Hawk. I thought you might find something of interest.</string>
  <string id="29817">Customize Character Abilities</string>
  <string id="29842" soundid="34941">Yes, yes... more questions. Are you sure I couldn&apos;t interest you in a bun? They&apos;re nice and fresh... or at least, they were when we started talking.</string>
  <string id="29843" soundid="34942">Death&apos;s Hand! Now there&apos;s a name you don&apos;t hear often. I&apos;m just a simple bun-seller, but even I know enough to be careful who I utter that name around.</string>
  <string id="29844" soundid="34943">For once we agree, husband. Death&apos;s Hand is a walking nightmare. It is said that if you see him coming, then it&apos;s already too late. </string>
  <string id="29845" soundid="34944">But enough of wives&apos; tales. Just be careful who you mention that name to, unless you wish to draw bad attention to yourself.</string>
  <string id="29846" soundid="34945">If he hasn&apos;t bought a bun from me, I likely don&apos;t know him. Come to think of it, if he hasn&apos;t bought a bun from me, I don&apos;t *want* to know him!</string>
  <string id="29847" soundid="34946">Junda, you withered old coconut, what&apos;s your problem? There&apos;s more to life than selling these buns you know.</string>
  <string id="29848" soundid="34947">I&apos;m sorry to say I haven&apos;t heard of your friend either, and I&apos;m not sure what you mean by &quot;master.&quot; Try the Scholars&apos; Garden. The people there might know your friend.</string>
  <string id="29849" soundid="34948">Go then. I have buns to sell, and it doesn&apos;t look like you&apos;re buying.</string>
  <string id="29850" soundid="34949">Don&apos;t mind him. He just takes a while to get used to. Much like an ache in the bones, if it lasts long enough. Eventually you learn to ignore it. Good day to you.</string>
  <string id="29851" soundid="34950">Did you hear that, Lina? I think we were just told to keep it short. Perhaps I&apos;ll keep it short and say goodbye!</string>
  <string id="29852" soundid="34951">Now, now, Junda. It&apos;s nothing worse than you&apos;ve already said yourself. Not everyone is as tolerant of your ramblings as I am.</string>
  <string id="29853" soundid="34952">Go on then. Ask your questions, and we&apos;ll try to answer them as quickly as possible.</string>
  <string id="29854" soundid="34953">You again. We have nothing to say to you. Move along. I have buns to sell.</string>
  <string id="29855" soundid="34954">Junda! Who are you berating now? Oh, it&apos;s you. We have no time for the likes of you!</string>
  <string id="29857" soundid="34956">I hear you&apos;re the new arena champion. I&apos;d like to think my buns gave you strength and helped you win... but I don&apos;t think you ever bought one, did you?</string>
  <string id="29858">The Dragon of Storms</string>
  <string id="29868" soundid="34967">So, you&apos;ve thrown your lot in with those damn Assassins. I don&apos;t sell buns to them or their friends.</string>
  <string id="29869" soundid="34968">Junda! Don&apos;t go judging our potential customers, especially based on rumors. Besides, I saw you selling buns to an Assassin just the other day.</string>
  <string id="29870" soundid="34969">That was different. He looked like he might... cause some trouble if I didn&apos;t offer him something. So... you buying any buns then?</string>
  <string id="29878" soundid="138750">The human comes out of the air and smells of blood!</string>
  <string id="29879" soundid="138751">All is perfect! The Mother is free, the caves in the back are open, and this one will feed us tonight!</string>
  <string id="29880" soundid="138752">Then you are strong. Strong enough that we will grow even more powerful when we consume you!</string>
  <string id="29881" soundid="34980">There&apos;s a terrible commotion over at the Lotus Assassin fortress. You wouldn&apos;t have anything to do with that now would you?</string>
  <string id="29882" soundid="34981">Junda! You know better than to pry into our customers&apos; affairs. It&apos;s none of our business.</string>
  <string id="29883" soundid="34982">Junda thinks he&apos;s a grand inquisitor sometimes. He&apos;s really just a nosey old man. Can I get you some fresh buns today? I just made them.</string>
  <string id="29884" soundid="138753">With the Mother free, we are stronger than ever!</string>
  <string id="29885" soundid="138754">[Success] You are strong, but there are many of us in the caves below! You would not dare follow.</string>
  <string id="29886" soundid="138755">Quickly, we flee!</string>
  <string id="29887" soundid="138756">[Failure] You are a pathetic thin-blood! We will clean our teeth with your entrails!</string>
  <string id="29889">*I* freed the Mother by killing the Forest Shadow!</string>
  <string id="29891">Come and defeat me if you can, beasts.</string>
  <string id="29892">[Intimidation] I killed the Keeper, and I&apos;ll do the same to you unless you run... now!</string>
  <string id="29893" soundid="34992">Get your buns here. Fresh buns, just made this morning.</string>
  <string id="29894" soundid="34993">Hot buns, fresh from the oven. Come and get them while they last.</string>
  <string id="29895" soundid="34994">Ha! No time to talk he says! The only time *you&apos;re* ever quiet is when you&apos;re eating one of my buns... now be polite and answer some questions.</string>
  <string id="29896" soundid="34995">We&apos;re members of the local traveling circus. I&apos;m a fire eater, and Lina is a juggler. We just sell buns on the side to make a little extra silver.</string>
  <string id="29897" soundid="34996">Junda! Could you try to be civil just this once?</string>
  <string id="29898" soundid="34997">This buffoon of a man is Junda, and I am Lina, his wife... as he is fond of reminding me. We sell buns here in the city. Well, I bake, and he sells.</string>
  <string id="29899" soundid="34998">There is much to tell about the city, but we do need to sell the buns while they&apos;re fresh. Perhaps you could be more specific.</string>
  <string id="29901" soundid="35000">Why don&apos;t you go and check out the Imperial Arena. It&apos;s a prosperous place to sell buns, especially before a big fight.</string>
  <string id="29902" soundid="35001">You and those fights... I can&apos;t stand watching them. I prefer to take walks by the Wall or just gaze at the magnificent palace.</string>
  <string id="29903" soundid="35002">What&apos;s to tell? Fighters fight, spectators watch, gamblers gamble... it&apos;s just like any other arena. Except the level of competition is very high here.</string>
  <string id="29904" soundid="35003">I&apos;d talk to Qui the Promoter if you really want to know more about the arena. He talks more than you do, but at least he buys my buns.</string>
  <string id="29905" soundid="35004">It&apos;s busy, but it&apos;s a good place to get information and meet people. Best wine in the Empire, too.</string>
  <string id="29906" soundid="35005">How would you know, you lazy lout? You&apos;ve never been outside the city in your life! Best in the Empire... ha! Probably the only wine you&apos;ve ever had.</string>
  <string id="29907" soundid="35006">The Wall is magnificent... it just keeps growing. Though I pity the criminals who are forced to work there. Very few ever return.</string>
  <string id="29908" soundid="35007">The palace is truly one of our greatest treasures. The heavens have indeed blessed our Empire greatly to give to us such a beautiful edifice.</string>
  <string id="29909" soundid="35008">Bah! It&apos;s unnatural I say. Just floating up in the air. Emperor or no, it&apos;s not right to live in a place that just... floats like that.</string>
  <string id="29910" soundid="35009">What did you want to know?</string>
  <string id="29911" soundid="35010">Well, this district is called the Market District. This is where most of the buying and selling happens. Most of the lower classes live and work here.</string>
  <string id="29912" soundid="35011">And die here, too! Not like those nobles and wealthy merchants over in the Golden Way or in the Scholars&apos; Garden. Born into a life of luxury... ha, must be nice.</string>
  <string id="29913" soundid="35012">Yes dear. Life has been cruel hasn&apos;t it? Good work, a wonderful family, and many friends... poor Junda. Next you&apos;ll blame the nobles for your backaches, too.</string>
  <string id="29918" soundid="138767">Through Sun Li&apos;s cunning, the armies of the Emperor laid siege to the gates of Dirge. They came to seize the Water Dragon&apos;s power and her life-giving waters.</string>
  <string id="29920">Could I go back to my original questions?</string>
  <string id="29925">I should be going.</string>
  <string id="29930">Being an argument on the origins of Focus.

Min Shi the Dragon of Storms was a master who lived hundreds of years before the formation of the Jade Empire. Legends of her exploits could fill a library, and while the veracity of such fables must be questioned, all the yarns agree that she formalized the teachings of the Storm Dragon style and brought knowledge of true focus to the martial arts. 

Debates still rage on the subject, but the evidence is there to support such claims. Take, for instance, that harmonic combinations initiated by Storm Dragon invariably allow the user to collect his thoughts and steal some of his opponent&apos;s focus essence. Such a synergy is hard to dismiss, and when I questioned Jian the Iron Fist, a master of some renown, he replied, &quot;Only a fool denies legends. They always hold a grain of truth.&quot; Jian speaks wisely; would it be so hard to accept that Storm Dragon was developed to make it easier for its adepts to achieve true focus in battle? This author thinks not.</string>
  <string id="29964">Tell me about the key landmarks in the city.</string>
  <string id="29966">What can you tell me about the arena?</string>
  <string id="29968">Tell me more about the tavern.</string>
  <string id="29970">I&apos;d like to know more about the Wall and the palace.</string>
  <string id="29973">I want to ask you something else about the city.</string>
  <string id="29974">I&apos;d like to know more about the various districts.</string>
  <string id="29978" soundid="35078">Hello there. Our buns are nice and fresh. I just took them out of the oven.</string>
  <string id="29979" soundid="35079">Talk to Junda if you&apos;d like to buy some buns.</string>
  <string id="29980" soundid="35080">I expect bad attitudes from Junda, but I don&apos;t need it from you as well.</string>
  <string id="30121" soundid="80371">Ah, there you are, my student. Your bout with Jing Woo had a surprising end. I hope I have not caused you to grow complacent in practice bouts.</string>
  <string id="30122" soundid="80372">You came here an orphan and became my greatest pupil, but have I done enough? Second chances at victory are very rare. Have you given thought to your future?</string>
  <string id="30133">Who are you?</string>
  <string id="30134">Very well, Master.</string>
  <string id="30195">You have %d Style points to spend to upgrade your fighting styles.</string>
  <string id="30210">Honren</string>
  <string id="30237">Ren Feng</string>
  <string id="30238" soundid="139533">You&apos;re welcome to visit the school and spar with us whenever you like. The students need someone like you to knock some sense into them from time to time.</string>
  <string id="30246" soundid="165700">How is that possible? The Inquisitors are master spies themselves! How would you avoid notice?</string>
  <string id="30250">To the City</string>
  <string id="30252" soundid="139534">And I should get back to the students. There is so much I need to do. I barely know where to begin. Thank you again for everything.</string>
  <string id="30278">Lu the Prodigy</string>
  <string id="30279">Custom Character</string>
  <string id="30309">Creature</string>
  <string id="30350">Starting Styles</string>
  <string id="30406">You have come under the attention of Lucky Cho, who wishes to speak with you before you face Crimson Khana for the Bronze Division championship.</string>
  <string id="30407">A Bronzed Opportunity</string>
  <string id="30417">Qui has informed you that Soldier will not face you until you speak with him in private. </string>
  <string id="30418">Soldier&apos;s Offer</string>
  <string id="30419">Improvised Spear</string>
  <string id="30420" soundid="145691">Citizen! I heard about your encounter with Aishi the Mournful Blade. She was as deadly as she was rotten. Here, I collected the bounty for you.</string>
  <string id="30423" soundid="145694">Some *fantasy* from her childhood, was it? We should settle your bounty. Because of your discretion, I will award you this additional purse from my own funds.</string>
  <string id="30499" soundid="35625">Hm... a little cold-blooded, aren&apos;t you?</string>
  <string id="30500" soundid="35626">But business is business. If they aren&apos;t living anymore, I bury them.</string>
  <string id="30501" soundid="35627">Here&apos;s the reward for your work. Don&apos;t spend it all in one place.</string>
  <string id="30502" soundid="72429">It seems the play was a success, but I have heard nothing of its deep meaning, the message it was meant to convey.</string>
  <string id="30503" soundid="72430">So disappointing, but that&apos;s what I get for trusting an amateur! Ah well, at least it wasn&apos;t that mockery of a revision that was read.</string>
  <string id="30511" soundid="71426">Would you turn your back on this crowd? No, I&apos;m not about to let them get up to their tricks.</string>
  <string id="30515" soundid="72431">Here, take this. You&apos;ve earned it, if only just. Farewell.</string>
  <string id="30518">Elder Tanner Fong is dead for good, now.</string>
  <string id="30521">I&apos;ll leave you to it, then.</string>
  <string id="30522" soundid="72434">That was a curious interpretation of your role. It lacked some of the punch we&apos;ve come to expect from the great lady. Ah well, what&apos;s done is done.</string>
  <string id="30523" soundid="72435">Your performance was a mockery of all things good and decent! &quot;He was tired of winning all the time?&quot; Where in all the Empire did that tripe come from?</string>
  <string id="30524" soundid="72436">How could you have botched such a well-known piece of history? Do you know nothing of our glorious past?</string>
  <string id="30525" soundid="71427">Betting? Did I say something about betting? Age must be assailing my mind, for I know nothing of betting here. Slip of the tongue.</string>
  <string id="30526" soundid="71428">Did I say &quot;bets?&quot; I must have meant, &quot;very expensive pets.&quot; Small exotic dogs, trained pandas, that sort of thing.</string>
  <string id="30527" soundid="71429">As you say. I certainly should. Now, drink?</string>
  <string id="30528">What&apos;s so vital that you can&apos;t look around once in a while?</string>
  <string id="30529">Who do I see if I want to bet?</string>
  <string id="30530">Ah ha! I&apos;ve got you! You just admitted to knowing about the betting in this place!</string>
  <string id="30531">Aren&apos;t you the owner? Shouldn&apos;t you know?</string>
  <string id="30535">Improvised Dual Small</string>
  <string id="30536">Chunks of Wood</string>
  <string id="30537">Improvised Dual Large</string>
  <string id="30538">Hams</string>
  <string id="30539" soundid="109596">I spent my life as a pirate, and look where it got me. Now I&apos;m barely above the slaves. If you see Gao, give him a kick for me... even if he&apos;s already dead!</string>
  <string id="30540" soundid="109597">Is there something else you need? I&apos;m too old to fight, but I&apos;ll do whatever I can to help you against Gao and the Lotus Assassins.</string>
  <string id="30541" soundid="109598">Gao the Greater, as he calls himself, is the leader of the Guild, a powerful crime syndicate. They never used to bother with us, until Gao came to power.</string>
  <string id="30542" soundid="109599">Gao himself came and took over our operations. He began building the flyers, and he made slaving our main activity. My own men turned on me. Now they treat me like a dog!</string>
  <string id="30543" soundid="109600">A few months later, the Lotus Assassins showed up. Gao must have some kind of deal worked out with them. Whatever they&apos;re up to. it must be something big.</string>
  <string id="30544" soundid="109601">Back in my day, a pirate ship stayed on the water, where it belonged! Now they&apos;ve got some kind of factory up on the top floor where they build those blasted airships.</string>
  <string id="30545" soundid="109602">There&apos;s something suspicious about those airships. Sure, the pirates use them, but I think that&apos;s just a cover so the Lotus Assassins can come and go as they please. </string>
  <string id="30547">What do you know about the airships?</string>
  <string id="30550">Tell me about Gao.</string>
  <string id="30551">Lotus Assassins?</string>
  <string id="30573">You decided against participating in Incisive Chorus&apos; play. Someone else will likely fill in the part, but Chorus&apos; original version will likely never be read in the Imperial City.</string>
  <string id="30607">Spirit Font</string>
  <string id="30608">Defeat multiple opponents at a time. Switch from hard-hitting punches to paralyzing nerve strikes by changing combat styles in an instant.</string>
  <string id="30609">Defeat multiple opponents at a time. Switch from hard-hitting punches to paralyzing nerve strikes by changing combat styles in an instant.</string>
  <string id="30610">Defeat multiple opponents at a time. Switch from hard-hitting punches to paralyzing nerve strikes by changing combat styles in an instant.</string>
  <string id="30611">Defeat multiple opponents at a time. Switch from hard-hitting punches to paralyzing nerve strikes by changing combat styles in an instant.</string>
  <string id="30620" soundid="100868">But you, Raging Dragon, are what truly draws them in! Once in a lifetime does a single person throw the grand institution of the arena into such disarray!</string>
  <string id="30621" soundid="100869">That&apos;s nothing compared to the skills of Silver Phoenix, who has soared so high, so quickly! Words like those spread like raging flames.</string>
  <string id="30622" soundid="100870">What really catches the crowd, though, is the story of Tiger Lifts the Mountain. They come to see the noble warrior who strides up the rankings like the heroes of legend!</string>
  <string id="30623" soundid="100871">Will you face Soldier now? The Silver Division championship awaits you.</string>
  <string id="30624" soundid="100872">The Gold Division is the toughest series of fights in the Empire. Ultimately, you can think of it as a test to see if you&apos;re ready to face the Ravager.</string>
  <string id="30625" soundid="100873">Your first match will be a rare challenge. There is a style that was banned from the tournament combat five centuries ago. You will face the Phoenix Unity style.</string>
  <string id="30626" soundid="100874">I was going to do something different, but I&apos;ve had a request from the Sung brothers. They said that there has been, ah... an affluence of the fates and a... a remergence of the planets.</string>
  <string id="30627" soundid="100875">I&apos;m not quite sure what that means, but if they want to face you, then I have to honor their request. Besides, defeating them is important to your career.</string>
  <string id="30628" soundid="100876">I require that any fighter who wishes to face the Ravager be able to defeat all three of the Sung brothers. Then I know you won&apos;t be torn to shreds.</string>
  <string id="30629" soundid="100877">Well, at least not before the gong stops ringing, at any rate. The brothers are ready if you are.</string>
  <string id="30630" soundid="107779"></string>
  <string id="30631" soundid="107780"></string>
  <string id="30632" soundid="100880">I want to give you a shot at the championship. I really do. I need to convince... others, though.</string>
  <string id="30633" soundid="100881">I&apos;m going to hold an event so huge that it will rock the reaches of the Empire: the Imperial Engagement. The arena turns upon you.</string>
  <string id="30635" soundid="103085">Master Li used to say that the arena was once the greatest contest in the Empire but that it has been corrupted in recent years.</string>
  <string id="30636" soundid="103086">The fighters here are skilled, but you would fare better than many of them. I hear the winnings are lucrative, as well.</string>
  <string id="30637" soundid="103087">The Lotus Assassins watch this place like vultures circling a sick buffalo. They recruit new talent from among the best fighters.</string>
  <string id="30638" soundid="103088">If you join this place, you&apos;ll want to avoid attracting their attention.</string>
  <string id="30639" soundid="100887">Are you ready for me to finish the arrangements? If so, we&apos;ll get everyone set up.</string>
  <string id="30640" soundid="100888">As I told you before, you&apos;re going to have to emerge victorious from the Imperial Engagement before I can give you that opportunity.</string>
  <string id="30641" soundid="107781">I will guard the gate, but you need to get down there and stop them!</string>
  <string id="30642" soundid="103089">This place can chew you up and spit you out... or so I&apos;m told. The drinks are the best in the Empire, though!</string>
  <string id="30643" soundid="103090">This place houses the finest competition in the Empire. If you wish to hone your skills, you will find few challenges more worthy.</string>
  <string id="30644" soundid="107782"></string>
  <string id="30646" soundid="100894">These are truly tremultuous times for this institution. Kai Lan is waiting. He is ready when you are.</string>
  <string id="30647" soundid="100895">Your friend is ready to fight. When he was here before, he was always ready. Tell him to be careful, Kai Lan is not easily defeated.</string>
  <string id="30648" soundid="100896">Han isn&apos;t a champion, exactly, but he&apos;s solid enough that all fighters must beat him before they can leave the qualifiers.</string>
  <string id="30649" soundid="100897">I like Hapless Han, personally. He never quits trying. Reminds me of a young me trying to clamor my way up from the streets. He&apos;ll go far, you rest assured.</string>
  <string id="30650" soundid="100898">Khana&apos;s a bit of a mystery to me. Keeps not a coin of her winnings, but is unbeaten. She&apos;s in this purely for the challenge, I think.</string>
  <string id="30651" soundid="100899">If you face her, you&apos;ll find that her swordsmanship is deadly. Khana&apos;s studied techniques only found in the Prosperous East, the provinces she calls home.</string>
  <string id="30652" soundid="100900">Soldier is a worthy opponent. I hope you understand how many warriors have tried to extrapolate him from the Silver Division championship.</string>
  <string id="30653" soundid="100901">He&apos;ll be watching you, so expect him to anticipate your style if you face him.</string>
  <string id="30654" soundid="100902">The real champion is the Ravager, but the Sung brothers are your first hurdle. Who were you curious about?</string>
  <string id="30655" soundid="100903">The crowd loves to hate him. He&apos;s vicious, he never talks, and he has no interest in the fans, but when he fights he&apos;s unstoppable.</string>
  <string id="30656" soundid="100904">Right now, almost no one will face him, so it&apos;s rare that the Ravager steps into the ring. It&apos;s for the better I think. He tends to cripple people, despite the protective magic of this place.</string>
  <string id="30657" soundid="100905">They&apos;re an odd triptuplet if you ask me. They were three of the best individual fighters to participate in the arena, but things changed after they fought together against the Ravager and lost.</string>
  <string id="30658" soundid="100906">They&apos;re sort of a buffer: If the three of them together couldn&apos;t match the Ravager, only someone who can face all three will stand a chance against him.</string>
  <string id="30659" soundid="100907">It cuts down on the number of injuries at the Ravager&apos;s hands. If you want to know more about them, you can ask the brothers themselves.</string>
  <string id="30660" soundid="100908">The only person left to face is the Ravager. Defeat him and the championship is yours. What more is there to say?</string>
  <string id="30661" soundid="100909">Recruiters hover around this place, I&apos;ll admit. Nothing anyone can do about that. If they haven&apos;t approached you yet, they will.</string>
  <string id="30662" soundid="100910">The Executioners always recruit from the top arena talent; we lose a lot of rising stars to their order, but... I&apos;m sure they&apos;re provided for.</string>
  <string id="30663" soundid="100911">Take my advice, though: Don&apos;t bind yourself to their mill wheel. It can lead to no good. I didn&apos;t give you that advice though, and I&apos;d rather not talk about them any further.</string>
  <string id="30664" soundid="100912">Don&apos;t pester me about them, I&apos;m sure they will approach you soon enough.</string>
  <string id="30665" soundid="100913">Recruiters? Well, yes, recruiters are occasionally interested in the talent here at the arena, but it&apos;s nothing to concern yourself over.</string>
  <string id="30666" soundid="100914">They are merely observing. Obey the laws of the Empire and the assassins will leave you alone.</string>
  <string id="30667" soundid="100915">You know all about him by now, don&apos;t you? Ex-champion, magician of great prestidigitation, and the man behind everything wrong with this place.</string>
  <string id="30668" soundid="100916">It was simple enough for him. There&apos;s always been an affiliation of criminals known as the Guild in this city.</string>
  <string id="30669" soundid="100917">Kai Lan&apos;s skills as a magician and his huge prize winnings allowed him to work his way high in their ranks. Now there&apos;s something of a... gap at the top.</string>
  <string id="30670" soundid="100918">No one really knows. He didn&apos;t seem to have them when he was in the arena, but there was a period after his retirement when he vanished like the dying strains of a song.</string>
  <string id="30671" soundid="100919">By that, I mean you would think you had heard of him, but could never be sure. Then suddenly he returned and just... stepped into control of the arena.</string>
  <string id="30672" soundid="100920">There are rumors that he might have gone off to join the Lotus Assassins, but no one&apos;s really sure. It might explain his newfound skills, though.</string>
  <string id="30673" soundid="100921">Me? I&apos;m just a simple promoter. If the Guild tightens their hold, I simply make do. I don&apos;t necessarily want to help them, but I know the price of resisting them.</string>
  <string id="30674" soundid="100922">I&apos;m not like you. I can&apos;t defend myself in the same way.</string>
  <string id="30675" soundid="100923">Always nice to move on to other subjects, I assure you.</string>
  <string id="30676" soundid="100924">Kai Lan is truly in charge of this place because of his association with the Guild. If he gets things his way, he&apos;ll seize control of the whole Guild before long.</string>
  <string id="30677" soundid="100925">It&apos;s nothing to concern yourself with. If anything comes up with the Guild or the Serpent, I will negotiate and delibertate with them, not you.</string>
  <string id="30678" soundid="100926">More than I&apos;d care to. I strongly suspect that Lucky Cho&apos;s disappearance was no coincidence.</string>
  <string id="30679" soundid="100927">I wondered when things would come to a head. I was hoping Black Whirlwind would just stay away, but he won&apos;t, will he? Not while you&apos;re here.</string>
  <string id="30680" soundid="100928">No, no! Not lying. Sure, I had some suspicions, but I have no proof.</string>
  <string id="30681" soundid="100929">I wondered. It seemed too convenient that he&apos;d one day just suddenly leave and never return, with only a letter to tell us he was going.</string>
  <string id="30683" soundid="100931">The last thing he needs is accusations of murder. He&apos;s already filled a dozen scrolls with records of public drunkenness, crimes against decency, and violence.</string>
  <string id="30684" soundid="100932">Now, let&apos;s not speak of this again. If you must speak of it, talk to your friend directly.</string>
  <string id="30685" soundid="100933">Talk to your friend if you must know about Raging Ox. Leave me out of it.</string>
  <string id="30686" soundid="100934">Your large friend there was once a competitor here, so I know him in passing, you might say.</string>
  <string id="30687" soundid="100935">This is his business, though. Why not ask him? I&apos;m sure he&apos;ll tell you whatever he deems appropriate.</string>
  <string id="30688" soundid="100936">I&apos;ll have to revise my stories of this place to include your rise to champion. It was for the better, but you unsettled a great many things here.</string>
  <string id="30689" soundid="100937">I&apos;m always happy to share some history with this arena&apos;s greatest fighters. Would you like to hear some of the tales?</string>
  <string id="30690" soundid="100938">The first thing to know is that this arena was founded under the auspices of Sagacious Tien himself. The Emperor&apos;s blessings rest upon this place as the one true test of martial skill in the Empire.</string>
  <string id="30691" soundid="100939">Interestingly, while we call it &quot;the arena&quot; commonly, its full name is &quot;The Trials of the Seven Gladiatorial Schools of Beneficent Light.&quot;</string>
  <string id="30692" soundid="100940">A bound volume of the finest parchment contains the arena&apos;s rules. This tome holds over three thousand rulings, the first dating back to the birth of the arena.</string>
  <string id="30693" soundid="100941">Besides the name being unwieldable by the tongue? Largely due to inaccuracy. There are far more than seven schools recognized across the Empire now.</string>
  <string id="30694" soundid="100942">Further, the Order of Beneficent Light disbanded hundreds of years ago. They are no longer the governing body of martial education, so these are not their trials anymore.</string>
  <string id="30695" soundid="100943">Still, we hold on to the name as a reminder of the glory days.</string>
  <string id="30696" soundid="100944">Many emperors have graced this place with their presence from a secure private viewing room.</string>
  <string id="30697" soundid="100945">When he was younger, Emperor Sun was a regular attendant, but I&apos;m sure the years have stolen away the time he once made for us.</string>
  <string id="30698" soundid="100946">No one knows them as well as I do, and that&apos;s likely for the better. Technically, we&apos;re supposed to lead a donkey around the fighting surface before each match.</string>
  <string id="30699" soundid="100947">I consider that to be one of the traditions best... overlooked. </string>
  <string id="30700" soundid="100948">Enough asses wander the streets around this building these days that I expect my predecessors&apos; spirits will be satisfied.</string>
  <string id="30702" soundid="100950">I must say, I&apos;m disappointed! You&apos;re ready to start your career, but you walk away. Insuspicious beginnings, my friend.</string>
  <string id="30703" soundid="100951">Be sure to return when you&apos;re ready to continue your climb through the qualifying round.</string>
  <string id="30704" soundid="100952">Do not be gone too long. Khana may well rise to become the Silver Division champion while you&apos;re away.</string>
  <string id="30705" soundid="100953">When you walk the streets and hear your name among the crowds, be sure that your ego does not swell like the body of Eleven Gaping Maw, god of inopportune gluttony.</string>
  <string id="30706" soundid="100954">Things are... interesting right now. Be as careful walking the streets as you are in the ring. I don&apos;t think Kai Lan is pleased with your progress.</string>
  <string id="30707" soundid="154011">There are few fates worse than being reduced to nothing. Lotus Assassins can belong nowhere else. Service to Death&apos;s Hand is your life.</string>
  <string id="30708" soundid="154012">Master Gang has been lax in indoctrinating you. No doubt he wants to make use of your fiery disposition before stripping you of it. You will come to understand.</string>
  <string id="30709" soundid="100957">Remember, the Serpent has asked to speak with you. It is best not to keep him waiting.</string>
  <string id="30718" soundid="100966">I apologize if I&apos;m using words beyond your grasp. Very few people can match either the supply or the command of my language.</string>
  <string id="30719" soundid="100967">Don&apos;t get flusterated. Everything I say is perfectly cromulent, and it might do you well to embiggen your vocabulary before you fling accretions my discretion.</string>
  <string id="30720" soundid="100968">A single glance tells me you are a remarkable woman with the perfect mix of strength and grace to grab a crowd&apos;s imagination!</string>
  <string id="30721" soundid="100969">A spirit of leaping flames dwells within you!</string>
  <string id="30722" soundid="100970">Strong build, good shoulders... not half bad looking, either. You&apos;ve got what it takes to make it in today&apos;s arena.</string>
  <string id="30723" soundid="100971">Livestock can be accordiated great value, but that&apos;s not the point here.</string>
  <string id="30724" soundid="100972">The question is, can you fight? Are you worthy of the arena? I say the answer is a clarion and resoundering, &quot;Yes!&quot;</string>
  <string id="30725" soundid="100973">In times like these, when even the Lotus Assassins can fall under attack, the people need something they can hold on to, something to soothe them.</string>
  <string id="30726" soundid="100974">Some might be suspicious of one seen publicly consorting with the Lotus Assassins, but I have no such qualms. You&apos;re as welcome here as the Emperor himself!</string>
  <string id="30728" soundid="138687">Of course. I was just thinking about things. Gao richly deserved his death, but I&apos;m not sure I ever really expected it to happen.</string>
  <string id="30729" soundid="100977">I&apos;ve heard that you were asking around and talking to some of our best and brightest. Your interest tells me all that I need to know about you.</string>
  <string id="30730" soundid="138688">Yes, I would welcome the chance.</string>
  <string id="30731" soundid="100979">I may not have heard your name before, but you walk like one who has seen many battles. You are indeed mysterious, stranger.</string>
  <string id="30732" soundid="100980">What say we get you signed up for the greatest attraction in all the Empire? The arena awaits!</string>
  <string id="30733" soundid="108306">[Failure] I don&apos;t see how balancing us against each other is productive.</string>
  <string id="30734" soundid="100982">Here you fight for silver; glory is yours for the taking if you value it. The rewards start small, but in the Gold Division you could easily retire on your winnings.</string>
  <string id="30735" soundid="100983">In fact, our last champion, Raging Ox, did just that. Suddenly up and left to enjoy his winnings, clearing the way for the Ravager to take his place.</string>
  <string id="30736" soundid="100984">You&apos;ll start low and advance on my say so, but I can already tell you&apos;re going to expel in this place. You&apos;ll not languish in the qualifiers for long.</string>
  <string id="30737" soundid="108307">Agreed. You are not giving much incentive for the continued... extra interest you have enjoyed.</string>
  <string id="30739">What is a Spirit Monk?</string>
  <string id="30740" soundid="108310">I... I did not think you would find the concern of your... closest friends trivial.</string>
  <string id="30741" soundid="108311">Yes, this is possibly the last we would see of you. If this is not appropriate now, when is it?</string>
  <string id="30742">&quot;Austi....&quot; Don&apos;t you mean, &quot;auspicious?&quot;</string>
  <string id="30743">Did you just butcher the language on purpose, or out of stupidity?</string>
  <string id="30744" soundid="108312">Thank you for your assurance. I know we have all been struggling with the responsibilities destiny imparts. I don&apos;t wish to add to that in an unpleasant way. </string>
  <string id="30745" soundid="108313">Yes, I can see how you would not want to be... overburdened. I think... I think we are done here.</string>
  <string id="30746" soundid="108314">Yes, Princess, I believe we are.</string>
  <string id="30747">If I joined the arena, who or what would I face?</string>
  <string id="30748" soundid="108315">Take care in the Assassins&apos; fortress. Master Li is waiting for us, and... I am looking forward to turning our attention to happier concerns.</string>
  <string id="30753" soundid="108319">It does.... Of course it does. I never had a doubt. I have asked a great deal from you, but I know you can provide more than I need.</string>
  <string id="30754" soundid="108320">Well, far be it from me to get in the way of what a princess needs. Whatever it is, I&apos;m sure it is far more important than what the... the rest of us want.</string>
  <string id="30755" soundid="108321">I think we are done here. I trust you will be careful as you progress from here. You must expose Death&apos;s Hand and save your Master.</string>
  <string id="30756" soundid="108322">And when all this is done, we can deal with more pleasant concerns.</string>
  <string id="30758" soundid="108324">I see. Well, if silence is what you want, I&apos;m sure that can be arranged.</string>
  <string id="30759" soundid="108325">Y-yes, it certainly can. I&apos;m sorry I was nothing more than... a distraction.</string>
  <string id="30760" soundid="108326">Be careful inside. There are still a great many people depending on you to discredit Death&apos;s Hand.</string>
  <string id="30761" soundid="108327">Even if they cannot depend on you in all things.</string>
  <string id="30762" soundid="154013">Soon you will have nothing else but your life here. Your role as a Lotus Assassin leaves no room for anything other than loyalty to Death&apos;s Hand and the Emperor.</string>
  <string id="30764">Are these fights deadly?</string>
  <string id="30767">What happened twenty years ago?</string>
  <string id="30768">What if someone specifically tries to dispel the protections?</string>
  <string id="30770">Let&apos;s go back to my other questions about the rules.</string>
  <string id="30771">I want to join the arena.</string>
  <string id="30772" soundid="154014">Slaves continue to be brought to the fortress from the Wall and unimportant villages that have no voice to object. Our golem force continues to grow.</string>
  <string id="30773">I am called &lt;FullName&gt;.</string>
  <string id="30776">I would rather keep that to myself.</string>
  <string id="30778">I am Egregious Prevaricator, respected scholar and grower of pipe weed. I&apos;m shocked you haven&apos;t heard of me.</string>
  <string id="30780">I want to be called Raging Dragon.</string>
  <string id="30781">Yes, that&apos;s what I want.</string>
  <string id="30782">Bill me as Silver Phoenix.</string>
  <string id="30783">Yes, that&apos;s what I want.</string>
  <string id="30784">Call me Tiger Lifts the Mountain.</string>
  <string id="30785">Yes, that&apos;s what I want.</string>
  <string id="30788">That&apos;s all I need to know?</string>
  <string id="30789">I&apos;ve got it. Let&apos;s get started.</string>
  <string id="30793">Tell me about my first fight.</string>
  <string id="30794">No, I&apos;ve changed my mind.</string>
  <string id="30795" soundid="154015">Operations in Tien&apos;s Landing have temporarily halted, but we received glorious news that a hated enemy of the Emperor has been delivered to the palace!</string>
  <string id="30796">I&apos;m not interested in the arena. I should talk to someone else.</string>
  <string id="30799" soundid="35966">I hear you&apos;re doing well in the arena, though I doubt you&apos;ve impressed the Ravager.</string>
  <string id="30800" soundid="35967">So, you have won honor in the arena. That&apos;s very good for someone who is... new to fighting.</string>
  <string id="30801" soundid="35968">The arena can be very dangerous, especially if you are unprepared.</string>
  <string id="30802" soundid="35969">If you&apos;re going to do well in the arena you&apos;ll need strength and luck. Lots of luck.</string>
  <string id="30803" soundid="35970">If I catch my husband betting at the arena again he&apos;ll have a *real* fight on his hands.</string>
  <string id="30804" soundid="35971">Oh good, another fighter. Just what this city needs, more fighters.</string>
  <string id="30805" soundid="35972">I don&apos;t know what&apos;s worse, the Outlander&apos;s noisy weapon or his loud mouth.</string>
  <string id="30806" soundid="35973">The Outlander reminds me of my first husband. Perhaps he&apos;ll disappear, as well.</string>
  <string id="31092">Tell me more about Kai Lan the Serpent.</string>
  <string id="31097">Henpecked Hou&apos;s wife finally tracked him down and brought him back home to settle back into the simple bun master&apos;s life. A few years later, he became a father for the first time. Though having septuplets at his age was not unheard of, having seven daughters at once was a bit peculiar. Shortly thereafter, Hou became deathly ill after accidentally eating a bun he intended to give to his wife. Hou&apos;s wife invited her entire family to live with them while he was bedridden. Hou recovered more quickly than expected, but word of his poisonous bun made sure that his career as a bun master was over. Instead, Hou became a delivery man, delivering packages throughout the Empire. He has yet to return from his first delivery.</string>
  <string id="31145">The Black Whirlwind accepted a job hunting demons for the Celestial Bureaucracy, but the ensuing red tape frustrated him so much that he gave up and made for the Mysterious East. Shortly thereafter, the Empire received a great influx of Outlanders, many of whom were missing limbs and other body parts. He returned to the Jade Empire several years later, but this time he came from the west. He couldn&apos;t explain how he did it, but he was the only person unsurprised to arrive back where he started. Expressing a newfound hatred for a people who couldn&apos;t make a decent bowl of wine, the Black Whirlwind vowed to never again leave the Jade Empire. A week later, he got bored and headed off to the north.</string>
  <string id="31162">Chi Damage Increase</string>
  <string id="31163">Healing Rate</string>
  <string id="31165">Type in some text....</string>
  <string id="31167">Chi Cost Reduction</string>
  <string id="31179">Speed Increase</string>
  <string id="31182">Block Threshold</string>
  <string id="31183">Projectile Range</string>
  <string id="31184">Chi Damage</string>
  <string id="31185">Poison Duration</string>
  <string id="31186">Paralysis Duration</string>
  <string id="31202">Inquisitor Lim</string>
  <string id="31239">Quarry Cave</string>
  <string id="31287">Mummy</string>
  <string id="31290" soundid="36484">More death, more intruders... My tomb has lain sacrosanct for centuries and now mortals tread on my very ashes.</string>
  <string id="31292" soundid="36486">Your corpse will lie here with those of my subjects, and your spirit will feed my own.</string>
  <string id="31295">Mummy</string>
  <string id="31302">Why do you let Lucky Cho push you around, Qui?</string>
  <string id="31304" soundid="158228">It would be an honor to say that I aided someone who was greeted by Princess Sun Lian herself!</string>
  <string id="31306">Enough about what Lucky Cho said. Can you tell me more about the Guild?</string>
  <string id="31309">I&apos;ll be careful who I talk to.</string>
  <string id="31311">They sound like a gang of common thugs. I should turn them in!</string>
  <string id="31314">I&apos;ll discuss what I want with whoever I want. They cannot touch me.</string>
  <string id="31325">Hold on, Qui! How do you know the Black Whirlwind?</string>
  <string id="31326">You&apos;re friends with the lummox who won&apos;t stop following me, I take it?</string>
  <string id="31338">I hope this proves my skill to you.</string>
  <string id="31340">What did he want to talk about?</string>
  <string id="31342">He&apos;ll have to wait, I&apos;m ready for my next match now.</string>
  <string id="31348">The crowd loved that fight. I think it was worth some extra silver, don&apos;t you?</string>
  <string id="31349">[Charm] You&apos;re too savvy a businessman to not reward your star performers.</string>
  <string id="31351">[Intimidation] I make it easier for you to fill the seats. That means nothing to you?</string>
  <string id="31354">Forget it. Let me ask you something instead.</string>
  <string id="31355">I should ask you about some things.</string>
  <string id="31359">What about the protective spells? Were they removed as well?</string>
  <string id="31361">How can I trust you? You&apos;re Kai Lan&apos;s man, aren&apos;t you?</string>
  <string id="31364">You&apos;re sure they won&apos;t try something like this again?</string>
  <string id="31365">How can I trust the Guild? Weren&apos;t they behind this?</string>
  <string id="31369">The last time I met someone down there it ended poorly.</string>
  <string id="31370">Did he say what he wants?</string>
  <string id="31371">I don&apos;t want to talk to that arrogant cur.</string>
  <string id="31374">The crowd loved that fight. I think we need to talk about some extra silver.</string>
  <string id="31375">[Intimidation] Pay me now so I don&apos;t demand that you up the payments on every fight.</string>
  <string id="31377">[Intuition] Would Soldier have let such a fight go without being paid extra?</string>
  <string id="31380">Very well, let me ask you something, then.</string>
  <string id="31381">I have some questions for you.</string>
  <string id="31385">I deserve more silver than this.</string>
  <string id="31386">[Intimidation] You can&apos;t afford to lose me, Qui. The crowds demand to see my matches.</string>
  <string id="31389">[Intuition] You&apos;ve said yourself that this division is a test for me. Surely the rules are less strict here. </string>
  <string id="31392">Very well, let me ask you something, then.</string>
  <string id="31393">I have some questions for you.</string>
  <string id="31394" soundid="103036">You will be the first. As I said, I *need* you to have the crowd&apos;s heart. Kai Lan does not want you to face the Ravager. I do.</string>
  <string id="31397">How can he be so strong?</string>
  <string id="31407" soundid="103041">It is that time. The Ravager awaits. You remember what I told you about fighting him?</string>
  <string id="31408" soundid="103042">I merely want you to think of your safety. The Ravager strikes with such power that even the wards of this arena may not be able to save you.</string>
  <string id="31409" soundid="103043">Your match could end in death. It almost happened when Sung Bu faced him alone, and he was the last opponent to tackle the champion.</string>
  <string id="31410" soundid="103044">The Ravager grows more fierce with each fight, as if time were making him stronger. If you face him, we may not be able to end the match in time.</string>
  <string id="31411" soundid="103045">Can I assist you with anything else?</string>
  <string id="31418">Now that I know what I&apos;m facing, I will crush your little pet!</string>
  <string id="31420">I&apos;m right here, don&apos;t talk around me as if I&apos;m not.</string>
  <string id="31422">Perhaps I lost on purpose. I don&apos;t appreciate someone suggesting that I should win.</string>
  <string id="31424">I look forward to the rematch.</string>
  <string id="31425">What happens if I refuse?</string>
  <string id="31428">If you find yourself running out of Chi, try using Spirit Thief to draw Chi from your opponents. </string>
  <string id="31437">Lotus Assassins are using rat demons to find gems. One of the rat demons said he could feel a gem nearby, in the ruins.</string>
  <string id="31486" soundid="154016">The accomplices who hid him were butchered, their pitiful village razed. We look forward to a day when all who oppose our masters are dealt with.</string>
  <string id="31487">Gems in the Quarry</string>
  <string id="31497">Is there anyone who wants to face me?</string>
  <string id="31500">Dirge - Temple Summit</string>
  <string id="31502" soundid="175219">I have energy enough only to instill knowledge of one, not both. Knowledge of the other may come in time, but not today.</string>
  <string id="31503">If I choose one, am I prohibited from learning the other?</string>
  <string id="31504">It&apos;s worth a try Whirlwind. It might make you less irritable.</string>
  <string id="31508">Yes, let&apos;s begin.</string>
  <string id="31514">I need answers, but I can do without the banter.</string>
  <string id="31522">The Great Dam downriver from Tien&apos;s Landing is open, and now the Silkworm River is running faster and lower than it has for years. It is impossible for larger vessels to navigate, essentailly cutting off the town from the trade that sustains it. Minister Sheng in the town square can provide more details.</string>
  <string id="31524">The Great Dam</string>
  <string id="31529">Please choose this option if you would like to make your own character from scratch.</string>
  <string id="31530">A fast character may not be the strongest, but she can maintain Focus in battle longer than others, easily sidestepping strikes and delivering counterattacks with blinding speed.</string>
  <string id="31531">Though not as physically strong as others, a magical character is the best at channeling her Chi to enhance her physical strikes and fuel powerful elemental magics.</string>
  <string id="31532">A fast character may not be the strongest, but he can maintain Focus in battle longer than others, easily sidestepping strikes and delivering counterattacks with blinding speed.</string>
  <string id="31533">While not the fastest or strongest of warriors, the balanced character is the most versatile. The balanced character excels at adapting to exploit his enemies&apos; weaknesses.</string>
  <string id="31534">A strong character trades speed and magical aptitude for raw strength and power, enabling him to dish out and withstand much more damage than other warriors.</string>
  <string id="31539">Locate the bomb hidden in the Palace and prevent it from killing the King.</string>
  <string id="31558" soundid="198521"></string>
  <string id="31596">Pleasing the peasants and the director is all well and good, but Incisive Chorus was unpleased with your rendition of the altered script. He stormed off without paying you his reward.</string>
  <string id="31597" soundid="149847">I will never believe it until I hear it from her own lips! And if she&apos;s that close, you can bet my hands will be around her neck!</string>
  <string id="31598" soundid="149848">Bring her here to me. Let me have my revenge.</string>
  <string id="31600" soundid="149849">My wife decided I wasn&apos;t good enough. She poisoned my food one day and left me to die, choking on my own swollen tongue.</string>
  <string id="31603" soundid="149850">Likely she has taken all I owned and sold it, lining her own pockets and finding some younger, more fit man to satisfy her.</string>
  <string id="31610" soundid="37050">Couldn&apos;t handle the stupidest ogre in the Empire, huh? Word gets around fast here.</string>
  <string id="31611" soundid="37051">Not even if it offers you a chance at the Bronze Division championship?</string>
  <string id="31613" soundid="37053">I will not tolerate mindless insults. My services are in high demand for tasks more important than this.</string>
  <string id="31614">This follower is missing.</string>
  <string id="31615" soundid="37055">Crimson Khana&apos;s rise to Bronze Division champion has been good for business, but she has become troublesome of late.</string>
  <string id="31616" soundid="37056">She believes that the Serpent runs the arena with little concern for honor, and she&apos;s right. The problem is that she cares. </string>
  <string id="31617" soundid="37057">This place is not corrupt so much as... open to interpretation.</string>
  <string id="31618" soundid="37058">The Serpent and I believe that Khana needs to be stopped. We want you to replace her as the Bronze champion.</string>
  <string id="31620" soundid="37060">It should be a simple matter to slip a slow-acting, but extremely deadly, poison into Khana&apos;s drink before the match.</string>
  <string id="31621" soundid="109413">So, your lost sheep, Sagacious Zu, returned to save you. I didn&apos;t think he had the nerve.</string>
  <string id="31623" soundid="109414">That&apos;s because people are nothing but tools to you!</string>
  <string id="31624" soundid="37064">If you accept, the Guild will cover half of Lyn&apos;s usual fee. The remaining cost would be roughly half of your winnings from defeating Khana.</string>
  <string id="31625" soundid="37065">If you&apos;re that sure, why are we still talking? You want to cheat for the thrills?</string>
  <string id="31626" soundid="37066">[Success] You&apos;re going to make this difficult unless I make this easy, aren&apos;t you?</string>
  <string id="31627" soundid="37067">[Failure] This benefits you more than us. Others would leap at this opportunity. The price remains fixed.</string>
  <string id="31628" soundid="37068">Will you go ahead with this? Do you have the will to take your advantage?</string>
  <string id="31629" soundid="37069">Do you want to go ahead with this or not?</string>
  <string id="31630" soundid="37070">Excellent. Your payment will be reduced for Khana&apos;s match, but I&apos;m sure Qui knows better than to ask too many questions.</string>
  <string id="31631" soundid="37071">Khana will prove an easy foe under the influence of my concoction. Simply wait her out, if you wish.</string>
  <string id="31633" soundid="37073">You fool. The Guild *is* the authority in the arena. Anyone you approach would know better than to tangle with us.</string>
  <string id="31634" soundid="37074">If that is your choice, then so be it. You may deal with Khana on your own.</string>
  <string id="31635" soundid="37075">I strongly advise you not to bring this up to anyone. I hope my point speaks for itself.</string>
  <string id="31636" soundid="37076">Our business is concluded. It is time for you to leave.</string>
  <string id="31637" soundid="37077">Don&apos;t expect a hearty round of congratulations for defeating Han. There are trained apes in the Emperor&apos;s menagerie who could sit that one down.</string>
  <string id="31638" soundid="37078">Do not hover around me like a curious dragonfly. People will be suspicious enough when they see Khana in the ring.</string>
  <string id="31644">Bandit</string>
  <string id="31648" soundid="37088">It seems our little arrangement worked out extremely well. Be sure to keep quiet about it, if you value your own reputation.</string>
  <string id="31649" soundid="37089">I am always watching, even you dogs in the qualifying rounds. Remember that.</string>
  <string id="31650" soundid="37090">Now that you&apos;re not fighting with the trained apes, the bets placed on you will actually be worth the time they take to process.</string>
  <string id="31651" soundid="37091">With Crimson Khana out of the way, my job is going to be much easier.</string>
  <string id="31653" soundid="37093">What do you want?</string>
  <string id="31656" soundid="37096">Yes. I know that they scout among the highly skilled fighters.</string>
  <string id="31657" soundid="37097">They usually only watch those fighting well above you, so if you have hopes of joining their ranks, I suggest you practice.</string>
  <string id="31658" soundid="109415">My dear little Dawn Star. I&apos;m a princess. People bow to me. That is the way things are. </string>
  <string id="31659" soundid="109416">Of course, many things are not as I thought they were, if what we learned from Jia is true.</string>
  <string id="31660" soundid="109417">I know what you found and what the implications of it are: The Emperor himself ordered the golems constructed, and... the workers were stolen from their homes.</string>
  <string id="31661" soundid="109418">By the Water Dragon&apos;s mercy, they are enslaved until they die... and then trapped within the golems. I have seen the proof... but how can it be true?</string>
  <string id="31664" soundid="138634">Suppose you were a young noble who has just inherited a fortune.</string>
  <string id="31665" soundid="37105">If you want to bother someone with inane queries, I suggest you speak with Qui the Promoter about the arena or the tavern keeper about the city.</string>
  <string id="31666" soundid="37106">Those two will have more than enough time to waste on you, I am sure. Now, was there something important you needed to ask?</string>
  <string id="31677" soundid="37117">Good. Only come to me when you have business to conduct. I am not here to debate philosophy or discuss the conditions of the weather.</string>
  <string id="31678" soundid="37118">You&apos;re the one Qui found to fill the roster? He must have been desperate.</string>
  <string id="31679" soundid="37119">Every time an event like the arena occurs, some people enjoy adding a certain edge to the proceedings.</string>
  <string id="31680" soundid="37120">When those people feel like investing in a particular fighter&apos;s chances, Lucky Cho is the man they want to see.</string>
  <string id="31681" soundid="37121">No. You&apos;re a fighter, you can&apos;t bet on the matches.</string>
  <string id="31682" soundid="37122">Watch that barbed tongue of yours. It could come back to snag you.</string>
  <string id="31692" soundid="37132">Before you face Khana, I&apos;d like to present you with a mutually beneficial arrangement.</string>
  <string id="31693">Bet Taker</string>
  <string id="31694" soundid="37134">This is Sweet Poison Lyn, a master of the toxicant arts.</string>
  <string id="31696" soundid="37136">Lyn, this is Raging Dragon, the fighter we discussed.</string>
  <string id="31697" soundid="37137">Sweet Poison, standing before you is Silver Phoenix, the one we discussed.</string>
  <string id="31698" soundid="37138">Lyn, allow me to introduce Tiger Lifts the Mountain.</string>
  <string id="31699">Mrs. Jong</string>
  <string id="31705">Imperial City Gates</string>
  <string id="31706">Why is this foul poisoner here?</string>
  <string id="31708" soundid="109423">No! I will not believe it! We have to go to the palace and give him the chance to explain.</string>
  <string id="31710">What does this have to do with me?</string>
  <string id="31711">She is a fool if she thinks something this large would not be corrupt.</string>
  <string id="31713" soundid="109424">Stand beside me or don&apos;t. I am going to question my father and straighten this out. It&apos;s all just a mistake.</string>
  <string id="31714">Go on.</string>
  <string id="31715">I was wondering when you would come to the point.</string>
  <string id="31716">I will not be party to a murder.</string>
  <string id="31717" soundid="109425">We must be on our guard. Is there another way to reach the palace? The princess doesn&apos;t want to see the danger.</string>
  <string id="31719" soundid="109426">She says she can get my Marvelous Dragonfly there in one piece. I have heard no other options, and I won&apos;t risk the finish flying blind.</string>
  <string id="31720">That is too much silver for something I could do on my own.</string>
  <string id="31721">[Charm] This is mutually beneficial. Why worry about silver?</string>
  <string id="31722">[Intimidation] How big are the bets on this match? Can you afford leaving it to chance?</string>
  <string id="31725">Forget lowering the cost.</string>
  <string id="31726">Let&apos;s do it. Poison her and take the silver from my winnings.</string>
  <string id="31731">What if I tell the authorities about this?</string>
  <string id="31732">I will not dishonor myself by resorting to poison.</string>
  <string id="31740" soundid="107777">I think you&apos;ll be able to handle yourself, but I&apos;m not holding back out there.</string>
  <string id="31745" soundid="58472">From what I hear, you and I will meet next. I&apos;m really looking forward to it.</string>
  <string id="31746" soundid="105623">Still a mouth on you. I like that. You&apos;re going to do fine.</string>
  <string id="31747" soundid="58474">We&apos;ll take care of that in the next match, new blood, trust me. I&apos;ve been looking forward to taking you down a notch.</string>
  <string id="31748" soundid="58475">Our honored opponent! How you must feel knowing that you are to face us next!</string>
  <string id="31750">Villager</string>
  <string id="31752">Imperial Guard</string>
  <string id="31757">Do you know anything about recruiters for the Lotus Assassins?</string>
  <string id="31759" soundid="109427">Everyone, be quiet!</string>
  <string id="31760" soundid="109428">Are you ready to go? If you have business left in the Imperial City, you&apos;d better finish it. I won&apos;t be leaving the palace without an answer.</string>
  <string id="31761" soundid="160266">The only real visitor we ever have is that strange fellow who came in for supplies once or twice. He&apos;s just some mad hermit, though. He tries to avoid the village proper.</string>
  <string id="31762" soundid="109430">I thank you, but this has been a great deal to absorb. I don&apos;t know what to think about anything.</string>
  <string id="31763" soundid="109431">We still have much to talk about, but it will have to wait. I must speak to my father. Forgive me.</string>
  <string id="31765">Do you have a moment for some questions?</string>
  <string id="31778">I don&apos;t need anything else from you.</string>
  <string id="31779">Is there any way I can participate?</string>
  <string id="31781">Amazing. You managed to make being a petty bet-monger sound half-respectable.</string>
  <string id="31787" soundid="70281">You&apos;re bringing word to the court that the Emperor has halted his advance on the Horselords.</string>
  <string id="31793">Who else is benefiting from this arrangement?</string>
  <string id="31799">Merchants&apos; Square</string>
  <string id="31800">I don&apos;t like the tone this &quot;offer&quot; of yours is taking.</string>
  <string id="31802">Go ahead and tell me what you have to say.</string>
  <string id="31815" soundid="37394">Enjoy your stay in wonderful Tien&apos;s Landing, where things are never as bad as they seem!</string>
  <string id="31819">I want to ask you some questions.</string>
  <string id="31820">I find your optimism... disturbing.</string>
  <string id="31847">Tien&apos;s Landing Fight Club</string>
  <string id="31851">Tell me the history of this town.</string>
  <string id="31857">Tell me about the town&apos;s problems.</string>
  <string id="31861">Where did the name Tien&apos;s Landing come from?</string>
  <string id="31862">Sounds interesting. Go on.</string>
  <string id="31864">I don&apos;t see any palace around here.</string>
  <string id="31868">Rumors</string>
  <string id="31869">***TEMP FIND OUT ABOUT FIGHT CLUB?</string>
  <string id="31871">Some of the locals in Tien&apos;s Landing mentioned a fight club down by the waterfront where a fighter can earn some money sparring. It is located in a large boathouse.</string>
  <string id="31873">Where can I buy and sell things?</string>
  <string id="31884">***TEMP FIGHT CLUB</string>
  <string id="31885">***TEMP GAIN ENTRANCE TO FIGHT CLUB</string>
  <string id="31886">***TEMP YOU FIND A FIGHT CLUB ON THE WATERFRONT IN TIEN&apos;S LANDING</string>
  <string id="31887">***TEMP YOU GAINED ENTRANCE TO SAID FIGHT CLUB AND JOINED CLUB.</string>
  <string id="31888">***TEMP INITIATION ROUND</string>
  <string id="31889">***TEMP WIN THE INITIATION ROUND</string>
  <string id="31897">***TEMP YOU WON INITIATION ROUND. NOW WIN ROUND 2</string>
  <string id="31898">***TEMP ROUND 2</string>
  <string id="31901">***TEMP  WIN ROUND 2</string>
  <string id="31917">***TEMP YOU WON ROUND 2, NOW WIN ROUND 3</string>
  <string id="31918">***TEMP ROUND 3</string>
  <string id="31919">Do you know where I can find Ru the Boatswain?</string>
  <string id="31921">***TEMP  WIN ROUND 3</string>
  <string id="31922">I have questions about the town itself.</string>
  <string id="31925">***TEMP YOU WON ROUND 3, AND HAVE JOINED THE PROFESSIONAL ECHELON. NOW WIN ROUND 4</string>
  <string id="31935">***TEMP ROUND 4</string>
  <string id="31936">***TEMP  WIN ROUND 4</string>
  <string id="31937">Goodbye.</string>
  <string id="32045" soundid="68557">No, no, this is too soon. You shouldn&apos;t be back here. The play has begun!</string>
  <string id="32054" soundid="68558">I am ruined!</string>
  <string id="32133">I couldn&apos;t bring myself to perform.</string>
  <string id="32181" soundid="109290"></string>
  <string id="32184">Lost Spirit</string>
  <string id="32262" soundid="59872">How you made it to me is mystifying, but since we meet next, should I notify any kin after I crush your spirit?</string>
  <string id="32349" soundid="59878">Still, you have to respect tradition. I&apos;m... er... not exactly sure what she&apos;s done that&apos;s so bad, but I know it set the nobles aflame with gossip.</string>
  <string id="32371" soundid="38099">You have made me proud.</string>
  <string id="32372" soundid="38100">I can see that, my student.</string>
  <string id="32373" soundid="162014">[Small cracks in the mine allow a few beams of light from outside. An emaciated slave might be able to reach the surface, but no one else would fit.]</string>
  <string id="32382">Thank you, Master. I have learned much.</string>
  <string id="32383" soundid="196467"></string>
  <string id="32389" soundid="38117"></string>
  <string id="32390" soundid="38118">Twenty years, Li. I have waited long enough. Atone for your treachery and give me what I require.</string>
  <string id="32391" soundid="38119">Look to yourself, brother. You would have done the same.</string>
  <string id="32392" soundid="38120">I am the eldest and, therefore, the Emperor! I have you at a disadvantage, and yet you toy with me. What do you know, Glorious Strategist? Where is the Spirit Monk amulet?</string>
  <string id="32393">Your followers will fight alongside you, but you can also access their support abilities. Use the Followers screen to change their tactics.</string>
  <string id="32394">Skip</string>
  <string id="32395" soundid="38123">You will find out soon enough, brother.</string>
  <string id="32396" soundid="153174">The only reason I was interested in Bei was because I figured he was my only chance of ever finding a husband, and I knew he was a decent guy.</string>
  <string id="32397" soundid="38125">Father!</string>
  <string id="32402" soundid="38130">Child? What are you doing here? I have important matters and... what have you done to yourself? You look like a common street woman.</string>
  <string id="32403" soundid="38131">And who is this? You invite filth into the halls of my palace? This is not how the child of the Emperor should act.</string>
  <string id="32404" soundid="38132">Don&apos;t lecture me. Master Li&apos;s student brought me evidence from the Lotus Assassin fortress. You allowed Death&apos;s Hand to corrupt the Empire.</string>
  <string id="32405" soundid="38133">Master Li&apos;s student?</string>
  <string id="32406" soundid="38134">This child... the very person who tested my Lotus Assassins... brought to my doorstep by my own daughter. </string>
  <string id="32407">Mosquito</string>
  <string id="32408" soundid="38136">Brother Li, did you plant the seeds for this fool to come here? Layers upon layers. Always the Glorious Strategist.</string>
  <string id="32409" soundid="126583">An amusement left by the previous master of this school, meant to test the students with basic problem solving. I haven&apos;t bothered to have it removed.</string>
  <string id="32410" soundid="38138">I don&apos;t blame you for your foolishness. What can you possibly know? The Emperor is the manifestation of divine power.</string>
  <string id="32411" soundid="38139">That is your role as figurehead. How could you betray the people? Your greed has unsettled the whole of the Empire. The dead no longer sleep!</string>
  <string id="32412" soundid="38140">My child, remember your place. I have no patience for anyone who challenges my authority. Not even you.</string>
  <string id="32413" soundid="153175">It&apos;s not like he was the love of my life or anything. He just seemed like a logical choice. There&apos;s not a lot of options in this town.</string>
  <string id="32414" soundid="38142">Kill the rest. They are unimportant.</string>
  <string id="32415" soundid="38143">No, I won&apos;t let you disgrace the Empire!</string>
  <string id="32419" soundid="38147">ENOUGH!</string>
  <string id="32422" soundid="38150">I am God-Emperor Sun!</string>
  <string id="32423" soundid="38151">In my youth I ruled dutifully, but nature does not respect titles. Withering drought, not battle, threatened to take my throne. But I would not allow it!</string>
  <string id="32424" soundid="38152">I assaulted the underworld and claimed the great Water Dragon, and neither the treachery of my siblings nor my failing body could stop me! I am no longer a slave to time&apos;s decay!</string>
  <string id="32425" soundid="38153">My actions have brought the Empire great strength and its Emperor endless power! Who among you would dare challenge my right to rule?</string>
  <string id="32426" soundid="38154"></string>
  <string id="32427" soundid="38155">That glow. Brother Li hid the amulet in plain sight and acted as his own diversion. Just as Death&apos;s Hand diverted attention from me. The obvious threat hid the insidious one.</string>
  <string id="32429" soundid="38157">Do you even know what you hold, child? What truly led you here?</string>
  <string id="32430" soundid="38158">But who has set you on this path, and why? Do you blindly follow your master&apos;s mantra? Is anything ever so obvious? You were guided to me.</string>
  <string id="32432">Combatant 3</string>
  <string id="32433">I learned of your family. Do you use them to justify this?</string>
  <string id="32434" soundid="38162">Even if you are impervious to my sorcery, it changes nothing. I am a god! Come, student of Li! Your quest for death is at an end!</string>
  <string id="32435" soundid="38163">But for whom, I wonder? Do you blindly follow the will of your master? Is anything so simple? You were guided to me.</string>
  <string id="32436" soundid="38164">But where did it begin? Do you blindly follow the will of your master? Is anything so simple? You were guided to me.</string>
  <string id="32438" soundid="38166">I am the Emperor. I *am* the heart of the Empire. Death&apos;s Hand is a diversion. He is Death&apos;s *Hand.* *My* hand.</string>
  <string id="32439" soundid="38167">The lost sibling of the beloved Emperor Sun, forced to hide at the edge of the Empire. Until Death&apos;s Hand brought him to me.</string>
  <string id="32440" soundid="38168">This cannot be. I am Emperor Sun! I am a god!</string>
  <string id="32453">Here! Face me!</string>
  <string id="32457">I am the one who must end your evil.</string>
  <string id="32460">I learned of your family. Do you use them to justify this? Your child lives.</string>
  <string id="32462">You have upset the order of things. I do what I must.</string>
  <string id="32464">I alone can resist you! Enough talk! This ends now!</string>
  <string id="32466">Forgive me, but I cannot let you continue.</string>
  <string id="32467">You are blind to your own corruption, old man.</string>
  <string id="32468">Do you see, Princess? Your father is at the heart of it all.</string>
  <string id="32470">As I tried to say, Princess, Master Li is the Emperor&apos;s brother.</string>
  <string id="32472">Then it is true, Master Li? You are the Emperor&apos;s brother?</string>
  <string id="32473">I am &lt;FullName&gt;. I demand vengeance for the assault on my home!</string>
  <string id="32474">I am &lt;FullName&gt;. I will open your eyes to the suffering of your people.</string>
  <string id="32477">Town of Two Rivers</string>
  <string id="32480">You seem to have gotten over Bei pretty quickly.</string>
  <string id="32489">My name is &lt;FullName&gt;. I am here to rescue my Master.</string>
  <string id="32490">**TEMP** Description for Crescent Blades</string>
  <string id="32492">Double Rings</string>
  <string id="32493">**TEMP** Description for Double Rings</string>
  <string id="32496" soundid="173414">Do you see? This is what dropping heavily armed flyers and exploring caves that were very securely locked will get you! Some people never learn.</string>
  <string id="32547" soundid="38275">Father? You said your brothers were killed. I don&apos;t understand.</string>
  <string id="32559" soundid="125754">I haven&apos;t been able to sleep since you fell. All I could think of was finding a way to take revenge. So much hate washed over me.</string>
  <string id="32567" soundid="86716">I have been afraid to talk to you. I worry that you might have changed... that you might have forgotten me.</string>
  <string id="32568" soundid="86717">Do you still feel the same way for your Heavenly Lily?</string>
  <string id="32571" soundid="86720">I haven&apos;t slept since you fell. For all the influence my position is supposed to carry, I was as helpless as a lamb.</string>
  <string id="32572" soundid="86721">But now, to have you back here, with me. It&apos;s almost too much to bear.</string>
  <string id="32573" soundid="86722">I wish that saying it would make it true, but there is so much that is uncertain.</string>
  <string id="32574" soundid="86723">Whatever comes tomorrow, thank you for what we have *right now.* This moment... is beautiful.</string>
  <string id="32575" soundid="86724">You should kiss me before I remember who I am supposed to be.</string>
  <string id="32577" soundid="86726">Do you remember the hearts you left behind? I am not the only one waiting for an answer.</string>
  <string id="32580" soundid="86729">If you had to make a choice between me and her... would you? Could you? Who would it be?</string>
  <string id="32581" soundid="86730">Ah, it&apos;s just as we suspected. It&apos;s a shame, really.</string>
  <string id="32583" soundid="86731">A decision of one or the other can&apos;t help but hurt someone. We agreed that we wouldn&apos;t let that happen. Not after sharing such grief.</string>
  <string id="32584" soundid="86732">I should go.</string>
  <string id="32593" soundid="138459">The Imperial City is beautiful, but you still have to be careful in certain areas.</string>
  <string id="32594" soundid="86734">Ahhh... it&apos;s just like we thought. Poor, poor, lovable man, caught by feelings he can&apos;t stop.</string>
  <string id="32597" soundid="196989"></string>
  <string id="32598" soundid="86735">I never imagined that I&apos;d love someone like you....</string>
  <string id="32599" soundid="138460">Emperor Sun Hai is a great man. Without him the Empire would still be living in a drought.</string>
  <string id="32602" soundid="86739">Your... death, left us shaken. It seemed like an eternity before Dawn Star had that vision of the Water Dragon... before we knew you might return.</string>
  <string id="32603" soundid="86740">We consoled each other. Dawn Star and I started talking... got to know each other better.</string>
  <string id="32609">The Executioner</string>
  <string id="32637">That depends. Is she still willing to take what makes her happy?</string>
  <string id="32639">I haven&apos;t been able to stop thinking of you.</string>
  <string id="32642">I&apos;ll never let you go again.</string>
  <string id="32653" soundid="138461">I&apos;ve seen some strange things in this city, but it&apos;s still the only place I&apos;d want to live.</string>
  <string id="32654" soundid="138462">I love shopping in the city. They have everything here.</string>
  <string id="32657">If it&apos;s too much, I could leave again. Not by the same method, I hope.</string>
  <string id="32659">I don&apos;t understand. what have you been up to?</string>
  <string id="32662">I&apos;d choose you, Sun Lian.</string>
  <string id="32663">I&apos;d have to choose Dawn Star. I am sorry.</string>
  <string id="32669">** [temp] description for divine void style</string>
  <string id="32670" soundid="38398">Come to kick this tired old dog?</string>
  <string id="32671" soundid="38399">Careful, boy. This mongrel&apos;s still got all his teeth.</string>
  <string id="32705">Viper Style Power-up!</string>
  <string id="32706">Grants the Viper combat style</string>
  <string id="32707">Pirate</string>
  <string id="32712" soundid="105624">I&apos;m going to hang around this place a while longer. Call me curious to see what else you can stir out of this midden.</string>
  <string id="32713" soundid="38441">Sit, if you please. I have something I must finish.</string>
  <string id="32717" soundid="38445">You will not be champion! This is *my* arena!</string>
  <string id="32810">Use your environment to your advantage. Some areas allow you to manipulate destructible objects to defeat your opponents.</string>
  <string id="32812">Come with me. I could use your help.</string>
  <string id="32817">Wait here for me.</string>
  <string id="33085" soundid="197846">[These gates are sealed shut and will never open]</string>
  <string id="33086">Gate</string>
  <string id="33090" soundid="144618">Indeed. Indeed I do. You&apos;ve gotten rid of a very pesky mother-in-law for me. A ghost of course, eh-heh, but still. Yes, you&apos;ll get a reward.</string>
  <string id="33100">Graverobber</string>
  <string id="33102">Tien&apos;s Landing</string>
  <string id="33131">Beggar Song</string>
  <string id="33146">Imperial City</string>
  <string id="33147" soundid="68930">I&apos;ll be lucky if the director doesn&apos;t fling me into the river! I must go try to calm him.</string>
  <string id="33180">CHUD 1 description</string>
  <string id="33181">CHUD 2 description</string>
  <string id="33182">CHUD 3 description</string>
  <string id="33183">Monkey 1 description</string>
  <string id="33184">Monkey 2 description</string>
  <string id="33185">Monkey 3 description</string>
  <string id="33186">Dog 1 description</string>
  <string id="33187">Dog 2 description</string>
  <string id="33188">Dog 3 description</string>
  <string id="33189">ITEM_SPIRIT_OGRE</string>
  <string id="33190">ITEM_SPIRIT_MASK</string>
  <string id="33191">ITEM_SPIRIT_HORSE</string>
  <string id="33192">ITEM_SPIRIT_TOAD</string>
  <string id="33193">ITEM_SPIRIT_BRONZE</string>
  <string id="33194">ITEM_SPIRIT_REDMINISTER</string>
  <string id="33200" soundid="39153"></string>
  <string id="33202" soundid="39155"></string>
  <string id="33203" soundid="39156">Please... leave me alone! I&apos;m just a poor peasant woman. I have nothing left for you to take!</string>
  <string id="33204" soundid="39157">I am surprised to see you back, mighty one. Tien&apos;s Landing is doomed, and I thought our troubles would have driven you away.</string>
  <string id="33205" soundid="39158">I am Gufu, great one. Some call me Gufu the Sweet, though I don&apos;t know why, I usually smell like the fish I sell. Perhaps they are making fun of me.</string>
  <string id="33206" soundid="39159">But now there are no fish to sell. I have lived in Tien&apos;s Landing all my life, but now I am ashamed to say I wish I lived somewhere else.</string>
  <string id="33207" soundid="39160">Pirates are raiding the countryside, capturing peasants and taking them as slaves. Luckily, they have not attacked Tien&apos;s Landing... yet. </string>
  <string id="33208" soundid="39161">Now that the dam is closed, fish will soon return to Tien&apos;s Landing. I can go back to earning a living, and I have you to thank for that.</string>
  <string id="33209" soundid="39162">You don&apos;t know? The Great Dam has been opened, and now the river&apos;s level has dropped. It is too low and fast to navigate. Without the river, we are nothing.</string>
  <string id="33212">Display the credits of Jade Empire.</string>
    <string id="33228">These are not final credits

BioWare
Animation
Lead Animator
Deo Perez

Game Animation
Carmen Cheung
Steve Gilmour
Chris Hale
Mark How
Jim Jagger
Rick Li
John Santos
Henrik Vasquez

Lead Cinematics Animator
Tony de Waal

Cutscene Art and Animation
Jonathan Cooper
Nick DiLiberto
Paul Dutton
Cristian Enciso
Rod Green
Joel MacMillan
Chris Mann
Sherridon Routley
Steve Runham
Gina Welbourn
Shane Welbourn

Motion Capture Performance and Choreography
The Smashcut Action Team

Motion Capture at
Giant Studios
Syncrude Center for Motion and Balance

BioWare Director of Animation
Steve Gilmour
Art
Art Director
Matt Goldman

Artists
Nolan Cunningham
John Gallagher
Mike Grills
Shane Hawco
Kevin Hayes
Jessicah Mih
Matthew (Joonseo) Park
Eric Poulin
Arun Ram-Mohan
Alex Scott
Shareef Shanawany
Sean Smailes
Jason Spykerman
Rob Sugama
Rion Swanson
Jillian Tamaki
Neil Valeriano

Lead Technical Artist
Harvey Fong

Technical Artists and Art Tools Programmers
Ted Chen
Ben Hindle
Lindsay Jorgensen
Kees Rijnen

Additional Art
Dean Andersen
Ryan Blanchard
Warren Heise
Mike Leonard
Tobyn Manthorpe
Suhwan Pak
Mike Spalding
Mike Trottier
Derek Watts

Contract Artists
Grant Arthur
Dave Cathro
Jez Elford
Paul Hodge

BioWare Director of Art
Dave Hibbeln
Audio
Audio and External Resources Producer
Shauna Perry

Sound Designers
Michael Kent
Michael Peter
Steven Sim

Audio Intern
Craig Westley

Audio Programmer
Don Yakielashek

Original Score
Jack Wall

Additional Audio Design
Dave Chan
John Henke

Design
Lead Designer
Kevin Martens

Senior Technical Designers
Brent Knowles
Aidan Scanlan
Georg Zoeller

Senior Writers
Drew Karpyshyn
Luke Kristjanson
Mike Laidlaw

Designers
Jason Booth
Dusty Everman
James Henley
Brian Kindregan
Cori May
Brad Prince
Aidan Scanlan
Peter Thomas
Jay Turner
Mac Walters
Keith Warner
John Winski

Editing
Jay Turner
Laura Hamilton

Additional Design
Rob Bartel
Preston Watamaniuk

Original Language Development
Wolf Wikeley

BioWare Director of Design
James Ohlen

Localisation
Localisation Producer
Jenny McKearney

Localisation Programmers
Rob Krajcarski
Kris Tan

Production
Producer/Project Director
Jim Bishop

Executive Producers
Ray Muzyka
Greg Zeschuk

Assistant Producer
Sheldon Carter

Line Producers
Chris Klassen
Keith Soleski

Programming
Lead Programmer
Mark Darrah

Programmers
Rob Boyd
Mike Devine
Aaryn Flynn
Neil Flynn
Dan Hein
Ryan Hoyle
Pat Labine
Adriana Lopez
Dan Morris
Ernesto Novillo
Jan Sacharuk

Lead Graphics Programmer
Patrick Chan

Graphics Programmers
Brook Bakay
Matt Peters

Lead Tools Programmer
Chris Christou

Tools Programmers
Marwan Audeh
Jonathan Baldwin
Lee Bererton
Christopher Mihalick
Rejean Poirier
James Redford
Sydney Tang
Jon Thompson
Ryan Warden
Darren Wong

Additional Programming
Andrew Flavell
Frank Klier
Robert Niewiadomski
Sophia Smith
Tim Smith

BioWare Director of Programming
Scott Greig

BioWare Assistant Director of Tools
Don Moar

BioWare Assistant Director of Graphics
Jason Knipe

Quality Assurance
 
Quality Assurance Lead
Alain Baxter
 
Quality Assurance
Derrick Collins
Jonathan Epp
Scott Horner
Chris Priestly
Guillaume Bourbonniere
Mitchell T. Fujino
Nathan Frederick
Keith &quot;K2&quot; Hayward
Rob Henry
Sam Johnson
Curtis Knecht
Alex Lucas
Bob McCabe
Andrew Nobbs
Ryan Plamondon
Bruce Venne
Stanley Woo
Iain Stevens-Guille

Contract Testers
Steven Deleeuw
Michael Goldman
Chris Halina
Stephen Ho
Ryan Hrycun
Brian Mills
Sean Molofee
Celest Morris
Kyle Scott

BioWare Director of Quality Assurance
Phillip DeRosa

BioWare Marketing/Communications
Public Relations Lead
Teresa Cotesta

Promotional Art
Todd Grenier
Mike Sass
Colin Walmsley

Web Manager
Robin Mayne

Web Developers
Johnn Four
Jeff Marvin

Client Care Specialist
Jason Barlow

Community Manager
Jay Watamaniuk

Director of Marketing
Craig Priddle

BioWare Admin
Joint CEOs
Ray Muzyka
Greg Zeschuk

Director of Finance and Systems Administration
Richard Iwaniuk

Finance
Todd Derechey
Kelley Grainger
Jo-Marie Langkow

Business Advisor
Robert Kallir

Director of Outsourcing
Diarmid Clarke

Human Resources
Theresa Baxter
Mark Kluchky
Leanne Korotash
Donna Poburan

Systems Administration
Julian Karst
Nils Kuhnert
Dave McGruther
Craig Miller
Brett Tollefson
Duleepa &quot;Dups&quot; Wijayawardhana
Chris Zeschuk

Administrative Assistants
Agnes Goldman
Teresa Meester

Voice
Lead VO Director
Ginny McSwain

VO Direction
Rob King
Caroline Livingstone
Shauna Perry

Casting Services
TikiMan Casting
 
VO Recorded at
Technicolor Sound Services
Blackman Productions Inc.

Voice Actors
Actor 1
Actor 2
Actor 3
Actor 4
Actor 5
Actor 6
Actor 7
Actor 8
Actor 9
Actor 10
Actor 11
Actor 12
Actor 13
Actor 14
Actor 15
Actor 16
Actor 17
Actor 18
Actor 19
Actor 20
Actor 21
Actor 22
Actor 23
Actor 24
Actor 25
Actor 26
Actor 27
Actor 28
Actor 29
Actor 30
Actor 31
Actor 32
Actor 33
Actor 34
Actor 35
Actor 36
Actor 37
Actor 38
Actor 39
Actor 40
Actor 41
Actor 42
Actor 43
Actor 44
Actor 45
Actor 46
Actor 47
Actor 48
Actor 49
Actor 50
Actor 51
Actor 52
Actor 53
Actor 54
Actor 55
Actor 56
Actor 57
Actor 58
Actor 59
Actor 60
Actor 61
Actor 62
Actor 63
Actor 64
Actor 65
Actor 66
Actor 67
Actor 68
Actor 69
Actor 70
Actor 71
Actor 72
Actor 73
Actor 74
Actor 75
Actor 76
Actor 77
Actor 78
Actor 79
Actor 80
Actor 81
Actor 82
Actor 83
Actor 84
Actor 85

Special Thanks
Marc and Laurel Holmes
Mathew Kaustinen
Greg Philyaw
</string>
</tlk>