<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<tlk language="0">
  <string id="95817" soundid="148439">You have seen nothing of my temper. This... indignity is beyond all belief. I would kill you if I could.</string>
  <string id="95818" soundid="148440">Don&apos;t you dare mention that night in the same breath as this abomination. Giving is beautiful... it is something few are fortunate enough to experience.</string>
  <string id="95819" soundid="148441">You disgust me. Such a petty use of power.</string>
  <string id="95820" soundid="148442">You can command what you wish, but my heart holds nothing but hatred for you. To think the fate of the Empire is in your degenerate hands!</string>
  <string id="95821" soundid="148443">Leave... you sicken me.</string>
  <string id="95822" soundid="148444">[Princess Lian obediently stops talking, but her eyes blaze with hatred.]</string>
  <string id="95823" soundid="148445">It was not lost. It was stolen. The only passion you will see from me is in combat if I get free.</string>
  <string id="95824" soundid="148446">Care for me? You don&apos;t even know me if you think I would accept this!</string>
  <string id="95825" soundid="148447">Whatever you force upon me, I am lost to you. Let there be no doubt in your mind; my heart is cold.</string>
  <string id="95826" soundid="148448">It is all you will ever have. Take me, take the Empire, take it all; in the end, you will have nothing that matters.</string>
  <string id="95827" soundid="148449">There is no strength in this. Only the most insecure leader would command such forced obedience.</string>
  <string id="95828" soundid="148450">Are you so fearful of opposition? Poor child, grasping for control.</string>
  <string id="95829" soundid="148451">No choice? Lies! I see now what a coward... what a child you are. You are no better than your master, doing anything to get your way.</string>
  <string id="95830" soundid="148452">If only I were so lucky, but I still feel your presence. I believed you were someone special. Now you make me sick.</string>
  <string id="95831" soundid="148453">Alone? You are the one who is alone. Forced obedience means nothing. You will see.</string>
  <string id="95832" soundid="148454">I have seen everything that I believe in torn apart, one after another. Hopefully, it is all over soon.</string>
  <string id="95833" soundid="148455">The Empire has suffered at the hands of fools for too long. Wait until they see the new Emperor I am bringing them. </string>
  <string id="95834" soundid="148456">Sun Li is a fool. If a member of the royal family is to be enslaved in Death&apos;s Hand, he should at least be in competent hands.</string>
  <string id="95835" soundid="148457">And Sky... that worm deserved far worse, but I&apos;m sure he will still serve as an example.</string>
  <string id="95836" soundid="148458">We will make things right. Tomorrow will bring a new rule, I know it.</string>
  <string id="95837" soundid="148459">Let the heavens try and stop it. I doubt they have that power anymore.</string>
  <string id="95838" soundid="148460">I will make certain of it. You and I are owed that reward.</string>
  <string id="95839" soundid="148461">Respect is earned, not forced. Show that you have the wisdom to use the power you have before claiming something that might be beyond you.</string>
  <string id="95840" soundid="148462">It is a lesson I wish my father had learned.</string>
  <string id="95841" soundid="148463">For twenty years a fool has misused a wonderful gift. If the opportunity to make use of that strength is given, I hope you make the right choice for the Empire... and us.</string>
  <string id="95842" soundid="148464">Power is nothing. My family has proven that great strength only amplifies the mistakes made. With the wisdom I bring to your side, I know the Empire will prosper.</string>
  <string id="95843" soundid="148465">There will be more. Don&apos;t let the weight of your choices cloud your vision.</string>
  <string id="95844" soundid="148466">I will be there, watching what you do. I trust that you will make the right choices for the Empire and its people. I won&apos;t let either be abused again.</string>
  <string id="95845" soundid="148467">When the time comes, all the power in the world will be at your disposal. Remain true to the glory of the Empire and all will be well.</string>
  <string id="95846" soundid="148468">The power that has been unleashed cannot be handled carelessly. The fate of the Empire is at stake. You and I will make things right.</string>
  <string id="95847" soundid="148469">I will be ready. Don&apos;t worry.</string>
  <string id="95848" soundid="148470">You were wise to kill Sky. It is sad, but he deserved no less. If the Empire is to be safe, those that place it in peril must be removed. Our cause is too great.</string>
  <string id="95849" soundid="148471">I wanted Sky dealt with in a more permanent fashion, but if you are certain we are moving toward a free Empire, then I will stand by you.</string>
  <string id="95850" soundid="148472">The sins of my family must be dealt with. Only then can the Empire regain the glory it has lost.</string>
  <string id="95855">Try all weapons. Use your Fight Style keys to switch weapons.</string>
  <string id="95861" soundid="196238"></string>
  <string id="95863">Use the Left and Right triggers to switch among targets.</string>
  <string id="95864">It may be too late if what we know is true.</string>
  <string id="95866">Maybe we should seek another path.</string>
  <string id="95869">Why should you lead? They obviously know your secrets.</string>
  <string id="95871">The defeat of Sun Li signaled a new beginning for the Jade Empire, and a personal awakening in Dawn Star. Despite the loss of the Master she thought she knew, with the restoration of the natural order the Empire seemed alive with possibility. She had seen the heart of the land in turmoil, so she retraced her steps, replacing memories of destruction with sights of renewal. Soon she found herself back in the ruin of Two Rivers. It was painful, but she took comfort in knowing that the fish were abundant and the land remained fertile; eventually new settlers would come. She replanted her garden, a flower for each of her lost friends, and set out across the Empire once more.</string>
  <string id="95873">Student</string>
  <string id="95876">Student</string>
  <string id="95879">Accept the custom character?</string>
  <string id="95880">Who is entombed here?</string>
  <string id="95881" soundid="162488">There was a time when I might have disagreed with such a ploy, but that was before you showed me how to stand up to this world.</string>
  <string id="95882">Master Li is the Emperor&apos;s brother and he is alive.</string>
  <string id="95883">Have you actually seen inside the tombs?</string>
  <string id="95885">If Master Li is alive, what about Prince Kin?</string>
  <string id="95888">Let&apos;s get going.</string>
  <string id="95889">Why shouldn&apos;t I? Your father&apos;s word is hardly worth more.</string>
  <string id="95890">This can&apos;t be the tomb of the Glorious Strategist.</string>
  <string id="95891">Master Li is the Glorious Strategist. He told me so.</string>
  <string id="95895">His word is hardly worth more than my master&apos;s.</string>
  <string id="95896">It doesn&apos;t matter. Have you seen inside the tombs yourself?</string>
  <string id="95899">Bah! I told you already that Master Li is the Glorious Strategist.</string>
  <string id="95900">That&apos;s impossible. You must have been lied to.</string>
  <string id="95901">Are you certain of this? Have you seen the bodies?</string>
  <string id="95902" soundid="162489">Whoever Master Li is now, he is not the father I never had. If he deserved that role, he would have recognized me. He abandoned me by never searching.</string>
  <string id="95903">I have no interest. We should get moving.</string>
  <string id="95905" soundid="162490">I am more concerned with... with what I have now. Sometimes I wonder what I would do if I lost you.</string>
  <string id="95910">You are second to none, Dawn Star.</string>
  <string id="95911">You both feign annoyance to hide your intrigue. We will discuss it after we deal with the Emperor.</string>
  <string id="95915">This is neither the time, nor the place! Both of you shut up!</string>
  <string id="95918">And what of the court? What of the rules that bind you?</string>
  <string id="95921">I&apos;ll stand by you, my Heavenly Lily.</string>
  <string id="95923">I want no one else, my Silk Fox.</string>
  <string id="95927">I won&apos;t wait. You have my love, Dawn Star.</string>
  <string id="95931">Be silent, my Dawn Star. If it *must* be said, then we are sure to live until it is.</string>
  <string id="95934">And now is not the time. Let me concentrate.</string>
  <string id="95937">I&apos;m ready. Let&apos;s go.</string>
  <string id="95939">I have some words for your father, too.</string>
  <string id="95941">Now, now. Temper.</string>
  <string id="95942">Such fire... why couldn&apos;t you have been like this two nights ago?</string>
  <string id="95943">I have merely removed the guesswork.</string>
  <string id="95944">But so amusing. We will work on your performance later.</string>
  <string id="95945">Goodbye for now.</string>
  <string id="95946">Enough of your chatter. Be quiet!</string>
  <string id="95947">And hardly worth it. You&apos;ve lost all passion.</string>
  <string id="95948">I only wanted to ensure loyalty. I still care for you.</string>
  <string id="95950">I will have Kang construct slippers. Your obedience is all I want.</string>
  <string id="95951">Be grateful. You will stand at my side. Or slightly behind.</string>
  <string id="95952">I had to preserve loyalty. As a princess, don&apos;t you understand?</string>
  <string id="95954">Say what you wish. I will not be swayed.</string>
  <string id="95955">I was left with no choice in the matter.</string>
  <string id="95956">You seemed perfectly happy to let me have my way two nights ago.</string>
  <string id="95957">Fine, I will leave you alone.</string>
  <string id="95961">I hope there is time for us in all of this.</string>
  <string id="95962">Everyone will respect the power I bring.</string>
  <string id="95964">I have made some difficult decisions to get here.</string>
  <string id="95966">Be ready. I will signal when we will leave.</string>
  <string id="95967" soundid="148589"></string>
  <string id="95969" soundid="148591">I am not here to fight you. I have information you might find useful... if you are willing to trade for it.</string>
  <string id="95970" soundid="148592">Not quite yet. There is much you do not know, and I may yet enlighten you... for a price.</string>
  <string id="95971" soundid="148593">Powerful forces are at work here. You are caught in great events that are beyond you. But I may have use for someone as... impetuous as you.</string>
  <string id="95972" soundid="148594">Trust? I never said we should trust each other. I don&apos;t trust you at all, but our goals may be similar.</string>
  <string id="95973" soundid="148595">I want nothing more than for you to continue your journey. You seek the old man who was taken from Two Rivers, correct? </string>
  <string id="95974" soundid="148596">Of course you do. He was taken by Death&apos;s Hand. I could tell you where his minions have gone... for a price.</string>
  <string id="95975" soundid="148597">A simple trade: I tell you where the abductors are, and you tell me who that old man is.</string>
  <string id="95976" soundid="148598">I&apos;ve underestimated you once. I will not do so again. Attack me here, and the local guards will have you in a noose.</string>
  <string id="95977" soundid="148599">What I ask is very reasonable: information for information. Tell me who he is.</string>
  <string id="95978" soundid="148600">You mix truth with lies. He must be more for Death&apos;s Hand to keep him alive. Still, you&apos;ve told me what I need to know.</string>
  <string id="95979" soundid="148601">Sun Li... ha! You think me a fool? You are either a liar or very, very confused.</string>
  <string id="95980" soundid="148602">You don&apos;t know as much as you think you do. But you have answered my question, and I will answer in kind.</string>
  <string id="95981" soundid="148603">The Glorious Strategist has been dead for twenty years! Everyone knows this! You mean to confuse me, but I am not a willing fool.</string>
  <string id="95982" soundid="148604">No idea? I saw your concern over the destruction of the village. Do not think to fool me!</string>
  <string id="95983" soundid="148605">I will let you maintain this deception for now, just to see where it leads, but we share an enemy in Death&apos;s Hand. For that reason, I will help you.</string>
  <string id="95984" soundid="148606">It would take a season to reach the Imperial City by land or water. Air is the only quick way, but you need a wind map. I know the location of one.</string>
  <string id="95985" soundid="148607">Lord Yun governs much of the Great Southern Forest. He petitioned the Lotus Assassins for a wind map so he could settle a trade disruption.</string>
  <string id="95986" soundid="148608">Of course, that has earned him their attention, in addition to whatever trouble is infesting his lands. I doubt he has time for charity, but you might try to find him.</string>
  <string id="95987" soundid="148609">Upriver from this village is a pirate stronghold, the river fortress of Gao the Greater, a minion of Death&apos;s Hand.</string>
  <string id="95988" soundid="148610">The flyers that attacked your village came from that stronghold... and returned there.</string>
  <string id="95989" soundid="148611">The old man must have passed through it. He may still be there, although I know that Death&apos;s Hand has already moved on.</string>
  <string id="95990" soundid="148612">I have matters of my own to attend. If you survive, we will see what use you are to me.</string>
  <string id="95991" soundid="148613">Do not presume familiarity with me. Our paths have crossed for a moment, but no more. I have matters of my own to attend.</string>
  <string id="95992" soundid="148614">His flyers give the Lotus Assassins mobility and speed. If you can stop Gao, or even hinder him, you will hurt Death&apos;s Hand.</string>
  <string id="95993" soundid="148615">Remember, if you want to reach the Imperial City, you must go to the forest and get that map from Lord Yun. My path takes me elsewhere.</string>
  <string id="95994" soundid="148616">If you actually reach the Imperial City, I will be impressed. Until then, I wish you luck. You are a surprising little peasant.</string>
  <string id="95995" soundid="148617"></string>
  <string id="95996" soundid="148618">Remember, if you seek the old man or revenge on Death&apos;s Hand, go to Gao&apos;s fortress. My path takes me elsewhere.</string>
  <string id="95997" soundid="148619">I do not seek a servant in you. Although that much fire in a man&apos;s spirit is... stimulating.</string>
  <string id="95998" soundid="148620">Stop where you are.</string>
  <string id="95999" soundid="148621">It is clear that you are one of his hirelings, or perhaps one of Gao the Greater&apos;s marauding pirates. You will pay for the crimes you have committed.</string>
  <string id="96000" soundid="148622">Don&apos;t waste your last breath on lies. I didn&apos;t get there in time to help anyone, but I saw you leave the massacre in Two Rivers. Clearly you were involved.</string>
  <string id="96001" soundid="148623">Death&apos;s Hand went too far in ordering its destruction, and Gao the Greater sought to profit from it. My retribution will end with them, but it will begin with you.</string>
  <string id="96002" soundid="148624"></string>
  <string id="96003" soundid="148625"></string>
  <string id="96004" soundid="148626">Enough!</string>
  <string id="96005" soundid="148627">The way you move seems odd... a flaw I cannot see, perhaps? But you are... better than I expected. You might even beat me, if I allowed such insolence. </string>
  <string id="96006" soundid="148628">You are too skilled to be just a hireling. Death&apos;s Hand would view such ability outside his assassins as... dangerous, and Gao the Greater prefers his servants docile.</string>
  <string id="96007" soundid="148629">So it would appear. You lack their branding... but if you are not one of them, who are you? A monk? A mercenary? A bandit?</string>
  <string id="96008" soundid="148630">You chase a great evil... larger than you realize. Leave, and you may survive. Others have tried to face Death&apos;s Hand, but were destroyed, as Two Rivers was.</string>
  <string id="96009">Bamboo Cask</string>
  <string id="96010" soundid="148632">Your honor sends you toward peril, but you do not flinch from it.</string>
  <string id="96011" soundid="148633">A trait of fools... and perhaps the occasional hero. I also seek answers from Death&apos;s Hand and his minions.</string>
  <string id="96012" soundid="148634">If you truly oppose him, you will need to find your way to the Imperial City. Of course, only the Lotus Assassins can come and go as they please, thanks to Gao.</string>
  <string id="96013" soundid="148635">Travel routes by land and water are blocked, but they use wind maps and flyers to further their goals here and in the surrounding forest.</string>
  <string id="96014" soundid="148636">Perhaps, if you are capable, we will meet again. I wish you good luck, but you will need far more than that to survive.</string>
  <string id="96015" soundid="148637"></string>
  <string id="96016" soundid="148638">You show no fear, even after seeing the power he wields.</string>
  <string id="96017" soundid="148639">Death&apos;s Hand may be our common foe, but the enemy of my enemy is not necessarily my friend.</string>
  <string id="96018" soundid="148640">I see truth in your eyes; you seek revenge on Death&apos;s Hand. You are not my enemy, but... who are you? A monk? A mercenary? A bandit?</string>
  <string id="96019" soundid="148641">You have managed to survive. I suppose someone of your skill cannot be easily dissuaded.</string>
  <string id="96020" soundid="148642">You may call me Silk Fox. I apologize for my previous aggression, but I thought you were in league with an enemy of mine. I was clearly mistaken.</string>
  <string id="96021" soundid="148643">You are more skilled than I expected, but I rarely need to escape from anyone. I had to... step back, which allowed me to see that you are not my enemy.</string>
  <string id="96023">Student remains</string>
  <string id="96025">I do not follow Death&apos;s Hand.</string>
  <string id="96026">What do you know of Gao the Greater?</string>
  <string id="96027">Get out of my way. You won&apos;t delay my revenge.</string>
  <string id="96033">I am not in league with Gao or the Lotus Assassins.</string>
  <string id="96035">Chair</string>
  <string id="96036">That is why I must face him: to avenge the dead.</string>
  <string id="96038">I will pursue them both! I am not afraid!</string>
  <string id="96043">My business with Death&apos;s Hand is my own!</string>
  <string id="96045">Who are you? Why do you fight the Lotus Assassins?</string>
  <string id="96047">Get out of my way. I&apos;m after Death&apos;s Hand!</string>
  <string id="96049">Who are you? Why did you attack me?</string>
  <string id="96051">Another ambush? You barely escaped last time.</string>
  <string id="96053">Get out of my way.</string>
  <string id="96055">Why should I trust you?</string>
  <string id="96057">What do you want?</string>
  <string id="96059">What do you want for this information?</string>
  <string id="96060">I could beat it out of you. You can&apos;t defeat me.</string>
  <string id="96062">The old man was Master Li, my teacher.</string>
  <string id="96064">He is Sun Li the Glorious Strategist, the Emperor&apos;s brother.</string>
  <string id="96065">Believe what you will. I know the truth.</string>
  <string id="96067">Do not call me a liar!</string>
  <string id="96069">Why? What do you know?</string>
  <string id="96070">I have no idea. Now, tell me where his captors have gone.</string>
  <string id="96077">Help me to defeat Death&apos;s Hand.</string>
  <string id="96079">Now that we&apos;re friends, who are you really?</string>
  <string id="96081">What do you know of Gao?</string>
  <string id="96083">Thank you for your help. Farewell.</string>
  <string id="96087">I will not be your errand-boy!</string>
  <string id="96089">I will not be your errand-girl!</string>
  <string id="96090" soundid="148712"></string>
  <string id="96091" soundid="148713"></string>
  <string id="96092" soundid="151054">I know you&apos;re very busy, but if you happen to have time and be passing by the beach, I&apos;d appreciate it if you would at least ask Old Ming.</string>
  <string id="96093" soundid="151055">If I&apos;m lucky, he might know of an herb, and if heaven smiles upon me, he&apos;ll know where to find some.</string>
  <string id="96094">I think I know enough about this herb.</string>
  <string id="96098" soundid="151063">I hope you took a moment to celebrate as you flooded the valley.</string>
  <string id="96099" soundid="151064">Whatever you hoped to achieve by drowning that sad place will soon be undone.</string>
  <string id="96100" soundid="151065">Sergeant, if you will, eliminate this pest.</string>
  <string id="96101" soundid="151066">You hope to appeal to my sense of pity? What&apos;s next? &quot;The town was suffering. Think of the people!&quot; Bah. My loyalty is to the Empire!</string>
  <string id="96102" soundid="151067">That is precisely the idea. I&apos;m sure you are very confident in your skills, but I assure you that these fine men of the Imperial Army are more than your match.</string>
  <string id="96103" soundid="151068">The Sergeant knows his place, and he understands that what we Assassins do is for the good of the Empire as a whole.</string>
  <string id="96104" soundid="151069">If a few people suffer, then they do so for the glory of Emperor Sun.</string>
  <string id="96105" soundid="151070">You treasonous dog! This dam is one of Emperor Sun Hai&apos;s great civic projects, and you smash its controls like they were nothing!</string>
  <string id="96106" soundid="151071">Your acts spit in the face of our glorious Empire, and for your treason, you will die.</string>
  <string id="96107" soundid="151072">An order given by the Lotus Assassins is obeyed without question, and to the letter. No one wanted those controls to be disabled permanently!</string>
  <string id="96108" soundid="151073">These worms are beneath my notice, let alone my concern.</string>
  <string id="96109" soundid="151074">We are the will of the Emperor, and if we choose to flood this place or empty it, that is our prerogative.</string>
  <string id="96110" soundid="151075">You have interfered with our plans, and now you will die. That is the way of things.</string>
  <string id="96113">Wait! You don&apos;t need to follow this Assassin&apos;s orders, Sergeant!</string>
  <string id="96115">You&apos;ll have to go through me if you want to open this dam again.</string>
  <string id="96119">It was your order that emptied this lake in the first place.</string>
  <string id="96121">An Assassin caring about the people of Tien&apos;s Landing? Won&apos;t that make you seem weak?</string>
  <string id="96124">If you&apos;re here to kill me, try it. Don&apos;t waste my time posturing.</string>
  <string id="96125" soundid="151090">The Scourge of the South has destroyed whole villages in the south. Many innocents have suffered at the hands of the Scourge.</string>
  <string id="96126" soundid="151091">Out of sheer spite the Scourge flooded ancient ruins... wantonly destroying our very own heritage.</string>
  <string id="96127" soundid="151092">Out of sheer spite the Scourge interrupted the economic trade in Tien&apos;s Landing and all the towns surrounding it. Hundreds have fled.</string>
  <string id="96128" soundid="151093">The Scourge associates with nefarious fox spirits, aiding them in their occupation of our once pristine forests in the south.</string>
  <string id="96129" soundid="151094">The Scourge associates with foul beasts and cannibals who are responsible for Lord Yun&apos;s untimely demise in his family&apos;s forests.</string>
  <string id="96130" soundid="151095">A group of river-faring businessmen have been attacked and forced to flee. Nobody is safe from this criminal.</string>
  <string id="96131" soundid="151096">His own master died at his hands, and he had fellow students kidnapped and tortured, just because they didn&apos;t agree with him.</string>
  <string id="96132" soundid="151097">Her own master died at her hands, and she had fellow students kidnapped and tortured, just because they didn&apos;t agree with her.</string>
  <string id="96133" soundid="151098">If you think you&apos;ve seen this person, you must report it to the authorities at once. It is your duty.</string>
  <string id="96134">Sergeant</string>
  <string id="96137">Lotus Apprentice</string>
  <string id="96140">Imperial Soldier</string>
  <string id="96143">Old Man</string>
  <string id="96148" soundid="151113">He will find you. I had my contacts spread rumors of your interest. Just return to the arena.</string>
  <string id="96150" soundid="151115">Anything else you want to know about the ghosts?</string>
  <string id="96151" soundid="151116">Eh-heh, right then. If you need to find me, I&apos;ll be at my house a little farther down this path.</string>
  <string id="96152" soundid="151117">If you need to find me again, I&apos;ll be at my house down the road.</string>
  <string id="96154">Not right now.</string>
  <string id="96155">Arena Tavern</string>
  <string id="96157" soundid="194019"></string>
  <string id="96158">I should go.</string>
  <string id="96159">Warehouse</string>
  <string id="96160">Slave Pen</string>
  <string id="96162" soundid="151131">The child screamed for help; his cries were shrill with terror, for he could not swim. I moved to help him, but I felt a hand on my arm.</string>
  <string id="96163" soundid="151132">The boy I loved turned to me and said &quot;If we help him, he&apos;ll only tell the others what we&apos;ve done. We have to let him go.&quot; Something in his voice.... I believed him.</string>
  <string id="96164" soundid="151133">That poor child was swept away in the current and was found dead down river days later. We never told anyone what we had done, but I could never forget.</string>
  <string id="96165">I have heard that you have a bounty on your head.</string>
  <string id="96166">Slave Breaker</string>
  <string id="96167">To Workshop</string>
  <string id="96168" soundid="163978">Good day to you. Are you here to help my friend, Prefect Jitong, with this little difficulty we&apos;re having?</string>
  <string id="96169" soundid="163979">Oh, no, I suppose you aren&apos;t. Well, then I really shouldn&apos;t be speaking to you. I don&apos;t want to make his job any harder than it is already.</string>
  <string id="96170">That&apos;s terrible! Why would he do such a thing?</string>
  <string id="96172">What happened to the child?</string>
  <string id="96173" soundid="151142">Captain Sen is a well respected man here in the city, but something about him makes my skin crawl. His ambition is well hidden; perhaps that&apos;s all there is to it.</string>
  <string id="96174" soundid="151143">It&apos;s a shame, but the army gave up trying to arrest me years ago. Too many casualties. Guess I should have sent home more missing limbs than missing heads.</string>
  <string id="96175" soundid="151144">If this captain wanted a real hunter, he should be hiring my wife. There&apos;s a woman who can scent a crime from miles away.</string>
  <string id="96180">jdk_01</string>
  <string id="96181">Gate Guard</string>
  <string id="96184">First Gate</string>
  <string id="96185">Second Gate</string>
  <string id="96186">Portal</string>
  <string id="96187">Cave Entrance</string>
  <string id="96188">Gate Guard</string>
  <string id="96191">Teahouse Door</string>
  <string id="96194" soundid="148816"></string>
  <string id="96195" soundid="148817">Please, I don&apos;t want to talk.</string>
  <string id="96196" soundid="148818">My head moves as you direct, but that makes you a master, not a friend.</string>
  <string id="96197" soundid="148819">Yes, I was a bit of a fool to let you get so close to me. You were... special to me. Now, I don&apos;t know you.</string>
  <string id="96198" soundid="148820">My heart is no longer yours, regardless of how you direct my body. If I am merely a toy, perhaps payment should be arranged. </string>
  <string id="96199" soundid="148821">I have never forced my will on anyone. You really do know very little about me. And I did not know you.</string>
  <string id="96200" soundid="148822">I do not look forward to your next visit.</string>
  <string id="96201" soundid="148823">[A hateful look for a moment, with no sound or words. Just a second or two.]</string>
  <string id="96202" soundid="148824">You expected otherwise? How would you react to being manipulated? Perhaps by striking back, even across the Empire.</string>
  <string id="96203" soundid="148825">How like your Master you have become.</string>
  <string id="96204" soundid="148826">If you think my reaction to this is a surprise, you know very little about me. Imprisonment... even death... is almost preferable to losing all control.</string>
  <string id="96205" soundid="148827">I cannot atone for my deeds if I am not allowed to act. You compound my shame by not giving me the chance to correct what I have done.</string>
  <string id="96206" soundid="148828">After what we have been through together, you must know that this is unbearable.</string>
  <string id="96207" soundid="148829">I am sorry, I did not understand how deeply you have been scarred by betrayal and treachery. You are becoming just like your master.</string>
  <string id="96208" soundid="148830">You collar those who would be friends so that they have no chance to oppose you. That is not strength. That&apos;s fear.</string>
  <string id="96209" soundid="148831">I do not know who you have become. When this is all done, will the people of the Empire recognize you as one of their own or just another tyrant?</string>
  <string id="96210" soundid="148832">Was it? If you believe that, then you truly do not understand the depth of my shame for my actions.</string>
  <string id="96211" soundid="148833">It would seem that you do not understand me, or the shame I now feel because of this imprisonment.</string>
  <string id="96212" soundid="148834">There was a time I kept thoughts of you very close to my heart. Now I want you out.</string>
  <string id="96213" soundid="148835">I wish you would, but I feel your mind within me.</string>
  <string id="96214" soundid="148836">We are a long way from the farm I once called home. I never thought I would make such a journey.</string>
  <string id="96215" soundid="148837">But you have shown me what power can bring. The closer we get to our goal, the more intrigued and... excited I am at your potential.</string>
  <string id="96216" soundid="148838">The toy you have taken is interesting too. It is a shame that Dawn Star and the princess could not appreciate the value of having Death&apos;s Hand as a puppet.</string>
  <string id="96217" soundid="148839">Time? Of course. Who would dare stop us? If you will it, it will be.</string>
  <string id="96218" soundid="148840">Anything else would be unbearable. I can&apos;t even begin to think about what we will do after this is finished, but I want whatever it is to keep us together.</string>
  <string id="96219" soundid="148841">And many of those who have fallen deserved to do so, but there will come a time when all the tyrants will be gone. I hope your rage will depart with them.</string>
  <string id="96220" soundid="148842">Yes, the old oppressors must be ousted. Then you will have enough power to enforce the freedom that people deserve.</string>
  <string id="96221" soundid="148843">Such anger in your voice. When this is all done, I will help you enjoy some simpler things. Your burden is too great.</string>
  <string id="96222" soundid="148844">I will help you carry that weight, but I&apos;m not sure how much use I can be.</string>
  <string id="96223" soundid="148845">I will stand by you. Once the corruption is excised, the Jade Empire will be a blank slate, my friend.</string>
  <string id="96224" soundid="148846">You seem poised to take control of the Empire. Power brings freedom, and I will be there to do what I can.</string>
  <string id="96225" soundid="148847">Nothing can move me from your side. No matter what comes, I will be there for you.</string>
  <string id="96226" soundid="148848">I will be ready. Rely on it.</string>
  <string id="96227" soundid="148849">It is a shame you could not take Death&apos;s Hand for your own, but I suppose it is best to cast off old enemies whenever possible.</string>
  <string id="96229" soundid="148851">I am sorry for the pain I caused you. I risked everything. I will not take this new opportunity you have given me for granted.</string>
  <string id="96230" soundid="148852">Your master is a formidable opponent. We cannot leave the Empire in his hands.</string>
  <string id="96256">What does the central pedestal do?</string>
  <string id="96258">What colors typically represent what seasons?</string>
  <string id="96260">Can you tell me anything else?</string>
  <string id="96261">Could you repeat what you said before about the furnaces?</string>
  <string id="96276" soundid="155009">What! Zi Bao? Gone? It&apos;s... it&apos;s all my fault. I never should have entrusted this mission to a stranger. And now I&apos;ll have Songtao&apos;s death on my hands.
</string>
  <string id="96277">My style is faulty!</string>
  <string id="96278" soundid="155011">Here you are! I was despairing for your return. What news do you bring? </string>
  <string id="96281">Back off!</string>
  <string id="96284" soundid="151221">His corpse has risen, covered in the protective wrappings he was buried in. I... I would not have survived. Please, get the liver from him quickly!</string>
  <string id="96285" soundid="151222">He lies buried in one of the large tower-tombs closer to the entrance of the Necropolis. His body has risen, covered in the preservative garments it was buried in.</string>
  <string id="96286" soundid="151223">He is most dangerous. If I had not fled, I don&apos;t think he would have left me alive. Be careful there, but please, hurry so my daughter can be saved!</string>
  <string id="96289">Tell me about the nobleman.</string>
  <string id="96291" soundid="151229">Leave Zhong alone.</string>
  <string id="96292" soundid="151230">Zhong! You can&apos;t stay up here forever. This isn&apos;t your home! You need to come back with me to the farm.</string>
  <string id="96293" soundid="151231">No! Zhong not want to go home. Zhong doesn&apos;t want to see ox.</string>
  <string id="96294" soundid="151232">[sigh] It wasn&apos;t your fault... it was an accident. I need you back at the farm, now let&apos;s go, Zhong.</string>
  <string id="96295" soundid="151233">I am Dong Ping, Zhong&apos;s employer. Zhong works on my farm, but the other day, he accidentally killed one of my oxen, and since then he has refused to come back.</string>
  <string id="96296" soundid="151234">Zhong is no ordinary ogre. He is, despite his simple nature, very skilled.</string>
  <string id="96297" soundid="158330">Well, I&apos;m glad to see you are back. What was that all about?</string>
  <string id="96298" soundid="151236">Some of the patrons here are unnerved by his size. I&apos;m worried that if he doesn&apos;t leave with me soon, the owners may take matters into their own hands.</string>
  <string id="96299" soundid="151237">If he gets hurt... or worse, I&apos;ll be ruined. I can&apos;t run the farm without him. But I don&apos;t know what else to do. He won&apos;t listen to me.</string>
  <string id="96300" soundid="151238">You... will? I must warn you... Zhong is... well, he&apos;s very strong willed, and very strong. I am grateful for your help, but please be careful.</string>
  <string id="96301" soundid="151239">Zhong the Ox Carrier came by his name honestly. I would hate to see him hurt you, or anybody else, for that matter. Speak softly to him, and you should be okay.</string>
  <string id="96302" soundid="151240">Yes, indeed it is.</string>
  <string id="96303" soundid="154597">Excellent idea. Your next opponent is Third Brother Renshan.</string>
  <string id="96304" soundid="154598">Once you&apos;ve defeated Third Brother, come and see me. Good luck.</string>
  <string id="96305" soundid="154599">A good idea. Your next opponent is Fourth Brother Yu.</string>
  <string id="96306" soundid="151244">What have you done? How will I run my farm now? It&apos;s bad enough with things the way they are in town. Now I&apos;m surely ruined!</string>
  <string id="96310">Who are you, and who is Zhong?</string>
  <string id="96311">What&apos;s the matter with your ogre?</string>
  <string id="96313">What are you doing with an ogre?</string>
  <string id="96317">Don&apos;t worry, I&apos;ll speak with him.</string>
  <string id="96318">I&apos;ll make sure he leaves.</string>
  <string id="96320">That&apos;s your problem, old man.</string>
  <string id="96321" soundid="154600">A wise decision. Your next opponent is Fifth Brother Shangjin.</string>
  <string id="96322" soundid="154601">Very good. Your next opponent is Sixth Brother Gaoshan.</string>
  <string id="96323" soundid="151261">Go away! Zhong not want to speak to you.</string>
  <string id="96324" soundid="151262">Zhong kill ox. Zhong too strong, too rough with ox. Zhong not want to hurt ox, Zhong only playing. Now Zhong cries for ox.</string>
  <string id="96325" soundid="151263">Zhong not want to go. Zhong think you should go before Zhong get angry. Zhong not mean to kill ox... but will mean to kill you if you make Zhong mad.</string>
  <string id="96326" soundid="151264">Ox like to play with Zhong. Ox like it when Zhong throw her in the air and catch her. Zhong missed. Zhong dropped ox on her head. Ox is dead.</string>
  <string id="96327" soundid="151265">Zhong no play game. Leave Zhong alone, or Zhong will crush you. I will throw you and drop you on your head like I did to ox.</string>
  <string id="96328" soundid="151266">Ox was Zhong&apos;s friend. Zhong killed a friend, and now Zhong is bad.</string>
  <string id="96329" soundid="151267">Master already have another ox. Poor ox... Zhong killed ox&apos;s sister. Now ox won&apos;t like Zhong anymore.</string>
  <string id="96330" soundid="151268">Master have other ox. Master won&apos;t starve... master better off without Zhong.</string>
  <string id="96331" soundid="151269">Ox not dumb... ox was smart. Ox&apos;s brother is dumb... but now ox has no sister. Zhong is very bad.</string>
  <string id="96332" soundid="151270">[Success] Zhong is lonely. Ox must be lonely, too. Maybe ox will forgive Zhong, and we be friends again. I will go and see.</string>
  <string id="96333" soundid="151271">You have been nice to Zhong. Zhong like you. Zhong hope you have good day.</string>
  <string id="96334" soundid="151272">Noooo! Zhong won&apos;t let you hurt ox!</string>
  <string id="96335">Why are you so upset?</string>
  <string id="96336">My, you&apos;re a big one aren&apos;t you?</string>
  <string id="96337">Get out of here, Zhong, or I&apos;ll throw you out!</string>
  <string id="96338">I believe you. I&apos;m sure you didn&apos;t do it on purpose.</string>
  <string id="96339">Tell me exactly how it happened, Zhong.</string>
  <string id="96341">No more games, Zhong! It&apos;s time to leave.</string>
  <string id="96343">Maybe you can get another ox.</string>
  <string id="96345">You don&apos;t have a choice. Look at me.</string>
  <string id="96346">You seemed to like such direction the other night.</string>
  <string id="96347">You can still be of use to me. You might even enjoy it.</string>
  <string id="96348">Ooh, you don&apos;t like being a plaything? Lingering guilt over past behavior, perhaps?</string>
  <string id="96349">Goodbye for now.</string>
  <string id="96350">Silence!</string>
  <string id="96351">I find your tone very unappealing.</string>
  <string id="96353">You are so distant. Is this really so bad?</string>
  <string id="96355">Certain obedience is far more useful to me than trust.</string>
  <string id="96356">The handsome rogue is lecturing me on using people? Amusing.</string>
  <string id="96357">I have learned to use my strength. Is that so bad?</string>
  <string id="96359">It had to be done. That is all I will say.</string>
  <string id="96360">I am sorry, but binding you was necessary.</string>
  <string id="96361">I know your shame. I quite enjoyed it the other night.</string>
  <string id="96362">Fine, I will leave you alone.</string>
  <string id="96365">Will there still be time for us after all this is done?</string>
  <string id="96366">I will destroy anything in my way.</string>
  <string id="96367">Some of these decisions have been hard to make.</string>
  <string id="96369">Ready yourself. We will be leaving soon.</string>
  <string id="96548" soundid="149170"></string>
  <string id="96549" soundid="149171">I am no common bandit. I&apos;ve been hunted by far worse than you!</string>
  <string id="96550" soundid="149172">Let&apos;s go. The main camp is to the north, but there are soldiers all around this area. If you want to find trouble, let&apos;s do it quickly.</string>
  <string id="96551" soundid="149173">I do not blame you. There are times when *I* do not trust myself, but I will help you here today.</string>
  <string id="96552" soundid="149174">You don&apos;t really have much to lose by following my lead. You would have to turn back without it. Now, let&apos;s get moving.</string>
  <string id="96553" soundid="149175">I can refuse some fool determined to get lost in the swamp, but I doubt your friend earned her fate. Gao the Lesser shouldn&apos;t get such a prize without a fair fight.</string>
  <string id="96554" soundid="149176">Dawn Star? I know that name, but I still can&apos;t... I don&apos;t look for trouble. Fighting about it is pointless. You would still be left without your directions.</string>
  <string id="96555" soundid="149177">Gao the Lesser? I know the family. This is a brazen act, even for them, but now I understand why their men are clearing a path through the marsh.</string>
  <string id="96556" soundid="149178">Carrying someone? They took someone from your village? That is very brazen, even for them, but it explains why they are clearing a path through the marsh.</string>
  <string id="96557" soundid="149179">If you know that name you know they are not choosy about who they attack. Would a bandit stop to ask you why you are in the marsh?</string>
  <string id="96558" soundid="149180">I see your point. There are differences. Tien was a knowledgeable man, whereas I feel that a person can sometimes think too much.</string>
  <string id="96559" soundid="149181">I don&apos;t believe I need to explain myself beyond that.</string>
  <string id="96560" soundid="149182">I meant nothing. It&apos;s just that I was trained fairly well, so I recognize when someone else is skilled.</string>
  <string id="96561" soundid="149183">I am no bandit. Stay on your guard if you want, but I have no desire to test your training. I&apos;ve passed through your village once or twice. I&apos;ve seen your skill.</string>
  <string id="96562" soundid="166418">Yes, this is her. She killed the twisted ones for us.</string>
  <string id="96563">Vase</string>
  <string id="96564" soundid="166419">Yes, this is him. They died because of him; the monsters.</string>
  <string id="96565" soundid="149502"></string>
  <string id="96566">Tell me more about yourself, Hou.</string>
  <string id="96569" soundid="155720">There&apos;s always fire in his eyes. Dark magic burns inside him.</string>
  <string id="96570" soundid="155721">Yeah, but this time it was worse. Better stay out of his way for the next little while. Something really set him off.</string>
  <string id="96571" soundid="149509">Suspicious? Oh, heavens no. Everyone here is extremely legitimate and completely normal. Yes, indeed.</string>
  <string id="96572" soundid="149510">Erm... well, no, not him. He, of course, isn&apos;t usual in the usual... er, sense. Not at all. Everyone else, though, is perfectly legitimate.</string>
  <string id="96573" soundid="149511">General questions? Who has time for such mundane subjects! Go ask one of the scholars. One of the *other* scholars, that is.</string>
  <string id="96574" soundid="149512">Indeed you should. There are many things that I must attend to or science itself will suffer.</string>
  <string id="96575" soundid="149513">I&apos;m still here. Have you figured out what you&apos;re going to do with this poor wretch yet?</string>
  <string id="96576" soundid="149514">You need more proof than my pathetic attempt to pose as a scholar? How about the fact that Lord Rento was out of town when I &quot;bilked&quot; him.</string>
  <string id="96577" soundid="149515">Not that anyone but Lady Rento will confirm that for you. Still, it should be apparent that I&apos;m not some great confidence man.</string>
  <string id="96578" soundid="149516">I&apos;ll admit that I can&apos;t match the bounty on my head, but I could give you half of what they&apos;re offering. I have an idea how I could get out of the city, too.</string>
  <string id="96579" soundid="158226">Remember: Find my body in the palace and destroy it, or you will not be able to defeat Sun Li. Enter the portal. I return to you the life that was so wrongly taken.</string>
  <string id="96580" soundid="149518">We should go see Captain Sen right away if you&apos;re sure. Is now a fair time to go down to the gate to get me out of here?</string>
  <string id="96581" soundid="149519">The only easy way out of this city is through the gate that Sen is guarding, and he&apos;s looking for me.</string>
  <string id="96582" soundid="149520">However, if I disguise myself as a mercenary and sneak past him, I might just get away, but you have to help me by distracting him.</string>
  <string id="96583" soundid="149521">Just tell him that I&apos;ve already escaped, and I&apos;ll get away just fine. I can&apos;t imagine what might go wrong.</string>
  <string id="96584" soundid="149522">I understand. Attend to whatever else you had to do, and if you are still willing to help me, come back and see me.</string>
  <string id="96585" soundid="149523">[Sigh] All the best actors die young.</string>
  <string id="96586" soundid="149524">I suppose I&apos;ll just wait here. There&apos;s no point in running, as you could track me down easily enough.</string>
  <string id="96587" soundid="155722">Wait a minute... you there! Who are you? You can&apos;t be up here!</string>
  <string id="96589" soundid="149527">I hope you&apos;re not here to pester me. I&apos;m a very busy, important, and educated man, you know!</string>
  <string id="96590" soundid="149528">Don&apos;t even bother lying to us. It&apos;s clear you&apos;re no scholar.</string>
  <string id="96591" soundid="149529">Of course not! I&apos;m... oh drat. This isn&apos;t working at all. How did you know?</string>
  <string id="96592" soundid="149530">You&apos;re here to hunt me down, then? Lord Rento has it in for me, and I figured it would come to this.</string>
  <string id="96593" soundid="149215"></string>
  <string id="96594" soundid="149216"></string>
  <string id="96595" soundid="149217">So, there is no discouraging you. You have come to the heart of the Assassins, and you already have enemies. Are you certain you are ready for what you will learn here?</string>
  <string id="96596" soundid="149218">I don&apos;t think the choice is yours anymore. This is my realm, where my demons hide. You will be forced to see them.</string>
  <string id="96597" soundid="149219">You have shown little interest in my warnings, but now you will see.</string>
  <string id="96598" soundid="149220">We have discussed much in our time together, but not everything. I left some things buried, but now you have descended to their level.</string>
  <string id="96599" soundid="149221">Whose side is worthy of having me? Is your motivation so clear now that you walk these halls?</string>
  <string id="96600" soundid="149222">Are you? Are you sure you know what kind of person I am? Is anyone so transparent? Are you?</string>
  <string id="96601" soundid="149223">Go, your new master is waiting. Secure a place near the heart of the Assassins, and you will be near your goal. Grand Inquisitor Jia is key.</string>
  <string id="96605" soundid="149227">It wasn&apos;t always like this. Fear used to be the primary tactic. Destroy the family of one to ensure the loyalty of all. It caused chaos, uprisings. Close allies turning on each other.</string>
  <string id="96606" soundid="157295">Kill Master Shin, my superior.</string>
  <string id="96607" soundid="157296">You are beneath notice, but you have surprising skill. No one will suspect you are planning such a thing, and no one will miss you if I have to kill you for refusing.</string>
  <string id="96610" soundid="165697">I&apos;ll get out of here yet! You&apos;ll see!</string>
  <string id="96612" soundid="149234">You approach the soul extractor. The Assassins want you to create a spirit shard; to crush a life to power a golem puppet. They are very efficient in their brutality now.</string>
  <string id="96613">Why trust me with this? I have only just arrived.</string>
  <string id="96614" soundid="149236">They seek control. There used to be a chance to disobey, when the order given was too harsh... the victims pointlessly innocent. Now there is only obedience.</string>
  <string id="96616" soundid="149238">Just go, the thieves await you. Remember, the deepest mines. They are closed now, for being too... troublesome. That is where you will find what you need.</string>
  <string id="96617" soundid="149239">I was one of the elite, and before that, part of the Order of the Lotus, but I am still shut out of some places.</string>
  <string id="96618" soundid="149240">The deep tombs hold malevolent spirits from a time when the Empire nearly fell. Chaotic and powerful, they hunger for revenge. I&apos;m sorry, but I must be sure of what you are.</string>
  <string id="96619" soundid="149241">Zeng Sai the Tree that Defies the Fire was one of many that threatened to level the Imperial City. The Spirit Monks, your people, stopped them. Or so they claimed.</string>
  <string id="96620" soundid="149242">I gambled that the vengeful spirits of these marauders would sense if you truly are a Spirit Monk. So many people are not what they seem to be. I had to be certain.</string>
  <string id="96626" soundid="149248">The Assassins use slaves for their golems now, in part because of tombs like this. That was a remnant of the Old Empire, the spirit of an ancient invading Horselord.</string>
  <string id="96627" soundid="149249">I had to be certain. I won&apos;t trouble you much longer. Now that you have disrupted Zeng Sai&apos;s spirit, you can take his body from his grave and use it in the extractor.</string>
  <string id="96628" soundid="149250">Even in life his kind were devoid of restraint. His spirit is pure chaos; a shard made using his ancient corpse will cripple the Jade Golem and those it commands.</string>
  <string id="96629" soundid="149251">Present the shard to your master, and it will earn you passage to the inner chambers. There you will find the information you seek, and you can proceed to the palace.</string>
  <string id="96630" soundid="149252">I will make that plain soon enough. Appease your master. When you are ready to enter the inner chambers, I will tell you why your success is so important. </string>
  <string id="96631" soundid="149253">This fortress holds many secrets. Some are valuable, some are dangerous, and some are hidden because the dark is where they belong.</string>
  <string id="96632" soundid="149254">Even if you are acting on selfish instinct, you have to see that leaving your enemy stronger would be foolish. This was a profitable move.</string>
  <string id="96633" soundid="149255">When you finish your master&apos;s other task, present the shard to earn passage to the inner chambers. Inside is the information you need to proceed to the palace.</string>
  <string id="96634" soundid="149256">You could, but I won&apos;t trouble you much longer, anyway. Now that you have disrupted Zeng Sai&apos;s spirit, you can take his body and use it in the extractor.</string>
  <string id="96635" soundid="149257">You are nearing your goal. Grand Inquisitor Jia keeps many secrets in the inner chambers. Enough to appease the Princess and earn your way to the palace.</string>
  <string id="96636" soundid="149258">But you may learn more than she wants to know. I know that I did, many years ago.</string>
  <string id="96637" soundid="149259">You know that Master Li tried to stop his brother and failed. I was not there to witness that, so I only have the details that you are aware of yourself.</string>
  <string id="96638" soundid="149260">Hui in Tien&apos;s Landing told you that in response to that act, Master Li&apos;s wife was condemned to death. She was with child at the time. This I know for certain.</string>
  <string id="96639" soundid="149261">I was there. I was one of the elite ordered to kill Master Li&apos;s family.</string>
  <string id="96640" soundid="149262">Death&apos;s Hand brought the order to kill the family. We were cowards if we could not see the wisdom of his order. It was the will of the Emperor.</string>
  <string id="96641" soundid="149263">I could not question the orders. They could not be wrong.</string>
  <string id="96642" soundid="149264">Dirge was burning, your master had fled, and we stood over a woman who had just given birth. I hesitated... and she was killed.</string>
  <string id="96643" soundid="149265">For years I wondered what kind of creature could issue such an order and what I was for following it. It was easier to be a coward than to question the Empire.</string>
  <string id="96644" soundid="149266">Now I understand, and I hope I have shown you, as well. They broke a sacred trust. I have returned because of that, even though I know what Death&apos;s Hand is.</string>
  <string id="96645" soundid="149267">My fate is sealed, but one secret must live on. I killed them all, my fellow Assassins. I would not let them finish their mission.</string>
  <string id="96646" soundid="149268">Master Li&apos;s child still lives.</string>
  <string id="96647" soundid="149269">You needed to know my role, even if you have not proven to me that you are any more thoughtful than those you pursue. I have secrets that will remain mine.</string>
  <string id="96648" soundid="149270">It shows the depths to which even principled men will sink if the order comes from high enough. If you don&apos;t want to listen, fine. I will keep my secrets.</string>
  <string id="96649" soundid="149271">But heed a simple warning. If your enemy begins to look familiar, it&apos;s not because *they* are changing. It took me a long time to learn that.</string>
  <string id="96650" soundid="149272">I have little use for morals, but honor? I have seen what you will face, seen his power. I ran once.... I hope for your sake you have not shaken my resolve.</string>
  <string id="96651" soundid="149531">I don&apos;t suppose running would do me any good?</string>
  <string id="96652" soundid="149532">This is what passes for justice in the Imperial City?</string>
  <string id="96653" soundid="149533">I was unjustly accused! I simply petitioned Lady Rento for some silver to support me as an actor! Patronage, it&apos;s called.</string>
  <string id="96654" soundid="149534">She agreed, but her husband flew into a rage when he found out, and now I have a death sentence on my head!</string>
  <string id="96655" soundid="149535">It&apos;s not fair, and if you were a decent person, you&apos;d help me get out of this city instead of taking me in. It&apos;s the only way I&apos;ll get clear of Lord Rento&apos;s wrath.</string>
  <string id="96656" soundid="149536">All manner of studies. The History of Dramatic Systems, Applied Theology, and... erm... Celestial Integration! All of these are vital pursuits of knowledge.</string>
  <string id="96657" soundid="149537">Not that you would understand such lofty matters.</string>
  <string id="96658" soundid="149538">Well, you see, drama can be broken down into several systems, and I study the history of those systems over time. How they&apos;ve changed, and that sort of thing.</string>
  <string id="96659" soundid="149281">I trust your plans go well, despite the dangers you face and inflict. Is there something I can do for you?</string>
  <string id="96660" soundid="160238"></string>
  <string id="96661" soundid="160239"></string>
  <string id="96666" soundid="149288">The time is coming, but not yet. There is a great challenge ahead of you, and I will be watching very closely.</string>
  <string id="96667" soundid="154299">Not everyone has to be destroyed. This wasn&apos;t necessary.</string>
  <string id="96668" soundid="154300">The pursuit of power demands sacrifice.</string>
  <string id="96669" soundid="149291">Goodbye.</string>
  <string id="96670" soundid="149292">I told you about your village, and that&apos;s all I&apos;m going to do. Get going. It&apos;s not my business, and you don&apos;t want it to be.</string>
  <string id="96671" soundid="149293">We should leave this place. Death&apos;s Hand obviously didn&apos;t want any survivors. He may send more Lotus Assassins to check on Gao&apos;s men.</string>
  <string id="96672" soundid="149294"></string>
  <string id="96673" soundid="149295">Hold your attack, young student. I am not your enemy. This was... a misunderstanding.</string>
  <string id="96674" soundid="149296">I have tried very hard to go unnoticed, but I also need to eat. I&apos;ve been on the outskirts of your village once or twice to trade goods. I saw you training.</string>
  <string id="96675" soundid="149297">My name is Zu. I have been called Sagacious Zu, if you prefer a title. It&apos;s a name I share with the first emperor, Sagacious Tien.</string>
  <string id="96676" soundid="149298">That is... a personal matter. You&apos;ll have to take my word that I&apos;m above common robbery, if not many other things.</string>
  <string id="96677" soundid="149299">Besides, I have already shown that I have no love for the more common kinds of filth roaming out here.</string>
  <string id="96678" soundid="149300">If you know that name you know the type of men the family employs. I wonder... does their increased presence in the marsh have anything to do with why you are here?</string>
  <string id="96679" soundid="149301">They took someone from your village? That is very brazen, and it explains why they wanted to clear a path through the marsh.</string>
  <string id="96680" soundid="149302">No wonder you came out here as you did; you&apos;re looking to rescue someone. You probably gave no thought to your own safety.</string>
  <string id="96681" soundid="149303">That is very selfless of you. I tend to think more... efficiently.</string>
  <string id="96682" soundid="149304">I did hear something about a camp. They seem to be killing bandits so they won&apos;t be disturbed. There wasn&apos;t much more. I just wanted some peace and quiet.</string>
  <string id="96683" soundid="149305">No. I&apos;m not interested in looking for trouble. I&apos;m sorry, but I have my reasons. As bad as this is, you are better off without my help.</string>
  <string id="96684">Your first special is Radiant Aura, a protective shield.</string>
  <string id="96685" soundid="149307">Dawn Star? I am... familiar with that name. But I still can&apos;t... I have spent a long time avoiding trouble. I don&apos;t want to go looking for it now.</string>
  <string id="96686" soundid="149308">I&apos;m sorry.</string>
  <string id="96687" soundid="149309"></string>
  <string id="96688" soundid="149310">Wait. Dawn Star... your friend... should not suffer because of my reluctance. A group of men went to the north. They had a large pack that was giving them trouble.</string>
  <string id="96689" soundid="149311">That may be where their camp is. There&apos;s no way to leave the marsh in that direction... not on foot, anyway. I will show you. It is easy to get lost.</string>
  <string id="96690" soundid="166479"></string>
  <string id="96691" soundid="149313">You don&apos;t know me. Never forget that.</string>
  <string id="96692" soundid="149314">Now come, we have some catching up to do. We&apos;ll find them. Like I said, they can&apos;t get out in that direction. Not on foot.</string>
  <string id="96693" soundid="149315">I will try not to make you regret it. Your task is probably complicated enough as it is.</string>
  <string id="96696">You act like you know me. I&apos;ve never seen you before.</string>
  <string id="96698">If you are not an enemy, why are you out here?</string>
  <string id="96700">Why were you fighting Gao&apos;s mercenaries?</string>
  <string id="96701">A student has disappeared under strange circumstances.</string>
  <string id="96705">You must know the swamp well. Can you lead me in the right direction?</string>
  <string id="96707">You were right: You&apos;re not a bandit, you&apos;re a coward. I&apos;ll find Dawn Star on my own.</string>
  <string id="96712">Rat Demon</string>
  <string id="96713">Thank you. I knew there was a shred of decency in you.</string>
  <string id="96715">Your assistance is welcome.</string>
  <string id="96717">I will go the way you say, but I will be watching you.</string>
  <string id="96719">Why should I believe you after you refused me before?</string>
  <string id="96720">You changed your mind when I mentioned Dawn Star. Why?</string>
  <string id="96722">Well, if you see a student named Dawn Star, at least show her how to get out of here.</string>
  <string id="96723">I should beat it out of you! Dawn Star deserves better than your cowardice!</string>
  <string id="96725">You seem familiar with their type. Is there anything else you can tell me?</string>
  <string id="96727">My friend is missing. Gao the Lesser may have something to do with it.</string>
  <string id="96729">Just tell me if there are more and if they were carrying someone!</string>
  <string id="96731">Gao&apos;s men seem to be clearing the marsh of outlaws. You could be a bandit.</string>
  <string id="96732">I don&apos;t picture a thoughtful and perceptive emperor fighting in a swamp.</string>
  <string id="96734">Why would my training interest you?</string>
  <string id="96735">I&apos;m in a hurry. Someone was taken from the village by Gao the Lesser.</string>
  <string id="96736">You could be just another bandit. Keep your distance.</string>
  <string id="96738" soundid="149539">Well, it&apos;s the application of the study of theological things, isn&apos;t it? For instance, knowing about spirits and then finding a use for that knowledge.</string>
  <string id="96739" soundid="149540">Well, no, not really. This is the study of applied theology, not the application of studied theology. That&apos;s something else entirely!</string>
  <string id="96740" soundid="149541">Celestial integration means just that; it&apos;s integrated... celestially. Thus the relationship between the heavens and earth is one of integration and, er, celestial.</string>
  <string id="96741" soundid="149542">It&apos;s a very advanced field of research. It would take several lifetimes to understand it properly, which is why my position as a scholar is so irrefutable.</string>
  <string id="96742" soundid="149543">Oh, I doubt it. You don&apos;t look the type for heavy reading.</string>
  <string id="96743" soundid="149544">No, but I am, and I certainly haven&apos;t heard of you.</string>
  <string id="96744" soundid="149545">You&apos;re far too fit to be properly read.</string>
  <string id="96745" soundid="149546">Of course, none of my books are published yet, but as a scholar, and a respected one, I will most certainly pen some marvelous books someday.</string>
  <string id="96746" soundid="149547">Well, yes... unless your theories are astoundingly brilliant, which is the case with me!</string>
  <string id="96747" soundid="149548">A shame. My studies are very important to me. I am a scholar, after all.</string>
  <string id="96748">You&apos;re Creative Yukong, aren&apos;t you?</string>
  <string id="96750">Let&apos;s call it a hunch.</string>
  <string id="96751">Your &quot;studies&quot; weren&apos;t very convincing.</string>
  <string id="96752">That was a pretty sad example of posing as a scholar.</string>
  <string id="96753">It won&apos;t matter in a few moments. You&apos;ll be dead.</string>
  <string id="96755">Lady Rento said the charges weren&apos;t real.</string>
  <string id="96756">How did someone of your skill manage to con a noble anyway?</string>
  <string id="96757">If you run, you&apos;ll only die tired.</string>
  <string id="96762">Whose side are you on, Zu?</string>
  <string id="96764">I am eager to have your help.</string>
  <string id="96773">If you know something that can help, get to the point.</string>
  <string id="96774" soundid="165701">Most people who decided to trail an Inquisitor would have been caught and eliminated within moments. You must be exceptionally skilled. Either that or you&apos;re lying to us.</string>
  <string id="96776" soundid="157314">The Imperial Army is weak, filled with questioning generals that do not know the path to glory. Even we Assassins envy the pure subservience of a golem.</string>
  <string id="96778">Can I ruin their plans *and* get what I need?</string>
  <string id="96779">Why should I trust you?</string>
  <string id="96780">Talk to Scholar Dongow</string>
  <string id="96781">If you have something useful to say, get to it!</string>
  <string id="96782">I&apos;m sick of you interrupting! How are you avoiding capture?</string>
  <string id="96789">Red Minister</string>
  <string id="96792">I trust I no longer need to prove myself to you?</string>
  <string id="96795">What do you mean, you won&apos;t be leaving?</string>
  <string id="96797">So you are staying? Rejoining your old accomplices?</string>
  <string id="96798">A normal shard would earn me passage, too. This battle was pointless.</string>
  <string id="96799">I should kill you where you stand.</string>
  <string id="96802">If you have something to say, Zu, now is the time.</string>
  <string id="96805">That is a remarkable admission. Go on.</string>
  <string id="96807">So you did it? You murdered my Master&apos;s family?</string>
  <string id="96813">The soldier always blames his commander.</string>
  <string id="96814">You take credit, but there is no way for me to verify this.</string>
  <string id="96815">Why does this matter now? What is the point of this?</string>
  <string id="96818">Zu! This better be important to interrupt now!</string>
  <string id="96822">What sort of studies keep you so busy?</string>
  <string id="96824">Why don&apos;t you tell me more about the History of Dramatic Systems?</string>
  <string id="96825">How have these systems changed?</string>
  <string id="96833">Are you ready to talk, Zu? </string>
  <string id="96834" soundid="154301">If a man can&apos;t defend himself, then what good is he, really?</string>
  <string id="96835" soundid="154302">That was... so cruel. I do not know if I have the stomach for this.</string>
  <string id="96836">Goodbye.</string>
  <string id="96837">Inquisitor Lim</string>
  <string id="96840" soundid="149462">[This large tomb is marked with a simple carved blessing board. The dust around the tomb lid looks disturbed, but you see no way to open it at this time.]</string>
  <string id="96841" soundid="149463">[Placing the token from the Lotus Assassin recruiter in a recessed portion of this blessing board causes a barely audible click. The tomb opens.]</string>
  <string id="96842" soundid="149464">You have become Gang&apos;s favorite, and that diminishes the rest of us. The golem army is replacing us as it is. It&apos;s time you learned your place.</string>
  <string id="96843" soundid="149465">I disagree, and so do my companions. It is hard enough to get ahead in this place without you distracting the master!</string>
  <string id="96844" soundid="149466">After you fall, Master Gang will realize he should have focused on us instead of you. That&apos;s all that matters.</string>
  <string id="96845" soundid="149467">If his favorite acolyte falls, that will prove it was a mistake to neglect us! We regain our place, and you are gone!</string>
  <string id="96846" soundid="149468">We want our place back, and if you have to die for that to happen, that&apos;s fine with us!</string>
  <string id="96847" soundid="149469">I am prepared this time! If you fall, Master Gang will have to turn his attention back to us!</string>
  <string id="96848">I did not mean to offend. I am sure there is room for all of us.</string>
  <string id="96850">Master Gang will not appreciate his favorite acolyte being threatened.</string>
  <string id="96852">If more of you want to die at my hand, so be it!</string>
  <string id="96854">I am not ready yet, Master.</string>
  <string id="96855" soundid="149478"></string>
  <string id="96856" soundid="195378">We must move quickly, mortal! I guided you to this place; If I fall, your spirit will be lost forever.</string>
  <string id="96860" soundid="149483">You have your map, and your flyer is ready to go. I don&apos;t know what else you want to do here. I suggest we get on our way as soon as possible.</string>
  <string id="96861" soundid="149484">I&apos;m not really looking forward to getting back to the Imperial City, but it appears both of our paths lead there.</string>
  <string id="96862" soundid="149485">I don&apos;t know what else I can do for you right now. If I can help you, I will, but for now I&apos;ve got nothing new to offer.</string>
  <string id="96865" soundid="149488">I think it&apos;s unwise to trust the Emperor&apos;s daughter. She acts without regard for her station, but she is a slave to it, like we all are. What other truths might she have missed?</string>
  <string id="96866" soundid="149489">She may have good information for you, but I suspect she has her own agenda. Be careful.</string>
  <string id="96868" soundid="195379">I must stop you, mortal. Your choices will have greater impact than the soul of one girl.</string>
  <string id="96869" soundid="188292"></string>
  <string id="96870" soundid="188293"></string>
  <string id="96873">What do you think of our current situation?</string>
  <string id="96876">What exactly is applied theology?</string>
  <string id="96877">Could you give me an example?</string>
  <string id="96878">Celestial integration? You made that one up.</string>
  <string id="96880">Do you have any works I would have read?</string>
  <string id="96884">Wouldn&apos;t you have to have written several books to be a respected scholar?</string>
  <string id="96885">Let&apos;s talk about something else.</string>
  <string id="96886">Have you spotted anyone acting suspicious here?</string>
  <string id="96887">Even the Outlander?</string>
  <string id="96888">Would you mind if I asked you some general questions?</string>
  <string id="96889">I should leave you to your thinking.</string>
  <string id="96890">Do you have any proof that you&apos;re falsely accused?</string>
  <string id="96892">What would my help be worth to you?</string>
  <string id="96893">I think I&apos;ll help you instead of collecting your bounty.</string>
  <string id="96894">I&apos;m ready to help you now.</string>
  <string id="96897">Not right now.</string>
  <string id="96898">I&apos;m not earning any silver talking to you. Time to collect a head.</string>
  <string id="96899">I don&apos;t really want to deal with you right now.</string>
  <string id="96903" soundid="149593">Anyone here could kill me, but there are always witnesses like those men over... uh... like those....</string>
  <string id="96904" soundid="149594">Hmm... it would appear that there would be no witness to my murder other than my slaves. That is... unfortunate. Perhaps we could come to an arrangement.</string>
  <string id="96905" soundid="149595">But... all they can do is hide until there&apos;s a chance of escape. Curse the heavens, I knew dealing with the Assassins would be the death of me!</string>
  <string id="96906" soundid="149596">Monstrous! Fight, slaves! Protect me! It&apos;s your lives too!</string>
  <string id="96907" soundid="149597">Then what? They try to hide until a slim chance for escape comes? Just because I force them to serve me doesn&apos;t mean I treat them poorly. They wouldn&apos;t harm me.</string>
  <string id="96908" soundid="149598">Would you?</string>
  <string id="96909" soundid="149599">Uh... your master demands an answer...?</string>
  <string id="96911">Move somewhere else. *Now!*</string>
  <string id="96912">Too late. I&apos;m killing you and setting your slaves free. I don&apos;t need your store.</string>
  <string id="96913">Too late. I don&apos;t need what you are selling anyway. I&apos;ll kill you *and* your slaves.</string>
  <string id="96914">Actually, it might be amusing to let your slaves kill you. </string>
  <string id="96918" soundid="149608">You know what you have to do. Let&apos;s get on with it.</string>
  <string id="96919" soundid="149609">The Lotus Assassin fortress is dangerous, but we have no other choice if we are to prove Death&apos;s Hand is a traitor.</string>
  <string id="96920" soundid="149610">I chose you because I knew you could handle this. After you get what I need, I will take you to the palace.</string>
  <string id="96921" soundid="149611">I hate the assassins. Can&apos;t they see the strings that pull at them? They are unquestioning, and even believe they do my father&apos;s bidding by following Death&apos;s Hand.</string>
  <string id="96922" soundid="149612">I will expose all of this. Do everything your &quot;masters&quot; ask of you and they will take us into the inner chambers. Then we can prove all of this to my father.</string>
  <string id="96923" soundid="149613">You&apos;ve given me proof... even if I didn&apos;t want to hear it. We must go to the palace and confront my father. I must have an explanation.</string>
  <string id="96924" soundid="149614">I&apos;m ready to guide you to the palace whenever you wish to leave... though I would prefer it to be sooner rather than later.</string>
  <string id="96925" soundid="149615">There is no time for discussion. We should hurry to my father as quickly as possible.</string>
  <string id="96926">What do you think about our current situation?</string>
  <string id="96930" soundid="149620">Too large a subject for your mind to comprehend, I&apos;m sure.</string>
  <string id="96931" soundid="149621">This answer should be interesting. I have a question I would ask of this &quot;scholar&quot; if you would permit me.</string>
  <string id="96932" soundid="149622">Well, of course not. A student of theater are you?</string>
  <string id="96933" soundid="149623">I was just wondering about the recent shift in dramatic presentations away from the customary iterative productions where the fourth wall is regularly deconstructed.</string>
  <string id="96934" soundid="149624">Does the shift towards more codified productions, with barriers established between the presented world and the actual environment, create a more immersive experience?</string>
  <string id="96935" soundid="149625">I... er. Well... ah....</string>
  <string id="96936" soundid="149626">That&apos;s what I thought.</string>
  <string id="96937" soundid="149627">Well, there&apos;s the... new system, of course, but everyone knows that. Then we have the, er, old system, which, as you may surmise, is no longer in use.</string>
  <string id="96938" soundid="149628">That&apos;s a brief summary of my latest work, at any rate.</string>
  <string id="96939" soundid="149629">Oh, it&apos;s all very complex, and I really don&apos;t feel like describing it to you at any length.</string>
  <string id="96940" soundid="149630">That&apos;s how you know I&apos;m a scholar, you see. An unwillingness to share all the information I have.</string>
  <string id="96942">My friend would like to ask you a question, if you don&apos;t mind.</string>
  <string id="96947">Can you outline some of these systems for me?</string>
  <string id="96950">That&apos;s enough about the history of dramatic systems.</string>
  <string id="96951" soundid="149641">Who are we to step in when a personal challenge is issued? Captain Sen could usually take care of himself.</string>
  <string id="96952" soundid="149642">I expect Captain Sen&apos;s death will haunt us with paperwork for months.</string>
  <string id="96953" soundid="149643">With all the flyers, the gate doesn&apos;t see the use it once did.</string>
  <string id="96954" soundid="149644">Have you heard about this Scourge of the South? Sounds like the Lotus Assassins are on edge.</string>
  <string id="96955" soundid="149645">I&apos;m not here to be your guide. Talk to Bai the Outcrier if you need directions.</string>
  <string id="96956" soundid="149646">This city&apos;s usually fairly calm, but there are reports of ghosts in the countryside.</string>
  <string id="96957" soundid="149647">Captain Sen made his share of enemies over the years, but Aishi the Mournful Blade is a foe you could be proud of.</string>
  <string id="96958" soundid="149648">I wonder if they&apos;ll send another officer down here anytime soon. If not, this could be a long shift.</string>
  <string id="96959" soundid="149649">This gateway isn&apos;t as busy as it used to be. People are skittish about traveling.</string>
  <string id="96960" soundid="149650">This whole Scourge of the South thing sounds made up to me. How much trouble could one person cause?</string>
  <string id="96961" soundid="149651">If you need assistance, Bai the Outcrier is near the Imperial Arena.</string>
  <string id="96962" soundid="149652">What is with all these stories about ghosts these days? Has gullibility finally consumed the Empire?</string>
  <string id="96972" soundid="149665"></string>
  <string id="96974" soundid="149667">You... what do you want? Have you come to torture me more? Have you come to see me suffer here unavenged? No one cries for Merchant Bai.</string>
  <string id="96975" soundid="149668">You know of me? You have heard about the pains I suffered in life and this continued torment I have to endure in death?</string>
  <string id="96976" soundid="149669">You... you can understand? You don&apos;t run in terror like the rest. Instead, you talk to me... Perhaps you can help.</string>
  <string id="96977" soundid="149670">I was a merchant in life. Not a rich one, but I made enough to survive. I sold mostly to the poorer sections of the city. My goods weren&apos;t the finest, but they were practical.</string>
  <string id="96978" soundid="149671">At the time, there were a pair of brothers, Si Tsu and Si Ran, who were the terror of the streets. They extorted money and goods from everyone. They tried to extort from me.</string>
  <string id="96979" soundid="149672">When I wouldn&apos;t give them what they wanted, they... they decided to make an example of me. They killed me... and mutilated me... and left me dead in that alley.</string>
  <string id="96980" soundid="149673">They terrorized the city for weeks after that, but they were finally run down. That might have been where it ended, justice done, but it wasn&apos;t....</string>
  <string id="96981" soundid="149674">They were buried here, with me! Their deaths, execution by beheading, were harsh enough that they have risen again!</string>
  <string id="96982" soundid="149675">My spirit cannot rest quiet with them here. Even now, in death, they mock me and torment me as they did in my final moments of life. They drive me mad!</string>
  <string id="96983" soundid="149676">Yes! Yes! If my killers are at last removed from this world, their spirits will no longer torment me! You... you must find a way to defeat them and drive them from this place.</string>
  <string id="96984" soundid="149677">They were common criminals, so they were not given a normal burial. They were dumped in a communal grave underground, to the south. I&apos;m sure you can find them.</string>
  <string id="96985" soundid="149678">Thank you, stranger, if you can truly help me. If... if you do, I&apos;ll show you something that even Shen hasn&apos;t found yet.</string>
  <string id="96986" soundid="149679">They... they were. They caught me in an alley and demanded my goods or my life. My goods *are* my life. How could they take one or the other?</string>
  <string id="96987" soundid="149680">You know nothing, then! Begone if you&apos;re of no help to me!</string>
  <string id="96988" soundid="149681">You... you seek to destroy me, as well? You&apos;re no different from them! But... but I can fight you! And kill you! And I will!</string>
  <string id="96990" soundid="149683">You again? What do you want? To make my suffering and tormented existence even worse? Be gone with you if you&apos;re no help!</string>
  <string id="96991" soundid="149684">Have... have you managed to defeat them at last?</string>
  <string id="96992" soundid="149685">Please, find them and destroy them. They have made my death unbearable, even after they took my life!</string>
  <string id="96993" soundid="149686">Thank you! Thank you! I feel as if a great weight has been lifted from my... er... spirit.</string>
  <string id="96994" soundid="149687">Here, let me show you this.</string>
  <string id="96996" soundid="149689">Something Shen hasn&apos;t found yet. I hope you use it well, and... thank you.</string>
  <string id="96998" soundid="149691">This is all that binds me to this tormented existence! Please, stranger, find them and destroy them so they torment me no longer!</string>
  <string id="96999">You are Merchant Bai?</string>
  <string id="97000">Tell me what is bothering you.</string>
  <string id="97003">What did you do?</string>
  <string id="97007">If I help you, will you rest peacefully?</string>
  <string id="97011">Where can I find them?</string>
  <string id="97012">If you&apos;re mad, I&apos;ll just destroy you.</string>
  <string id="97013">So they killed you?</string>
  <string id="97014">I heard they were killed as well.</string>
  <string id="97016">I really don&apos;t care about your problems.</string>
  <string id="97017">I really don&apos;t care what&apos;s wrong with you.</string>
  <string id="97019">Why are you causing trouble here?</string>
  <string id="97020">I&apos;ve been paid by Shen to put you down.</string>
  <string id="97023">I haven&apos;t found them yet.</string>
  <string id="97025">I have defeated them.</string>
  <string id="97030">If you don&apos;t go back, your master will starve.</string>
  <string id="97031">I don&apos;t have time for this right now.</string>
  <string id="97033">It&apos;s the truth.</string>
  <string id="97037">Forgive her.</string>
  <string id="97044">You two can make up on your own time.</string>
  <string id="97045">I&apos;ll just leave you two alone for a bit.</string>
  <string id="97047">If you can&apos;t accept the truth, then there is no hope for you.</string>
  <string id="97048">I won&apos;t let you.</string>
  <string id="97051">Take her, then.</string>
  <string id="97055">Then I&apos;ll end both of yours!</string>
  <string id="97058">The fish is mightier than the sword.</string>
  <string id="97060" soundid="150010">My family would have named him after... after I passed beyond. Shen must know, or there must be some way to find him. I remember so little since I... I passed away.</string>
  <string id="97061" soundid="150011">He was my darling child. My only son. I had planned to name him... I... I don&apos;t remember what it was. So much of the past is unclear to me now.</string>
  <string id="97062" soundid="150012">I remember... There was an... aunt? An uncle? Or was it his father? I... I don&apos;t remember it any clearer than that. Every time I try to grasp it, it slips away.</string>
  <string id="97063" soundid="150013">I&apos;d... I&apos;d have to see his grave. I&apos;d have to see it with my own eyes. And look inside... If he was dead, if he was here, I&apos;d see the tiny spark of his spirit there, calling to me.</string>
  <string id="97064" soundid="150014">But... if it isn&apos;t... if it isn&apos;t him. I&apos;m so close to breaking completely now. The madness that has overtaken all the other ghosts here has its claws in me as well.</string>
  <string id="97065" soundid="150015">My despair is so great that if you lie, if you prove false, then all hope would be lost, and I fear I would descend into madness from which there is no return.</string>
  <string id="97066" soundid="150016">Are... are you sure? I know I wouldn&apos;t be able to stand it if I was separated from him again. Please don&apos;t let this madness consume me. Are you sure it is the right grave?</string>
  <string id="97068" soundid="150018">I... I cannot read. Which... which one is he?</string>
  <string id="97070" soundid="150020">This... this is a woman! Who is this woman?</string>
  <string id="97071" soundid="150021">You... you lied to me after all! Everyone... everyone lies and takes my precious things away!</string>
  <string id="97072" soundid="150022">I... I can&apos;t take... this....</string>
  <string id="97075" soundid="150025">This... this boy... he is not mine. He is not related to me!</string>
  <string id="97077" soundid="150027">This... this old man. He can&apos;t be my son!</string>
  <string id="97078">You&apos;re Miss Chan?</string>
  <string id="97081">What has Shen done with your baby?</string>
  <string id="97083">Your baby is dead, Miss Chan.</string>
  <string id="97084">Whether you like it or not, he&apos;s dead.</string>
  <string id="97087">What can you tell me about your baby?</string>
  <string id="97090">How would I prove your baby is here?</string>
  <string id="97093">I think I know which grave belongs to your baby.</string>
  <string id="97094">Yes. I&apos;ll show you.</string>
  <string id="97096">This is him. Chan Han.</string>
  <string id="97102">This is him. Chan Li.</string>
  <string id="97105">This is him. Chan Deng.</string>
  <string id="97108">This is him. Chan Tuo.</string>
  <string id="97113">I need more time to think about it.</string>
  <string id="97114">I&apos;ll look for your baby.</string>
  <string id="97115">How can I prove to you that he is dead?</string>
  <string id="97116">I&apos;ll go out and look, then.</string>
  <string id="97118">How can I help you find your baby?</string>
  <string id="97119">Your baby was a boy?</string>
  <string id="97121">I&apos;ll speak with Shen.</string>
  <string id="97123">You&apos;re dead. You know that, right?</string>
  <string id="97125">Shen has paid me to put you to rest, spirit.</string>
  <string id="97126">I&apos;m putting you down. Now.</string>
  <string id="97128">How can I prove to you that your baby is dead?</string>
  <string id="97129">I haven&apos;t found your baby yet.</string>
  <string id="97130">I don&apos;t care about your dumb ox!</string>
  <string id="97145">[Intuition] The other ox will be lonely if you don&apos;t go back.</string>
  <string id="97177">Student</string>
  <string id="97219">Get out of here, or I&apos;ll kill the other ox myself!</string>
  <string id="97224" soundid="151287">Thank you for getting rid of that... thing. Business is bad enough without that ogre scaring away my customers.</string>
  <string id="97225" soundid="151288">Here&apos;s a little something to thank you. It&apos;s not much, but it&apos;s about all I can afford these days.</string>
  <string id="97255" soundid="151805">We are here. Have you any other directions? Perhaps I should sweep the ground before you walk on it.</string>
  <string id="97256" soundid="151806">Please, Princess. This slavery is bad enough without you making light of it.</string>
  <string id="97270" soundid="151807">I would agree.</string>
  <string id="97271">I... I&apos;m very sorry... Zi Bao got away.</string>
  <string id="97272">Get out of here!</string>
  <string id="97273">Here it is!</string>
  <string id="97308">I should have known that wouldn&apos;t work?</string>
  <string id="97309">Ha! That was a good one.</string>
  <string id="97310">I&apos;ve been practicing!</string>
  <string id="97311">Feel my sting!</string>
  <string id="97312">Let&apos;s go!</string>
  <string id="97313">I&apos;ll win this one!</string>
  <string id="97314">Time is up for you.</string>
  <string id="97323">Aishi</string>
  <string id="97326">Man</string>
  <string id="97588" soundid="150625">Your own ancestors would not approve. The dead do not like to be disturbed.</string>
  <string id="97589" soundid="150626">Ya Zhen: Ah... and another one begins.</string>
  <string id="97593" soundid="151808">What is your next wish, Master?</string>
  <string id="97595" soundid="150632">Please... please. You&apos;ve got to help me. It&apos;s my son!</string>
  <string id="97596" soundid="150633">Oh, it&apos;s terrible. He&apos;s back there behind the arena, and he needs your help.</string>
  <string id="97597" soundid="150634">No... please. Please... my boy is innocent and just needs your help. You&apos;re strong; you can help him!</string>
  <string id="97598" soundid="150635">Thank you... thank you so much. Just follow me.</string>
  <string id="97599" soundid="150636">But... who will help my son?</string>
  <string id="97600">What&apos;s wrong with your son?</string>
  <string id="97601">Sorry, I don&apos;t have time. There are guards nearby who could help.</string>
  <string id="97602">Get away from me, crazy lady.</string>
  <string id="97603">Lead on. It sounds like there&apos;s no time to waste.</string>
  <string id="97604">Hold on. Why would you let your son play behind the arena?</string>
  <string id="97605">I don&apos;t have time for this. Leave me alone.</string>
  <string id="97606" soundid="150643">Hey, she did it. I guess we won&apos;t get to slice up the boy after all.</string>
  <string id="97607" soundid="150644">That remains to be seen. Keep the boy... and the woman. We may yet have need of them.</string>
  <string id="97608" soundid="150645">Hold your tongue, or I&apos;ll have it removed... before I kill you. We&apos;ve been looking for you, or someone who looks like you.</string>
  <string id="97609" soundid="150646">Killing Gao the Greater was a very big mistake. We have other leaders and other means. The Guild is not going to just... go away.</string>
  <string id="97610" soundid="150647">Maybe you do, and maybe you don&apos;t. It really doesn&apos;t matter. You fit the description... roughly. That&apos;s all that matters.</string>
  <string id="97611" soundid="150648">We know you just arrived here in the city, and you fit the description... roughly.</string>
  <string id="97612" soundid="150649">I&apos;m just glad we found you first. There&apos;s a lot of people looking for you.</string>
  <string id="97613" soundid="150650">Come on out boys... it&apos;s time to gut this pig!</string>
  <string id="97614" soundid="150651">Yes... I&apos;m afraid my boys need a little... release. You understand I&apos;m sure.</string>
  <string id="97615" soundid="150652">Go slowly boys... make sure you savor the moment.</string>
  <string id="97617">Who are you? What do you want?</string>
  <string id="97618">Let the boy and his mother go!</string>
  <string id="97619">Only cowards use women and children to protect themselves!</string>
  <string id="97621">I don&apos;t know what you&apos;re talking about.</string>
  <string id="97623">What makes you think I killed Gao?</string>
  <string id="97625">Don&apos;t be a fool. If I can kill Gao, I can kill you too.</string>
  <string id="97629" soundid="150666">Hold up a minute there, friend. There&apos;s a fee for passing through. It&apos;s not much, just a few silver will do.</string>
  <string id="97630" soundid="150667">You don&apos;t get it. We&apos;ll get our fee... one way or another. You pay... or you don&apos;t leave.</string>
  <string id="97631" soundid="150668">Because I said so. Is that good enough for you? You pay, or you don&apos;t leave. Got it?</string>
  <string id="97632" soundid="150669">You don&apos;t understand... you&apos;re already here. It doesn&apos;t matter which way you want to go... you pay, or you don&apos;t leave.</string>
  <string id="97633" soundid="150670">We&apos;re not alone neither. We&apos;ve got friends... but if we have to call them over, then the fee goes up. Everybody likes to get paid.</string>
  <string id="97634" soundid="150671">[Failure] Nice try. It&apos;ll take more than that to scare us off.</string>
  <string id="97635" soundid="150672">[Success] Okay, okay! We have to try don&apos;t we? It&apos;s the only way to make a living around here.</string>
  <string id="97636" soundid="150673">C&apos;mon. Let&apos;s go find someplace else to collect.</string>
  <string id="97637">Transcribed leaf note</string>
  <string id="97638">A note scribbled by Kang that he copied off of a leaf floating around Lord Lao&apos;s Furnace. It suggests that one of the machine&apos;s configurations may be found in a chest in &quot;the cages of animals kept for sport.&quot;</string>
  <string id="97640">The Test of the Closed Fist</string>
  <string id="97641">I suggest you move along before you get hurt.</string>
  <string id="97642">Why is there a fee?</string>
  <string id="97643">I&apos;ll just head back, then.</string>
  <string id="97645">[Intimidation] Move, or I&apos;ll gladly kill you and your friends. No charge.</string>
  <string id="97648">Patched together note</string>
  <string id="97649">I&apos;m going to clean the ground with you!</string>
  <string id="97653">Gravestones</string>
  <string id="97657" soundid="150771">Yes, of course. I have some very... interesting items now.</string>
  <string id="97658" soundid="150772">Of course, of course. Thank you for your help. Come and see me if you&apos;re interested in more of the same. Good fortune to you.</string>
  <string id="97659">Who are you and why do you want to know?</string>
  <string id="97660">Yes, I own it. Why do you want to know?</string>
  <string id="97661">That&apos;s none of your business.</string>
  <string id="97664">And now you want me to help you, I suppose.</string>
  <string id="97665">What exactly do you want me to do?</string>
  <string id="97670">Enough! Just tell me what you want me to do.</string>
  <string id="97671">It is a little rickety actually.</string>
  <string id="97673" soundid="156182">Begone if you&apos;re of no help to me!</string>
  <string id="97674">Kang&apos;s right, this flyer is the best of its kind.</string>
  <string id="97677">You&apos;ve got a deal.</string>
  <string id="97678">I&apos;ll just be leaving now.</string>
  <string id="97679">I&apos;m not interested right now. Thanks.</string>
  <string id="97680">I&apos;m not interested.</string>
  <string id="97683">Let me see your upgrades.</string>
  <string id="97684">I want to do the next mission.</string>
  <string id="97685">I need to go right now. Goodbye.</string>
  <string id="97688" soundid="150804">Get the prefect home safely and I will reward you well. The prefect has also told me to offer you extra silver for destroying as many of the raiders as you can.</string>
  <string id="97689" soundid="150805">The prefect is anxious to be going. Here&apos;s your wind map, and remember, protect the prefect&apos;s flyer at all costs.</string>
  <string id="97691" soundid="150807">This next mission is close to my heart. My family lives in a remote province some distance from here.</string>
  <string id="97692" soundid="150808">The area has been cut off from the main trade routes due to unusually cold weather and bold pirates. I need you to get supplies to my family.</string>
  <string id="97693" soundid="150809">The prefect was so impressed by your assistance, he&apos;s offered the use of his own flyer. It&apos;s equipped to drop supplies, instead of bombs. It&apos;s slower, but it&apos;s tough.</string>
  <string id="97694" soundid="150810">You&apos;ll have to get the supplies as close to the huts and houses as you can to make it worth your while. Take out as many pirates as you can and I&apos;ll gladly pay you extra.</string>
  <string id="97695" soundid="150811">Remember, drop the supplies as close to the homes as possible. Good luck.</string>
  <string id="97696">I&apos;ve decided it would just be easier to destroy you instead.</string>
  <string id="97697">Pay Gambler Daoshen&apos;s Fee</string>
  <string id="97698">Sweet Poison Lyn is is the back room, past where Qui and the fighters rest up between matches. Speak to her and pay Daoshen&apos;s fee of five hundred silver on his behalf and he&apos;ll happily pay you back.</string>
  <string id="97699">Gambler Daoshen, who runs his game in the common room of the tavern in the Imperial Arena, needs someone to pay a five hundred silver fee to a Guild representative named Sweet Poison Lyn. Once the fee is paid, he&apos;ll be able to safely play for larger stakes.</string>
  <string id="97701">I think I should destroy you and put you to rest.</string>
  <string id="97703" soundid="150819">Excellent work. The prefect is happy to be home safe, no doubt.</string>
  <string id="97704" soundid="150820">You did an excellent job clearing out the raiders as well. You&apos;ll get quite a bit extra for that.</string>
  <string id="97705" soundid="150821">I see you were able to dispatch a few of the raiders on your way. I&apos;ll top up your payment a little for that.</string>
  <string id="97706" soundid="150822">The raiders gave you some trouble, I see, but at least the prefect is safe. Here&apos;s the amount I promised you.</string>
  <string id="97707" soundid="150823">Would you like to see some of my upgrades, or could I interest you in doing another mission for me?</string>
  <string id="97708" soundid="150824">There you are! I was wondering if the pirates or the weather had finally stopped you.</string>
  <string id="97709" soundid="150825">You did an excellent job getting the supplies to the people of my province.</string>
  <string id="97710" soundid="150826">I&apos;m glad you were able to get the supplies there. I only wish you could have gotten more to them.</string>
  <string id="97711" soundid="150827">It seems the mission was almost a complete failure. I fear the people of my province will have to make do until the weather clears.</string>
  <string id="97712" soundid="150828">Thankfully, the pirates will no longer be a problem for them.</string>
  <string id="97713" soundid="150829">If only you could have gotten rid of a few more pirates, but at least you were able to destroy some of them.</string>
  <string id="97714" soundid="150830">The pirates were just too much for you it would seem. I hope my friends and family can resist them a bit longer.</string>
  <string id="97717" soundid="150833">I regret I have no more missions for you, but I&apos;m always here if you require upgrades for your flyer. Thank you again.</string>
  <string id="97718" soundid="150834">Hello again. Would you like to see some upgrades for your flyer?</string>
  <string id="97719" soundid="150835">As you wish. I will be here if you change your mind.</string>
  <string id="97720">Who are you again?</string>
  <string id="97721">Yes, I&apos;d like to hear your proposal.</string>
  <string id="97722">No, I&apos;m still not interested.</string>
  <string id="97730" soundid="156189">Curse it all! The wench betrayed us!</string>
  <string id="97735" soundid="156190">The boy will suffer once we&apos;re done with you! So will she, for that matter.</string>
  <string id="97736">Take the Fee to Sweet Poison Lyn</string>
  <string id="97737">With a five hundred silver purse in trust. Go the back room of the Imperial Arena, past the room where the fighters rest up between matches, and speak with Sweet Poison Lyn about Gambler Daoshen.</string>
  <string id="97738">Gambler Daoshen of the Imperial Arena needs a five hundred silver fee taken to Sweet Poison Lyn, a Guild representative, so that he can raise the stakes on his game. You&apos;ve talked Daoshen into giving you the fee up front, and he&apos;s done so in a winnings purse clearly marked as his. This little twist of fate opens up some intriguing possibilities.</string>
  <string id="97758" soundid="150874">And I will take that mishap with the suspended golem as a reminder to always adequately reward you. I would not want our agreement to go sour.</string>
  <string id="97759" soundid="150875">We see them daily at about this time, but they have not arrived yet. Probably delayed in the Necropolis.</string>
  <string id="97760">Is there a shipment of slaves due soon?</string>
  <string id="97761" soundid="150877">Perhaps. They are not often late unless delayed by spirits outside in the Necropolis. Shin makes a point of demanding they be on time.</string>
  <string id="97762">Is there a shipment of slaves due soon?</string>
  <string id="97763">Is there a shipment of slaves due soon?</string>
  <string id="97770" soundid="150897"></string>
  <string id="97771" soundid="158334">I... I don&apos;t believe it! Thank you, mighty one! You have no idea what this means to me.</string>
  <string id="97772" soundid="158335">I have no silver to offer you, but I&apos;ll give you a discount on all the goods I sell. Would you like to see what I have in stock?</string>
  <string id="97773" soundid="158336">I have no silver to offer you, but I&apos;ll give you a discount on all the goods I sell... as soon as the dam is closed and I can replenish my stock.</string>
  <string id="97774" soundid="158337">Tong and his friends are usually off getting drunk near the store houses, past Beggar&apos;s Pier in the southeast end of town. Be careful. I&apos;ve heard they&apos;re good with their fists.</string>
  <string id="97775" soundid="158338">The figurine isn&apos;t worth much, but it belonged to my mother. I wish there was some way to get it back.</string>
  <string id="97776" soundid="158339">Of course. I understand. Your problems, like Sheng&apos;s, are far greater than mine. But, if you should happen to run into Tong, please think of me.</string>
  <string id="97777" soundid="158340">If you convince him to return my mother&apos;s figurine, I&apos;ll give you a discount on all my merchandise when it arrives.</string>
  <string id="97778" soundid="158341">But until Minister Sheng finds someone to close the Great Dam, the river is too low for any trade to come into town, and I can&apos;t replenish my stock.</string>
  <string id="97781">Have you told the authorities about this?</string>
  <string id="97782">This isn&apos;t my problem.</string>
  <string id="97784">I don&apos;t have time for this.</string>
  <string id="97785">I want to ask about something else.</string>
  <string id="97787">I have your figurine here.</string>
  <string id="97789">Where can I find Tong?</string>
  <string id="97790">Maybe you should give it back now.</string>
  <string id="97791">[Charm] Your mother wouldn&apos;t like you taking someone else&apos;s things.</string>
  <string id="97793">[Intuition] The figurine was a gift from Cheung&apos;s own mother.</string>
  <string id="97795">[Intimidation] Give the figurine back, shameless dog!</string>
  <string id="97797">Hey, it&apos;s okay. Don&apos;t cry.</string>
  <string id="97798" soundid="150925">Three years. Three long years of tracing these slavers to their master, only to find that there were more above him.</string>
  <string id="97799" soundid="150926">The consolation lies in finding others who share my goals. I did not expect to be lucky enough to find a friend in this place.</string>
  <string id="97800" soundid="150927">I also found a strong ally, but I&apos;m not sure if the greater consolation lies in your ability, determination, or beauty. I look forward to finding out.</string>
  <string id="97801" soundid="150928">That makes two of us. I&apos;ll keep you informed as we deal with Gao&apos;s masters. They&apos;ll be harder to chase down.</string>
  <string id="97802" soundid="150929">Of course. I wouldn&apos;t dream of breaking you down into components. Treating people like commodities was Gao&apos;s business, not mine.</string>
  <string id="97803" soundid="150930">Oh, I never get ideas, only impressions. Don&apos;t worry about what I will accomplish. Finding Gao was only the beginning.</string>
  <string id="97804" soundid="150931">Why? Because I... we have succeeded at a goal that I&apos;ve been working towards for three years?</string>
  <string id="97805" soundid="150932">I feel fine, but determined. Our work isn&apos;t done, but we&apos;ve taken a small step by removing that stain upon the Empire&apos;s honor.</string>
  <string id="97806" soundid="150933">Fair enough. Don&apos;t worry, I know what lies ahead. I tracked my daughter&apos;s killer for three years, after all.</string>
  <string id="97807" soundid="150934">Now you look here, missy! In my day, we respected our elders! I&apos;m sorry, I can&apos;t do that voice justice. I&apos;m only, what, eight years older than you?</string>
  <string id="97808" soundid="150935">Of course, eight years make a difference when you lose three of them chasing your daughter&apos;s killer.</string>
  <string id="97809" soundid="150936">Gao&apos;s slavers took my daughter, Pinmei, and I was able to follow them. Fortunately, they didn&apos;t cover their tracks. I chased them down, trying to reach her.</string>
  <string id="97810" soundid="150937">I was too late. Pinmei was spirited, and I&apos;m sure she fought them. I believe they decided she was too much trouble and killed her. Five years old... and they ran her through.</string>
  <string id="97811" soundid="150938">I found her dead by the roadside and stopped my pursuit. By the time I cared to continue my chase, the slavers were long gone.</string>
  <string id="97812" soundid="150939">It&apos;s... fine. Thank you for your concern, but for the most part I have come to terms with her death.</string>
  <string id="97813" soundid="150940">There are ways to track men who don&apos;t want to be found. It&apos;s all a matter of time and dedication.</string>
  <string id="97814" soundid="150941">Is that what you&apos;re doing? Chasing after your Master without a thought for the others in your town? Yes, I&apos;ve heard about the attack.</string>
  <string id="97815" soundid="150942">I&apos;m sorry. That wasn&apos;t fair. You&apos;re right. I could have saved myself three years if I&apos;d just run those bastards down.</string>
  <string id="97816" soundid="150943">Why dwell on this? Gao is dead, and perhaps Pinmei has found some peace. That&apos;s what really matters. That and what we still have to accomplish.</string>
  <string id="97817" soundid="150944">You&apos;re right, but we have to pick our time, and now isn&apos;t it. We can talk about this later </string>
  <string id="97818" soundid="150945">We&apos;ll talk about Gao later. We have much to do, and none of it will be accomplished if we stand here hashing over the past.</string>
  <string id="97819" soundid="150946">That wasn&apos;t my intent! I don&apos;t even remember how we got on to the subject of Pinmei!</string>
  <string id="97820" soundid="150947">I almost never talk about her, and then I open up to you and you throw it in my face. Let&apos;s just... forget it and get on with what we&apos;re doing.</string>
  <string id="97821" soundid="150948">All right. If you want to bring it up again, it might do me some good to talk, but we do have more important matters right now.</string>
  <string id="97822" soundid="150949">I should apologize. I can be sensitive about my daughter, and your comment that I was &quot;whining&quot; touched a nerve, but I shouldn&apos;t have snapped at you.</string>
  <string id="97823" soundid="150950">That would be best. I don&apos;t normally hold a grudge; hunting Gao for three years was a unique circumstance.</string>
  <string id="97824" soundid="150951">I don&apos;t think of you as one likely to accuse me of whining, but we&apos;re all full of surprises, aren&apos;t we?</string>
  <string id="97825" soundid="150952">I&apos;ll note that. I wouldn&apos;t want you getting too much of an advantage. Your smile&apos;s already distracting enough.</string>
  <string id="97826" soundid="150953">You have an odd way of handling people, but we all have our quirks.</string>
  <string id="97827" soundid="150954">Thank you. I&apos;m pretty resistant to most jokes at my expense, but some subjects....</string>
  <string id="97828" soundid="150955">I never really answered your question about how I tracked Gao down. It&apos;s not that bad a story, if you still want to hear it.</string>
  <string id="97829" soundid="150956">I&apos;ll make you a deal: If you start to look bored, I&apos;ll throw in a Lotus Assassin or two to spice things up.</string>
  <string id="97830" soundid="150957">I lost the men who murdered my daughter, but there are other ways to track men besides following their footprints, something I know all too well.</string>
  <string id="97831" soundid="150958">Eight years ago, when my wife passed away giving birth to Pinmei, I decided to settle down. Before that, my life was less... stable.</string>
  <string id="97832" soundid="150959">You should have seen Pinmei&apos;s mother fight. We met because we both liked to operate outside of the law.</string>
  <string id="97833" soundid="150960">Curses, you&apos;ve uncovered my secret. Actually, the truth isn&apos;t far off. My wife and I met because we both operated outside of the law.</string>
  <string id="97834" soundid="150961">Not every girl likes pompous nobles or stuffy scholars. She and I saw eye-to-eye on many things, including living life to the fullest.</string>
  <string id="97835" soundid="150962">You would have liked her if you&apos;d met her. As long as she wasn&apos;t slipping through the upper window of your house to steal all your valuables.</string>
  <string id="97836" soundid="150963">You remind me of her. Though, she was flighty where you are intense, and she fought with nothing approaching your skill. You also don&apos;t burgle people&apos;s houses.</string>
  <string id="97837" soundid="150964">Not really. She was a wonderful woman, but she was taken from me long ago. I meant the comparison as a compliment.</string>
  <string id="97838" soundid="150965">I called in a lot of favors tracking down Gao, but you never know.</string>
  <string id="97839" soundid="150966">As I followed the trail of various slave-trading rings, I started seeing connections. Strangely enough, all of them seemed tied to the Lotus Assassins.</string>
  <string id="97840" soundid="150967">They would observe. They would ask the same questions I had, but they did nothing.</string>
  <string id="97841" soundid="150968">Every slave-trading ring I saw, the Assassins were at least aware of.</string>
  <string id="97842" soundid="150969">Apparently not. They seemed to be aware of all of these slave rings, and yet they did nothing about them.</string>
  <string id="97843" soundid="150970">I started drawing conclusions, and when I heard that Gao the Greater was dealing heavily with them, I started looking into him.</string>
  <string id="97844" soundid="150971">By approaching it from the top down--Assassins to Gao to slavers--I managed to piece together his involvement and learn the location of his base.</string>
  <string id="97845" soundid="150972">I don&apos;t have an answer to that, though I would very much like to know. If they support these slavers....</string>
  <string id="97846" soundid="150973">My home was not far from Tien&apos;s Landing, so I am certain that it was Gao&apos;s men who took my daughter.</string>
  <string id="97847" soundid="150974">Meeting you, and being given this chance to take the fight higher, I&apos;m glad I chased that bastard down.</string>
  <string id="97848" soundid="150975">It&apos;s good to be here. There&apos;s much ahead of us, but at least we have allies... and friends.</string>
  <string id="97849" soundid="150976">That will make the road easier. Speaking of which, we should keep moving, don&apos;t you think?</string>
  <string id="97850" soundid="150977">You&apos;re right! We should keep moving while we still have surprise on our side.</string>
  <string id="97851" soundid="150978">I know. There&apos;s some peace in Gao&apos;s death, but not enough. People are still being taken as slaves, and much worse happening in this Empire. I won&apos;t forget that.</string>
  <string id="97852" soundid="150979">Fair enough. Ask me later, if you still want to hear about it.</string>
  <string id="97853" soundid="150980">If you&apos;re not interested, that&apos;s fine by me. We have plenty of other things to do than to stand around and talk.</string>
  <string id="97854" soundid="154933">Good luck. Third Brother is worthy opponent. Do not underestimate him.</string>
  <string id="97855">How does that make you feel?</string>
  <string id="97856">How long were you searching for him?</string>
  <string id="97858">I look forward to hearing which of those you settle on.</string>
  <string id="97859">For us to be allies, you have to accept the whole package.</string>
  <string id="97860">Don&apos;t get any ideas. You&apos;re only here because you&apos;re useful.</string>
  <string id="97861">You&apos;re not going to fall into a depression on me, are you?</string>
  <string id="97862">You&apos;re right. That&apos;s a reason to celebrate.</string>
  <string id="97863">I just want you focused. We have a long road ahead of us.</string>
  <string id="97864">Well, it can happen to men your age. They start acting odd when their youth slides away.</string>
  <string id="97866">How did you track Gao?</string>
  <string id="97869">That&apos;s terrible. I&apos;m sorry to bring this up.</string>
  <string id="97871">How did you eventually catch up with them?</string>
  <string id="97873">You should have chased them down. Vengeance is more effective than sorrow.</string>
  <string id="97876">Things like this are important to dwell upon.</string>
  <string id="97878">You still haven&apos;t told me how you found Gao.</string>
  <string id="97879">Are you going to whine about your daughter every time I talk to you?</string>
  <string id="97881">I don&apos;t really feel like talking about this right now.</string>
  <string id="97883">It was a harsh thing for me to say. I apologize as well.</string>
  <string id="97884">Let&apos;s call it water under the bridge and forget about it.</string>
  <string id="97886">I didn&apos;t picture you as one likely to apologize.</string>
  <string id="97887">I like to keep people on their toes. It keeps them honest.</string>
  <string id="97890">I shouldn&apos;t tease you. I was wrong to call you a whiner.</string>
  <string id="97892">One last surprise: I don&apos;t really care about your past. Let&apos;s drop the subject.</string>
  <string id="97893">Snap or not, I doesn&apos;t really matter to me.</string>
  <string id="97894">I&apos;d be quite interested.</string>
  <string id="97895">Tell me, but it had better be exciting.</string>
  <string id="97898">It seemed odd that a doting father would have your skills.</string>
  <string id="97900">I&apos;ve got it! You were raised by a traveling circus troupe.</string>
  <string id="97902">How did you meet your wife if your life was so chaotic?</string>
  <string id="97904">Don&apos;t you feel strange comparing me to your dead wife?</string>
  <string id="97905">Your connections in the underworld tracked down Gao?</string>
  <string id="97906">Could the people you know help us in any way?</string>
  <string id="97908">How were the Assassins connected?</string>
  <string id="97910">What kind of connections did you see?</string>
  <string id="97912">Is there anything they&apos;re not involved with?</string>
  <string id="97915">How do you know Gao&apos;s slavers were the ones who took your daughter?</string>
  <string id="97916">Did you learn anything else? Why are the Assassins ignoring the slave traders?</string>
  <string id="97919">I&apos;m glad I could help, and I&apos;m happy to have your company.</string>
  <string id="97921">Just remember that things will only get harder.</string>
  <string id="97922">Don&apos;t let your anger slip because Gao&apos;s dead. We need that fire.</string>
  <string id="97923">There&apos;s no time to hear it now.</string>
  <string id="97924">I don&apos;t really care about your past. You&apos;re here because you&apos;re useful now.</string>
  <string id="97925" soundid="154934">What are you doing here? Is Master Smiling Hawk... did you deal with him?</string>
  <string id="97926" soundid="154935">But nevertheless... you have chosen the wrong master to follow. I cannot allow you to help Master Smiling Hawk... you will be stopped!</string>
  <string id="97936">Lotus Assassin</string>
  <string id="97939">Man</string>
  <string id="97942">Man</string>
  <string id="97945">Woman</string>
  <string id="97948">Woman</string>
  <string id="97954">Spirit Font</string>
  <string id="97958" soundid="151338"></string>
  <string id="97960">You cannot switch followers during combat.</string>
  <string id="97961">Commoner</string>
  <string id="97964">Pirate</string>
  <string id="97967">Pirate</string>
  <string id="97970" soundid="156363">I am pleased by your directness. You are the Imperial Champion--impressive enough--but now you will be so much more. Proceed to our fortress.</string>
  <string id="97972">Pirate</string>
  <string id="97976" soundid="155788">Look, you can&apos;t trust Kai Lan. I know he was probably offering you the world, or maybe all the wine in it, if he were really crafty, but....</string>
  <string id="97977" soundid="155789">You didn&apos;t honestly think you were going to slip down here after that little display, did you, Whirlwind?</string>
  <string id="97978" soundid="155790">Step back, Cho. For once in my life I&apos;ve got something important to tell someone.</string>
  <string id="97979" soundid="155791">You have nothing important to say, you lummox. You&apos;ve embarrassed Kai Lan the Serpent, and I&apos;m going to make sure you never get a chance to repeat your performance.</string>
  <string id="97980" soundid="155792">I&apos;ve been waiting for this. Time to cut off the Serpent&apos;s tail!</string>
  <string id="97983">Mugger</string>
  <string id="97986">Mugger</string>
  <string id="97990" soundid="151370">I have said enough for the time being. The events that surround you cause me great concern. I want to see more of what is coming before I decide my next action.</string>
  <string id="98002" soundid="151385">What a wondrous flyer you have. You don&apos;t see any of that design about the city! Since they became more common among the nobles, flyers have been fascinating to me.</string>
  <string id="98003" soundid="151386">Allow me to officially welcome you to the Imperial City. I am Bai the Outcrier, and I am here to direct you around our illustrious capital if you have any questions at all.</string>
  <string id="98004" soundid="151387">Out by the waterway, you can find the city gates and all manner of merchants hawking their wares.</string>
  <string id="98005" soundid="151388">There&apos;s also a path off the Market District that leads up to the Black Leopard School, home to an ancient order that studies the ways of combat.</string>
  <string id="98006" soundid="151389">The Scholars&apos; Garden is a wonder to behold. It is decorated with rocks taken from The Valley of Sprightly Stones. The finest minds in the Empire congregate in the garden.</string>
  <string id="98007" soundid="151390">If you have a taste for history, the Necropolis is accessible from the Golden Way as well. A city of the dead, the Necropolis is filled with tombs of rich and poor alike.</string>
  <string id="98008" soundid="151391">I believe I made it very clear that we were not discussing the Emperor&apos;s protectors. That is all I&apos;m saying.</string>
  <string id="98009" soundid="151392">You should not dwell on this topic. It&apos;s for your own good.</string>
</tlk>