<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<tlk language="0">
  <string id="26566" soundid="145367">You... stranger. You are not like me. You are something different... something special. I noticed it when you first came in. Your energy... your chi, is different.</string>
  <string id="26567" soundid="145368">Please, stranger, I beg of you. Use whatever you can, sacrifice whatever you can so that my daughter will live. Innocence like hers should not have to die in a place like this.</string>
  <string id="26568" soundid="145369"></string>
  <string id="26569" soundid="145370">Stranger... you are... amazing.</string>
  <string id="26570" soundid="146882">I had a stutter once. Put some garlic on it every night, that made it go away. Now, ah... where was I? Oh, yeah.</string>
  <string id="26572" soundid="109289">Hello again. Things are certainly shaping up around here now that Master Radiant is gone.</string>
  <string id="26573" soundid="144610">Strange things have been going on here... ghost troubles and such. I don&apos;t know, but it seems like it&apos;ll soon be too dangerous for even me to stay here.</string>
  <string id="26575" soundid="144611">Sure, sure.</string>
  <string id="26576" soundid="144612">Help! One of those damn spirits came up right in my backyard! The stupid thing won&apos;t let anyone get by! It&apos;s got my tools and everything! Just kill the damn thing!</string>
  <string id="26577" soundid="144613">Haven&apos;t you killed it yet? I can&apos;t do anything without my tools. I can&apos;t get you your reward for anything else, either, &apos;til it&apos;s gone. Just kill it!</string>
  <string id="26578" soundid="139509">Master Smiling Hawk is not interested in teaching the students or the brothers. He seeks only to improve his own abilities.</string>
  <string id="26580">Quit Game</string>
  <string id="26583" soundid="144614">It&apos;s dead then? Heh, good. I knew that old bag would try to come back for me someday. But she wouldn&apos;t have guessed I&apos;d have someone like you on my side. </string>
  <string id="26584" soundid="144615">Eh-heh, yeah, I guess you could say that. She was my mother-in-law. Never once in her life did she say a kind word to me, and now she tried to keep at me even in death.</string>
  <string id="26585" soundid="144616">You got what you deserved! Do you hear me? You deserved it!</string>
  <string id="26586" soundid="144617">Eh-heh, but any good job deserves a reward, of course.</string>
  <string id="26593">Quit the current game and go to the title screen.</string>
  <string id="26594" soundid="51043">A student... here? I had long forgotten the stench of the living.</string>
  <string id="26595" soundid="51044">I ruled this place... taught with wisdom. Why can&apos;t I find my way? Where is the voice that should call to me?</string>
  <string id="26596" soundid="51045">Master, student, farmer... whatever I was, I should be dust. Instead, I am pulled to nowhere. Frustration!</string>
  <string id="26598" soundid="51046">Lies? You cannot see the lie! The lie pulls us nowhere! Frustration!</string>
  <string id="26599" soundid="51047">The living understand nothing! The living cannot feel the pull to nowhere! The frustration!</string>
  <string id="26600" soundid="51048">The way is blocked, the shepherd is gone! Cannot escape the living. Milling... stinking... you cloud the way!</string>
  <string id="26601" soundid="51049">To judgment and to be renewed, but the way of things has been unbalanced! No souls return to the living.</string>
  <string id="26602" soundid="51050">Desire! Arrogance! The way of things is broken! No souls return to the living.</string>
  <string id="26603" soundid="51051">You can see nothing, but soon you will know! The number grows ever larger! No souls return to the living.</string>
  <string id="26604" soundid="51052">What will become of the world if no souls are replenished? Eventually there will be an end. You are blind to the danger, blind to the truth.</string>
  <string id="26610" soundid="145372">Wait! What... what is that?</string>
  <string id="26611" soundid="145822">Enough talk. I will delay your death no longer! May your fall sate the anger of Death&apos;s Hand, will of the Emperor!</string>
  <string id="26612" soundid="145374">You! You have driven me out of her--*my* liver, but I&apos;ll have my vengeance yet! I&apos;ll destroy you and her both!</string>
  <string id="26613" soundid="145823">You are foolish to think one such as he can be intimidated. He is a force beyond what you can understand. All of the Lotus Assassins know his power.</string>
  <string id="26614" soundid="145376">No! Please! I&apos;ll give you anything I can, I just need you to--What? W-wait a minute. She&apos;s stopped trembling.</string>
  <string id="26615" soundid="145377"></string>
  <string id="26616" soundid="145378">Her breathing has slowed, and her heart rate is returning to normal levels. It... it worked! She&apos;s saved!</string>
  <string id="26617" soundid="145379">Thank you, stranger, for what you have done for me. As I promised, I will give you all that I have left. Everything else was spent in pursuit of this dream.</string>
  <string id="26618" soundid="145380">I must take her to a place where she can heal. You have my eternal gratitude for what you have done.</string>
  <string id="26619" soundid="145381">Yes... yes! It looks like it has been preserved well enough! I am amazed that you managed to get this intact.</string>
  <string id="26620" soundid="145382">Her... her breathing has slowed, and her heart rate is returning to normal levels. Whatever you did, stranger, you have saved my daughter.</string>
  <string id="26621" soundid="145383">You have my gratitude forever for this. I know this must have cost you dearly. If ever I find a way to repay you, I will seek you out.</string>
  <string id="26622" soundid="145384">But now... this is not place to heal. My daughter is saved, but she is not well. I must take her to somewhere she can rest in peace, not surrounded by death.</string>
  <string id="26623" soundid="145385">Here is all that I have. Everything else was spent in pursuit of my dream. I thank you... *we* thank you from the bottom of our hearts.</string>
  <string id="26624" soundid="145824">So you fight with no knowledge of your enemy? That will be your undoing. I do not know your face, but I have studied what you have done here. I can defeat you!</string>
  <string id="26625" soundid="145387"></string>
  <string id="26626" soundid="145388"></string>
  <string id="26627" soundid="145389">Thank you for what you have done. I have been redeemed in my own eyes and in the eyes of heaven. Peace indeed *can* come to any soul.</string>
  <string id="26628" soundid="145825">Sagacious? Is that what you call yourself now? Hardly a worthy representation of the blood you spilled.</string>
  <string id="26629" soundid="145391">It&apos;s not right! It can&apos;t be possible that I... It&apos;s you! And this... this must be the doctor!</string>
  <string id="26630" soundid="145392">Please, madam, if you could help me, you would have my eternal gratitude! I am desperate, and I have no other recourse!</string>
  <string id="26631" soundid="145393">This girl. Such a strong, vibrant life energy in one so young... and so fragile. She is too young to have such a cruel fate.</string>
  <string id="26632" soundid="150702">Keep an eye out for a young man dressed in plain blues and greens. He is heavily armored from head to foot.</string>
  <string id="26633">Not right now.</string>
  <string id="26634" soundid="145396">Please... will you help my daughter? I will give you anything, all my research, just for you to save her. The liver... the liver would be my own. No one else would be harmed.</string>
  <string id="26635" soundid="145397">My skill in acupuncture can keep you alive through the operation, but.... you will not live long after. If you tell me how to proceed, I believe I can help her. </string>
  <string id="26636" soundid="145398">Doctor, my spirit will be indebted to you for all time. Si Wei... I love you... forever. Let us proceed, Doctor.</string>
  <string id="26637" soundid="145826">You do not know me, assassin.</string>
  <string id="26638" soundid="145827">Perhaps, but I know what you were. Not that it matters anymore.</string>
  <string id="26639" soundid="145401">It is done. The man&apos;s methods are... extreme, but very effective. As was his love for his daughter. A true parent would do anything to save his child. </string>
  <string id="26640" soundid="145402">She will live, provided she does not remain here. I will take her with me and care for her. If she wishes, I will teach her of her father&apos;s legacy. He would want that, I think.</string>
  <string id="26641" soundid="145403">Thank you for bringing me here, and giving me the chance to save them. I&apos;ll return to the Imperial Arena with her.</string>
  <string id="26642" soundid="145828">Is that what he calls himself now? Hardly an honest representation of the blood he spilled. It doesn&apos;t matter. No matter your allies, I cannot let you survive.</string>
  <string id="26644" soundid="31136">Should you emerge the victor of our fight, I will train you in some of my more advanced techniques. You have shown the purity of spirit to wield a weapon with the required precision.</string>
  <string id="26646" soundid="31138">I keep only what I need to survive from my winnings. The rest goes back to my school in the east. The training is all I can, or will, offer you. Now, what else do you need?</string>
  <string id="26647">Forget it, then. Let me go back to my questions.</string>
  <string id="26651" soundid="31143">Every city has its masters. I came here to compete against the Empire&apos;s best and I have managed to hold my own. Is there anyone else you wish to ask about?</string>
  <string id="26653" soundid="31145">It&apos;s hard to say with him. Perhaps his smile is that of the full and satisfied tiger. Not vacant, as the others believe. Is there anyone else you want to know about?</string>
  <string id="26654" soundid="31146">I believe so, yes. I do not really agree with such a philosophy, but it is worthy of respect, nonetheless. Is there anyone else you want to know about?</string>
  <string id="26655" soundid="31147">You have faced him; I leave you to your own judgments. Is there anyone else you want to know about?</string>
  <string id="26656" soundid="31148">You mock him, but I would reserve judgment until you face him. Is there anyone else you want to know about?</string>
  <string id="26658" soundid="31150">The Gate saw frequent use in the past but now Emperor Sun allows no one to pass through. Then again, he has flyers at his disposal, I suppose.</string>
  <string id="26660" soundid="31152">The Wall&apos;s defensive role has long since been eclipsed but it remains an ever-expanding monument to the Empire&apos;s strength. All land within it is the Emperor&apos;s own.</string>
  <string id="26663" soundid="31155">Of course.</string>
  <string id="26668" soundid="31160">Leave me. I will not waste more time with you.</string>
  <string id="26669" soundid="31161">Thank you again for your warning. It will be good to know that our fight will be fair.</string>
  <string id="26672">What will you do now?</string>
  <string id="26673">Running away from your defeat?</string>
  <string id="26680">Why wouldn&apos;t you exploit that opening?</string>
  <string id="26682">My training was flawless. You must be mistaken.</string>
  <string id="26684">I&apos;ll not take commentary on my skills from one as weak as you!</string>
  <string id="26687" soundid="105608">Many of you are asking yourselves why the Serpent would return to the ring. Am I not retired? Yes! But does that mean I do not care about your entertainment? No!</string>
  <string id="26688" soundid="105609">You&apos;ve all seen the fury and the intense focus of Raging Dragon in the ring! Now, it&apos;s time to put those abilities to the test!</string>
  <string id="26689" soundid="105610">We&apos;ve all seen the flawless technique of the soaring star that is Silver Phoenix. Now, it is time to put these aptly demonstrated skills to the test!</string>
  <string id="26690" soundid="105611">Tiger Lifts the Mountain has climbed the ranks with great power and deliberation. Who wants to see what this fighter can really do?</string>
  <string id="26691" soundid="105612">And so, the Serpent gives you a real spectacle! Have your silver handy to place your wagers! I give you evil and terror incarnate!</string>
  <string id="26696">I should warn you: Lucky Cho is trying to eliminate you.</string>
  <string id="26697">Lucky Cho offered me the services of a poisoner.</string>
  <string id="26698">I consider you a worthy opponent. I want to make sure our match is honest.</string>
  <string id="26699">We have to watch each other&apos;s backs, or the Guild will fix every fight.</string>
  <string id="26701">Because I expect a reward from you, and a generous one at that.</string>
  <string id="26704">That is a fine reward. Thank you.</string>
  <string id="26705" soundid="105621">You earned it. Eliminating the General couldn&apos;t have been easy. He was getting on in years, but was never an easy opponent.</string>
  <string id="26706">That&apos;s it? Training only if I defeat you? I was expecting silver.</string>
  <string id="26709" soundid="62629">Life in a small town on the edge of the Empire can be hard, and many people die untimely deaths. What more needs be said on the subject?</string>
  <string id="26712">Why have you come here, specifically?</string>
  <string id="26713">Are there many different styles taught in the Prosperous East?</string>
  <string id="26715">You think he throws fights?</string>
  <string id="26717">He values learning more than victory, then?</string>
  <string id="26719">That&apos;s pathetic. He deserves to be called Hapless, then.</string>
  <string id="26722">Is there any way through the Emperor&apos;s Gate?</string>
  <string id="26724">Do you know any of the history of the Wall?</string>
  <string id="26727">Let me ask about another area of the city.</string>
  <string id="26731" soundid="108709">Ya Zhen: Your role is of great importance indeed. Mortals are never returned to life in their own form.</string>
  <string id="26732" soundid="105622">And here, take this. Li-Li collected for us. I&apos;m sure you&apos;ll be happy with the sum. I&apos;m ready to leave whenever I get bored.</string>
  <string id="26733" soundid="144871">Even so, I did my best. I made you strong enough to achieve your destiny, but with a weakness I could exploit. I thought I anticipated everything, but you proved me wrong.</string>
  <string id="26734">Dong Ping</string>
  <string id="26737">Zhong</string>
  <string id="26742">Henpecked Hou</string>
  <string id="26745" soundid="151584"></string>
  <string id="26746" soundid="151585">This has been... troubling. We should return to the flyer as soon as possible so everyone can discuss what we have learned.</string>
  <string id="26747" soundid="151586">I don&apos;t like what we have seen here. We must return to your flyer so everyone can discuss what we have learned.</string>
  <string id="26748" soundid="151587">A regrettable adventure. We should return to the flyer so everyone can discuss what we have learned.</string>
  <string id="26749" soundid="151588">This has been very troubling. We must return to the flyer so we can discuss these strange events with everyone present.</string>
  <string id="26750" soundid="151589">This has been a confusing evening. We should go back to the flyer to unload this information on someone more concerned with it... and for wine.</string>
  <string id="26751" soundid="151590">Chai Ka: We are closer to the heart of the enemy. The others will want to know about this. We should return to the flyer.</string>
  <string id="26753" soundid="151592">The Soul Extractor certainly kills whatever is placed within it, but little is left of the victim, so you cannot prove they did not belong there. Only a spirit shard remains.</string>
  <string id="26754" soundid="151593">The golem press is far more dangerous, but I have nothing to do with that ungainly device. I prefer the elegance of ripping slaves apart.</string>
  <string id="26755">The machine looks dangerous. Have accidents claimed any lives?</string>
  <string id="26758" soundid="153200">What slave traders would that be? I&apos;ve never heard of anybody trading slaves around here.</string>
  <string id="26760">Lotus Assassin</string>
  <string id="26764">Mummy</string>
  <string id="26768">Mummy</string>
  <string id="26772" soundid="151611">All right, this is as far as I&apos;m going. I&apos;m a guide, not a soldier.</string>
  <string id="26773" soundid="151612">Your allies are fighting already. You better join them. I don&apos;t need any of these outlaws reaching me.</string>
  <string id="26774" soundid="151613"></string>
  <string id="26777" soundid="161266">We will need our weapons before we can properly deal with the bandits. We should see Gujin as quickly as we can.</string>
  <string id="26782" soundid="151621">Hey... you! What do you think you&apos;re doing here? Get out of here, or we&apos;ll throw you out.</string>
  <string id="26783" soundid="151622">Ha! You sound like my weakling friend over here. &quot;Please let me pass.&quot; No!</string>
  <string id="26784" soundid="151623">I&apos;m not the one in trouble here. *We* outnumber *you*... in case you haven&apos;t noticed.</string>
  <string id="26785" soundid="151624">Ha! Not bad, you&apos;ve got some spirit, but it&apos;ll take more than that to get past us.</string>
  <string id="26786" soundid="151625">Now, how about you just turn yourself around before you get hurt.</string>
  <string id="26787" soundid="151626">You don&apos;t hear so well, do you? Maybe we&apos;ll just have to *show* you what we mean!</string>
  <string id="26788" soundid="151627">Boys! We may be young, but we&apos;ve trained all our lives.</string>
  <string id="26789" soundid="151628">Only a fool looks forward to a beating! Ha!</string>
  <string id="26790" soundid="151629">C&apos;mon... let&apos;s teach our visitor some respect!</string>
  <string id="26791">I&apos;m just visiting. Please let me pass.</string>
  <string id="26793">Careful what you say. It might get you into trouble.</string>
  <string id="26795">Just try it. It&apos;ll be the last thing you do!</string>
  <string id="26797">How about you let me pass!</string>
  <string id="26799">Get out of my way, boys!</string>
  <string id="26801">I&apos;m looking forward to this. Let&apos;s go!</string>
  <string id="26803" soundid="151671">You gain the envious ability to buy and sell at your whim. And I... I can prove my worth in my new role. Perhaps I will even do well enough to get promoted.</string>
  <string id="26804" soundid="151672">Well, that is a most excellent way to think about it.</string>
  <string id="26806" soundid="151673">Simply call upon me as you would any of your followers, and I&apos;ll be there. In the meantime, I have much to do.</string>
  <string id="26807" soundid="151674">As you wish. I have much work to do myself.</string>
  <string id="26808" soundid="151675">I&apos;m afraid my supplies are a little low at the moment. But fear not, I will acquire new items as quickly as I can. I should go and see what I can dig up for you.</string>
  <string id="26809" soundid="151676">Don&apos;t worry, I&apos;ll be around. Just call on me if you need something. Good day!</string>
  <string id="26811">Who are you?</string>
  <string id="26814">Great. I could use someone of your skill.</string>
  <string id="26824">Ya Zhen</string>
  <string id="26829" soundid="132378">Thank you, oh great and noble friend! Minister Sheng weeps with relief to hear such news! I have no doubt you will take care of this in a quick and efficient fashion.</string>
  <string id="26830" soundid="132379">Kill me? But... but why? What has poor Minister Sheng ever done to you that you would want to spill his precious blood?</string>
  <string id="26841" soundid="132380">Help! Guards! Minister Sheng is in trouble! Help! Help!</string>
  <string id="26867">This is the Journal screen. Click on the quests in the window on the left or individual tasks in the window on the right to view more details. A description for the selected quest or task appears in the window below. Click Filter to filter your quests, click Dialog Review to review past dialogs, or click Plot Items to view your inventory.</string>
  <string id="26875" soundid="128718">Look! He&apos;s back!</string>
  <string id="26879">Not hurt?</string>
  <string id="26880">The Drowned Orphans</string>
  <string id="26882" soundid="42802">Hello! Greetings! Welcome! My name is Steeper Yanru and I&apos;ll be.... No! That&apos;s not right! Not right at all! Idiot! I&apos;m Barkeep Yanru now, not Steeper Yanru. </string>
  <string id="26883" soundid="42803">I&apos;m sorry about that. I still can&apos;t get the hang of this new position. Sometimes I wish Old Mother Kwan still owned the teahouse so things could go back to the way they were.</string>
  <string id="26885">Pedestal</string>
  <string id="26887" soundid="42807">Slow down, my friend! I can&apos;t serve you wine yet; I&apos;m not a real barkeep. Master Dutong just has me practicing so I&apos;ll be ready when he turns this place from a teahouse into a tavern.</string>
  <string id="26888" soundid="42808">Master Dutong wants me to practice giving out advice for now. He wants me to stay focused until I get the hang of it. No wine--except for him, of course. You want some advice? </string>
  <string id="26906" soundid="115744">No, it wouldn&apos;t have. But these days I live a sad, pathetic existence. Would things be any worse if I was a ghost in the ruins?</string>
  <string id="26907" soundid="115745">Your disgust is nothing compared to my own self-loathing. Sometimes I wonder if I would be better off as a spirit wandering the ruins instead of the broken shell I am now.</string>
  <string id="26912" soundid="42826">Hello again! A salutorious greeting and welcome! I&apos;m going to be the best barkeep in Tien&apos;s Landing, as soon as Three Sheets Dutong turns this place into a tavern.</string>
  <string id="26913" soundid="42827">I would rather have kept my old job, but Dutong&apos;s in charge now. He says I have to practice giving out wine and advice so I can become a real barkeep, just like the ones in the Imperial City.</string>
  <string id="26914" soundid="115746">Nothing. It&apos;s not important. Not anymore.</string>
  <string id="26915" soundid="115747">Why are you bothering me? I&apos;ve done nothing to you. I&apos;m just a tired old man trying to drink his tea.</string>
  <string id="26916">Fine, I&apos;ll go.</string>
  <string id="26917">Throwing your own life away wouldn&apos;t have saved them.</string>
  <string id="26922" soundid="42836">Dutong gets very friendly when he starts to drink. You might get a confession out of him then, but I doubt it. He&apos;s not really all that drunk at that stage.</string>
  <string id="26923" soundid="42837">Usually after about seven bowls, he slips into depression and sorrow. He complains about how his life is worthless and what a bad and sinful man he is. Not a pretty sight.</string>
  <string id="26924" soundid="42838">By the ninth glass he starts to get paranoid. You can&apos;t really talk to him then. Usually around that time I try to slip a restorative potion into his glass to sober him up.</string>
  <string id="26926">Golem</string>
  <string id="26937" soundid="42851">No problem. We have two sorts of wine here: peasants&apos; wine and Imperial seasoned spirits. The peasants&apos; wine is pretty weak, but that&apos;s usually what Dutong drinks. </string>
  <string id="26938" soundid="42852">The Imperial seasoned spirits are a lot stronger. One bowl of that is worth three bowls of peasants&apos; wine. And if Dutong gets too drunk, I have the restorative to sober him up.</string>
  <string id="26939" soundid="42853">One drink for Master Dutong, coming up. Anything else I can do for you?</string>
  <string id="26943" soundid="42857">Sure thing. He doesn&apos;t like taking it, but I&apos;ll just slip it into a glass. He&apos;ll drink it and be sober as a judge in no time. Anything else I can do for you?</string>
  <string id="26948" soundid="42862">Sure. Just remember, I&apos;m pretty new at this. I&apos;m still practicing. Let&apos;s try this one: Every bureaucrat knows a tree grows toward the light--but a rock grows not at all. </string>
  <string id="26949" soundid="42863">The wise man will always remember that falling leaves spiral downwards, but only until they rest on the earth. </string>
  <string id="26950" soundid="42864">I kind of like this next one: If you drop a rock in a well, you&apos;ll hear a splash--but if you drop a feather in a fire, you&apos;ll hear something very different.</string>
  <string id="26951" soundid="42865">Here&apos;s a short one: If you must sleep on the same bed, at least try to dream different dreams.</string>
  <string id="26952" soundid="42866">When one&apos;s foot knows what one&apos;s hand is doing, one is dangerous; but if the belly button has not been consulted, havoc will ensue.</string>
  <string id="26953" soundid="42867">I have no idea. Dutong just had me memorize a bunch of wise sayings. None of them make much sense to me. Maybe they&apos;ll sound better if people drink the wine.</string>
  <string id="26954" soundid="42868">Just remember what I told you. You never know when a bit of homespun wisdom will come in handy.</string>
  <string id="26955" soundid="42869">Sorry, but Dutong only had me memorize five sayings. You bled me dry earlier. I have no more advice left. Is there anything else you need?</string>
  <string id="26956" soundid="42870">Farewell! Take care! If you ever need any advice, I&apos;ll be right here, handing it out like a barkeep should. Goodbye!</string>
  <string id="27053">How does this work... exactly?</string>
  <string id="27055">Whatever you say. Can I go now?</string>
  <string id="27058">What are you talking about?</string>
  <string id="27059">Get out of my way!</string>
  <string id="27062">What? Why would you need to do that?</string>
  <string id="27063">I still have no idea what you&apos;re talking about.</string>
  <string id="27065">So don&apos;t do it! It won&apos;t bother me one bit.</string>
  <string id="27070">It sounds like a very difficult job.</string>
  <string id="27071">I&apos;m sorry if this has caused you trouble, but I do what I must.</string>
  <string id="27072">Get out of my way or I&apos;ll move you!</string>
  <string id="27074">I don&apos;t have time for this, Zin Bu!</string>
  <string id="27077">What do you need me for?</string>
  <string id="27079">So, how does that help you?</string>
  <string id="27080">So, I have to sell you something now?</string>
  <string id="27082">Zin Bu the Magical Abacus</string>
  <string id="27086" soundid="151716">There wasn&apos;t much of it left when I left. The place was empty, and no one in their right mind would return.</string>
  <string id="27087">Why did you leave Broken Path?</string>
  <string id="27092" soundid="108674">Though you did earn a few points by making her storm out of here for good. All that talk of honor was taking the fun out of crushing my foes.</string>
  <string id="27093">What is the difference? The person dies each time.</string>
  <string id="27095">[Leave.]</string>
  <string id="27098" soundid="31648">That was such an exciting event. All the fighting, the crowd cheering.... I almost got distracted.</string>
  <string id="27099" soundid="31649">Well, I did get distracted, and that wasn&apos;t so good, but it was fun, and I learned a lot from it.</string>
  <string id="27103" soundid="139510">All we really know, is that Second Brother is missing. Master Smiling Hawk sent him on an errand,  but no one has seen him since.</string>
  <string id="27105" soundid="139511">It is unlike Second Brother to be gone this long without contacting us. I suspect that something has happened to him.</string>
  <string id="27108" soundid="139512">We have students looking for him now. I hope we find him soon. He is a good man... and an excellent brother.</string>
  <string id="27110" soundid="139513">It&apos;s named after Master Black Leopard, the school&apos;s first true master. He founded the school in a remote region of the Empire hundreds of years ago.</string>
  <string id="27113" soundid="139514">The school grew slowly but steadily under Master Black Leopard&apos;s tutelage, but it wasn&apos;t until he was quite old that the school became as popular as it is today.</string>
  <string id="27115" soundid="139515">Emperor Zhu Fu, having trained at the school as a youth, moved the school to the Imperial City. Since then, the school has become the very best in the Empire.</string>
  <string id="27121" soundid="60070">Oh really? You find me disagreeable? You should try standing downwind of yourself, peasant.</string>
  <string id="27124" soundid="108688">She seemed to take particular offense that it was you who defeated her. Not surprising, considering you two weren&apos;t on speaking terms.</string>
  <string id="27125" soundid="60071">And please, don&apos;t bother firing yourself up to challenge me out of some fool notion of pride.</string>
  <string id="27131">Master Gang</string>
  <string id="27175" soundid="106270">The arena floor will be set up with ancient magical devices. They will attempt to fry you to a crisp, much to the crowd&apos;s delight.</string>
  <string id="27176" soundid="106271">Your job is to stay on your feet for the course of the match, while they fling deadly projectiles your way. I&apos;d suggest dodging, but that&apos;s just me. </string>
  <string id="27187" soundid="106286">Hello and welcome to Chumin&apos;s Woodcrafts. I&apos;m afraid I don&apos;t have any woodwork items ready right now; my inventory is a bit under stocked.</string>
  <string id="27192" soundid="126762">Do you mind? I am in no mood for company, given my present state of despondency.</string>
  <string id="27193" soundid="126763">I confess that I am eager to find a woman of genuine intellect and class; however, I have long given up hope of finding such a bride in this all too provincial town.</string>
  <string id="27194" soundid="126764">My name is Yaoru, though some of the locals disparagingly refer to me as Yaoru the Sailor. You see, I am predisposed to seasickness, ergo I despise the water.</string>
  <string id="27195" soundid="126765">Yet I suffer their verbal slings and arrows with nary a complaint; it is just one more misfortune to pile atop the great heap that buries me in misery.</string>
  <string id="27196" soundid="126766">I am at the stage of my life in which I long for companionship, a wife with intellect and refinement comparable, but just slightly inferior, to my own.</string>
  <string id="27197" soundid="126767">Unfortunately, this town presents scant opportunity for a suitable match. Seamstresses, barmaids, peasants... I may as well marry the harlots selling themselves in the street!</string>
  <string id="27198" soundid="126768">Ai Ling? Surely you jest! The infamy of that woman&apos;s gang leads me to believe she is barely above a beast... though I hear she is fair to gaze upon.</string>
  <string id="27199" soundid="126769">You have thrust that unappetizing morsel onto my palate once before; I refused it then, and I do so again without hesitation.</string>
  <string id="27200" soundid="126770">[Success] I admit I am quite capable of bringing culture even to one such as her. And she is a stunning physical specimen.</string>
  <string id="27201" soundid="126771">Perhaps you are right. It could be a worthy challenge to try and affect the grand metamorphosis on this ugly caterpillar; my reward may well be a gorgeous butterfly.</string>
  <string id="27202" soundid="126772">[Success] She is undeniably beautiful. And she has run her unsavory organization with an efficacy that hints at some modicum of intelligence.</string>
  <string id="27203" soundid="126773">[Failure] A match for me? I would be offended were the suggestion not so ludicrous as to be completely dismissible. Ai Ling is no match for me! </string>
  <string id="27204" soundid="126774">[Success] I am well versed in Ai Ling&apos;s reputation; I have no desire to endure the protracted beatings she unleashed on that unfortunate baker.</string>
  <string id="27205" soundid="126775">Very well, I consent to a meeting with Ai Ling herself. Take me to her, that we may move events to their ultimate conclusion.</string>
  <string id="27206" soundid="126776">[Failure] Such threats may cause those with less sophistication to befoul themselves, but I know the laws of the Empire protect me against unprovoked assault upon my person!</string>
  <string id="27207" soundid="126777">Harsh words will not sway my opinion of Ai Ling; in fact, your attitude merely confirms my belief that she would make a most unfit bride.</string>
  <string id="27209" soundid="126778">Gladly... though I fear even the potentiality of such a match will now leave a permanent scar upon my already tortured mind.</string>
  <string id="27210" soundid="126779">Or perhaps everyone else&apos;s standards are far too low! I shall not allow myself to be saddled with a marriage of convenience; not when I deserve so much more.</string>
  <string id="27211" soundid="126780">I understand your desire to seek elucidation from one whose vocabulary is elevated above the grunts and squawks of the general rabble inhabiting this town.</string>
  <string id="27212" soundid="126781">However, I am in no mood to converse with you. Not while my heart bears the weight of my great burden.</string>
  <string id="27213" soundid="126782">Your jibes can nary prick the armor of my pride; they are blunted barbs forged by the sputtering flames of your lesser intellect.</string>
  <string id="27214" soundid="126783">Farewell. Perhaps we shall speak again, if you ever tire of the braying and neighing of these barnyard animals.</string>
  <string id="27215" soundid="126784">Why have you returned? I suspect there must be some reason beyond the desire to add the agony of conversing with you to my already incalculable sufferings.</string>
  <string id="27216">I know a woman who might be interested in you.</string>
  <string id="27217">Who are you?</string>
  <string id="27219">What&apos;s wrong?</string>
  <string id="27222">Ai Ling is looking for a husband.</string>
  <string id="27223">[Charm] I bet you could transform her into a true lady.</string>
  <string id="27226">[Intuition] She&apos;s smart and beautiful... a perfect match for you.</string>
  <string id="27232">Map Not Available</string>
  <string id="27233">Restless Spirit</string>
  <string id="27238">[Intimidation] Ai Ling wants to meet you. I strongly suggest you go!</string>
  <string id="27242">Charm</string>
  <string id="27244">Intimidation</string>
  <string id="27245">Intuition</string>
  <string id="27246">Body and Mind</string>
  <string id="27247">Spirit and Body</string>
  <string id="27248" soundid="31836">Do not bother me. Introductions merely clutter the mind.</string>
  <string id="27249" soundid="31837">I don&apos;t think they was bothering you, Sui. It&apos;s Bo being talked to.</string>
  <string id="27250" soundid="108288">I am... unaccustomed to admissions of this kind, but the situation demands no less. I want proof of Death&apos;s Hand misdeeds, but... there is more at stake.</string>
  <string id="27251" soundid="31839">Allow me to apologize for not speaking with you earlier. We believe that speaking with the spectators cheapens our role here.</string>
  <string id="27252" soundid="31840">It is an honor to speak with the champion. What may we do for you?</string>
  <string id="27253" soundid="31841">Anyone who can best our combined might deserves our fixed attention. What may we do for you?</string>
  <string id="27256" soundid="31844">You have come far in a short time. We have been watching you with keen interest.</string>
  <string id="27257" soundid="31845">A victory against an unbeaten opponent is no small thing.</string>
  <string id="27258" soundid="31846">Han falls to your strikes, as have so many before. Now that you have entered the Bronze Division, we shall see how you truly fare. Now, what did you need?</string>
  <string id="27259" soundid="31847">Do not worry too much about us, though. There are many fights between you and the Sung brothers, but we shall humor your questions.</string>
  <string id="27260" soundid="31848">Indeed, had we forced you from your path, we might have introduced several notes of dissonance into the family harmony, leaving us in the berry-stained shoes of Tuneless Tao.</string>
  <string id="27261" soundid="108289">You must be very careful. If they learn your identity, you will face the whole fortress. As strong as you are, I don&apos;t think you would live to discredit Death&apos;s Hand.</string>
  <string id="27262" soundid="108290">I don&apos;t want to lose you in a place like this. You could die here, and I wanted to say I would find that... very unfortunate.</string>
  <string id="27263" soundid="106852">General Kao is a good man, and an exceptional warrior. He will accept any challenge put before him, though.</string>
  <string id="27267" soundid="31855">As a result, he was the only emperor to pass several major decrees posthumously, his advisors having long since taken over his duties. It was a fitting end, in a way.</string>
  <string id="27268" soundid="31856">We don&apos;t have a stable! That donkey&apos;s going to get cold!</string>
  <string id="27269" soundid="31857">I&apos;m sure the donkey will be fine, brother, or, at least, justifiably unhappy instead of randomly petulant.</string>
  <string id="27270" soundid="31858">My brothers drift from the matter at hand! What may we do for you?</string>
  <string id="27271" soundid="31859">Though Han seems less cheerful these days than before. I hope his illusions haven&apos;t finally been shattered.</string>
  <string id="27272" soundid="31860">I&apos;m sure he will bounce back as fresh as ever, though. He always does.</string>
  <string id="27281" soundid="108291">Princess... no, you pretend about too much to be genuine in this. Honest affection comes from years of growth.</string>
  <string id="27285" soundid="108292">Even if it was only... recently discovered.</string>
  <string id="27286" soundid="108293">Ah, but that is not always an option. Sometimes there are difficult choices that must be made.</string>
  <string id="27287" soundid="106853">General Kao has defeated more men in single duels than there are ways to ruin a cake. I&apos;d be careful.</string>
  <string id="27292" soundid="31899">Yes, yes. Minister Sheng is most appreciative. Now if you&apos;ll excuse me, I must plan my triumphant return to the Imperial City!</string>
  <string id="27293" soundid="31900">Ha! It is hard to argue with success! My lord, Judge Fang, Chief Minister of Harmony, will surely be impressed with me. He will protect me from the vile Assassins!</string>
  <string id="27294" soundid="31901">No. Or I should say, not another! You have the thanks of the Ministry, and I do believe the good Captain Ing already sent a runner with his thanks.</string>
  <string id="27295" soundid="31902"></string>
  <string id="27298" soundid="31905">Pretty!</string>
  <string id="27300" soundid="31907">Stop! Thief! Come back here with my sword!</string>
  <string id="27301" soundid="31908"></string>
  <string id="27302" soundid="31909">Put that sword back, lout! Surely there was never a minister as unlucky as Minister Sheng, to suffer such insolence!</string>
  <string id="27303" soundid="31910"></string>
  <string id="27304" soundid="31911">Is that it? You&apos;re just going to let the thief walk free?</string>
  <string id="27305" soundid="31912">And still poor Minister Sheng suffers the insults of tradesmen who know nothing of justice! Where would I put the lout?</string>
  <string id="27306" soundid="31913">My jail has been burned to the ground. Along with my office, I might add. I have no place to put thieves! So stop questioning your betters!</string>
  <string id="27307" soundid="31914"></string>
  <string id="27309" soundid="31916">It is not easy to be Minister Sheng! Beset with troubles and doom, and now interrupted by some difficult stranger!</string>
  <string id="27310" soundid="31917">Truly, can you not see that I am busy watching my career slide into oblivion? Minister Sheng simply hasn&apos;t time for your petty concerns! I have problems of my own!</string>
  <string id="27311" soundid="31918">The Ministry of Harmony, which oversees taxation and execution, usually in that order. But poor Minister Sheng oversees nothing in this dying town! Nothing but failure!</string>
  <string id="27314" soundid="31921">You what? Insolence! My career is on the line, and you want to talk about something else? Look about you!</string>
  <string id="27315" soundid="31922">This backwater pimple of a town lives off of the lake created by the Great Dam. But the Great Dam is open and the lake is dry. The town is dying... under my supervision!</string>
  <string id="27316" soundid="83234">I thank you, and my Fen will thank you when she is returned to me.</string>
  <string id="27317" soundid="31924">Not by me. I cannot act against that horrible Assassin Lim, who opened the Great Dam! I&apos;m not supposed to even say his name, but I am desperate for a solution.</string>
  <string id="27318" soundid="31925">Who cares about that? The Great Dam was opened by... no, I cannot say. It is too dangerous. Unless... very well, you&apos;ve convinced me. It was that horrible Inquisitor Lim!</string>
  <string id="27319" soundid="31926">I didn&apos;t want the town to panic, so I kept Lim&apos;s presence here a secret. Better the peasants think it was ghosts... a much less terrifying idea.</string>
  <string id="27321">Nobody else seems to know about the Assassins.</string>
  <string id="27322" soundid="31929">I am sure you do. But first you will hear my cries of pain! You must help Minister Sheng!</string>
  <string id="27323" soundid="31930">Think of the people of the town! All the little children and nice merchants, slowly dying. Old ones in the street, gasping their last. Minister Sheng needs your help!</string>
  <string id="27324" soundid="31931">Some brave soul must travel through the old ruins, which are absolutely not infested with ghosts, and close the Great Dam. The gate to the ruins is locked, but I have a key.</string>
  <string id="27325" soundid="31932">I cannot order, or even ask, someone to go do this! If the Great Dam closes, the ruins will flood! Various Assassins and soldiers will be killed! Not good for my career.</string>
  <string id="27326" soundid="83235">My precious Flower of the Fields. I can&apos;t leave without her.</string>
  <string id="27327" soundid="31934">But if I happened to *lose* the key and someone happened to *find* it... the town could be saved and the problem solved without any sanction from me!</string>
  <string id="27328" soundid="31935">Think about what? I don&apos;t know what you&apos;re talking about. So, stranger, is there anything else Minister Sheng can do for you?</string>
  <string id="27329" soundid="31936">What are you talking about? I haven&apos;t given you anything. Although, I will need that back when you&apos;re done.</string>
  <string id="27330" soundid="31937">I&apos;ve barely said two words to you, and certainly nothing about closing the Great Dam. You can never claim I said anything about that!</string>
  <string id="27331" soundid="31938">Not from me, certainly, because I never asked you to do anything. Right? Now I happen to know of a ship&apos;s captain down on the waterfront--Ing, I think--who is trapped here.</string>
  <string id="27332" soundid="31939">He has a big cargo rotting in his hold. I am sure he would pay a good sum to anyone who could close the Great Dam.</string>
  <string id="27333" soundid="31940">And again you bother me! Is there no end? Did you find the controls to the Great Dam? You must close the Great Dam. Not that I said anything about that, of course.</string>
  <string id="27334" soundid="31941">You haven&apos;t gotten to it? Have you been busy seeing the sights of this lovely town? Wandering the serene countryside? Visiting relatives?</string>
  <string id="27335" soundid="31942">The dam is closed, and the town is saved, so Minister Sheng feels magnanimous. That means I will answer your questions, by the way.</string>
  <string id="27336" soundid="31943">Oh do you? Then ask, by all means. My life and troubles can simply wait while you satisfy your curiosity!</string>
  <string id="27337" soundid="31944">My career is in tatters. My life is over. But you have questions, so we&apos;d better deal with that!</string>
  <string id="27338" soundid="31945">Well, I think that is wonderful. Let&apos;s sit and chat while the sky falls all around us... along with my career!</string>
  <string id="27339" soundid="31946">Ah, my favorite subject! Ask and Sheng, Imperial Minister of Harmony for this entire region, will let you bask in the glory that is... me!</string>
  <string id="27341">I need some directions.</string>
  <string id="27342" soundid="31949">Don&apos;t... Why... How dare... yes. You are right. I am minister of this bleeding puss-pool of a town. And yes, it is because I am in disfavor. Are you through?</string>
  <string id="27343" soundid="31950">Very well. I still feel some slight affection for your earlier service to me. Ask and Minister Sheng shall answer.</string>
  <string id="27344" soundid="31951">Excellent. Truly good news! I haven&apos;t anything else to do. I&apos;m still hours away from committing suicide.</string>
  <string id="27345" soundid="31952">Minister Sheng needs doers, not askers! What has happened to the helpful-but-silent peasant that was once a staple of the Empire?</string>
  <string id="27346" soundid="31953">I once lived in the Imperial City! I was almost a regular at court! Now Minister Sheng is reduced to answering questions in the street.</string>
  <string id="27347" soundid="112474">You&apos;ve got style, girl. You&apos;re just fine in my book, as long as your purse is full.</string>
  <string id="27348" soundid="31955">Woe to Sheng, that his sole ally is an uneducated simpleton! The Ministry of Harmony oversees taxes and executions for this entire region.</string>
  <string id="27349" soundid="31956">Judge Fang, the Chief Minister of Harmony! He didn&apos;t want me anywhere near the seat of power! He sent me here--an exile as unjust as any in the history of the Empire!</string>
  <string id="27350" soundid="31957">Jealousy! You see, by the rosters of the Imperial bureaucracy, I am next in line for Fang&apos;s job. It was only a matter of time until Minister Sheng ascended to his position!</string>
  <string id="27351" soundid="112475">You&apos;re not half bad, for a man. You&apos;re in my good books as long as you have the silver to stay there.</string>
  <string id="27352" soundid="31959">Fang does not think much of me, so he banished me to this remote branch of the Ministry of Harmony. Now one of his lackeys will take my rightful position as his successor!</string>
  <string id="27353" soundid="31960">The shame! When the Great Dam opened and the lake drained, a ship was trapped in port, and the sailors got quite rowdy.</string>
  <string id="27354" soundid="31961">They got drunk and set fire to the Ministry of Harmony&apos;s office. That is the ruin of it over there. Fortunately, since the Great Dam has been closed, the sailors are gone!</string>
  <string id="27355" soundid="31962">The shame! Since the Great Dam opened and the lake drained, there has been a ship trapped in port, and the sailors are growing increasingly rowdy.</string>
  <string id="27356" soundid="31963">Some of them got drunk and set fire to the Ministry of Harmony&apos;s office. That is the ruin of it over there.</string>
  <string id="27357" soundid="31964">What can be done? The sailors want to leave as badly as the town wants them gone. But until the dam is closed, their ship isn&apos;t going anywhere.</string>
  <string id="27358" soundid="31965">I&apos;m sure Captain Ing down by the pier would offer you some sort of reward to close the Great Dam and free his ship. That is what we in the Ministry of Harmony call a hint.</string>
  <string id="27359" soundid="31966">About what? Are you mad? I never said anything about that. What do you want to know?</string>
  <string id="27360" soundid="112476">Sweet Poison Lyn&apos;s my name, and I trade in rarities of a magical nature. I guarantee I have something you need.</string>
  <string id="27361" soundid="112477">What do you need from me?</string>
  <string id="27362" soundid="112478">I have my sources. Some of them rich, some of them poor, and all of them very concerned with their privacy.</string>
  <string id="27363" soundid="112479">These fine wares may have changed hands a few times over history, but that&apos;s the nature of such things. If you&apos;re that worried, don&apos;t buy anything. </string>
  <string id="27364">Filter - Active Main Story Quests</string>
  <string id="27365" soundid="83236">That is as much as I can ask, I suppose. Thank you.</string>
  <string id="27366" soundid="83237">I have lost all that I had. All I really want back is my precious Fen. If you find anything else of mine with these bandits, it is yours.</string>
  <string id="27367" soundid="31974">I&apos;m not, because I never asked you to do this. Right? I happen to know a ship&apos;s captain down on the waterfront--Ing, I think--who is trapped here since the Great Dam opened.</string>
  <string id="27368" soundid="31975">He has a big cargo rotting in his hold. I am sure he would pay a good sum to any who could close the Great Dam. Be sure to stop by Beggar&apos;s Pier and talk to Captain Ing.</string>
  <string id="27369" soundid="112481">Do you have any idea how much magic the arena itself holds? These walls have seen more than you or I can imagine, and there&apos;s enough security for me not to worry.</string>
  <string id="27370">Filter - Active Subquests</string>
  <string id="27371" soundid="112483">What the Imperial bureaucrats don&apos;t know won&apos;t hurt them. First they decree wind maps off limits, and now there&apos;s concern over magical artifacts.</string>
  <string id="27373" soundid="112485">Certain items have always been considered &quot;questionable,&quot; but enforcement has been more strict in the past few years.</string>
  <string id="27374" soundid="112486">Perhaps, but there&apos;s more happening than a simple crackdown. Who can say, though?</string>
  <string id="27375" soundid="112487">All I really know is that the restrictions have done wonders for my customers&apos; tolerance for raised prices. What more could I ask for?</string>
  <string id="27376" soundid="112488">Magical enhancements and knowledge. Have a look at my wares and see for yourself.</string>
  <string id="27377" soundid="112489">I&apos;ll be here when you need more of my goods.</string>
  <string id="27378">I have enough to keep your interest.</string>
  <string id="27379">My purse is my own concern.</string>
  <string id="27381" soundid="83238">Please, I am grateful for whatever you can do. My Flower of the Fields. I can&apos;t leave without her.</string>
  <string id="27382">Whether or not you get any of my silver depends on what you have for sale.</string>
  <string id="27385" soundid="31992">Oh, please. Ask away. Minister Sheng--that&apos;s Imperial Minister Sheng of the Ministry of Harmony--has nothing better to do than act as your guide to local customs!</string>
  <string id="27386">Where do you find your wares?</string>
  <string id="27387">Are these goods stolen?</string>
  <string id="27388">Spear Catches Leaf</string>
  <string id="27389" soundid="31996">It is true, I am knowledgeable and well-traveled. Very well, let me elucidate.</string>
  <string id="27390" soundid="31997">But I respect him! Oh yes, I respect him so very, very much.</string>
  <string id="27391">Do you ever worry about this much magic in one place?</string>
  <string id="27392" soundid="31999">Ru announced three days ago that he was going to close the Great Dam, but first he stopped at the teahouse for a bowl of wine. As far as I know, he is still there.</string>
  <string id="27394" soundid="32001">I believe I saw him down by his barge, on Beggar&apos;s Pier. You can probably find him there. Just follow the smell of wine.</string>
  <string id="27395" soundid="83239">You have not felt her charms upon your soul. Fine, be on your way, but please... if you see my Fen, my Flower of the Fields, get her away from those bandit mongrels.</string>
  <string id="27396" soundid="32003">Minister Sheng remembers when flyers were reserved for the wealthy elite of the Imperial City. Now pirates use them to raid the countryside. Disgraceful!</string>
  <string id="27397" soundid="83240">They&apos;ll work her to death, I know it. Or eat her... or worse. I can&apos;t leave this place without her.</string>
  <string id="27398" soundid="112543">The man to see is named Qui the Promoter. He knows everything there is to know about this place.</string>
  <string id="27399" soundid="32006">I recently saw a large fleet of flyers pass by. Minister Sheng held out hope that they had come to escort him away from this demeaning post and back to the Imperial City.</string>
  <string id="27400" soundid="112544">Might even be looking for a new body to fill out the roster. This could be your chance. If you&apos;re interested, he&apos;s usually up in his office. Up and around to the back.</string>
  <string id="27401" soundid="112545">Of course, champion! Always an honor to have your patronage.</string>
  <string id="27402" soundid="32009">But the flyers never stopped in Tien&apos;s Landing. They headed upriver, toward the pirates&apos; camp. No doubt they went there to refuel, though where they are now, I could not say.</string>
  <string id="27403" soundid="112546">Stop by again! Miniature Ravager hoods for the kids are coming in any day now. You know you&apos;ll want two!</string>
  <string id="27404" soundid="112547">Come back again soon! </string>
  <string id="27406" soundid="32013">Exactly! Because I never actually asked you to help, right? Very good. Now go close the Great Dam. Quickly!</string>
  <string id="27407" soundid="32014">Yes, yes. Go and leave Minister Sheng alone to ponder his troubles. Now go close the Great Dam, and I never said that!</string>
  <string id="27408" soundid="32015">Yes, yes, go on your way. There is no hope anyway. The dam is destroyed and Minister Sheng is cursed! Woe!</string>
  <string id="27409" soundid="32016">Very well, run along! Now that the dam is closed again, Minister Sheng is on his way back to the Imperial City, I&apos;m sure of it!</string>
  <string id="27410" soundid="158473">Quit crying, fool, or we will gut you like a carp.</string>
  <string id="27411" soundid="83242">These reeds hide so many thieves... you could walk right past a camp and not see it. There&apos;s no telling where they took your friend, or my Fen.</string>
  <string id="27412" soundid="83243">My precious Fen. I hope these bandit thugs are merciful with her.</string>
  <string id="27413" soundid="83244">These marshes are not kind to gentle creatures.</string>
  <string id="27414" soundid="83245">She has a strong spirit, but there is only so much of a burden a heart can carry.</string>
  <string id="27415" soundid="108294">Yes, much like the danger we must choose to face, and deciding... whose heart you think of to get you through such times.</string>
  <string id="27416" soundid="108295">[Success] Well, of course you want to keep everyone together. How else are we to function as a team? I cannot fault you for trying to be an effective diplomat.</string>
  <string id="27417" soundid="108296">That&apos;s not what this is about. I was looking for a more personal assurance of... something.</string>
  <string id="27418" soundid="108297">[Success] I... am not certain what this means, but I am sufficiently intrigued to let it pass for now.</string>
  <string id="27419" soundid="108298">You phrase things is such a way that I feel I am equal with a princess. That brings me comfort, even if the rest of this is a bit confusing.</string>
  <string id="27420" soundid="108299">I imagine it would be, little Dawn Star. We shall have to see if anything comes of it.</string>
  <string id="27421" soundid="108300">For now, I believe we are done here. Take care within the Assassins&apos; fortress. To save your master, you must expose Death&apos;s Hand.</string>
  <string id="27422" soundid="154006">Ah, I know you. You are the new acolyte, and you have already brought change. I am the Keeper of the Archive, and I was about to write a new entry.</string>
  <string id="27423" soundid="108301">And when you have succeeded, the three of us can expand on what you have suggested.</string>
  <string id="27424" soundid="100598">Do you have any idea how much paperwork I have to do when a contestant of the Empire&apos;s finest tournament dies?</string>
  <string id="27425" soundid="100599">Wards and spells have protected fighters in this place since its construction. It&apos;s been easily twenty years since they failed.</string>
  <string id="27428" soundid="139516">Very little, I&apos;m afraid. The school enjoys a degree of privacy from the outside world. It allows us to focus on our training, but it also isolates us.</string>
  <string id="27430" soundid="139517">I haven&apos;t been beyond these walls in almost five years. There is really nothing for me in the world beyond. My focus is the school and its students.</string>
  <string id="27435">Press the BACK button to view the controller layout
Use your Fight Style keys to change styles.</string>
  <string id="27436" soundid="100601">It was a dark day. My predecessor lost several good men when the spells failed during an event he&apos;d ironically dubbed the Feast of the Ogres.</string>
  <string id="27437" soundid="100602">I&apos;m no sorcerer, but I suppose it could happen. Still, any magically inclined person would notice something like that.</string>
  <string id="27438" soundid="100603">Even if someone removed them, the protections would re-weave themselves automatically in time. They&apos;ve done so before.</string>
  <string id="27439" soundid="100604">I shall talk until the blueness of the over-quick diner tinges my face if that&apos;s what it takes for you to join!</string>
  <string id="27440" soundid="154007">Here ended the rule of Shin, a petty man who fell to the wiles of those he subjugated. He will be replaced by Master Gang and.... </string>
  <string id="27441" soundid="100606">That&apos;s the spirit of the thing! Now, what name proceeds you in your travels?</string>
  <string id="27442" soundid="100607">Ah... right. A fine name... a fine name indeed.</string>
  <string id="27443" soundid="100608">But it won&apos;t sell. Not at all. We need something more memorable for the crowds.</string>
  <string id="27444" soundid="100609">Have a bit of a past that you&apos;d rather not catch up with you? You&apos;re not the first!</string>
  <string id="27445" soundid="100610">I&apos;ve heard that one before. Have you any idea how many bored students peramputate down here from the Scholars&apos; Garden?</string>
  <string id="27446" soundid="100611">Think of something that would sound engaging ringing from the rafters. That&apos;s how we&apos;ll bill you!</string>
  <string id="27447" soundid="100612">Raging Dragon, huh? Sounds fast and powerful. I like it. Are you positive that&apos;s what you want?</string>
  <string id="27448" soundid="100613">Silver Phoenix.... Silver Phoenix. Conjures up quite an image. Are you certain?</string>
  <string id="27449" soundid="100614">Now that&apos;s a decisive name. Tiger Lifts the Mountain it is, if you&apos;re certain?</string>
  <string id="27450" soundid="100615">Then that is what you shall have. Come and tell me when you&apos;re ready for a fight, and I&apos;ll get you started.</string>
  <string id="27451" soundid="100616">Don&apos;t worry if you have to take off for a while; we&apos;ll work around your schedule. Don&apos;t forget about us, though, or we might forget about you.</string>
  <string id="27452" soundid="100617">Since you&apos;re new, you&apos;ll start in the qualifying rounds. The money&apos;s small at that level, but it&apos;s there. Any other questions?</string>
  <string id="27453" soundid="100618">One other thing. You should talk to the other fighters now and then. They will be watching you, and you should get to know them, as well.</string>
  <string id="27454" soundid="100619">We&apos;re all one big happy family!</string>
  <string id="27455" soundid="100620">You&apos;re a big, happy idiot, Han!</string>
  <string id="27456" soundid="100621">As you can see, they always have something to say.</string>
  <string id="27457" soundid="100622">Take your time; you have to be happy with it.</string>
  <string id="27458" soundid="154008">He escaped death, but there is no greater penalty for a Lotus Assassin than to be removed from the sight of Death&apos;s Hand and our Emperor.</string>
  <string id="27459" soundid="100624">Truly this is a loss for all involved. The offer stands as surely as the Wall itself, when your senses restore to their proper balance.</string>
  <string id="27460" soundid="100625">As sure as a dog will scratch where the flea bites, I knew you would return. Fighting&apos;s in your blood, and you&apos;ll itch until you test yourself in this grand contest!</string>
  <string id="27461" soundid="100626">Look at our Bronze Division champion, Crimson Khana. I can see that the two of you could be battle sisters: the way you stand, the steel in your eyes.</string>
  <string id="27462" soundid="100627">Testing yourself against the finest in the Empire: what else could a young man dream of?</string>
  <string id="27463" soundid="100628"></string>
  <string id="27464" soundid="100629">That was an impressive beginning. Normally I&apos;d have started you off against something easier, but you practically ooze potential!</string>
  <string id="27465" soundid="100630">You&apos;ve caught the eyes of the other fighters, as well. Go ask them if you don&apos;t believe me.</string>
  <string id="27466" soundid="100631">That really was a fantastic bout!</string>
  <string id="27467" soundid="100632">Beating the ogre&apos;s nothing special. I could have done better bound and blinded!</string>
  <string id="27471" soundid="100633">Sometimes you don&apos;t even need to ask.</string>
  <string id="27472" soundid="100634">One fight does not make a champion, though! There are many more opponents ahead of you. Let&apos;s move on, shall we?</string>
  <string id="27475">If you must.</string>
  <string id="27478">No.</string>
  <string id="27479">Won&apos;t the Lotus Assassins be mad at you?</string>
  <string id="27494">What are you minister of?</string>
  <string id="27497">This route is plagued with enemy ships. What do you want to do?</string>
  <string id="27499">What kind of problems do you have?</string>
  <string id="27500">I need to ask you some questions.</string>
  <string id="27502">Why is the Great Dam open?</string>
  <string id="27504">Is there anything that can be done?</string>
  <string id="27506">I&apos;m searching for a fleet of flyers. </string>
  <string id="27508">Why do you run your shop back here?</string>
  <string id="27509">Is there anything I can do?</string>
  <string id="27511">Do you have any idea why these restrictions are in place?</string>
  <string id="27512">I want to ask you about something else.</string>
  <string id="27514">This doesn&apos;t concern me.</string>
  <string id="27517">Slow down. Tell me what happened.</string>
  <string id="27519">Interesting. I&apos;ll think about it.</string>
  <string id="27520">Hey! What did you just give me? Is that a key?</string>
  <string id="27521">If you&apos;re done babbling, I have some questions for you.</string>
  <string id="27522">Is there a reward for doing this?</string>
  <string id="27524">I haven&apos;t gotten to it yet.</string>
  <string id="27525">I have some questions for you.</string>
  <string id="27526">I&apos;m curious about you.</string>
  <string id="27530">If I see her, I will do what I can.</string>
  <string id="27532">It couldn&apos;t just be that your goods are stolen?</string>
  <string id="27533">Doesn&apos;t &quot;this entire region&quot; just consist of this town?</string>
  <string id="27534">I want to ask about something else.</string>
  <string id="27536">What does the Ministry of Harmony do?</string>
  <string id="27537">Why were you sent to Tien&apos;s Landing?</string>
  <string id="27538">But why did he do that?</string>
  <string id="27540">Show me what you have to sell.</string>
  <string id="27541">Why are you standing here in front of a cart?</string>
  <string id="27544">Someone should do something about those sailors.</string>
  <string id="27546">I have questions about closing the Great Dam.</string>
  <string id="27547">Goodbye.</string>
  <string id="27548">Sailor</string>
  <string id="27551">Only if it does not interfere with my concerns.</string>
  <string id="27553">What kind of reward are you offering?</string>
  <string id="27561">Attack: Staff
Support: You deal extra damage with Weapon styles.
Zu&apos;s attacks can damage spirits. 

Sagacious Zu&apos;s mysterious past belies great experience and skill. His staff is a valuable asset in battle.

</string>
  <string id="27562">Attack: Long Sword
Support: You deal extra damage with Martial styles. 
Silk Fox&apos;s attacks can damage spirits. 

Silk Fox is as enigmatic as she is beautiful. When her long sword is not flashing from foe to foe, she lends her skill to you.

</string>
  <string id="27563">Attack: Demon Form
Support: Recovers your Health
Chai Ka&apos;s attacks can damage spirits. 

A guardian demon bound in the body of a child, Chai Ka will fight alongside you with his great strength or channel his power through you.

</string>
  <string id="27564">Attack: Demon Form
Support: Recovers your Health
Ya Zhen&apos;s attacks can damage spirits. 

A hideous demon using Wild Flower&apos;s body as an anchor, Ya Zhen tears through enemies with his claws and tongue.

</string>
  <string id="27565">Attack: Fallen Blades
Support: None
Death&apos;s Hand&apos;s attacks can damage spirits.

The body and spirit of the tortured Prince Kin are yours to command. Just as he did for both Sun Hai and Sun Li, Death&apos;s Hand serves you with ruthless efficiency and brutal strength.</string>
  <string id="27566">What would I receive for helping you?</string>
  <string id="27567">Strref 27567 : Wildflower</string>
  <string id="27568">Attack: Monk Spade
Support: Recovers your Chi, Focus, and Health
Abbot Song&apos;s attacks can damage spirits. 

The abbot of the doomed Spirit Monks, Abbot Song serves the Water Dragon, even in death. His hope for redemption lies with you. 

</string>
  <string id="27569">I need information about the town.</string>
  <string id="27570" soundid="112562">I have plenty of other items that might just fit, though! Why don&apos;t you have a look?</string>
  <string id="27571">I want to ask you about the Empire.</string>
  <string id="27574">Where can I find Ru the Boatswain?</string>
  <string id="27578">Your concerns do not interest me. Move aside.</string>
  <string id="27579">Let&apos;s take a look at your wares.</string>
  <string id="27580">Has a fleet of flyers passed by recently?</string>
  <string id="27583">Do you have anything I might be interested in?</string>
  <string id="27584">How can I get to the pirates&apos; camp?</string>
  <string id="27586">Tell me more about the arena.</string>
  <string id="27589">I never actually said I would help you.</string>
  <string id="27590">Goodbye.</string>
  <string id="27591" soundid="100635">Those boys won&apos;t be back any time soon. Losing as a group to one opponent would shame a peasant, let alone a student of the martial arts.</string>
  <string id="27592" soundid="100636">Excellent work. You have bested time itself in destroying that statue! No mean feat, I assure you.</string>
  <string id="27593" soundid="100637">You dealt with Han very well. I knew you would; all of our professional fighters move past him eventually.</string>
  <string id="27598" soundid="100638">Qui, that will be enough.</string>
  <string id="27599" soundid="100639">I bring you a message from my employer, Kai Lan the Serpent. He is impressed with how far you have come in such a short while.</string>
  <string id="27600" soundid="100640">The Serpent wants you to know that he is watching your progress very closely. He is most interested to see how you fare in the Bronze Division.</string>
  <string id="27601" soundid="100641">Qui, you may breathe again. That is all I had to say.</string>
  <string id="27602" soundid="100642"></string>
  <string id="27603" soundid="100643">Well, that was... good, I think.</string>
  <string id="27604" soundid="100644">He has a distinct interest in the proceedings here. He is an ex-champion, you see.</string>
  <string id="27605" soundid="100645">He retired some time ago, even before Raging Ox, who was the champion before the Ravager. Kai Lan couldn&apos;t leave the arena alone, though.</string>
  <string id="27606" soundid="100646">He has become a very important man here, with the help of a group called the Guild.</string>
  <string id="27607" soundid="100647">Lucky Cho is a thug, pure and simple, but he&apos;s very good at what he does. He is also a member of the Guild, and reports directly to Kai Lan. </string>
  <string id="27608" soundid="100648">Kai Lan &quot;oversees&quot; things here in the arena, and the Guild ensures that the authorities leave us in peace.</string>
  <string id="27609" soundid="108691">I see no need to rise to your taunts. I&apos;ve come to accept that most people do not care to understand my philosophy.</string>
  <string id="27610" soundid="108692">Indeed, we should.</string>
  <string id="27611" soundid="100651">The Guild is the organization that controls all of the betting in this place. That gives them considerable sway. It is good that they are happy with your progress.</string>
  <string id="27612" soundid="100652">Between us, the Guild is also involved in more illicit activities. They are very sensitive about remaining an &quot;open secret.&quot; Many know about them, but few acknowledge that fact.</string>
  <string id="27613" soundid="100653">Do not discuss them openly. The Guild has many ears. You may ask some of the others in the arena about them, if you wish, but I would not bring it up to just anyone.</string>
  <string id="27614" soundid="100654">A wise decision. Very wise.</string>
  <string id="27615" soundid="100655">I would not recommend that. I&apos;m sure the authorities are already aware of their existence.</string>
  <string id="27616" soundid="100656">Reporting them for activities you cannot prove is like stirring a chamber pot with a short stick. You&apos;re the one likely to lose in that situation.</string>
  <string id="27617" soundid="100657">You are strong, but they are many and work in shadows. </string>
  <string id="27618" soundid="100658">For the sake of your career, I suggest that you limit any questions you have to your fellow fighters.</string>
  <string id="27621" soundid="100661">Well done! That fight was much better than this wine! </string>
  <string id="27622" soundid="100662">With all the pure water pouring from the palace you&apos;d think they might have learned how to make wine that didn&apos;t taste like goat piss.</string>
  <string id="27623" soundid="100663">Black Whirlwind? That *is* you! Are you back to...?</string>
  <string id="27624" soundid="100664">No! Just here visiting and making sure nothing happens to your newest fighter.</string>
  <string id="27625" soundid="100665">So you won&apos;t be...?</string>
  <string id="27626" soundid="100666">No. Leave it alone, Qui. You know better than to bring this up. Just mind your business, Promoter, and I&apos;ll mind mine.</string>
  <string id="27627" soundid="100667">He.... You travel in curious company. Regardless, when you&apos;re ready, come talk to me again, and we&apos;ll discuss your next match.</string>
  <string id="27628" soundid="100668">I know him, yes, but I know better than to contravicate *his* wishes. If you want to talk about it, ask him. I&apos;m staying out of it.</string>
  <string id="27629" soundid="100669">Now, if you&apos;ll excuse me, I must prepare for your entry into the Bronze Division. It will take me a bit of time before you&apos;ll be ready for your next fight.</string>
  <string id="27630" soundid="100670">That was a good start to the Bronze Division. Those beasts are far stronger than they look.</string>
  <string id="27631" soundid="100671">Fantastic! A test of speed passed with exceptional celery! Now, I&apos;ve....</string>
  <string id="27632" soundid="100672">Your sudden and polite silences are always appreciated, Qui.</string>
  <string id="27633" soundid="100673">I have a message for Raging Dragon.</string>
  <string id="27634" soundid="100674">I&apos;m sure you won&apos;t mind if I take a moment to pass a message to Silver Phoenix.</string>
  <string id="27635" soundid="100675">I have a message for you, Tiger Lifts the Mountain.</string>
  <string id="27636" soundid="100676">Kai Lan the Serpent has, as promised, been watching you intently. You have impressed him so far, and he is interested to see how you fare in your next match.</string>
  <string id="27637" soundid="35942">My husband thought all the smoke was from burning incense... but there&apos;s just too much.</string>
  <string id="27638" soundid="100677">The Serpent foresees your victory in the next match, and he has backed his prediction with silver. He sincerely hopes that his faith in your skills was not misplaced.</string>
  <string id="27639" soundid="108693">You&apos;re lucky you&apos;ve never said anything as piggish to me.</string>
  <string id="27640" soundid="100679">That is all. If you will excuse me, I have some people who need to be spoken to.</string>
  <string id="27641" soundid="100680">Ha, well, I&apos;m certain that won&apos;t be a problem for you. Did you have a question for me?</string>
  <string id="27642" soundid="100681">That was an exceptional fight. I haven&apos;t seen demons in the ring before.</string>
  <string id="27643" soundid="100682">No one questions your skills; that is why you were allowed to fight that beast.</string>
  <string id="27644" soundid="100683">That reminds me, I was asked to instruct you to talk with Lucky Cho before your next match. </string>
  <string id="27646" soundid="100684">He didn&apos;t say, and when I asked, he gave me that glare of his.</string>
  <string id="27647" soundid="100685">I understand, and it is never my intent to impediment your progress! That said, Lucky Cho is not a man I can ignore.</string>
  <string id="27648" soundid="100686">Go, speak with him now. The sooner you do, the sooner I can return you to the ring.</string>
  <string id="27649" soundid="100687">Khana&apos;s winning streak has been broken at last.</string>
  <string id="27661">Menu</string>
  <string id="27662" soundid="83035">The heavens welcome my machines, but not without considerable cajoling. If you want to fly more than a short distance, I will need an Inscrutable Power Source.</string>
  <string id="27663" soundid="83036">Ha! What wonders cling to you, my friend! There were only two in this whole region, and I destroyed one so Inquisitor Lim would not make off with my Marvelous Dragonfly.</string>
  <string id="27665" soundid="83038">The other was with the Lotus Assassins, but the fools only used it for demolition. Now here you stand with it. I will put it in the Dragonfly, and it will be ready to go.</string>
  <string id="27666" soundid="83039"></string>
  <string id="27667" soundid="83040"></string>
  <string id="27668" soundid="83041">Hm... not the ideal placement. If it shook more, the heavens might think we were afraid and take pity. This is more stable... but not as fun. </string>
  <string id="27669" soundid="83042"></string>
  <string id="27670" soundid="83043"></string>
  <string id="27671" soundid="83044">Okay, she&apos;s ready to go! Hop on. I know a nice safe landing place just outside Tien&apos;s Landing. Very unlikely we&apos;ll crash.</string>
  <string id="27676" soundid="83049">I don&apos;t know. There was one here for the Dragonfly... until I blew it up! That was the only way to keep Inquisitor Lim from taking my Dragonfly to the Imperial City.</string>
  <string id="27677" soundid="83050">I know the Assassins have another one. They were using it for blasting and excavation. Lim once said something about ruins.</string>
  <string id="27678" soundid="83051">If you&apos;re looking for the Inscrutable Power Source, I&apos;d find some ruins that also have Assassins in them.</string>
  <string id="27679" soundid="83052">Ha! Why not just build another sun? Or the tumbling waters of a river? No, an Inscrutable Power Source must be found, not built. Gao found one and brought it here... then I blew it up!</string>
  <string id="27680" soundid="83053">It was the only way to make sure they did not take my Marvelous Dragonfly and fly off to the Imperial City without me. Without an Inscrutable Power Source, she won&apos;t fly very far.</string>
  <string id="27681" soundid="83054">Oh, the Assassins have an Inscrutable Power Source. In fact, they had two. One was here, and they planned to put it in the Dragonfly.</string>
  <string id="27682" soundid="83055">But Kang was fast and smart. Kang exploded the Power Source. That way they couldn&apos;t take my beautiful Dragonfly and fly away without me!</string>
  <string id="27683" soundid="83056">And of course, when you get the Inscrutable Power Source, someone has to actually put it in the Dragonfly. Nobody else can do it!</string>
  <string id="27685" soundid="83058">Ah, yes, the Assassins have one that they took from my workshop. They use it for excavating. I think that Inquisitor Lim said something about the ruins.</string>
  <string id="27686" soundid="83059">So, if I had to hazard a guess, I&apos;d say that if you&apos;re looking for the Inscrutable Power Source, I&apos;d find some ruins that also have Assassins in them.</string>
  <string id="27688">Horse Demon</string>
  <string id="27689">What&apos;s on the other side of the door?</string>
  <string id="27690" soundid="83063">But they *can* make a new inductor. It is extraneous, after all. So a few days ago, I blew up the Inscrutable Power Source. Now the Dragonfly can only make short hops.</string>
  <string id="27692">I have an Inscrutable Power Source.</string>
  <string id="27705">Where would I find an Inscrutable Power Source?</string>
  <string id="27709">Why don&apos;t you build one?</string>
  <string id="27712">How was Lim planning to use the Dragonfly without a Power Source?</string>
  <string id="27714">You can concentrate better, slowing down the world around you even more.</string>
  <string id="27718">Where can I find the Inscrutable Power Source?</string>
  <string id="27720">You have better insight to your opponent&apos;s strengths, allowing you to avoid them.</string>
  <string id="27724">Enough of this. I have to go.</string>
  <string id="27725">Thug</string>
  <string id="27729" soundid="83104">Get to work, mad fool. Do whatever it takes to get that ship built. I will take a short-range flyer and check on some of our other operations in the area.</string>
  <string id="27730" soundid="83105">If the Marvelous Dragonfly is not ready to launch when I return, those captive demons will have a new playmate.</string>
  <string id="27731">But there are pirates wandering all over this town!</string>
  <string id="27735">That&apos;s all I need for now.</string>
  <string id="27741" soundid="83117">Well, if I know Ru he&apos;ll be in the teahouse. He has a fine appreciation for wine, a true connoisseur.</string>
  <string id="27753">Inventory View</string>
  <string id="27765" soundid="134673">Great Mistress! It is heaven itself to see you again. I have been so... so lost without your wisdom.</string>
  <string id="27768" soundid="83266">Thank you for saving me. I was getting tired of catering to these fools.</string>
  <string id="27775" soundid="83453"></string>
  <string id="27784" soundid="158474">My poor Fen. What have you done to her?</string>
  <string id="27789">I have lost someone as well. Did they have anyone else with them?</string>
  <string id="27797" soundid="83176">I have nary a clue. Unless... very well, you&apos;ve convinced me to talk. It is dangerous to say anything, but I am a brave man. It was that horrible Inquisitor Lim!</string>
  <string id="27799" soundid="83178">Lim oversees the Lotus Assassin operations in this area. A few weeks ago, he came to town and demanded a key to the ruins. Then his men went up there and opened the Great Dam!</string>
  <string id="27801">Thunderous Taoran</string>
  <string id="27802" soundid="83181"></string>
  <string id="27803" soundid="83182">Because you haven&apos;t yet picked on my appearance or my family history. Why stop short of completely obliterating the last little bit of dignity to which Minister Sheng clings?</string>
  <string id="27804" soundid="83183"></string>
  <string id="27811" soundid="142017"></string>
  <string id="27812" soundid="142018"></string>
  <string id="27813" soundid="126666">Back on the farm, I ain&apos;t never seen so many people and buildings in one place. &apos;Cept for livestock. But I guess they ain&apos;t people... or buildings.</string>
  <string id="27814" soundid="126667">My name&apos;s Tian, but everyone calls me Big Tian &apos;cause I&apos;m so big. I came to the city to try and find me a wife. So far it&apos;s not going so good.</string>
  <string id="27815" soundid="126668">Say, you&apos;re real pretty. You want to be my wife? You could come live on my farm. I got chickens and oxen and lots of land.</string>
  <string id="27816" soundid="83195">Minister Sheng has been reduced to a tour guide! The teahouse is the large building just down the hill from here, near the entrance to the town.</string>
  <string id="27817" soundid="83196">It is the lowest point in town, in every sense of the word. Keep following paths downward until you can go no lower. When you see painted ladies and thugs, you&apos;ve arrived.</string>
  <string id="27818" soundid="83197">Minister Sheng may be banished to this festering boil of a town, but I refuse to learn anything of its history! There is far too much for me to worry about as it is.</string>
  <string id="27819" soundid="126669">It would be hard at first, working the farm by ourselves. But after you have six or seven kids, they can help out too!</string>
  <string id="27820" soundid="83199">Ask your questions of the old fool who crouches on the north side of the square, muttering to himself about the old days.</string>
  <string id="27821" soundid="126670">Oh... okay. Well, do you know any other pretty young gals looking for a husband?</string>
  <string id="27822" soundid="126671">But that would really hurt... oh, I get it. You don&apos;t want to marry me. That&apos;s okay. You know any other young gals looking for a husband?</string>
  <string id="27823" soundid="126672">I&apos;m sorry. I don&apos;t know too much about your fancy city ways. I didn&apos;t want to make you mad. I&apos;m just trying to find a nice gal to marry me and come live on my farm.</string>
  <string id="27824" soundid="126673">You wouldn&apos;t happen to know any pretty young gals, would you? Someone who&apos;d want to come live on the farm with me?</string>
  <string id="27825">I&apos;m sorry. There was no other way.</string>
  <string id="27828">Why did they do that?</string>
  <string id="27829">Smiling Mountain</string>
  <string id="27833" soundid="126674">Well, that&apos;s a real shame. If you run across any nice gals, do me a favor and mention my name to them: Big Tian. You have a nice day now.</string>
  <string id="27834" soundid="126675">Wait, don&apos;t go yet. I&apos;m new to the city and I don&apos;t know my way around too good. I&apos;m a little bit lost, too. So many people.</string>
  <string id="27835" soundid="126676">You do? That&apos;s great! Is she pretty? Is she a nice, simple gal who&apos;ll help out on my farm and keep me warm at night?</string>
  <string id="27836" soundid="126677">Well, let&apos;s go meet her. You better lead the way, &apos;cause I don&apos;t know where we&apos;re going.</string>
  <string id="27837" soundid="126678">Price? What are you talking about... oh! I get it! My old father warned me about your type. I ain&apos;t lookin&apos; to buy me no woman. No lady-for-hire type gals for this country boy.</string>
  <string id="27838" soundid="126679">I just want a nice, respectable gal to be my wife. One who can help me out on the farm and such.</string>
  <string id="27839" soundid="126680">Okay. Well, goodbye then. Have a nice day and all.</string>
  <string id="27840">You think Tien&apos;s Landing is a big city?</string>
  <string id="27841">Where is the teahouse?</string>
  <string id="27842">Where is Beggar&apos;s Pier?</string>
  <string id="27843" soundid="100688">Doctor An has already pronounced the poor girl dead. The Doctor wouldn&apos;t say what killed her, though. I suspect a weakness of the heart or some such.</string>
  <string id="27844" soundid="100689">It will not look good that she collapsed when fighting you, but your record has been strong enough to both avoid and pervert suspicion.</string>
  <string id="27846" soundid="108694">This is exactly what I&apos;m talking about. This place draws scum to it as a dunghill pulls flies! Leave me. I will not waste more time with you.</string>
  <string id="27847" soundid="100691">I don&apos;t know if you&apos;ve heard, but Khana has proclared that the first fighter who extriciates her from her championship will learn the secrets of her technique.</string>
  <string id="27848" soundid="100692">Come talk to me when you have a moment.</string>
  <string id="27849" soundid="100693">Come now! The arena works on a strictly regenticated payment system for the fights. There&apos;s no way I can give you extra.</string>
  <string id="27850" soundid="100694">[Success] You&apos;re right, and I suppose the books won&apos;t miss a small token. Here, take this. Don&apos;t tell the others!</string>
  <string id="27851" soundid="100695">[Success] I mean no offence, it&apos;s just.... I see your point. Here take this and don&apos;t tell the others!</string>
  <string id="27852" soundid="100696">[Failure] I&apos;m sorry, but there&apos;s no room for bonuses, extra payments, or gratitudes of any kind. You&apos;ll be fine with the usual winnings.</string>
  <string id="27853" soundid="100697">Now that that&apos;s settled, what else can I do for you?</string>
  <string id="27854" soundid="100698">Another demon falls. We shall have to add a new division for you alone if this keeps up.</string>
  <string id="27855" soundid="100699">Kai Lan the Serpent wishes to speak with you personally. This is a rare honor. Do try to be polite.</string>
  <string id="27856" soundid="100700">You have already been granted access to the back room of the arena, and the Serpent&apos;s private chamber is just off of it. You may as well go now and see what he wants.</string>
  <string id="27857" soundid="108695">Oh, that&apos;s just cold.</string>
  <string id="27858" soundid="100702">I do not know who those men were! The fighters I picked for you to face were not Guild men, and they certainly lacked poison-coated blades.</string>
  <string id="27859" soundid="100703">The wards are useless against poison. That&apos;s a danger we have never been able to solve.</string>
  <string id="27860" soundid="35943">The Emperor&apos;s Tomb is a cherished landmark here in the city. Why would somebody destroy it?</string>
  <string id="27861" soundid="35944">I met the rudest man over in the Scholars&apos; Garden. Apparently he&apos;s an Outlander.</string>
  <string id="27862" soundid="100704">Those men were Kai Lan&apos;s, not mine. I keep myself as far away from that end of things as I can. You have to believe that I look out for my fighters.</string>
  <string id="27863" soundid="100705">Just before you came up here, I received word from one of the Guild men from outside the arena. They send their apologies!</string>
  <string id="27864" soundid="100706">I believe they feel Kai Lan&apos;s actions were not... appropriated to the situation. You shouldn&apos;t have to fear assassins again, not after that message.</string>
  <string id="27865" soundid="100707">You are not hearing this from me, but tensions have risen between the Serpent and the Guild itself. He&apos;s making a bid for control and some... factions are quite upset.</string>
  <string id="27866" soundid="100708">You may feel caught in the middle, but the weather sages say the eye of the storm is the safest place.</string>
  <string id="27867" soundid="108696">I try to share some of my insights and you fling them in my face with all the class of a two silver whore!</string>
  <string id="27868" soundid="100710">I knew you could defeat those... things. The Imperial Army&apos;s telling me they&apos;ve figured out some way to improve upon the design, thanks to you!</string>
  <string id="27869" soundid="35945">The Outlander isn&apos;t so bad, if you don&apos;t mind being shouted at by a fat, obnoxious windbag.</string>
  <string id="27870" soundid="35946">I&apos;m not worried about ghosts. If there are any, the Emperor will deal with them quick enough.</string>
  <string id="27871" soundid="35947">Watch yourself around the Lotus Assassins, there&apos;s something... unnatural about them.</string>
  <string id="28012" soundid="32756">Brother Sui is right. No one can defeat the Ravager, not even the three of us. You stay away from him.</string>
  <string id="28013" soundid="32757">You should steer away from their order. That is all the advice we can offer, and all you should need.</string>
  <string id="28014" soundid="32758">It is a sensitive subject for my brother. He doesn&apos;t like the thought of the arena being less... liberal than he imagines it.</string>
  <string id="28015" soundid="32759">The Guild cares more for a good show than fair play. Good shows keep the bet money flowing, especially if a favored fighter were to suddenly and surprisingly lose.</string>
  <string id="28016" soundid="32760">If you let fear guide your decisions, Brother Bu, you will find that you have walked the coward&apos;s path.</string>
  <string id="28017" soundid="32761">Philosophy aside, the Empire certainly could wipe them out, but wouldn&apos;t another similar organization appear? Regardless, if something could be done, the Empire would have done it already.</string>
  <string id="28018" soundid="32762">You&apos;ll only deal with the lower ranks at this point. Bother us about fighters when you advance to a respectable level.</string>
  <string id="28019" soundid="32763">It seems unfair, does it not? However, you must ask yourself if you wish to be beheaded instantly when you consider this topic.</string>
  <string id="28020" soundid="32764">Let us put it this way. Individually, each of us is an excellent warrior: fast, strong, or smart as it may be. </string>
  <string id="28021" soundid="32765">When we faced the Ravager individually, he beat us quite handily.</string>
  <string id="28022" soundid="32766">He was victorious. Those who guide this arena were so pleased with the spectacle that they created a new challenge. Us.</string>
  <string id="28023" soundid="32767">The thought was that anyone who couldn&apos;t defeat the brothers Sung would be obliterated by the Ravager. I&apos;m sure we have saved more than a few lives.</string>
  <string id="28024" soundid="32768">We have explained this to you already. Either that, or the snake of time--as theorized by the learned sage Eleven Fingers Zhou--has bitten itself in the tail.</string>
  <string id="28025" soundid="32769">Ahh, there&apos;s a mysterious one. Left the Imperial Army under &quot;circumstances.&quot; His skills quickly earned him a high rank in this contest.</string>
  <string id="28026" soundid="32770">I expect he saw things during his time of service that would blanch the ever-rosy face of jolly Ying Tsun the Intoxicated.</string>
  <string id="28027" soundid="32771">And yet, Pretty Li-Li is always hanging off him. We have often speculated why she is so interested in him, but such things are not fit for polite discussion.</string>
  <string id="28029" soundid="32773">Though my brothers sound like offended courtesans, they have a point. We can&apos;t deny the Ravager&apos;s abilities, but he lacks precision.</string>
  <string id="28030" soundid="32774">Strength is part of his technique. In fact, he may be the strongest fighter here in years--stronger even than Raging Ox, our last champion.</string>
  <string id="28031" soundid="32775">All types of combat styles have achieved championship levels.</string>
  <string id="28032" soundid="32776">According to the legends, his stomach reacted violently to eating fish. This spared him the food poisoning that eventually defeated his peers.</string>
  <string id="28033" soundid="32777">Indeed. We wish you luck and promise to attend your funeral after your attempt.</string>
  <string id="28034" soundid="32778">The Ravager&apos;s prowess lies in his incredible stamina. Blows that would fell lesser men are like the bite of a gnat to him. If you face him, use your strongest techniques.</string>
  <string id="28035" soundid="32779">We don&apos;t know nuthin &apos;bout the army.</string>
  <string id="28036" soundid="32780">Please excuse Brother Bu. He occasionally feels the need to speak on things to which he has not given his full attention.</string>
  <string id="28037" soundid="32781">Please, accept our apologies. I&apos;m certain one of the others would be happy to tell you about the city.</string>
  <string id="28038" soundid="62630">The survivors must carry on as best they can. Now, Fuyao and I should be on our way. If we must brave the wilderness, I would rather do it with the sun still in the sky.</string>
  <string id="28039">Talk to Ing</string>
  <string id="28040" soundid="32784">That&apos;s right, Brother Sui. I don&apos;t like ancient people either!</string>
  <string id="28041">Talk to Ing on Beggar&apos;s Pier in Tien&apos;s Landing for a reward.</string>
  <string id="28042" soundid="32786">I would not end this conversation immediately, Brother Bo. Not just before facing this one in the ring. </string>
  <string id="28043" soundid="32787">Brother Sui has an ear for these things and a knowledge of history, you understand? So, I wish you a fond goodbye *and* a distinguished farewell.</string>
  <string id="28044" soundid="32788">Very tricky! Breaking your sentence&apos;s rhythm with an extra well-wishing comment, brother. Skillfully done.</string>
  <string id="28045" soundid="32789">Well, may the full spectrum of the rainbow guide you safely.</string>
  <string id="28046">You cannot change the difficulty settings when you are in combat.</string>
  <string id="28047">You cannot change the difficulty setting when you are flying a mission.</string>
  <string id="28048" soundid="32792">Yes. We shall see you around, of that you can be sure.</string>
  <string id="28051">On Beggar&apos;s Pier in Tien&apos;s Landing, Captain Ing offered a reward to the one who could close the Great Dam. Go to Beggar&apos;s Pier in Tien&apos;s Landing and find Captain Ing to collect your reward.</string>
  <string id="28056">Let&apos;s talk about you. Why are you allowed to fight as a team?</string>
  <string id="28057">Why would I be beheaded?</string>
  <string id="28058">If you&apos;re threatening me, Sung Bo....</string>
  <string id="28060">What made you start fighting together, then?</string>
  <string id="28066">Is he just incredibly strong, then?</string>
  <string id="28068">If he&apos;s clumsy, why is he champion?</string>
  <string id="28071">Regardless, I will crush him eventually and take his title.</string>
  <string id="28074">Can you answer some questions about the city?</string>
  <string id="28075">He&apos;s clearly an idiot, but I still want my questions answered.</string>
  <string id="28077" soundid="62631">Farewell, honored traveler. If you must enter Tien&apos;s Landing, speak with Minister Sheng in the town square. But a better plan would be to get away while you can.</string>
  <string id="28079">Perhaps if you stopped wasting your time worrying about ancient sages and myths you&apos;d feel better!</string>
  <string id="28082">Old Ming</string>
  <string id="28130">Though not as physically strong as others, a magical character is the best at channeling his Chi to enhance his physical strikes and fuel powerful elemental magics.</string>
  <string id="28139" soundid="35948">I hope my daughter will grow to be as beautiful as the princess, though perhaps less... unruly.</string>
  <string id="28140" soundid="35949">If there are ghosts, why haven&apos;t I seen one? All this talk about spirits is just nonsense.</string>
  <string id="28142">Mechanic Hin Goo</string>
  <string id="28145">** [temp] description for willow style</string>
  <string id="28146">Send Yushan Back</string>
  <string id="28147">Find Kindly Yushan in Tien&apos;s Landing and compel him to return to the orphanage in the ruins to bury the bones of the orphans he abandoned. If the man feels guilty about what happened, he might be driven to drink in the teahouse, so you could start your search there.</string>
  <string id="28149">Kill Kindly Yushan</string>
  <string id="28150">Find Kindly Yushan in Tien&apos;s Landing, kill him, and bring his head back to Miao at the orphanage in the ruins. If the man feels guilty about what happened, he might be driven to drink in the teahouse, so you could start your search there.</string>
  <string id="28152">Speak to Bin</string>
  <string id="28153">Return to Bin and Miao.</string>
  <string id="28155" soundid="32945">My friend says he heard lots of strange sounds coming from the Necropolis. Then the fire started.</string>
  <string id="28156" soundid="32946">My dad says the gods are angry. That&apos;s why the Emperor&apos;s tomb is on fire.</string>
  <string id="28157" soundid="32947">That guy in the Scholars&apos; Garden is always yelling and shouting. He reminds me of my mom.</string>
  <string id="28158" soundid="32948">There&apos;s a real funny looking guy over in the Scholars&apos; Garden. I don&apos;t think he&apos;s from around here.</string>
  <string id="28159" soundid="32949">My friend says he saw a ghost when he went traveling with his uncle. He&apos;s so lucky.</string>
  <string id="28160" soundid="32950">Do you know any Lotus Assassins? My dad says I shouldn&apos;t bother them, but I think they&apos;re neat.</string>
  <string id="28161" soundid="32951">I saw the princess the other day. My mom says she&apos;s beautiful, but I think she&apos;s looks kinda silly.</string>
  <string id="28162" soundid="32952">Have you seen any ghosts? I&apos;ve looked everywhere, but I can&apos;t find any.</string>
  <string id="28163" soundid="32953">I set our chicken coop on fire once, but it sure didn&apos;t make as much smoke as the fire in the Necropolis.</string>
  <string id="28164" soundid="32954">There&apos;s lots of smoke over at the Emperor&apos;s tomb. I guess somebody&apos;s mom let *them* play with fire.</string>
  <string id="28165" soundid="32955">I don&apos;t know what happened, but that Outlander guy finally stopped shouting all the time.</string>
  <string id="28166" soundid="32956">I think I liked the Outlander more before he got beat up. Now he&apos;s kinda boring.</string>
  <string id="28167" soundid="32957">I wonder if the Outlander got scolded by his tutor and that&apos;s why he doesn&apos;t scream and shout anymore.</string>
  <string id="28168" soundid="32958">My friends said that someone beat up the Outlander. That&apos;s why he&apos;s not yelling anymore.</string>
  <string id="28169" soundid="32959">I saw the Lotus Assassins fight once; they&apos;re really good. I guess that&apos;s why you joined up with them, huh?</string>
  <string id="28170" soundid="32960">If I was a Lotus Assassin like you, I&apos;d go beat up all the boys who make fun of me.</string>
  <string id="28171" soundid="32961">My mom thinks I shouldn&apos;t talk to you &apos;cause you&apos;re friends with the Lotus Assassins and all.</string>
  <string id="28172" soundid="32962">Someone said you were talking with the Lotus Assassins before... I bet that was really fun.</string>
  <string id="28173" soundid="32963">I bet an arena champion like you could fight a tiger with your bare hands and win!</string>
  <string id="28174" soundid="32964">When I grow up, I want to be an arena champion, too, just like you!</string>
  <string id="28175" soundid="32965">You&apos;re the one who beat the Ravager! I didn&apos;t think anyone could beat him.</string>
  <string id="28176" soundid="32966">Wow... I never thought I would meet an arena champion. You&apos;re amazing.</string>
  <string id="28177" soundid="32967">I&apos;ve never met a Silver round winner before.</string>
  <string id="28178" soundid="32968">My dad says he likes the way you fight &apos;cause you make him lots of silver.</string>
  <string id="28179" soundid="32969">Are you gonna fight the Ravager soon? He&apos;s real tough. I don&apos;t know if you could beat him yet.</string>
  <string id="28180" soundid="32970">I saw the last fight you won. You were great!</string>
  <string id="28181" soundid="32971">If my mom caught me talking to one of the arena fighters, she&apos;d give me a thrashing.</string>
  <string id="28182" soundid="32972">My dad says that when I get bigger, he&apos;ll take me to see the fights in the arena.</string>
  <string id="28183" soundid="32973">Sometimes I sneak in and watch the fights at the arena. Maybe I&apos;ll see you fight next time.</string>
  <string id="28184" soundid="32974">Are you fighting in the arena now? I bet you&apos;ll be really good.</string>
  <string id="28185" soundid="32975">You should see the sword the Outlander has! It makes a real big sound, and smoke comes out of it.</string>
  <string id="28186" soundid="32976">The big guy in the Scholars&apos; Garden talks funny. He sounds like my uncle when he&apos;s been drinking.</string>
  <string id="28216" soundid="33007">No, my friend, it is time to bask in the glory of triumph!</string>
  <string id="28227" soundid="33689">You have successfully completed the mission I gave you. As your reward, we will allow you to begin your training as an Inquisitor of the Lotus Assassins.</string>
  <string id="28229" soundid="33690">There is much that still lies ahead, but I think you will do well. Our training regime is difficult. For some, it is even lethal. But you should have the skills to survive.</string>
  <string id="28231" soundid="33691">Report to the fortress at the far end of the Necropolis. The entrance is there, now that you are worthy of finding it. Make certain your affairs are in order before you go.</string>
  <string id="28241" soundid="33032">Have you seen the smoke and fire? My mom is worried that something bad has happened.</string>
  <string id="28242" soundid="33033">Why would anybody set fire to the Emperor&apos;s Tomb?</string>
  <string id="28243" soundid="33034">That big man in the Scholars&apos; Garden was yelling and shouting and stamping around like an elephant.</string>
  <string id="28244" soundid="33035">I saw a very funny looking man over in the Scholars&apos; Garden today. My friend says he&apos;s an Outlander.</string>
  <string id="28245" soundid="33036">I don&apos;t care even if there are ghosts. The Emperor is stronger than all the ghosts put together.</string>
  <string id="28246" soundid="33037">I&apos;m not scared of the Lotus Assassins, but still wouldn&apos;t want to talk to one.</string>
  <string id="28247" soundid="33038">The princess is very beautiful. If I was like her then all the girls would like me.</string>
  <string id="28248" soundid="33039">My brother teases me about ghosts all the time. But I don&apos;t think there are any.</string>
  <string id="28249" soundid="33040">I bet the ghosts in the Necropolis are the ones who set fire to the tomb.</string>
  <string id="28250" soundid="33041">I saw a big flame shoot up from the Emperor&apos;s Tomb. It kinda looked like when my dad cooks dinner.</string>
  <string id="28251" soundid="33042">The Outlander finally stopped yelling and screaming all the time. I bet he got in trouble with his mom.</string>
  <string id="28252" soundid="33043">I didn&apos;t really like the Outlander before &apos;cause he was always screaming.</string>
  <string id="28253" soundid="33044">My cousin yelled too much, and he lost his voice. Maybe that&apos;s what happened to the Outlander.</string>
  <string id="28254" soundid="33045">I wonder where that Outlander comes from. He sure does have funny clothes.</string>
  <string id="28255" soundid="33046">I don&apos;t know if I should talk to you now that you&apos;re friends with the Lotus Assassins.</string>
  <string id="28256" soundid="33047">You aren&apos;t going to drag me away are you? My mom says the Lotus Assassins like to drag people away.</string>
  <string id="28257" soundid="33048">My dad says the Lotus Assassins are okay, as long as they don&apos;t bother us.</string>
  <string id="28258" soundid="33049">Hey, what&apos;s it like being a Lotus Assassin? I bet you get to do lots of fun stuff.</string>
  <string id="28259" soundid="33050">I bet now that you&apos;re the arena champion you can have any kind of dessert you like.</string>
  <string id="28260" soundid="33051">My brother and me like to play arena. We pretend we&apos;re you and the Ravager fighting for the championship.</string>
  <string id="28261" soundid="33052">I saw the Ravager fight once. He was really good. You must be great!</string>
  <string id="28262" soundid="33053">Hey, you&apos;re the new arena champion, aren&apos;t you? My brother will be so jealous I got to meet you.</string>
  <string id="28263" soundid="33054">My dad says that he&apos;s going to start betting on you now.</string>
  <string id="28264" soundid="33055">My dad said fighting in the arena is only for boys, but I know I could do it.</string>
  <string id="28265" soundid="33056">I wonder if the Ravager is scared now that you&apos;ve won the Silver round.</string>
  <string id="28266" soundid="33057">I had an uncle who won the Silver round, and he was a great fighter.</string>
  <string id="28267" soundid="33058">You don&apos;t look so tough to me. My brother says you have to be real tough to fight in the arena.</string>
  <string id="28268" soundid="33059">My mom thinks the arena is silly. My dad says mom needs to get a hobby.</string>
  <string id="28269" soundid="33060">I like watching the fights at the arena, but only when the good fighters are there.</string>
  <string id="28270" soundid="33061">Is it fun beating up people in the arena? I don&apos;t think I&apos;d like that.</string>
  <string id="28271" soundid="33062">The Outlander is always yelling and fussing. I think he needs a nap.</string>
  <string id="28272" soundid="33063">I tried to listen to the Outlander, but I couldn&apos;t understand anything he was saying.</string>
  <string id="28273">Lord Lao Recipe 3</string>
  <string id="28274">Lord Lao Recipe 4
</string>
  <string id="28275">Lord Lao Recipe 5</string>
  <string id="28283">Lord Lao Recipe 6
</string>
  <string id="28284">Lord Lao Recipe 7
</string>
  <string id="28285">Lord Lao Recipe 8
</string>
  <string id="28286">TEMP: You are instructed to activate the Water Wheel and the Conductor and to begin the cycle with the Dragon button.</string>
  <string id="28299">Secret Buff. This recipe may not appear. If it does, you are instructed to activate the Water Wheel, the Whirling Cogs, the Cranking Cauldron and the Clapper Chimneys, and to start the process with the Dragon Button.</string>
  <string id="28301">Activate the Conductor and the Whirling Cogs, and then start the machine with the Dragon button.</string>
  <string id="28302">Activate the Conductor, the Clapper Chimneys, and the Whirling Cogs, and start the process with the Dragon button.</string>
  <string id="28303">Activate the Cranking Cauldron and the Whirling Cogs, and then start the machine with the Tiger button.</string>
  <string id="28304">Activate the Conductor, the Whirlign Cogs, and the Water Wheel, and then start the machine with the Tiger switch.</string>
  <string id="28305">Activate the Conductor, the Clapper Chimneys, and the Cranking Cauldron, and then start the machine with the Tiger Switch.</string>
  <string id="28306">Activate the Conductor, the Clapper Chimneys, the Cranking Cauldron, and the Water Wheel, and then start the machine with the Tiger Button.</string>
  <string id="28314">Cow Bezoar</string>
  <string id="28315">Eyes of the Void</string>
  <string id="28316">A bar of nickeled iron</string>
  <string id="28317">A vial of sulfurous water</string>
  <string id="28343" soundid="33135">Have you seen anyone matching the description? The Lotus Assassins are getting impatient.</string>
  <string id="28344" soundid="33136">I don&apos;t know. She is wearing similar clothing... the dark blues. It&apos;s not enough to be sure.</string>
  <string id="28345" soundid="33137">I don&apos;t know. The shaved head and impressive build are similar. It&apos;s not enough to be sure.</string>
  <string id="28346" soundid="33138">I don&apos;t know. The long hair, the purple clothing... very similar. It&apos;s not enough to be sure.</string>
  <string id="28347" soundid="33139">You are mistaken, peasant. If you are the person we seek, your business is of great concern to us.</string>
  <string id="28348" soundid="33140">I don&apos;t like your attitude. I think you are beginning to look more like the person we want.</string>
  <string id="28349" soundid="33141">They were very vague and wouldn&apos;t answer my questions. Are they even sure of who they are looking for?</string>
  <string id="28350" soundid="33142">Just question everyone. This person apparently caused a lot of damage in the south.</string>
  <string id="28352" soundid="33144">Here, what about this one? At least it&apos;s a man, like they said.</string>
  <string id="28354" soundid="33146">You! Identify yourself!</string>
  <string id="28355" soundid="33147">By order of the Emperor and the Lotus Assassins, state your name and purpose for being in the Imperial City!</string>
  <string id="28356" soundid="33148">We are questioning everyone who has arrived in the city recently. You... bear a resemblance to someone we are looking for.</string>
  <string id="28357" soundid="33149">I don&apos;t know. The hair may be similar, as are the wrapped hands and the reddish clothes. It&apos;s not enough to be sure.</string>
  <string id="28358" soundid="33150">Hmm... we could hold him anyway. It&apos;s not a good match, but the Lotus Assassins would leave us be for a few days while they question him.</string>
  <string id="28360" soundid="33152">Is there a problem here, Captain?</string>
  <string id="28362" soundid="33154">Well? Is there?</string>
  <string id="28363" soundid="33155">N-no, Princess Lian. We were questioning this traveler by order of the Lotus Assassins.</string>
  <string id="28364" soundid="33156">There is no need to pursue this questioning any further. You may go.</string>
  <string id="28365" soundid="33157">My apologies, Princess, but I was ordered to detain anyone even vaguely matching....</string>
  <string id="28366" soundid="33158">Captain, this man is here on a personal matter of mine that does not concern you. Do I make myself clear?</string>
  <string id="28367" soundid="33159">Y-yes, Princess Lian.</string>
  <string id="28368" soundid="33160">Then, unless you wish to be transferred to the Wall, you will leave and continue your search.</string>
  <string id="28370" soundid="33162">I don&apos;t know. He is tattooed in a similar way. The clothes could be the same. It&apos;s not enough to be sure.</string>
  <string id="28371" soundid="33163">I don&apos;t know. The young looks... the tunic is similar as well. It&apos;s not enough to be sure.</string>
  <string id="28372" soundid="33164">I don&apos;t know. Shaved head, stern features, monk attire. It&apos;s not enough to be sure.</string>
  <string id="28377">My name is &lt;FullName&gt;. My business is none of yours.</string>
  <string id="28379">Back away. I answer to no one.</string>
  <string id="28387">Of course. I am &lt;FullName&gt;, a simple traveler.</string>
  <string id="28405" soundid="33197">Another pathetic gawker here to bask in the glory that is Iron Soldier, the Silver Division champion? What in all the Empire do *you* want?</string>
  <string id="28406" soundid="33198">Questions? I&apos;m going to waste my time on a pathetic dirt kicker like yourself? Not a chance.</string>
  <string id="28407">What&apos;s in this for me?</string>
  <string id="28408" soundid="126501">A magnificent metropolis. With the dam closed, I&apos;m certain it is only a matter of time until Minister Sheng is once again welcomed to its wondrous bosom.</string>
  <string id="28409" soundid="33201">You again? Go beg for someone else&apos;s time. I have no reason to talk to mere spectators.</string>
  <string id="28411" soundid="33203">Of course, he&apos;ll never do much better, even if more skilled fighters decide to waste their time trying to teach the fool.</string>
  <string id="28412" soundid="33204">Then again, watching Han stumble to Doctor An every time he tries to handle the real Bronze Division fights is one of the most entertaining things about this place.</string>
  <string id="28413">That doesn&apos;t seem very accurate.</string>
  <string id="28418" soundid="139518">Simply speak to them and request a match. The brothers are always eager to test their skills, especially with a new opponent.</string>
  <string id="28420" soundid="139519">Excellent work with the brothers. Now the real challenge begins. Third Brother Renshan will not be an easy opponent.</string>
  <string id="28422">To Vertical Slice</string>
  <string id="28424" soundid="33216">I&apos;m sure they&apos;d enjoy your curiosity. They&apos;re always very keen to know who&apos;s asking questions about their order.</string>
  <string id="28434">Temple of Dirge</string>
  <string id="28453">I&apos;d like to ask you a few questions</string>
  <string id="28457" soundid="62633">My apologies, great lord. In my haste and worry, I did not realize I addressed one so far above my own humble station. Please forgive me.</string>
  <string id="28494">Special Weapon Select</string>
  <string id="28495">Special Weapon Select</string>
  <string id="28496">Special Weapon Select</string>
  <string id="28497">Upgrade Select</string>
  <string id="28498">Start Mission</string>
  <string id="28502">Available Upgrades</string>
  <string id="28503">Selected Upgrades</string>
  <string id="28504">Attack</string>
  <string id="28505">Power Attack</string>
  <string id="28507">Menu</string>
  <string id="28508">Switch Style</string>
  <string id="28509">Movement</string>
  <string id="28510">Camera</string>
  <string id="28511" soundid="132040">We will not meet again mortal. This forest will need my attention in the months to come, and so I will close the portal in the temple. Farewell, young Spirit Monk.</string>
  <string id="28517">Silk Fox</string>
  <string id="28519">I want to join the Lotus Assassins.</string>
  <string id="28521">You could try to kill me. You&apos;d fail, but you could try.</string>
  <string id="28522">I wish to be part of the true power behind the throne.</string>
  <string id="28529" soundid="191428"></string>
  <string id="28530" soundid="191429"></string>
  <string id="28531" soundid="191430"></string>
  <string id="28535" soundid="136647">Whenever I was in the forest I felt uncomfortable. I think she knows the real reason why.</string>
  <string id="28536">Dawn Star</string>
  <string id="28539">Sky</string>
  <string id="28542">Lotus Assassin Fortress</string>
  <string id="28543">Mind and Spirit</string>
  <string id="28738" soundid="37049">You&apos;re not part of the arena, and I don&apos;t take bets from people who I don&apos;t know well. </string>
  <string id="28819" soundid="33692">I will tell them you are coming. Show them this seal when you arrive. Be mindful of your manners. Our trainers are not gentle, and they demand respect.</string>
  <string id="28820" soundid="33693">A new beginning. Your life becomes the Lotus Assassins. Death&apos;s Hand becomes your guiding spirit. The Emperor is your father above him.</string>
  <string id="28821" soundid="144093">You are like every other simpering peasant that has graced our dungeons. What did any of them contribute to the glory of our age before the Emperor dared to make something of them?</string>
  <string id="28822" soundid="33695">I wish you luck. Perhaps I will see you again. If you survive.</string>
  <string id="28823" soundid="33696">You are a potential recruit for the Executioner, just as you are a potential recruit for me. You still have far to go, but you are at least on your way.</string>
  <string id="28824" soundid="33697">That attitude will make your training more difficult. We lose many applicants because they believe they are something special when they are not. Take heed.</string>
  <string id="28827">You honor me with this opportunity.</string>
  <string id="28830">What can I expect when I arrive?</string>
  <string id="28832">Goodbye.</string>
  <string id="28833">The Executioners have already recruited me.</string>
  <string id="28835">Good. I&apos;m tired of these foolish errands.</string>
  <string id="28837">Clay Debris</string>
  <string id="28853" soundid="111991">They... they took Fuyao, my daughter! They took her to the upper levels. I can&apos;t leave without her. Please... you have to find Fuyao!</string>
  <string id="28854" soundid="111992">The slave breaker took her. Please don&apos;t let him hurt my Fuyao! Please, find my daughter and bring her back to me!</string>
  <string id="28902" soundid="111993">You want a reward? But... I have nothing. The pirates took it all. Can&apos;t you help her out of the goodness of your heart? </string>
  <string id="28905" soundid="111994">Please, have mercy! She&apos;s never hurt anyone. Don&apos;t leave her in the hands of these monsters! I&apos;m begging you, please!</string>
  <string id="28907">Don&apos;t worry. I&apos;ll find Fuyao for you.</string>
  <string id="28909">I might help you... if the price is right.</string>
  <string id="28910">I don&apos;t have time to look for your daughter.</string>
  <string id="28925" soundid="112025">You monster! You vile beast! You&apos;ve turned my daughter into a savage!</string>
  <string id="28926" soundid="112026">Come, Fuyao. Quickly. We must leave this place and all this bloodshed behind us. </string>
  <string id="28927" soundid="112027"></string>
  <string id="28937" soundid="112028"></string>
  <string id="28975" soundid="33848">There are rumors flitting about the city that you seek the attentions of the Executioners. These rumors come from the palace itself, leaving me intrigued.</string>
  <string id="28976" soundid="33849">You are a novice with no standing in the arena. What makes you think you are of any interest to me?</string>
  <string id="28977">In party</string>
  <string id="28978" soundid="33851">Then you do not need my recommendation. If you seek it anyway, you will have to earn it in the arena, and nowhere else.</string>
  <string id="28979" soundid="33852">I have no instruction to give. If you want to catch my eye you need to show me that your skills are far beyond the norm.</string>
  <string id="28980" soundid="33853">If you were to knock Iron Soldier from his perch as Silver Division champion, I would be impressed.</string>
  <string id="28981" soundid="33854">I will be here if you wish to petition me further, but I don&apos;t acknowledge anything less than the best. Return when you are worthy, and no sooner.</string>
  <string id="28982" soundid="33855">Then show it with your skills, not your mouth. Anyone can *talk* about their victories. I need people who let actions speak for them.</string>
  <string id="28983" soundid="33856">You have made a moderate showing in the arena, but that does not explain your brazen nature. What do you think you have to offer?</string>
  <string id="28984" soundid="33857">I have been watching you. Your skills suggested that you were the type of person we were looking for.</string>
  <string id="28985" soundid="33858">Do you think you stand a chance of joining the Lotus Assassins?</string>
  <string id="28986" soundid="33859">No, you are stronger than that. We will train away this timid front and tap a potential that you haven&apos;t yet dreamed of.</string>
  <string id="28987" soundid="33860">If you survive, you will join an order unlike any other. We enforce the will of Death&apos;s Hand and the Emperor. We guard the treasures of the Empire.</string>
  <string id="28988" soundid="33861">This will be your responsibility. Can you look on silver coins, golden tablets, or prophesied artifacts and think only of duty?</string>
  <string id="28989" soundid="33862">Then we will waste no more time. You are adequate, and I will allow you to begin training. Proceed to our fortress.</string>
  <string id="28990" soundid="33863">It lies at the far side of the burial ground that is the Necropolis, which you may reach through the rich section of the city. Present this token, so that they will know you.</string>
  <string id="28991" soundid="33864">If you survive your training and remain in control of your senses, perhaps you will serve at my side one day.</string>
  <string id="28992" soundid="33865">If these things do not tempt you, think no more of them. I only meant to illustrate the extent of our duties.</string>
  <string id="28993" soundid="33866">That is a strong position to take, and one that we respect. You will have to remember, however, that if we accept you, you will be a mere recruit.</string>
  <string id="28994" soundid="33867">Why come to me when you have already begun to court the Inquisitor? Do you seek the blessing of someone less corrupted?</string>
  <string id="28995" soundid="33868">He... does not follow the same path that I do, but if I were to call his behavior into question, mine would be examined as well. My work must continue unhindered.</string>
  <string id="28996" soundid="33869">Besides, the Inquisitor&apos;s attention may have a price, but his recruits are still tested for the skills they need. He is an annoyance, not a weakness.</string>
  <string id="28997" soundid="33870">Now, do you seek my recommendation?</string>
  <string id="28998" soundid="33871">Why have you chosen to come here when you have already earned the favor of the Inquisitor? Do you wish the blessing of someone less corrupted?</string>
  <string id="28999" soundid="33872">You are not yet worthy of my notice. Bronze will catch my eye. Silver will earn my respect.</string>
  <string id="29000" soundid="33873">You have shown some skill, but you are not of interest to me yet. Nothing lower than Silver will earn my respect.</string>
  <string id="29001" soundid="33874">Your victories are impossible for the other fighters to ignore. You are a master of the arena, the ground where Executioners are born.</string>
  <string id="29002" soundid="33875">Perhaps you have potential that you are not even aware of. There may be a role in the Executioners for you after all.</string>
  <string id="29004">I have been recommended by the Inquisitor.</string>
  <string id="29005">This follower is not available.</string>
  <string id="29007">I would be honored to seek your guidance.</string>
  <string id="29010">I am the most skilled fighter here.</string>
  <string id="29013">If you will have me.</string>
  <string id="29016">[Lie] I would be honored.</string>
  <string id="29019">You&apos;ve seen my skill. Just give your recommendation.</string>
  <string id="29020">Why mention such things to the uninitiated?</string>
  <string id="29021">If you are worthy of me.</string>
  <string id="29023">Why don&apos;t you expose the corruption of the Inquisitor?</string>
  <string id="29061" soundid="197962"></string>
  <string id="29089" soundid="139520">If you like, you can continue to spar with the brothers, or you can go and fight Third Brother.</string>
  <string id="29092">CHUD</string>
  <string id="29093">Dog</string>
  <string id="29098" soundid="144343">In this town, it&apos;s vital for a businessman to keep tabs on anyone with two coins to rub together. Things haven&apos;t been this slow since the Long Drought.</string>
  <string id="29100">Secret Exit from Fortress</string>
  <string id="29101" soundid="144344">That master of yours keeps things ludicrously stable, while merchants thrive on strife. During the Long Drought, prices rocketed into the sky like fireworks.</string>
  <string id="29102" soundid="144345">I can&apos;t say that. He&apos;s a wise man who sees to the heart of things. If I were to complain about anything, it&apos;s how few students he attracts.</string>
  <string id="29103" soundid="144346">A skilled master could bring a lot of people into this town, but he is very selective about who comes. That&apos;s his business, I&apos;m sure, but it affects my business, as well.</string>
  <string id="29104" soundid="144347">I get by. I suppose I shouldn&apos;t wish for strife, lest it come knocking on my door.</string>
  <string id="29113" soundid="145678">Of course! Thanks again for your help with those miscreants!</string>
  <string id="29114" soundid="145679">Right you are. Remember to keep an eye out for anyone suspicious.</string>
  <string id="29115" soundid="145680">If you change your mind, I&apos;m still looking for a competent hunter.</string>
  <string id="29116" soundid="145681">Greetings, citizen! Imperial Captain Sen at your service! Are you one of the mercenaries come to help me track down some criminal scum?</string>
  <string id="29118" soundid="145683">I was told that there were some new warriors in town looking for work, though none of them matched your description.</string>
  <string id="29120" soundid="145684">If you are who I&apos;m waiting for, you have some explaining to do!</string>
  <string id="29121" soundid="145685">Come now, you have the look of a warrior about you, and there&apos;s nothing common about that.</string>
  <string id="29122" soundid="145686">Admittedly, you don&apos;t resemble the ones described to me, but they&apos;re several days late. No doubt they&apos;ll blame it on the foolish ghost stories.</string>
  <string id="29124" soundid="145688">Criminals with lucrative bounties on their heads.</string>
  <string id="29125" soundid="145689">Now, don&apos;t be hasty. Let me make you an offer.</string>
  <string id="29126" soundid="145690">I need help tracking down a pair of criminals. Are you interested in a little well-paying work?</string>
  <string id="29127" soundid="49009">To attain peace, harmony, and balance is to discover true wealth.</string>
  <string id="29128" soundid="49010">To achieve a stronger spirit, you must first make peace with yourself.</string>
  <string id="29129" soundid="49011">True strength comes from harmony. Disharmony with the world will make you weak.</string>
  <string id="29131" soundid="49012">Focusing one&apos;s thoughts requires balance. Living without balance weakens the mind.</string>
  <string id="29132" soundid="49013">The teachings of Sagacious Tien are available to anyone.</string>
  <string id="29133" soundid="49014">Do not be fooled by those who would tell you that studying is the key to true enlightenment.</string>
  <string id="29134" soundid="49015">One cannot discover true enlightenment in the world; it comes only from within.</string>
  <string id="29135" soundid="49016">Come and learn about the ways of Sagacious Tien. Free your body, mind, and spirit.</string>
  <string id="29142" soundid="150703">Keep an eye out for a large wild-looking man wearing nothing but a loin cloth.</string>
  <string id="29143">*I&apos;m* the one who will kill you. Now.</string>
  <string id="29145" soundid="150704">Keep an eye out for a bare-chested wild man with hair covering his back and arms.</string>
</tlk>